<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
        <rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
        xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
        xmlns:openSearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearchrss/1.0/"
        xmlns:dfpvideo="http://api.google.com/dfpvideo"
        xmlns:tms="http://data.tmsapi.com/v1.1"
        version="2.0">
          <channel>
            <title>ViralBear videos</title>
            <dfpvideo:version>2</dfpvideo:version>
              
                  <item>
                  <media:title>gfdg</media:title>
                  <media:description>fgdfg</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>dfg</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>gfd</media:city>
                  <media:country>Angola</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>AO</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>WAR</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Road accidents</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>exclusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sun, 6 Aug 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2635</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 10:17:17 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear2.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2635.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear2.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2635.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Playful corgi Jam from Belarus delights in dandelions</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a heartwarming video captured by @no_fans_only_plants on May 18, 2023, in St. Petersburg, Russia, a delightful corgi named Jam stole the spotlight as he frolicked in a field of dandelions. The playful pup, originally hailing from Belarus, exhibited his exuberance and love for life, embodying the typical corgi spirit. However, what sets Jam apart is his endearing habit of munching on dandelions, which his owner allows without any reservations. Emphasizing the importance of letting pets be themselves, the author expressed a deep understanding and appreciation for Jam's individuality. This heartening tale of a free-spirited corgi cherishing life's simple pleasures reminds us to embrace our loved ones for who they truly are.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>playful,corgi,jam,video,Belarus,dandelions,field,StPetersburg,Russia,pets,love,individuality,free-spirited,happiness,nature,adorable,canine,companionship,joy,outdoor,embrace</media:keywords>
                  <media:city> St. Petersburg</media:city>
                  <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Thu, 18 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2631</guid>
                  <pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 14:06:33 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2631.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2631.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Unexpected chair collapse turns dining mishap into laughter at Semarang restaurant</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a heartwarming yet amusing incident at a restaurant in Semarang, Indonesia, a woman had a lighthearted response to an unexpected mishap. On July 18, 2023, @sambel.pinuk.alisamu captured a video that quickly gained attention on social media. The footage showed the woman falling off her chair as it collapsed beneath her while she was eating. However, instead of being flustered or embarrassed, she laughed it off with good humor. The man she was dining with rushed to her aid and helped her back up. According to the author it seemed that the chair had shifted and hit a gap between the tiles, leading to the unexpected accident. The heartwarming display of laughter and camaraderie in the face of a minor mishap brought a smile to many as the video went viral, reminding us all to find joy in life's little moments.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>restaurant,semarang,indonesia,video,woman,chair,collapse,unexpected,help,dining,laughter,mishap,socialmedia,humor,viral,camaraderie,joy,permission,tiles,accident</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Semarang </media:city>
                  <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>ID</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Fails and Funnies</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2629</guid>
                  <pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 14:04:14 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2629.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2629.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Traffic police car collides with child in Bataysk, Russia: investigation underway</media:title>
                  <media:description>In an unfortunate incident on July 11, 2023, in Bataysk, Russia, a young boy was involved in a collision with a traffic police patrol car on Slavy Street, 7. The incident was caught on video by residents of the house and shared on social media. The footage shows the child being knocked down but managing to get back up and limping in shock towards the entrance of the house. Surprisingly, the inspector driving the patrol car did not approach the child after the accident but instead returned to the driver's seat. The Main Directorate of the Ministry of Internal Affairs of Russia for the Rostov Region stated that the child, born in 2014, suddenly ran out onto the road due to parked vehicles. An investigation into the circumstances surrounding the incident is currently underway.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>accident,bataysk,russia,boy,traffic,police,patrol,car,video,social,media,collision,pedestrian,investigation,shock,limping,entrance,inspector,parked,vehicles</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Bataysk</media:city>
                  <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Road accidents</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2628</guid>
                  <pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 14:02:51 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2628.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2628.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Enigmatic equine enigma: a horse's puzzled encounter with a horse coat</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a heartwarming yet amusing scene at @abbottsviewlivery in Aston Abbotts, UK, a delightful video captured by the account owner on June 11, 2023, showcased their horse donning a horse coat. The comical attire covered the horse entirely, except for two eye holes, leaving the majestic creature looking perplexed and inquiring about the peculiar get-up. As the laughter of the onlookers filled the air, the horse appeared to be seeking answers from its amused companions, making for an endearing moment that truly highlighted the unique bond between humans and their equine companions.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>horse,coat,confused,video,Aston Abbotts,UK,laughter,equine,companions,amusement,head-to-hoof,enigma,bond,unique,moment,animals,livery,eye holes,inquiring,delightful,June 11</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Aston Abbotts</media:city>
                  <media:country>United Kingdom</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>GB</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2626</guid>
                  <pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 14:00:21 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2626.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2626.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Reckless white SUV causes collision with street light: violation of traffic rules in Jiangxi Province, China</media:title>
                  <media:description>In Jiangxi Province, China, a recent traffic incident captured on video by @Jiangxitrafficpolice has brought attention to the dangers of reckless driving. On June 15, 2023, a driver was maneuvering their vehicle along a normal route when disaster struck. As they passed an uphill section, a white SUV suddenly appeared, overtaking on the hill and violating traffic regulations. The video shows the desperate attempt of the driver to avoid the SUV, but tragically, they collided with a street light post instead. The footage clearly highlights the white SUV's failure to adhere to road rules as the main cause of the accident. As a result, no one was hurt.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>accident,video,traffic,jiangxi,china,collision,streetlight,SUV,overtaking,hill,regulations,responsible,driving,safety,road,incident,reckless,footage,violation,driver</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Jiangxi</media:city>
                  <media:country>China</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>CN</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Road accidents</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2625</guid>
                  <pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 13:59:40 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2625.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2625.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Unusual collision in Jiangsu: scooters smile and carry on despite impact at crossing</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a peculiar incident captured by @trafficsafetyeveryday in Jiangsu Province, China, on July 24, 2023, two motorists collided in front of a moving car at a crossing area. The collision involved a woman driving an electric scooter and a delivery rider, both also on electric scooters. Surprisingly, despite the impact, the two parties showed an unexpected reaction. Instead of anger and frustration, they exchanged smiles after checking for injuries and continued on their way. The scene left the author intrigued, leading them to save the video. The incident serves as a unique reminder of how even in the midst of accidents, a moment of understanding and positivity can arise on the roads.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>collision,motorists,Jiangsu,China,video,crossing,traffic lights,electric bicycles,delivery rider,interesting,smile,accident,understanding,positivity,roads,@trafficsafetyeveryday,July 24,2023,intriguing,motorists,movement</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Jiangsu</media:city>
                  <media:country>China</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>CN</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Road accidents</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2624</guid>
                  <pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 13:57:46 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2624.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2624.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Friend's car narrowly avoids major collision with large truck on rural road in Heilongjiang Province</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a heart-stopping incident captured by @trafficsafetyeveryday on July 20, 2023, in Heilongjiang Province, China, a group of friends experienced a harrowing moment while driving to the countryside. As they were passing through a rural road, their friend's car, positioned in front of the author's vehicle, collided with the body of a large truck. The tense situation unfolded when the truck abruptly slammed on its brakes, causing the vehicle to lose control and veer towards the back of the truck. Fortunately, luck was on their side as the collision was not as severe as it could have been, considering it occurred just as they were nearly past each other. No harm done.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>accident,traffic,safety,video,friends,car,truck,collision,countryside,rural,road,Heilongjiang,China,brake,control,closecall,tense,vigilance,luck,reminder</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Heilongjiang Province</media:city>
                  <media:country>China</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>CN</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Road accidents</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2623</guid>
                  <pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 13:55:37 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2623.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2623.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Close call at the torch relay: commemorating Suro in South Jakarta</media:title>
                  <media:description>On the night of July 18, 2023, in South Jakarta, Indonesia, @kibojagoo captured a thrilling moment during a torch relay procession held to commemorate the first night of Suro, the Islamic New Year's Eve. In a video shared online, the author was seen walking alongside others holding fire torches when a close encounter almost turned into a disaster. As a fire torch came dangerously close to his hair, the end of his bun caught fire, prompting a quick reaction from him. Acting swiftly, he released the bun and managed to brush off the fire, averting any serious damage. Unfazed by the incident, the author continued recording the video, still engrossed in reading the sholawat, a prayer in Islamic tradition. He even humorously remarked that due to his frizzy and messy hair, no burn marks were visible. The event served as a poignant reminder of the significance of Suro and the importance of vigilance during such celebratory occasions.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>torch relay,procession,fire,hair,close call,Suro,Islamic New Year's Eve,South Jakarta,Indonesia,video,celebration,vigilance,frizzy,messy,safety,tradition,prayer,commemoration,community,culture,night</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>South Jakarta</media:city>
                  <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>ID</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Fails and Funnies</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2622</guid>
                  <pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 13:54:01 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2622.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2622.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Laughing in the face of disaster: Cotabato City's titanic-style flood adventure</media:title>
                  <media:description>In the midst of a devastating flood in Cotabato City, Philippines, @‌_kathlilies captured a heartwarming video that showcased the remarkable resilience and humor of the residents. Waist-high waters flooded their home, but one of them ventured inside, playfully recreating a scene from the movie "Titanic" in a lighthearted manner. The video, filmed on July 12, 2023, quickly went viral, spreading joy and inspiration worldwide. Despite the chaos and destruction caused by the flood, the residents' ability to find humor amidst adversity served as a powerful reminder of the human spirit's indomitable nature. </media:description>
                  <media:keywords>flood,resilience,humor,CotabatoCity,Philippines,video,Titanic,lighthearted,disaster,community,unity,inspiration,viral,chaos,destruction,adversity,laughter,camaraderie,uncertainty,positivity</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Cotabato City</media:city>
                  <media:country>Philippines</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>PH</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Fails and Funnies</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2621</guid>
                  <pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 08:00:43 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2621.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2621.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Ezro John's hilarious CPR lesson: from jokes to saving lives</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a video captured on July 21, 2023, at Saint Louis University in Baguio City, Philippines, a medical technologist student named Ezro, with the social media handle @‌ezrojohn_rmt, took part in Basic Life Support training. Amidst the CPR lesson, Ezro humorously slapped the mannequin patient, jokingly captioning the moment, "POV: You are saving lives but has anger issues. Doesn't want to wake up, sooo." However, as the training progressed, Ezro and his fellow students were taught the proper and serious way of performing CPR. Learning the vital techniques to potentially save lives, the lighthearted start of the session eventually transitioned into a valuable lesson on the importance of the life-saving skill.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>cpr,training,medical,technologist,student,mannequin,lesson,humor,serious,life-saving,skills,education,practice,Saint Louis University,Baguio City,Philippines,video,caption,CPR training,Basic Life Support</media:keywords>
                  <media:city> Baguio City</media:city>
                  <media:country>Philippines</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>PH</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Fails and Funnies</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2620</guid>
                  <pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 08:01:41 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2620.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2620.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Persistent feline pursuit: hilarious toilet time with a tenacious cat</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a comical and relatable scene, @badnotwolf from Vinnytsia, Ukraine, shared a video of his persistent cat, Roxy attempting to join him in the bathroom. On July 11, 2023, while seated in front of the camera, the cat made numerous unsuccessful leaps towards its owner, who was simply seeking a moment of relaxation on the toilet. With only the legs visible in the video, viewers were left amused by the feline's determined efforts to be part of the action.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>cat,toilet,video,legs,Ukraine,Vinnytsia,July,2023,hilarious,comical,pet,owner,persistent,attempts,relaxation,funny,feline,jump,bathroom,amusing,scene</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Vinnytsia</media:city>
                  <media:country>Ukraine</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>UA</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2618</guid>
                  <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 13:20:43 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2618.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2618.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Convicted thief escapes Blagoveshchensk pre-trial detention center through transmission window</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a daring escape, a young man convicted of theft managed to break free from a pre-trial detention center in Blagoveshchensk, Russia, through a transmission window on July 30, 2023. The incident occurred on Sunday during a visitation and transfer session, taking advantage of the warden's absence. After being on the run for a few hours, the fugitive was finally apprehended on the night of July 31st. According to the Russian Federal Penitentiary Service for the Amur Region, the escapee had been in detention since December 2022. Now facing severe consequences, the convict may be sentenced to forced labor or imprisonment for up to four years, as per Article 313 of the Criminal Code of Russia. Additionally, the court will charge him for the expenses incurred during the search operation. The Federal Penitentiary Service is currently conducting an internal audit to assess the security breach that allowed this escape to occur.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>escape,convict,theft,pretrial,detention,Blagoveshchensk,Russia,transmission,window,caught,criminal,penalty,fugitive,imprisonment,search,audit,warden,apprehended,visitation,expenses</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Blagoveshchensk</media:city>
                  <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>News</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2617</guid>
                  <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 13:22:11 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2617.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2617.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Adorable foster kittens indulge in a 'paws'-itively messy drink!</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a heartwarming scene captured by @emiliexfosters on July 18, 2023, in Milwaukee, USA, three adorable foster kittens were caught on video enjoying a drink from a bowl. However, one mischievous kitten had its legs dipped into the liquid as it drank, resulting in a cute yet messy moment. With quick reflexes, the author lifted the little one out of the bowl, revealing its front paws soaked in the brown liquid used for weaning them. Despite the adorable mishap, the sight of these tiny furballs brought smiles to viewers' faces, showcasing the joys of caring for foster animals.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>adorable,foster,kittens,video,drink,bowl,legs,soaked,weaning,messy,cute,moment,reflexes,furballs,caring,animals,pets,@emiliexfosters,Milwaukee,USA</media:keywords>
                  <media:city> Milwaukee </media:city>
                  <media:country>United States</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>US</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2615</guid>
                  <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 13:22:47 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2615.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2615.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Boomer's midnight mischief: possum party at home!</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a humorous and slightly mischievous incident captured by @ndnchic33 on June 17, 2023, in Chelsea, Alabama, USA, her adorable dog, Boomer, became the center of attention. The video shows Boomer lounging on the couch late at night, accompanied by an unexpected guest - possums! Apparently, Boomer had invited his possum friend over to join him indoors, much to his owner's surprise. In the video, we hear the author playfully scolding Boomer, reminding him that bringing friends into the house is not allowed. The adorable footage showcases Boomer's nocturnal adventures and his owner's delightful reaction to the unusual situation. It's a heartwarming reminder of the unexpected antics our furry friends can get up to when the world sleeps.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>night,dog,Boomer,possums,couch,house,video,Chelsea,Alabama,USA,friends,mischief,adorable,owner,surprise,nocturnal,antics,furry,funny,pets</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Chelsea, Alabama</media:city>
                  <media:country>United States</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>US</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2613</guid>
                  <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 08:13:17 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2613.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2613.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Enchanting double rainbow delights travelers in Rakov, Belarus</media:title>
                  <media:description>On July 30, 2023, a mesmerizing sight graced the city of Rakov, Belarus, as @lucyfer_da captured a stunning video of a rainbow during her return journey. After a trip to Nalibokskaya Pushcha, she noticed a remarkably bright and clear rainbow hovering over a distant lake. Throughout the drive, the rainbow remained elusive, often obscured by trees and buildings. However, as they ventured onto the track and turned a corner, the rainbow revealed its full splendor, stretching wider than the entire roadway. Onlookers were left in awe, with people pulling over to capture the spectacle with their cameras. Curiously, there was no rain preceding or following the rainbow, but within its vivid hues, a fine drizzle could be seen, akin to droplets from a spray bottle. As if one rainbow wasn't enough, a larger, fainter one appeared above the brilliant arc, adding to the enchantment of the moment. Nature's breathtaking display left a lasting impression on all who bore witness to this extraordinary occurrence.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>rainbow,rakov,belarus,video,lake,trees,buildings,travel,enchanting,double,stunning,splendor,onlookers,cameras,drizzle,nature,display,breathtaking,moment,occurrence</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Rakov</media:city>
                  <media:country>Belarus</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>BY</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Cool</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2612</guid>
                  <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 08:14:07 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2612.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2612.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Swaddle buddies: heartwarming video shows cat and baby bonding in Ciamis, Indonesia</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a heartwarming display of unlikely companionship, a video captured by @sheisseu malikeymouse on July 22, 2023, in Ciamis, Indonesia, has taken the internet by storm. The footage shows a swaddled baby peacefully lying next to a swaddled cat, with the feline seemingly unfazed by the tiny human's presence. According to the account owner, the cat has a penchant for disturbing the child, prompting the clever idea of swaddling them both together. </media:description>
                  <media:keywords>swaddle,baby,cat,companionship,bond,video,Indonesia,Ciamis,heartwarming,pets,harmony,unexpected,love,animals,internet,admiration,unique,clever,touching,footage</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Ciamis</media:city>
                  <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>ID</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Heartwarming</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2611</guid>
                  <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 08:15:55 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2611.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2611.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Playful pranks and paw popping: a kitten's hilarious reflexes!</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a heartwarming and humorous video captured by @pinkintotheblue on May 28, 2023, in Cikande, Banten, Indonesia, a playful kitten steals the show with its adorable reflexes. The feline's owner, @pinkintotheblue's boyfriend, gently held the little furball in his hands while playfully making popping sounds with his mouth. The kitten's reaction was priceless - as soon as it heard the sounds, it instinctively lifted all its tiny legs in surprise, only to settle back down again in his hands. With a house full of cats, the couple thoroughly enjoys creating these delightful moments on camera. This heartwarming video captures the joy and bond shared between humans and their feline companions, reminding us of the simple pleasures that brighten our lives.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>playful,kitten,reflexes,video,popping,adorable,hands,joy,cats,love,fun,pets,cute,surprise,bonding,moments,laughter,Indonesia,Banten,Cikande</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Cikande, Banten </media:city>
                  <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>ID</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sun, 28 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2610</guid>
                  <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 08:16:32 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2610.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2610.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Midnight motorbike melody: barking serenade by excited street dogs</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a captivating video captured by @abdullaev.222 on July 9, 2023, in Saratov Rakhova, Russia, a group of street dogs showcased their curious behavior towards a motorbike. As the rider turned on the engine, the dogs immediately came rushing towards him, barking excitedly. However, whenever the engine was switched off, they would retreat, only to return with renewed enthusiasm once it roared to life again. The intriguing scene unfolded during the night when the rider stopped to answer a phone call, catching the dogs' attention and prompting him to start recording the delightful encounter. It's a heartwarming reminder of the special bond between humans and their four-legged companions, even in unexpected and amusing circumstances.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>motorbike,dogs,street,night,Russia,Saratov,barking,excitement,video,capture,curious,engine,retreat,enthusiasm,phone,call,recording,bond,humans,companions</media:keywords>
                  <media:city> Saratov Rakhova</media:city>
                  <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sun, 9 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2609</guid>
                  <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 08:12:32 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2609.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2609.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Unsuspecting seaside silliness: a chair, a wave, and laughter in Banda Aceh!</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a moment of pure beachside amusement, an unexpected encounter with a massive wave turned into a hilarious spectacle for @aleshafamily_ on July 6, 2023, in Banda Aceh, Indonesia. Seated comfortably in her chair by the water's edge, little did she anticipate the waves reaching her spot. As if to playfully challenge her, a colossal wave surged forward just as she attempted to escape its reach with her chair. Instead of escaping unscathed, she found herself tumbling onto the sandy shore, bursts of laughter echoing around her. The video she captured quickly spread, showcasing the joyous mishap that made the internet chuckle along with her seaside antics.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>beach,waves,chair,laughter,video,unexpected,Banda Aceh,Indonesia,amusement,moment,water,edge,hilarious,encounter,summer,sea,shoreline,sand,mishap,internet</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Banda Aceh</media:city>
                  <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>ID</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Fails and Funnies</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Thu, 6 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2607</guid>
                  <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 08:03:37 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2607.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2607.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Intense firepower unleashed: Ukrainian forces train and prepare for confrontation between Donbass and Bakhmut</media:title>
                  <media:description>In the tense and war-torn between Donbass and Bakhmut, Ukraine, a harrowing video emerged on July 24, 2023, capturing the relentless firing of warheads by soldiers in the fields. The footage was attributed to @vladhalidov, shedding light on the activity of the Sheikh Mansour Battalion (BShM) and the Special Tactical Army Group LOM. Under the command of Muhammad-Aslan, the group conducted a strategic briefing on the impending storming of Russian positions, while also providing crucial training to the Ukrainian army. The conflict between Ukraine and Russia had persisted for over a year, with this latest display of firepower indicating the ongoing severity of the situation in the region. As tensions escalated, the international community remained on high alert, closely monitoring the developments in this volatile conflict zone.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>soldiers,firing,warheads,Donbass,Bakhmut,Ukraine,video,Sheikh Mansour Battalion,BShM,Special Tactical Army Group LOM,commander,Muhammad-Aslan,briefing,storming,Russian positions,training,armed conflict,tension,international community,escalation</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Donbass</media:city>
                  <media:country>Ukraine</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>UA</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>News</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2606</guid>
                  <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 08:28:15 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2606.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2606.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Adorable cashier's assistant: the beloved parking lot cat of Odessa, Ukraine</media:title>
                  <media:description>In the bustling city of Odessa, Ukraine, a heartwarming scene unfolded at a local parking lot on July 29, 2023. @40medok, an observant passerby, captured a heart-melting moment as a charming cat sat gracefully at the cashier's window, patiently awaiting attention. With affectionate pets and gentle caresses, the feline earned its rightful place as the "Cashier's Assistant." Customers and visitors passing by couldn't resist showering the cat with respect and tenderness, creating a sense of community around this adorable furball. This endearing sight has become a cherished part of the parking lot's atmosphere, leaving everyone with a smile as they complete their errands, knowing that a little feline guardian watches over them.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>adorable,cat,cashier,window,parking lot,Odessa,Ukraine,pet,picture,baby,cute,good,respect,tenderness,community,furball,atmosphere,guardian,smile,errands</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Odessa</media:city>
                  <media:country>Ukraine</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>UA</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2605</guid>
                  <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 07:59:28 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2605.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2605.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Nature's fury unleashed: lightning strikes and flames explode in Shijiazhuang</media:title>
                  <media:description>On July 24, 2023, in Shijiazhuang, northern China, a startling and unintentional event was captured on video by @HomelessYuanyuan. As she stood in front of her apartment window with her mobile phone, attempting to capture a street scene during a rainstorm and thunder, lightning struck the transformer below her building. The intense impact caused sparks of flames to erupt, scattering fiery fragments in all directions. Nature's fury was unleashed, and in a split second, the author found herself witnessing a breathtaking display of raw power and danger.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>lightning,sparks,flames,explosion,rainstorm,thunder,Shijiazhuang,China,video,mobile,window,street,nature,fury,power,danger,unpredictability,awe,humbled,@HomelessYuanyuan</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Shijiazhuang</media:city>
                  <media:country>China</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>CN</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>News</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2604</guid>
                  <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 13:16:50 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2604.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2604.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Thrilling mishap: Audi drift attempt ends in guardrail collision at Suzhou GTshow </media:title>
                  <media:description>During the annual Suzhou GTshow on July 22, 2023, a highly anticipated automotive cultural event in China, a heart-pounding incident occurred as an Audi car attempted a daring drift maneuver. The vehicle lost control and collided with a guardrail, sending shockwaves through the crowd of car enthusiasts. Thankfully, no one was injured in the dramatic collision. The video captured by @ShanghaiUPAutomotiveTechnicalService shows the intensity of the moment, serving as a reminder of the risks involved in high-speed automotive displays. Despite the unexpected mishap, the event continued, showcasing a spectacular display of Custom cars and Supercars to the delight of the attendees.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>drift,audi,collision,guardrail,suzhou,china,g t show,automotive,event,enthusiasts,custom,supercar,annual,mishap,excitement,car,culture,display,injured,risk</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Suzhou</media:city>
                  <media:country>China</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>CN</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2603</guid>
                  <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 13:19:39 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2603.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2603.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Bear brawl at Guaipo Tiger Park: two black bears engage in fierce fight over food</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a thrilling and unexpected encounter at the Guaipo Tiger Park in Shenyang, Northeast China, two black bears engaged in a heated fight, captured on video by local resident @100millionfatballs on June 24, 2023. As she explored the living area of the black bears, the normally docile animals suddenly clashed, with their aggression escalating over a possible dispute for food. The shocking scene prompted the author to react quickly, loudly shouting in an attempt to intervene and put an end to the confrontation. Her bravery in the face of this intense encounter showcased the unpredictable nature of wildlife and served as a powerful reminder of the importance of respecting and preserving the delicate balance between humans and the animal kingdom.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>shenyang,china,black bears,fight,video,wildlife,park,encounter,food,aggression,shock,visitor,Guaipo Tiger Park,northeast,@100millionfatballs,nature,animals,conservation,bravery,balance</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Shenyang</media:city>
                  <media:country>China</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>CN</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2602</guid>
                  <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 13:12:52 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2602.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2602.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Terrifying Yokohama guerrilla rainstorm unleashes chaos with its fierce winds and torrential downpour</media:title>
                  <media:description>In Yokohama, Japan, on August 1, 2023, @Tomo_YNU captured a chilling video of a rainstorm known as Guerrilla. This local phenomenon is characterized by an unpredictable formation of cumulonimbus clouds, resulting in a short but intense downpour of over 100 mm per hour of rain. The video showcases the fury of the Guerrilla rainstorm, with powerful winds swaying trees in its path. The dangerous nature of this event highlights the need for caution and preparedness during such occurrences in Yokohama.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>rainstorm,guerrilla,yokohama,japan,video,downpour,cumulonimbus,clouds,intense,winds,trees,dangerous,unpredictable,weather,phenomenon,local,short,mm,hour,rain</media:keywords>
                  <media:city> Yokohama</media:city>
                  <media:country>Japan</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>JP</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Weather</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Tue, 1 Aug 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2601</guid>
                  <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 13:12:08 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2601.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2601.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Tokyo's sideways rain: nature's dance of wind and water</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a mesmerizing spectacle captured on August 1, 2023, from the heart of Tokyo, Japan, @4H6M8u0YmemZwmj shared a breathtaking video of sideways rain cascading down window panes. As nature's elements collided, the wind's mighty force compelled the raindrops to dance sideways, creating a captivating display of nature's power and beauty. The video serves as a vivid reminder of the unpredictable yet awe-inspiring wonders of the natural world, leaving viewers in awe of the harmonious choreography between wind and water. </media:description>
                  <media:keywords>wind,rain,sideways,video,Tokyo,Japan,nature,spectacle,mesmerizing,window,panes,dance,elements,force,beauty,power,display,awe,urban,landscape</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Tokyo </media:city>
                  <media:country>Japan</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>JP</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Weather</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Tue, 1 Aug 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2600</guid>
                  <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 13:12:22 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2600.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2600.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Playful and obedient: Khryapa's impressive 'swim' command!</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a heartwarming video captured by @mokryi_nosik_ on June 17, 2020, in Voronezh, Russia, her beloved dog, Khryapa, stole the spotlight with her incredible obedience and playful nature. The footage shows @mokryi_nosik_ talking to Khryapa in one of the rooms, when suddenly, the clever canine dashes off towards the bathroom. Without hesitation, Khryapa leaps into the bathtub, showcasing her impressive execution of the "swim" command. The three-year-old furry friend proves to be not only obedient but also full of joy and enthusiasm. Her charming antics have won the hearts of viewers worldwide, leaving a lasting impression of her delightful personality and the strong bond between her and her owner.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>playful,obedient,dog,swim,command,video,Khryapa,Voronezh,Russia,bathtub,bathroom,three years old,pet,canine,joy,love,bond,clever,cute,charming</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Voronezh</media:city>
                  <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2598</guid>
                  <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 10:57:32 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2598.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2598.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Serene lake birthday circus: a decade of joyful dancing and balloon delight!</media:title>
                  <media:description>In the quaint town of Bakota, Ukraine, a mesmerizing birthday celebration unfolded on July 5, 2023. The talented dancer @annadellart, captured by @sykannushka's lens, graced the serene waterbody backdrop with her enchanting moves. Celebrating her 22nd birthday, she danced with legs elegantly up and spread straight, each leg adorned with a balloon forming the number 2 to signify her special age. The joyous spectacle unfolded in a circus setting, a fitting choice as the circus has been an integral part of her life for an entire decade. With graceful movements and a touch of whimsy, @annadellart's performance was a testament to a decade filled with joy, passion, and artistry.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>circus,birthday,celebration,dancing,waterbody,Bakota,Ukraine,@sykannushka,@annadellart,video,legs,balloons,22,joyful,enchanting,talented,serene,whimsy,passion,artistry</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Bakota </media:city>
                  <media:country>Ukraine</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>UA</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Cool</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Wed, 5 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2596</guid>
                  <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 07:58:40 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2596.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2596.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Playful corgi's adorable 'poof' act delights internet in St. Petersburg, Russia!</media:title>
                  <media:description>In an endearing and amusing video that captured hearts on social media, a Corgi named Leo from St. Petersburg, Russia, showcased his unique talent for playing "dead." The video, shared by @prokopenkokate on April 29, 2023, depicts Leo sitting peacefully on the floor before his owner mimics a shooting gesture with her hands. Surprisingly, the adorable pup immediately flops down, pretending to be "shot" as part of a playful command he has mastered. As a reward for his impressive performance, Leo eagerly awaits a treat, proving that his favorite command is the delightful and harmless "poof," leaving viewers charmed by this clever and lovable canine's antics.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>playful,corgi,leo,video,internet,acting,dog,Russia,St. Petersburg,pet,owner,gun,pretend,cute,charm,humor,social media,adorable,command,sweet</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>St. Petersburg</media:city>
                  <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sat, 29 Apr 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2595</guid>
                  <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 10:53:38 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2595.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2595.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>First-time rider's mishap: girl's scooter adventure ends with a bump!</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a candid video captured by @wkmzxuk_ on July 15, 2023, in the City of Soligorsk, Minsk region, Belarus, a young girl's first-time experience with an electronic scooter took an unexpected turn. With enthusiasm and excitement, she hopped onto the scooter but found herself struggling to control its speed. Unaware of the gears and unfamiliar with braking, she careened toward a stationary sign near a building, unable to halt her momentum. The result was a comical yet cautionary collision, reminding viewers of the importance of learning the basics before embarking on new adventures. While the girl's misadventure might have left her a little shaken, it undoubtedly served as a valuable lesson for both her and others who dare to ride the scooters for the first time.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>scooter,mishap,video,girl,first-time,adventure,excitement,gears,braking,collision,cautionary,comical,lessons,learning,electronic,speed,sign,building,Belarus,Soligorsk</media:keywords>
                  <media:city> City of Soligorsk, Minsk region</media:city>
                  <media:country>Belarus</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>BY</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Fails and Funnies</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2594</guid>
                  <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 10:53:05 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2594.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2594.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Tranquil moments: Tokyo's beloved dog relishes in shallow creek at favorite park</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a heartwarming scene captured on June 24, 2023, in Tokyo, Japan, @mr.donbei_inu shared a delightful video of his beloved dog finding sheer bliss in a small, slow creek at their favorite park. The four-legged companion appeared completely at ease, comfortably resting its head on the surface of the shallow water, joyfully savoring the gentle flow around it. Unlike most dogs, this furry friend chose not to swim but found pure contentment in merely basking in the refreshing water. With a serene expression, the canine seemed to have discovered a little piece of paradise amidst the bustling city, making this tranquil spot its most cherished destination in the park.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>dog,creek,park,Tokyo,Japan,chilling,water,shallow,serene,bliss,favorite,video,pet,companion,contentment,relaxation,joy,tranquility,peaceful,happiness</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Tokyo</media:city>
                  <media:country>Japan</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>JP</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2593</guid>
                  <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 10:52:42 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2593.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2593.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Love blossoms at a birthday party: tender smiles of a toddler</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a heartwarming moment captured by @ayreeeshh_ on March 12, 2023, at a birthday party in Las Piñas, Manila, Philippines, a two-year-old boy named Drei melted hearts as he looked tenderly at a little girl named Aliah. The usually quiet and well-behaved toddler seemed to be smitten with Aliah, flashing sweet smiles and even raising his eyebrows at her, giving the impression of a young love in the making. Drei's mother shared the adorable video, describing how her son became seemingly interested in Aliah, and it quickly became a viral sensation, spreading joy and warmth across the internet. This endearing encounter serves as a reminder of the innocent and pure connections that can blossom even among the youngest of hearts.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>love,toddler,birthday,party,smiles,tender,falling,in,young,children,innocence,adorable,viral,internet,connections,heartwarming,Manila,Philippines,Aliah,Drei,@ayreeeshh_</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Las Piñas, Manila</media:city>
                  <media:country>Philippines</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>PH</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Heartwarming</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2592</guid>
                  <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 10:51:48 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2592.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2592.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Stranded in the muddy ravine: military jeep's dramatic rescue in Bakhmut, Ukraine</media:title>
                  <media:description>In the rural outskirts of Bakhmut, Ukraine, an extraordinary scene unfolded on May 15, 2023, when a military jeep found itself trapped in the treacherous aftermath of a heavy rainstorm. Captured by @koshkarov_yarik, the vehicle was in the midst of pulling another stuck automobile when it succumbed to the thick mud, leaving its occupants in a precarious situation. As the hours passed and the sun began to set, tension mounted as the stranded group awaited assistance. To their surprise, it was an unexpected twist of fate that came to their aid. While waiting, a bizarre event occurred when their brother arrived to "shoot at the neighbor," causing an uproar of noisy birds. Remarkably, amid the chaos, a timely rescue operation led by fellow military personnel swooped in just in time, ensuring the safe extraction of both vehicles and their relieved occupants. The daring rescue, coupled with the unusual circumstances, left an unforgettable mark on the small community, showcasing the unwavering camaraderie and ingenuity of those serving in Ukraine's military.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>ravine,rain,stuck,jeep,evening,brother,shoot,neighbor,birds,lancet,rescue,mud,Bakhmut,Ukraine,military,daring,trapped,assistance,occupants,community</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Bakhmut</media:city>
                  <media:country>Ukraine</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>UA</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>News</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Mon, 15 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2591</guid>
                  <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 13:06:37 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2591.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2591.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Ukrainian drones strike Moscow: facades damaged, no casualties reported </media:title>
                  <media:description>On the night of July 30, 2023, Moscow, Russia experienced another attack on its facilities by Ukrainian drones, as the ongoing conflict between the two nations continued. The Mayor of Moscow, Sergei Sobyanin, confirmed the incident, stating that the facades of two City office towers sustained slight damage, fortunately without any reported casualties or injuries. The Ministry of Defense revealed that one UAV was successfully destroyed in the air above the Odintsovo district, while two others were thwarted by electronic warfare, causing them to lose control and crash on the territory of Moscow City. Video footage captured the aftermath, depicting shattered glass scattered on the ground in front of the affected buildings. This incident marks yet another escalation in the year-long conflict between Ukraine and Russia, escalating tensions and raising concerns about the safety and stability of the region.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>attack,ukrainian,drones,moscow,russia,conflict,mayor,facades,damage,casualties,injured,ministry,defense,UAV,destroyed,Odintsovo,electronic warfare,crashed,territory,video footage</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Moscow</media:city>
                  <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>News</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2590</guid>
                  <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 13:05:13 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2590.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2590.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title> Ukrainian drones attack Moscow, captured on video by tourist amid ongoing conflict with Russia</media:title>
                  <media:description>On the night of July 30, 2023, Moscow experienced an unsettling incident as two Ukrainian drones launched an attack on the capital. Fortunately, there were no reported casualties or injuries, but the facades of two City office towers were slightly damaged. Mayor Sergey Sobyanin confirmed the attack and stated that the military successfully destroyed one UAV with air defense systems in the Odintsovo district of the Moscow region. Additionally, two more drones were brought down by electronic warfare, losing control and crashing onto the grounds of the Moscow City non-residential building complex. Among the witnesses was a young girl visiting the city with her grandmother, who unintentionally captured the dramatic moment of a drone's fall and subsequent explosion on video. The attack adds to the ongoing tension between Ukraine and Russia, which has been engulfed in a military conflict for over a year.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>moscow,attack,drones,ukrainian,explosions,mayor,damaged,casualties,military,air defense,electronic warfare,crash,witness,girl,grandmother,video,tension,conflict,authorities,implications</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Moscow</media:city>
                  <media:country>Ukraine</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>UA</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>News</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2589</guid>
                  <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 13:05:52 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2589.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2589.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Foiled Ukrainian drone attack on Moscow City tower amid ongoing Russia-Ukraine conflict</media:title>
                  <media:description>On July 30, 2023, Moscow, Russia, experienced the consequences of a foiled drone attack on the Moscow City tower, caught on video. The explosion caused significant damage, shattering windows on the 11th floor and leaving fragments of the drone and glass near the building's entrance. Thankfully, there were no casualties reported, and emergency services quickly responded to the scene. The Russian Ministry of Defense confirmed the attack, attributing it to Ukrainian unmanned aerial vehicles engaged in attempted terrorism. According to the Ministry, two UAVs managed to suppress electronic warfare before losing control and crashing onto the territory of Moscow City. This incident adds to the escalating tensions between Ukraine and Russia, as both countries have been in conflict for some time now.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>explosion,drone,attack,Moscow,Russia,windows,fragments,entrance,casualties,emergency,services,foiled,Ukrainian,electronic,warfare,conflict,tension,video,11th floor,Ministry,July 30</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Moscow</media:city>
                  <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>News</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2588</guid>
                  <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 13:06:05 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2588.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2588.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Tenacious twig tug-of-war: a dog's unyielding affair with nature's bounty</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a delightful and amusing scene captured by @chelseareject on May 21, 2023, in Jersey City, New Jersey, USA, her four-legged companion exhibited an unshakeable determination during a playful encounter with nature. The video showcased the adorable pup clenching onto a sizable twig of a tree, despite the owner's best efforts to convince it otherwise. With @chelseareject's voice gently coaxing the dog to release its prized find, the resilient canine remained unyielding, steadfastly refusing to let go. Undeterred, they strolled along together, the furry protagonist proudly showcasing its prized possession in an endearing tug-of-war with the forces of nature. The heartwarming display of canine spirit and persistence resonated with viewers worldwide, capturing the essence of a special bond between humans and their loyal companions.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>tree,dog,twig,nature,Jersey City,USA,May,2023,video,pet,playful,determined,adorable,owner,walk,bonding,persistence,loyalty,companionship,endearing,capture</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Jersey City, New Jersey</media:city>
                  <media:country>United States</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>US</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sun, 21 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2586</guid>
                  <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 09:23:40 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2586.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2586.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Cat burglar in Buenos Aires: feline filches cash and cuddles up!</media:title>
                  <media:description>In an amusing incident in Buenos Aires, Argentina, on July 6, 2023, a mischievous cat turned into a daring thief. A video captured by @gaston__joaquin showed the feline delving into a handbag and snatching a bundle of money before darting off towards the bedroom. The curious owner followed the sneaky cat's trail to find it lounging on the bed with the stolen cash. This lighthearted escapade left everyone amused and highlighted the unpredictable antics of our four-legged companions.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>cat,thief,money,video,Buenos Aires,Argentina,handbag,bed,owner,amusing,feline,daring,curious,sneaky,trail,lounging,stolen,cash,lighthearted,antics</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Buenos Aires</media:city>
                  <media:country>Argentina</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>AR</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Thu, 6 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2585</guid>
                  <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 09:24:40 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2585.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2585.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Fast-pass to thrills: a wild ride at Disneyland!</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a heartwarming yet adrenaline-pumping moment at Disneyland, California, USA, a father's attempt to reassure his daughter during a roller coaster ride took an unexpected turn. Captured by @enrique7kcg on July 9, 2023, the video shows the duo enjoying the thrilling experience, but with a hilarious twist. As they embarked on the coaster adventure, the father promised his daughter that they would take it slow, only to find the roller coaster had other plans. Despite his reassurances, the ride took off at high speed, resulting in his daughter's excited yet terrified screams. Sharing the video on social media, @enrique7kcg humorously captioned it as "I got a fast-pass to hell for this one." The heartwarming father-daughter moment, coupled with the roller coaster's unexpected speed, made it a cherished memory for both, an unforgettable day of family fun at the magical land of Disneyland.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>roller coaster,disneyland,california,usa,father,daughter,ride,fast-pass,thrill,adventure,hilarious,social media,caption,screams,family,fun,magical,amusement park,memory,excitement</media:keywords>
                  <media:city> California</media:city>
                  <media:country>United States</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>US</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Heartwarming</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sun, 9 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2584</guid>
                  <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 08:24:03 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2584.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2584.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Drone crashes into Moscow City tower in Russia</media:title>
                  <media:description>An explosion occurred on 30 July 2023 in the 50-storey building of the IQ-quarter located in Moscow City.

The incident took place in the building at 10/2 Presnenskaya Embankment, at the level of the fifth or sixth floors, where the glazing was “broken”. No harm done.

The tower was evacuated, law enforcement agencies arrived at the scene.

Shortly before this, air defense systems repelled an attack by drones in the Moscow region. According to 112, the drones were shot down near Odintsovo and Krasnogorsk.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>moscow,russia,drone,crash,war,ukraine,moscow city,explosion</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Moscow</media:city>
                  <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>News</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2582</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023 17:45:16 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2582.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2582.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Cake mishap: hilarious family moment in Ankara, Turkey</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a heartwarming yet comical family moment captured in Ankara, Turkey, a video shared by @amywinehouzze on July 15, 2023, showcased their little one indulging in a cake while kneeling on a dining chair. The child's innocent delight was infectious as they merrily savored the cake in one hand, but alas, laughter ensued as the sweet treat slipped from their grasp while trying to juggle it with the other hand. Surrounding family members couldn't help but burst into fits of laughter, turning the mishap into an unforgettable memory. This endearing scene reminds us of the simple joys and shared laughter that bring families together, creating cherished moments to be cherished for years to come.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>cake,kid,dining,table,Ankara,Turkey,video,laughter,family,moment,comical,mishap,sweet,treat,delight,memorable,joy,shared,precious,memory</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Ankara</media:city>
                  <media:country>Turkey</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>TR</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Fails and Funnies</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2581</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023 17:45:47 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2581.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2581.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Loving Thai cat Luna: a tale of motherhood and her warrior kitten, Himars</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a heartwarming incident captured by @uvarova0304 on December 4, 2022 in Kyiv, Ukraine, a young mother cat named Luna, of the Thai breed, displayed her loving and protective nature towards her kittens. In particular, Luna's adventurous kitten, Himars, was spotted hanging on a rope, prompting his mother's immediate intervention. With great care and determination, Luna managed to rescue Himars and carried him to safety. The three kittens, Javelina, Khimars, and Bayroktarovna, grew up under Luna's watchful eye, venturing out of their box as they became more curious about the world. Despite their curiosity, Luna remained a vigilant and caring mother, keeping a close eye on her offspring to ensure their safety. Himars, playfully referred to as "child of war" by the author, seemed to embody a spirited nature, often prompting his mother's protective instincts. Now living with their owners, the kittens are showered with love and affection, with regular photo and video updates shared with their original caretakers. It's heartening to see such a strong bond between Luna and her kittens, and the incident with the rope underscores the loving protection she provides, even when the situation might not have posed a significant threat, given Himars' proximity to the floor.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>kittens,motherhood,love,rescue,cat,Luna,Himars,Javelina,Khimars,Bayroktarovna,curiosity,protective,care,owners,Ukraine,Kyiv,video,photos,affection,adorable</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Kyiv</media:city>
                  <media:country>Ukraine</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>UA</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sun, 4 Dec 2022</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2580</guid>
                  <pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 08:53:45 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2580.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2580.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Intense hailstorm hits Central Ottawa: golf ball sized hail pummels the city for 5 minutes!</media:title>
                  <media:description>On July 28, 2023, residents of Ottawa, Canada, experienced an intense hailstorm that left them astonished and wary. The event was captured on video by @paulajroy, who shared the gripping footage of the hailstorm outside her house. Lasting for approximately five minutes, the hailstones reached nearly the size of golf balls, causing significant concern for property damage and potential risks to individuals caught outdoors. The severe weather phenomenon swept through central Ottawa, leaving a trail of destruction in its wake.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>hailstorm,ottawa,canada,weather,intense,video,paulajroy,golfball,sized,hail,central,astonishment,damage,risk,outdoors,severe,phenomenon,destruction,warnings,precautions</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Ottawa </media:city>
                  <media:country>Canada</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>CA</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Weather</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2579</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023 17:39:58 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2579.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2579.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Resourceful feline masters the art of door-opening: a fascinating tale from Jepara, Indonesia!</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a captivating video captured by @muktafil on April 24, 2023, in Jepara, Indonesia, an astonishing feat unfolded as their clever cat showcased its ingenuity. The footage showcases the feline effortlessly opening the door to the house, by jumping on the door handle leaving its owner in awe of its newfound talent. Expressing his astonishment, the author stated, "I was surprised that the cat opened the door by itself, now if you put it outside, it will open the door. Don't know where it learned from." The video has since captured the hearts of viewers worldwide, as they marvel at the resourceful cat's ability to conquer the seemingly insurmountable obstacle. This extraordinary tale serves as a reminder of the intelligence and adaptability possessed by our feline companions.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>clever,cat,door,opening,video,Jepara,Indonesia,surprise,talent,resourceful,ingenuity,amazement,owner,outside,learn,astonishment,heartwarming,intelligence,adaptability,feline</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Jepara</media:city>
                  <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>ID</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2578</guid>
                  <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 07:29:30 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2578.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2578.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Bathroom bliss: Indonesian cat's unique way to beat the heat</media:title>
                  <media:description>In Yogyakarta, Indonesia, a heartwarming video captured by @bagus_muhammad_ on March 28, 2023, showcases the adorable antics of his feline companion during a hot day. The short clip features his cat lying flat on its stomach in the cool confines of the bathroom, delightfully spreading its hind legs for ultimate relaxation. As temperatures rise, it seems this clever kitty has found its perfect oasis for beating the heat. With a contented expression on its face, it's evident that the bathroom has become the preferred spot for the cat to seek respite from the sweltering weather. </media:description>
                  <media:keywords>cat,bathroom,Indonesia,Yogyakarta,video,pet,feline,hot,heat,adorable,antics,relaxation,hind legs,oasis,cool,weather,comfort,pets,content,warmer days</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Yogyakarta</media:city>
                  <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>ID</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2577</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 08:17:01 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2577.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2577.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Miraculous rescue: cat safely recovered from perilous heights in Minsk</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a heartwarming incident in Minsk, Belarus, on July 19, 2023, a vigilant passerby, @victory_shh, captured a remarkable moment when a cat's life was saved from a precarious situation. The cat found itself in a perilous predicament, clinging onto a window pane on the outside of a story building. Curiosity piqued when the author noticed the presence of the Ministry of Emergencies' vehicle nearby. Upon approaching the scene, they witnessed the heartening sight of a rescue operation in progress. The skilled emergency responders swiftly rescued the cat after it appeared to fall and secured the frightened feline, bringing it to safety. Thankfully, the rescue was successful, and the cat was handed over to a man, presumably its owner.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>rescue,cat,building,Minsk,Belarus,window,emergency,passerby,video,heartwarming,precarious,Ministry,height,safe,owner,compassion,celebration,online,courage,grateful</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Minsk</media:city>
                  <media:country>Belarus</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>BY</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Rescue</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2576</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 08:16:28 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2576.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2576.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Devastating wildfire strikes near Volos, Greece</media:title>
                  <media:description>On July 27, 2023, a destructive wildfire ravaged the area near Volos, Greece, causing significant damage to an ammunition depot situated in the coastal town of Nea Aghialos. The depot, belonging to the Greek air force, was engulfed in flames, leading to powerful explosions that echoed through the region. Local media reported on the incident, and officials took immediate action, ordering the evacuation of several communities in the severely impacted Magnesia area along the northern coast of Athens. As the fires continued to spread, @peterjaygood captured a video showcasing smoke billowing from a distance from the fires near Volos. The situation remained critical, with authorities and emergency services working tirelessly to contain the blaze and protect the affected communities.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>wildfire,volos,greece,ammunition,depot,explosions,evacuation,magnesia,coastal,nea aghialos,greek air force,damage,smoke,fires,video,@peterjaygood,media,officials,communities,Athens</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Volos</media:city>
                  <media:country>Greece</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>GR</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>News</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2575</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 07:26:05 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2575.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2575.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Gas explosion rocks residential building in Nizhnekamsk</media:title>
                  <media:description>On July 25, 2023, a devastating gas explosion shook a five-story residential building in Nizhnekamsk, Russia, leaving behind a trail of destruction and injuries. The incident resulted in two people being injured, while eight other residents managed to evacuate independently from the burning structure. The building suffered partial destruction, with the load-bearing structures being severely damaged and the windows of some apartments shattered. As the dust settled, the community was left in shock and uncertainty as authorities began their investigation into the cause of the explosion. With no information yet on the root of the tragedy, residents and officials are left grappling with the aftermath, seeking answers and support for the affected individuals and families.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>explosion,residential,building,nizhnekamsk,russia,injured,evacuation,fire,damage,gas,incident,cause,investigation,shattered,uncertainty,shock,community,support,tragedy,aftermath.</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Nizhnekamsk</media:city>
                  <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>News</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2574</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 08:15:40 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2574.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2574.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Adventurous Manda: a curious cat's high-rise escapades in Yogyakarta!</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a captivating moment caught on video by @a.youu_ on July 4, 2023, in Yogyakarta, Indonesia, a curious cat named Manda was spotted perched atop an unfinished building. The enigmatic feline appeared unsure of its surroundings, leaving viewers both amused and intrigued by its daring escapade. With a playful spirit, the author decided to record the charming scene, showcasing Manda's adventurous nature and uncertain demeanor as it surveyed the world from its lofty vantage point.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>cat,video,Yogyakarta,Indonesia,Manda,building,perched,curious,confused,fun,playful,adventurous,daring,charming,uncertain,climb,pet,antics,moment,heartwarming</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Yogyakarta</media:city>
                  <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>ID</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Tue, 4 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2573</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 08:15:12 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2573.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2573.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                     </channel>
                  </rss>
                