<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
        xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
        xmlns:openSearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearchrss/1.0/"
        xmlns:dfpvideo="http://api.google.com/dfpvideo"
        xmlns:tms="http://data.tmsapi.com/v1.1"
        version="2.0">
         <channel>
           <title>ViralBear videos</title>
           <dfpvideo:version>2</dfpvideo:version><item>
             <media:title>Hailstorm halts play: Coors Field transformed into winter wonderland as Rockies await Dodgers</media:title>
             <media:description>On June 29th, 2023, Coors Field in Denver, Colorado, USA, experienced a severe hailstorm that interrupted the preparations for the Colorado Rockies' game against the Los Angeles Dodgers. 
 @KelsWingert captured a video of hail pouring into the press box, with thick hail covering the field and seats. Despite the challenging weather conditions, the forecast looked promising for game time. Coors Field workers were seen diligently filling buckets with the mixture of water and hail that blocked the dugout doors to the home clubhouse. Colorado Rockies catcher Elias Diaz even took an adventurous dive into the small hail on the field. As the storm subsided, the stadium transformed into a temporary winter wonderland as everyone awaited the resumption of the game at 6 p.m.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>hailstorm,Coors Field,Denver,Colorado,USA,weather,severe,thunderstorm,hail,press box,game,forecast,field,seats,workers,buckets,clubhouse,Rockies,Dodgers,dive,winter wonderland</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Denver, Colorado</media:city>
             <media:country>United States</media:country>
             <media:category>Weather</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2345</guid>
             <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 10:18:46 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/0a43c7aa-7d0f-4e52-acba-9f56426fa81c.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/a411fda8-3b34-4d53-ac5e-c94ecfe8ada2.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Sea Paradise Festival ignites Quy Nhon City: spectacular fireworks draw crowds and cause traffic on Reunification Day</media:title>
             <media:description>Quy Nhon City Center in Binh Dinh province, Vietnam, came alive on April 30th, 2022, as the Sea Paradise Festival unfolded with a mesmerizing display of fireworks as captured by @tksdo.04. The occasion was none other than Reunification Day, attracting throngs of people who eagerly gathered in the streets to witness the spectacular event. However, the surge in attendance resulted in overcrowding, leading to significant traffic jams throughout the city. Despite the challenges posed by the congestion, the people were eager to witness the celebration.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>fireworks,celebration,Reunification Day,festival,Quy Nhon,Binh Dinh,Vietnam,crowds,gathering,city center,traffic,chaos,overcrowding,mesmerizing,atmosphere,unity,joy,night sky,enchanting,spectacle</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Quy Nhon City </media:city>
             <media:country>Vietnam</media:country>
             <media:category>News</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2022</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2342</guid>
             <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 19:20:30 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/8e4c248b-db47-490d-be6a-a88123de073a.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/adb3d819-afc2-4fc9-a2eb-1cc7434498e6.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Unusual sunbathing buddy: large lizard pet enjoys window peeping in Bandung, Indonesia</media:title>
             <media:description>A remarkable video captured by @reptilergabut on June 16, 2023, in Bandung, Indonesia, showcases a peculiar sight—a large lizard-like reptile peeping on a window. Surprisingly, the author claims that this reptile is their pet. The footage, recorded at their home while sunbathing, has left viewers astonished and curious of the unusual sunbathing buddy. </media:description>
             <media:keywords>reptile,lizard,pet,video,window,Bandung,Indonesia,sunbathing,captured,peeping,home,astonishing,curious,encounter,mysterious,unusual,footage,remarkable,tags,small</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Bandung</media:city>
             <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
             <media:category>Animals</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2341</guid>
             <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 18:52:51 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/e28bf0d0-15a0-4377-a117-a74c5898d350.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/f6db2590-ef96-444a-bd6d-58605cb0eccf.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Startling workshop blast caught on camera!</media:title>
             <media:description>In a shocking incident captured on camera, a workshop in Nghe An province, Vietnam became the site of a sudden explosion. On March 17th, 2023, @nghenhanmockhoanghethuat, the owner of the workshop, was engrossed in his work on the opposite side of the room. Out of nowhere, an item he had plugged in on the table erupted in a violent explosion. As it turned out later, the battery exploded. Reacting swiftly, @nghenhanmockhoanghethuat cautiously made his way towards the switch and swiftly unplugged it, bringing an end to the dangerous situation. </media:description>
             <media:keywords>explosion,workshop,video,Nghe An province,Vietnam,@nghenhanmockhoanghethuat,March 17th,2023,danger,unplugged,table,incident,owner,camera,hazard,workspace,vigilant,responsive,shocking,small letters,tags</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Nghe An province</media:city>
             <media:country>Vietnam</media:country>
             <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2338</guid>
             <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 13:45:18 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/c42a4150-8f42-48bd-a75c-4d00c710f395.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/55e77597-13a8-4dc8-8b02-e2209ce35604.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>First steps by the shore: a father's love and a daughter's beach adventure</media:title>
             <media:description>In a heartwarming scene captured by @muoimuoi0306 on October 1st, 2021, at Vung Tau beach in Vietnam, a father and his just over one-year-old daughter shared a special moment. It was the little girl's first time at the beach, and her father gently carried her towards the shoreline. With a mix of excitement and trepidation, he set her down on the sand, allowing her to take her first steps on her own. However, as the waves rolled in, a sudden tide caught her off guard, causing her to stumble. But her father was there in an instant, scooping her up in his protective arms. From that point on, they continued their beach adventure together, with the father cradling his daughter as they enjoyed the rhythmic embrace of the tides. It was a beautiful display of a father's love and a precious memory that will surely be cherished for years to come.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>beach,family,father,daughter,love,milestone,joy,parenting,bonding,waves,tide,sand,first steps,adventure,Vung Tau,Vietnam,precious,memories,embrace,video</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Vung Tau</media:city>
             <media:country>Vietnam</media:country>
             <media:category>Heartwarming</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Fri, 1 Oct 2021</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2337</guid>
             <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 13:30:56 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/d614ddfe-a23b-4297-a7b0-6d546159f537.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/9bda8956-6224-4b9f-92a4-e9d6bc5f38ba.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Motherly cat takes kitten on a house adventure, returns it safely to siblings</media:title>
             <media:description>In a heartwarming scene captured by @izanzzz_ in Sleman, Yogyakarta, Indonesia on June 1st, 2023, a remarkable display of motherly instincts unfolded. A video showcased a cat, presumed to be the mother, carefully picking up a kitten and embarking on a gentle journey around the entire house. Initially, it seemed as though the mother was relocating her offspring, but to everyone's surprise, she returned the tiny feline to its original spot. The remarkable cat walked purposefully with the kitten in tow, ensuring its safety, before reuniting it with its siblings.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>cat,kitten,video,motherly,instincts,journey,house,tour,reunion,feline,bond,care,protection,love,animals,pets,adorable,heartwarming,Sleman,Yogyakarta</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Sleman, Yogyakarta</media:city>
             <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
             <media:category>Animals</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Thu, 1 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2335</guid>
             <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 12:29:13 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/58e91622-56f1-4cd0-9d5b-de5ed4f1001a.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/e404a538-53ca-47ae-9be2-2434d465e19b.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Michigan's skyline vanishes: Detroit engulfed in smoke as Canadian wildfires blanket the region</media:title>
             <media:description>Detroit, Michigan, USA - A video captured by @Michigameman313 on June 27th, 2023, reveals a disquieting sight as Michigan becomes shrouded in dense smoke originating from the ongoing wildfires in Canada. With the wildfires raging for several months now, more than a third of the US population, stretching from the Midwest to the East Coast, finds themselves under air quality alerts due to the pervasive reach of the Canadian wildfire smoke. The skyline of Detroit disappears behind a haze, casting an eerie atmosphere over the city as the impacts of the wildfires make their presence felt across the region.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>smoke,video,Detroit,Michigan,Canada,wildfires,air quality,alerts,Midwest,East Coast,USA,sight,shrouded,haze,skyline,eerie,atmosphere,impacts,region</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Detroit, Michigan </media:city>
             <media:country>United States</media:country>
             <media:category>News</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2333</guid>
             <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 11:49:32 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/462bf183-d2c6-405d-9566-0b611444c92d.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/f91c84a9-efc3-4579-b07a-49e02a604201.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Unfazed foodie: dining through floodwaters in Johor Bahru</media:title>
             <media:description>In a remarkable display of nonchalance, a local resident in Johor Bahru, Malaysia, captured a video that showcased an open restaurant engulfed in floodwaters. The footage, recorded by @bobieeee991 on May 3rd, 2023, revealed diners calmly continuing their meal as water flowed on the road and even under their tables. Undeterred by the unexpected turn of events, the author and his friend carried on eating, as the flooding subsided shortly after it began.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>flooding,open restaurant,video,eating,flood waters,road,table,Malaysia,Johor Bahru,nonchalance,diners,meal,water,unexpected,resilience,adaptability,nature,intervention,harm,surreal</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Johor Bahru</media:city>
             <media:country>Malaysia</media:country>
             <media:category>Weather</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Wed, 3 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2331</guid>
             <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 18:38:03 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/b2b66ff8-ca26-4043-a462-aed24f22d0e4.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/4bf813c1-ec59-4270-969d-518bc41f5733.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Adventures of Morty: the mischievous pancake bandit</media:title>
             <media:description>In a humorous video captured by @nas_sam on June 6th, 2020 in St. Petersburg, Russia, her mischievous feline companion named Morty, inspired by the popular show Rick and Morty, attempted to steal some pancakes from the table. Despite the owner's attempts to discourage this behavior, the cunning cat proved to be a persistent food thief. Fast forward to the present day in Uzbekistan, Morty's thieving antics continue, with no signs of stopping.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>kitten,stealing,food,table,wean,failed,Uzbekistan,Morty,Rick and Morty,three years old,video,captured,pancakes,cat,mischievous,thief,antics,household,humor,exasperation</media:keywords>
             <media:city>St. Petersburg</media:city>
             <media:country>Russia</media:country>
             <media:category>Animals</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Sat, 6 Jun 2020</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2329</guid>
             <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 17:57:32 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2dcb8344-5395-4202-8aef-9b0541cd617b.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/83aa1a18-073e-45db-9154-b09c05a255dd.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Playful pursuit: Sasuke the dog's hilarious chase with a clever crow</media:title>
             <media:description>In a delightful scene captured by @sasuke_2017.0808 on June 14th, 2023, in Tokyo, Japan, a video showcased the amusing encounter between a persistent dog named Sasuke and a clever black crow. The canine's excitement was sparked as it spotted the crow perched on the balcony. However, instead of flying away, the mischievous bird continuously relocated to different parts of the balcony, keeping Sasuke in a constant pursuit. The author, found great amusement in witnessing this comical interaction between his dog and the crafty crow, creating a moment filled with laughter and joy.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>dog,crow,chase,balcony,Tokyo,Japan,video,Sasuke,amusement,laughter,pets,animals,funny,entertaining,playful,clever,mischievous,owner,encounter,joy</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Tokyo </media:city>
             <media:country>Japan</media:country>
             <media:category>Animals</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2328</guid>
             <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 17:36:10 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/7c1bad1f-9d05-4c66-bca4-754b7fa5d8d5.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/77ce2601-f34d-4050-a660-13c350ae6a0b.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Captivating lightning illuminates Fredericksburg's night sky, creating a dazzling display</media:title>
             <media:description>In a captivating video captured by @thegavinwhite24 on June 26th, 2023, in Fredericksburg, Virginia, USA, the night sky was momentarily transformed into a breathtaking spectacle. As the author drove through the darkness, a bolt of bright streak lightning shattered the tranquility, illuminating the surroundings with an intensity that rivaled daylight. Lasting a mere five seconds, this incredible display left the author in awe, capturing the attention of viewers worldwide. </media:description>
             <media:keywords>lightning,night,Fredericksburg,Virginia,USA,video,driving,bright,streak,sky,day,moment,captivating,intense,power,awe,wonder,nature,raw,spectacle</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Fredericksburg, Virginia</media:city>
             <media:country>United States</media:country>
             <media:category>Weather</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2327</guid>
             <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 08:21:00 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/04c6f5a9-23cf-4cdc-94cd-25f934369613.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/3a12df32-fd41-4f1c-b6e9-e320859c7403.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>A woman is very lucky at a pedestrian crossing in Omsk, Russia</media:title>
             <media:description>In a heart-stopping incident in Omsk, Russia, a pedestrian's life was spared by a stroke of luck. On June 15th, 2023, a reckless driver failed to notice the woman as he sped towards the pedestrian crossing. Just a few meters away, the driver abruptly hit the brakes, narrowly avoiding a catastrophic collision. The vehicle skidded to a halt, teetering on the brink of overturning, while the shaken woman looked on in disbelief. The incident has ignited calls for the installation of speed bumps in front of the crossing, in the hope that such measures might deter future reckless drivers and safeguard pedestrians from similar encounters.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>reckless,driver,pedestrian,high speed,slowing down,speed bumps,safety,guardian angel,video,woman,narrow escape,emergency brakes,overturn,incident,Omsk,Russia,MSCh 9,crossing,collision,vigilance</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Omsk</media:city>
             <media:country>Russia</media:country>
             <media:category>News</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2326</guid>
             <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 08:10:46 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/ec700293-9ba9-4c39-a645-15e4a1198db0.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/e704584b-34fb-4611-9550-ae2ff4de109b.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Chasing the elements: spectacular double rainbow enchants Ontario's skies</media:title>
             <media:description>On June 26th, 2023, storm chaser @craigdunmore stumbled upon a mesmerizing sight near Staples, Ontario, Canada. Capturing the moment on video, he excitedly shared the footage of a double rainbow stretching across the sky. The day had already been filled with thrilling experiences, including a probable funnel and captivating cloud formations. However, it was this vivid display of nature's artistry that left the author in awe. With his chase day now complete, the enchanting double rainbow served as a breathtaking finale to an unforgettable adventure.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>rainbow,chase,storm,Ontario,Canada,video,beauty,clouds,mesmerizing,nature,artistry,enchanting,breathtaking,adventure,weather,double,vivid,finale,awesome,funnel</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Staples, Ontario</media:city>
             <media:country>Canada</media:country>
             <media:category>Weather</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2325</guid>
             <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 07:57:14 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/580bdf7c-66d2-4e23-aad4-e01d2ada3d79.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2edc6cd6-bf93-4e0e-a0a9-1a1df9cda32b.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Unauthorized helicopter landing at gas station in Altai</media:title>
             <media:description>The Gorno-Altai transport prosecutor's office has launched an investigation into an incident involving a helicopter in the Aktash village of the Altai Republic, Russia. Eyewitnesses captured footage of a Robinson helicopter landing at a gas stationon June 9th, 2023, raising concerns about safety. The pilot's departure from the site was marked by a perilous maneuver near power lines. The West Siberian Transport Prosecutor's Office revealed that the landing and takeoff had taken place without the necessary authorization from the aviation department. As the audit unfolds, there is a possibility of a criminal case being initiated.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>helicopter,incident,investigation,Altai,Russia,gas station,eyewitnesses,footage,safety,pilot,departure,power lines,unauthorized,landing,takeoff,transport prosecutor's office,audit,criminal case,Aktash village,West Siberian</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Altai</media:city>
             <media:country>Russia</media:country>
             <media:category>News</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Fri, 9 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2324</guid>
             <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 20:36:42 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/815d1424-308e-4441-96dd-ab80a7270e1c.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/75804d0a-1020-4301-931a-df0cd10df364.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Adorable surprise: little Valentina's birthday dance with cat melts hearts worldwide!</media:title>
             <media:description>In a heartwarming moment captured on camera, a small girl named Valentina stole the internet's heart as she danced with a cat at her mom's birthday party in Lancaster, Texas, USA. The adorable video, filmed by @rockysoto74 on  October 1, 2022 and shared on TikTok, showcased Valentina holding the cat by its fore legs, as if they were hugging, while dancing to her sister's favorite song. Little did the author know that the innocent video would go viral overnight, garnering immense love and attention from people around the world. Despite being an unintended surprise, Valentina's delightful dance with her feline friend resonated with viewers, spreading joy and warmth in a single, heartfelt moment.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>dance,cat,girl,viral,heartwarming,birthday,party,Texas,USA,video,TikTok,hug,favorite,song,surprise,love,attention,joy,warmth,moment</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Lancaster, Texas</media:city>
             <media:country>United States</media:country>
             <media:category>Heartwarming</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Sat, 1 Oct 2022</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2322</guid>
             <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 19:48:19 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/69e155e9-a4fb-49de-b050-19fed0a49fbd.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/af8b06eb-b934-44a6-ae4b-543d06426ff2.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Terrifying blaze engulfs Ajman One Tower 02 in UAE's Ajman City</media:title>
             <media:description>In the early evening hours of June 26, 2023, a massive fire erupted in Tower 02 of the Ajman One residential complex in Ajman, United Arab Emirates. A video captured by @Ali_Abdulla99 shows the building's corner engulfed in flames, with debris falling to the ground as emergency services rush to the scene. The fire, which quickly grew in intensity, was eventually brought under control after hours of relentless efforts. Fortunately, there are no casualties.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>fire,high-rise,residential,complex,Ajman,UAE,disaster,emergency,flames,video,footage,incident,authorities,panic,debris,inferno,firefighters,catastrophe,safety,evacuation</media:keywords>
             <media:city> Ajman City</media:city>
             <media:country>United Arab Emirates</media:country>
             <media:category>News</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2320</guid>
             <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 12:43:00 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/eda64977-01ef-4c9e-a84e-cc55fe4142f7.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/731d0c1e-b814-483c-83bb-aa3d32326b18.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Vibrant victory: Sporting CP handball team shakes up Portuguese Cup celebration bus!</media:title>
             <media:description>The Sporting CP handball team triumphed in the Portuguese Cup, and their exuberant celebration on a bus en route to the airport became a sight to behold. Captured in a video by @sportingcp.adeptos on June 12, 2023, in Santa Cruz, Madeira, Portugal, the victorious players' jubilation caused the entire bus to shake. The shaking was so intense that it jolted those seated inside, resulting in contagious laughter. The team's contagious joy and the unexpected bus tremors perfectly encapsulated the spirit of their Portuguese Cup victory.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>sporting,cp,handball,team,celebration,bus,portuguese cup,victory,video,shaking,laughter,santa cruz,madeira,portugal,triumph,exuberant,players,passengers,joy,tremors</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Santa Cruz, Madeira</media:city>
             <media:country>Portugal</media:country>
             <media:category>Sport</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2318</guid>
             <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 05:25:19 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2318.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2318.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Mischievous mac n' cheese muncher: wombat breaks into camper's tent in Melbourne!</media:title>
             <media:description>In a surprising turn of events, a video captured by @charliefowlvr on June 24, 2023, in Melbourne, Australia, shows a cheeky wombat making its way into a camper's tent. The mischievous creature apparently had a craving for mac n' cheese, as it had chewed its way through the tent to get a taste of the cheesy delight. In the footage, the wombat's head can be seen peeking inside the tent, while its body remains outside. This unexpected encounter highlights the resourcefulness and determination of Australia's native wildlife, even when it comes to satisfying their unusual appetites.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>wombat,tent,Melbourne,Australia,video,mac n cheese,chewed,wildlife,encounter,curious,mischief,resourcefulness,appetites,unexpected,capture,cheeky,craving,taste,camper,head</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Melbourne</media:city>
             <media:country>Australia</media:country>
             <media:category>Animals</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2317</guid>
             <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 05:00:05 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/25ed8c77-d811-4f5d-983f-d624ee57c5a3.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/c3722437-b69d-4adc-a6e4-971a6ab6d62f.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Captivating canine concert: witness the enchanting howl of a Weimaraner!</media:title>
             <media:description>In a charming display of canine vocal prowess, a Weimaraner in La Crosse, Wisconsin, USA, has captivated the internet with its melodious howl. Shared by @mizj3n on May 21st, 2023, a video captured the precious moment as the Weimaraner let out a soulful cry from the comforts of its home. The caption accompanying the footage reads, " You ever seen a Weimaraner howl?... Now you have." The enchanting video quickly garnered attention, drawing viewers into the captivating world of this elegant breed.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>weimaraner,dog,howl,video,La Crosse,Wisconsin,USA,mizj3n,captivating,enchanting,melodious,soulful,internet,moment,precious,caption,attention,breed,elegant,haunting,heartwarming</media:keywords>
             <media:city>La Crosse, Wisconsin</media:city>
             <media:country>United States</media:country>
             <media:category>Animals</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Sun, 21 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2314</guid>
             <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 18:54:29 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/b26d2ddf-bb9e-472c-b048-66136fed54d7.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/af7d812c-a21e-4821-9de5-238246397706.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Furry fun in Moscow: Ares and Axel delight in toy tent playtime!</media:title>
             <media:description>German Spitz breeder, @black_night_pom, based in Moscow, Russia, shared an adorable video on June 17th, 2023. The clip showcased two-month-old puppies, Ares and Axel, who have been reserved and will soon be named Amur and Umka by their excited new owners. The breeder captured the heartwarming moment as the playful pups frolicked inside a toy tent, showcasing their youthful energy and boundless enthusiasm. It's a joy for any owner to witness their beloved furry companions grow and thrive, and this delightful video perfectly captures the pure delight and happiness of these precious German Spitz puppies.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>puppies,breeder,German Spitz,Moscow,Russia,video,reservation,Ares,Axel,Amur,Umka,owners,baby,grow,captured,dogs,playing,toy tent,happy,dogs</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Moscow </media:city>
             <media:country>Russia</media:country>
             <media:category>Animals</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2312</guid>
             <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 18:00:24 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/5a5481d2-74a2-465c-beb5-c92627599d01.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2312.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Explosive chaos: massive fireworks mishap on Simferopol Highway sends shockwaves</media:title>
             <media:description>A disastrous incident unfolded on the night of June 23, 2023, as chaos erupted on the Simferopol highway (M-2) between Podolsk and the village of Aleksandrovka in the Moscow region, Russia. The calamity originated when a trailer, laden with pyrotechnics, detached from a truck traveling towards Moscow. The jolting caused by the explosive cargo potentially triggered the detonation, although the exact cause remains uncertain.

At approximately 23:45, the trailer became unhinged at the 42nd kilometer mark of the Simferopol highway, leading to a fiery accident. The driver, sensing trouble, swiftly maneuvered to the roadside and hastily abandoned the cab. For the next half an hour, a dazzling yet perilous fireworks display unfolded, with volleys detonating around the burning wreckage. Astonishingly, despite the reverberations being heard within a five-kilometer radius, no other vehicles were harmed. The prompt response from the fire department managed to quell the open flames by 00:34. Thankfully, the proximity of the incident to the surrounding forest, coupled with the region's prolonged drought, did not ignite a potentially catastrophic forest fire. By morning, the remnants of the trailer and cab were carefully dismantled and removed from the road, ensuring minimal disruption to traffic.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>trailer,accident,fire,pyrotechnics,detonation,emergency,truck,explosion,highway,fireworks,performance,cab,volleys,sound,surprise,burning,forest,drought,remains,traffic</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Moscow region</media:city>
             <media:country>Russia</media:country>
             <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2311</guid>
             <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 17:35:05 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/7b626fae-d959-4613-bcba-ddc0ae1af6f0.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2a154364-32cb-45de-a866-abd706da10bb.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Unforeseen wardrobe mishap: sister's skirt drops mid-performance, caught on camera!</media:title>
             <media:description>In an unexpected turn of events at a school event in Kediri, Indonesia, a video captured by @risazizah on June 15, 2023, showcased a girl's skirt falling during a performance. What made this incident even more surprising was the fact that the girl in question was none other than the sister of the author herself. As a teacher at the same school, the author had recorded the entire event, unaware that her sister would be the one experiencing a wardrobe malfunction. Fortunately, the girl had worn black leggings underneath, ensuring that she was not left completely exposed. </media:description>
             <media:keywords>school,event,video,skirt,fall,performance,sister,unexpected,captured,incident,leggings,permission,teacher,wardrobe,malfunction,exposure,Kediri,Indonesia,viral,twist</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Kediri</media:city>
             <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
             <media:category>Fails and Funnies</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2309</guid>
             <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 04:38:26 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/6977856a-62b4-4474-965f-1cf394fdc86e.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/ef49dfa7-fc7f-455d-97ee-a38b00918596.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Unforgettable bachelorette fun: hilarious raft tumble at beer olympics afterparty!</media:title>
             <media:description>In a memorable bachelorette party celebration in Collingwood, Ontario, Canada, a group of friends found themselves in fits of laughter and screams after a day of Beer Olympics. The jovial atmosphere was captured on video by @jordan.ash.t on May 24, 2023. The highlight of the day came when one of the friends ingeniously hopped onto a wooden raft by lying flat on her stomach and clutching onto its sides. As the raft tilted to one side, her companions couldn't maintain their balance, plunging into the water with a symphony of shrieks. Luckily, everyone emerged unscathed, floating near the raft on the serene water body. It was an unforgettable moment of joy and camaraderie, capturing the essence of an epic bachelorette celebration. </media:description>
             <media:keywords>beer,olympics,bachelorette,party,friends,video,wooden raft,hilarious,tumble,water,screams,serene,Canada,Collingwood,Ontario,fun,adventure,capture,memories,laughter</media:keywords>
             <media:city> Collingwood, Ontario</media:city>
             <media:country>Canada</media:country>
             <media:category>Fails and Funnies</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Wed, 24 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2308</guid>
             <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 04:22:19 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/94d1f8d6-7067-4cc0-8e05-be1f07e40423.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/c1097b14-f72a-4eee-bd0d-cf143bd60c70.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Jumping for veggies: Muffy the 6-month-old cat's playful vegetable adventure!</media:title>
             <media:description>In a charming video captured by @olga.fedorova1974 on March 31, 2023 in Saint Petersburg, Russia, her mischievous 6-month-old cat, Muffy, takes center stage. The adorable feline can be seen energetically playing with pieces of vegetables scattered on the floor. Standing on her hind legs, Muffy jumps and pounces with delight, displaying her agile moves. In the background, the author's laughter adds an infectious joy to the scene, capturing a heartwarming moment of feline playfulness.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>cat,video,vegetable,play,Muffy,Saint Petersburg,Russia,cute,playful,jumping,hind legs,laughter,adorable,agile,mischievous,floor,joy,feline,pet,entertainment</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Saint Petersburg</media:city>
             <media:country>Russia</media:country>
             <media:category>Animals</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Fri, 31 Mar 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2307</guid>
             <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 04:04:56 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/b9089e09-0f03-4bcb-98c6-53c01f4e366b.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/4319bcb7-a70b-4aa1-89d9-d01e83299779.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Adorable canine captain: fishing adventure awaits with patient pooch in Glendale!</media:title>
             <media:description>In a heartwarming scene captured by @bully_zeppelin on June 5, 2023, in Glendale, Arizona, USA, a video shows a dog sporting a sun hat while patiently waiting in a small boat on the riverbank. The dog's eager anticipation is evident as it awaits its human companion for a fishing trip. The adorable canine captain sits with an air of composure, ready to embark on an exciting adventure.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>dog,boat,riverbank,sun hat,fishing,Glendale,Arizona,USA,video,adorable,canine,captain,patience,waiting,companionship,outdoor,adventure,bond,pet,fishing trip,joy</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Glendale, Arizona</media:city>
             <media:country>United States</media:country>
             <media:category>Animals</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Mon, 5 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2305</guid>
             <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 03:27:20 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/d8cc7378-501f-413f-abb8-6b5d4d864413.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/b9a49555-630c-432b-ab14-92abce8a8db5.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Funny mishap: toddler gets drink in her eyes, dad can't stop laughing!</media:title>
             <media:description>In a heartwarming yet hilarious moment captured on video, a father from St. George, Utah, USA, found himself in a comical mishap while fixing a drink for his young daughter. The footage, shared by @callmedivajustice on May 16, 2023, shows the dad playfully asking his daughter if she wanted to try the drink after vigorously shaking it in a drinking bottle. However, things took an unexpected turn as he opened the lid for his daughter, causing the drink to gush out from the straw and enter the toddler's eyes. Despite the momentary surprise, the brave little girl reassured her dad that she was okay. Unable to contain his laughter, the dad's amusement at the situation was evident.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>video,father,daughter,drink,mishap,laughter,St. George,Utah,USA,toddler,eyes,funny,captured,moment,shake,bottle,gushing,okay,comical,amusement,family</media:keywords>
             <media:city>St. George, Utah</media:city>
             <media:country>United States</media:country>
             <media:category>Fails and Funnies</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Tue, 16 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2304</guid>
             <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 03:07:34 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/64fb124a-800a-4c01-9b11-9cd61d7dcca3.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/dd66a7b4-3eee-4b89-9a04-3d82ce60d72a.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Feline mechanic: adorable cat assists car repair by stretching V-belt on Opel Combo</media:title>
             <media:description>In a heartwarming and unexpected turn of events, a cat in Wyszkow, Poland, became an adorable assistant to its owner's car repair endeavors.  @michaljava350 captured a delightful video on April 1, 2023, showing his feline companion perched on the open hood of his Opel Combo. In the footage, the clever cat can be seen stretching the V-belt, seemingly lending a helping paw to its owner. This charming display of feline ingenuity and companionship showcases the unique bond between the author and his beloved cat.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>cat,car,repair,assistant,Opel Combo,Wyszkow,Poland,video,hood,stretching,V-belt,adorable,mechanic,pet,bond,feline,companion,assistance,unexpected,ingenuity,pets</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Wyszkow</media:city>
             <media:country>Poland</media:country>
             <media:category>Animals</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Sat, 1 Apr 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2292</guid>
             <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 19:35:59 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/474d1de1-67b0-473c-a66b-91bafd131927.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/4bab7513-bf2a-46a2-a2cf-912f16429f89.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Skater dad and his prince passenger: speeding through California with a canine twist!</media:title>
             <media:description>In a heartwarming video capturing the essence of an adventurous spirit, @lilmanlife from California, USA, showcased his unique bond with his furry friend on June 15th, 2023. The footage revealed the skater dad fearlessly gliding on the road with his loyal dog perched on his back. Captioned with a touching sentiment, "Behind every great dad, there is a prince passenger telling him to speed up," the video encapsulated the undeniable companionship between man and canine. </media:description>
             <media:keywords>skating,dog,California,adventure,bond,companionship,video,viral,skateboarding,pet,love,speed,thrill,joy,fatherhood,teamwork,trust,loyalty,outdoor,uplifting</media:keywords>
             <media:city>California</media:city>
             <media:country>United States</media:country>
             <media:category>Cool</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2291</guid>
             <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 19:17:53 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/8178c6e4-4191-4573-b16a-2a552e09f491.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2291.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>A captivating birth: the enchanting green-backed Firecrown at sunset</media:title>
             <media:description>On the evening of June 9th, 2023, as the warm sun began to set over the countryside of Colina, Santiago, Chile, a remarkable sight unfolded at a humble abode. In a hidden corner of the house, amidst a carefully crafted oasis for avian visitors, a captivating video was captured by @jpdelaharpe. The footage revealed a birth of natural splendor, unfolding from a little spring that cascaded like a gentle waterfall. This picturesque scene was home to a special place where birds came to quench their thirst and find respite.

Among the many feathered guests, a stunning Green-backed Firecrown stole the spotlight. Bathing in the dwindling light of the day, this delicate hummingbird gracefully indulged in its last refreshing dip. In this arid region, where bodies of water are scarce, the small waterfall became a sanctuary for an array of species. With over 40 different bird species documented in this oasis, the allure of capturing their essence through the lens was irresistible. Slow-motion recording added a touch of magic to the encounter, unveiling intricate details of the Green-backed Firecrown's vibrant plumage.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>birds,photography,nature,oasis,wildlife,hummingbirds,birth,spring,waterfall,sunset,Chile,Colina,countryside,sanctuary,feathers,beauty,tranquility,arid,biodiversity,slow-motion</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Colina, Santiago</media:city>
             <media:country>Chile</media:country>
             <media:category>Animals</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Fri, 9 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2290</guid>
             <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 19:07:50 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/acc5d1c4-94fb-49e3-8c9e-9b67c9f76da9.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/aa9ce601-0e88-4d74-b2be-a76b225514d7.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Electrifying spectacle: captivating slow motion lightning strikes illuminate Bayreuth, Germany</media:title>
             <media:description>On the night of June 22nd, 2023 Bayreuth, Germany was treated to a mesmerizing display of nature's power. A thunderstorm rolled in, unleashing a series of breathtaking lightning strikes that illuminated the darkened sky. @ProjectPhysX, an avid videographer, seized the opportunity to capture the spectacle in stunning detail. Armed with a camera capable of shooting at 240 frames per second, the author recorded slow-motion footage of the lightning strikes, preserving the electrifying essence of the storm. </media:description>
             <media:keywords>thunderstorm,lightning,Bayreuth,Germany,video,slow motion,recording,night,show,nature,power,spectacle,mesmerizing,captivating,storm,weather,electric,breathtaking,raw,beauty</media:keywords>
             <media:city> Bayreuth</media:city>
             <media:country>Germany</media:country>
             <media:category>Weather</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2287</guid>
             <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 18:03:49 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/5f8bc80d-bd65-40ed-8621-8336eea3139a.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/d71a1f0e-b729-4ff7-97d6-0393325d1457.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Awe-inspiring mammatus clouds blanket the skies of Aurora, Colorado</media:title>
             <media:description>On June 22nd, 2023, @DaleRatte, a resident of Aurora, Colorado, USA, captured a breathtaking video showcasing the extraordinary beauty of mammatus clouds. These mesmerizing cloud formations painted the skies in an awe-inspiring display. With their distinct bulbous shapes and hanging pouches, the mammatus clouds created a captivating scene that left viewers in sheer wonder. </media:description>
             <media:keywords>clouds,mammatus,Aurora,Colorado,USA,weather,nature,beauty,mesmerizing,captivating,sky,video,incredible,breathtaking,landscape,tranquility,amazement,wonder,phenomenon,picturesque,atmospheric</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Aurora, Colorado</media:city>
             <media:country>United States</media:country>
             <media:category>Weather</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2283</guid>
             <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 09:06:41 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/50b0f7ab-a28d-481a-af0f-627fc0854311.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/587b7878-1d50-4ea8-a0b5-a170d9d3a360.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Adorable cat becomes a charming beggar at outdoor restaurant</media:title>
             <media:description>In a heartwarming scene captured in East Jakarta, Indonesia, a video shared by @akunhalu21 on June 8th, 2023, showcases an endearing interaction between a hungry cat and a group of diners at an outdoor restaurant. The feline, longing for a meal, approached the group and cleverly tapped one of the friends, signaling for food. Amused by the cat's ingenuity, the author recorded the adorable encounter.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>cat,begging,food,outdoor,restaurant,Jakarta,Indonesia,video,capture,funny,tapping,paw,hand,adorable,friend,hungry,interaction,clever,amused,charming</media:keywords>
             <media:city>East Jakarta</media:city>
             <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
             <media:category>Animals</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Thu, 8 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2282</guid>
             <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 19:04:22 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/6e1ca370-97ec-496a-8f85-8959254d06a4.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/9eb1ad16-ade1-4af8-8ae5-8ca2d86e26ef.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>From grey to vibrant: a time-lapse journey of a sprite can drawing</media:title>
             <media:description>In a captivating time-lapse video captured by @EthanArts on June 3rd, 2022, in Parañaque, Metro Manila, Philippines, the artist skillfully crafted an intricate drawing of an empty Sprite can using colored pencils on grey paper. With remarkable attention to detail, the author dedicated three hours to complete the artwork. The video showcases the gradual transformation from a blank canvas to a vibrant representation of the iconic soda can, mesmerizing viewers with the artist's talent and precision.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>drawing,sprite,can,color pencils,grey paper,time-lapse,art,artist,skill,detail,Parañaque,Metro Manila,Philippines,video,empty,vibrant,transformation,talent,precision,captivating</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Parañaque</media:city>
             <media:country>Philippines</media:country>
             <media:category>Cool</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Sat, 3 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2281</guid>
             <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 18:01:08 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/5ef23738-49de-4934-9aba-8ce6a5dad4f8.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/5b485787-ceb4-49ce-a287-b1ee4decd82d.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Unexpected friendship unveiled: cat and frog share cozy moments in Majalengka</media:title>
             <media:description>In a heartwarming encounter captured by @dedento27_ on June 1st, 2023, in Majalengka, Indonesia, an unlikely friendship unfolded between a cat and a frog. The video shows the cat peacefully asleep, its gaze fixed upon the frog, while the frog faced the feline with apparent curiosity. The author says that he had left briefly to the living room and upon returning he found the cat and the frog on his bed. </media:description>
             <media:keywords>cat,frog,Majalengka,Indonesia,video,sleep,bed,friendship,unexpected,bond,animals,pets,peaceful,curious,living room,capture,June,pet,film,cozy</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Majalengka</media:city>
             <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
             <media:category>Animals</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Thu, 1 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2280</guid>
             <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 19:40:19 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/8244efaa-06be-4357-a395-27c0fabd32d6.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/031c3049-1acd-48c7-a94b-6a59a03cac79.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Unexpected discovery: mischievous cat hides in bucket, captured on video!</media:title>
             <media:description>In a surprising turn of events, a feline adventure unfolded in Pontianak, Indonesia, as captured by @kurnia_aniba on June 10th, 2023. The day began with a frantic search for a mischievous cat that seemed to have disappeared into thin air. Despite calling out its name repeatedly, the cat remained elusive. However, when nature called and the author headed towards the restroom, an unexpected sight greeted her. There, nestled inside a bucket, was the elusive feline, completely unaware of the commotion it had caused. Acting swiftly, the author rushed to her room to retrieve her cellphone and immortalize the amusing spectacle on video.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>cat,bucket,video,Pontianak,Indonesia,surprise,search,disappearance,elusive,nature,restroom,commotion,swift,cellphone,amusing,spectacle,feline,hiding,spots</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Pontianak</media:city>
             <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
             <media:category>Animals</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2279</guid>
             <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 18:46:37 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/f38d749b-236b-41bb-aa04-8b19600c26c5.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/87c3c06f-ea08-4c9f-a4dd-a98d54f7d8b9.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Adorable Teyla: the door-jumping doggo who loves greeting fellow canines</media:title>
             <media:description>In a heartwarming video captured in Los Angeles, California, USA, Teyla the dog has become an internet sensation for her endearing habit of jumping on the door. The clip, shared by @typicalteyla on May 23rd, 2023, showcases Teyla's daily routine of leaping up in excitement whenever she spots other dogs passing by. It seems Teyla's exuberance knows no bounds, as she even jumps for joy upon seeing people. This lovable canine's boundless energy and infectious enthusiasm have won the hearts of viewers worldwide, turning her into an online sensation.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>dog,jumping,door,daily,occurrence,adorable,canine,video,Teyla,Los Angeles,California,USA,pets,excitement,energetic,internet,sensation,joy,people,love</media:keywords>
             <media:city> Los Angeles, California</media:city>
             <media:country>United States</media:country>
             <media:category>Animals</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Tue, 23 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2278</guid>
             <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 13:18:33 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/bf7bff6d-abad-4d14-8c02-6cdf944631ce.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/3b520cdb-a593-4bd1-8295-bef00cdae113.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Hilarious cat battle: fierce felines engage in a paws-on standoff!</media:title>
             <media:description>In an amusing spectacle caught on camera by @syahmiemujahhid on May 18, 2023 in Segamat District, Johor, Malaysia, two cats engaged in an intense battle. The feline adversaries were seen standing upright on their hind legs, front paws locked in a confrontational embrace. Meowing loudly, as they displayed remarkable aggression. </media:description>
             <media:keywords>cats,fighting,video,Segamat,Johor,Malaysia,animals,pets,entertainment,amusing,intense,battle,hind legs,meowing,confrontation,hilarious,feline,companions,adorable,viral</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Segamat, Johor</media:city>
             <media:country>Malaysia</media:country>
             <media:category>Animals</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Thu, 18 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2277</guid>
             <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 12:58:46 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/b33af4e2-cc22-4b11-8104-5f39cfa51444.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/07f9ea06-faa2-45d5-b367-04a99adf683f.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Hungry bunny's unusual snack: rabbit nibbles on owner's hair!</media:title>
             <media:description>In a heartwarming yet peculiar incident captured on video, @ZhazhafanFriedRabbit, located in Hubei Province, central China, witnessed his pet rabbit, Dudu, engaging in an unexpected dining experience. The footage, recorded on 9th June 2023, shows Dudu nibbling on his owner's hair as if it were blades of grass.

The author had laid down, unwittingly offering his hair as an impromptu snack for the hungry bunny. Seemingly prompted by a growling tummy, Dudu wasted no time in using the author's locks as a makeshift grazing field. With each playful nibble, the rabbit chewed on the strands and effortlessly swallowed them, much to the amusement of the author and the online audience.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>rabbit,hair,pet,video,Hubei,China,central,Dudu,nibble,chew,swallow,bed,play,hungry,snack,owner,adorable,bond,antics,online</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Hubei</media:city>
             <media:country>China</media:country>
             <media:category>Animals</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Fri, 9 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2275</guid>
             <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 11:10:11 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/d2dcfabf-2165-4c88-9435-4cdc3111e202.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/60f0f5dd-89fd-42d3-bf57-db935ea6f40e.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Unexpected summer snowstorm sweeps Changbai Mountain in Jilin Province, China</media:title>
             <media:description>On June 6th, 2023, a rare and astonishing weather event took place in the picturesque Changbai Mountain of Jilin Province, China. Forest ranger @OldWuofChangbaiMountain, who happened to be on patrol that day, captured a remarkable video showcasing the unexpected heavy snowfall that blanketed the mountain. The footage reveals a sudden shift in weather as the sky turned dark and temperatures plummeted, accompanied by fierce winds that carried the blowing snow.

This unusual summer snowstorm came as a surprise to both locals and the forest ranger himself. Such weather conditions are extremely uncommon during this time of year, making this occurrence even more extraordinary. </media:description>
             <media:keywords>snow,weather,ChangbaiMountain,JilinProvince,China,video,rare,summer,unexpected,patrol,dark,cold,blowing,winds,forest,ranger,phenomenon,extraordinary,winter,wonderland,nature</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Jilin Province</media:city>
             <media:country>China</media:country>
             <media:category>Weather</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Tue, 6 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2274</guid>
             <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 10:40:27 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/7ec0f56e-d4fb-40f9-a39b-0b21a76d3697.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/33baf0b7-48a2-4658-b92a-67957adaea68.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Playful kitten Takjil tries to engage with disinterested adult cat Nob</media:title>
             <media:description>In a captivating video captured by @ekawidyann on  10th April, 2023 in Surabaya, East Java, Indonesia, a playful kitten named Takjil is seen attempting to engage with an adult cat named Nob. The adorable kitten can be observed climbing on top of the laid-back cat, eagerly seeking playtime. However, Nob remains uninterested and unmoved, maintaining a disinterested demeanor throughout the interaction.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>playful,kitten,Takjil,Surabaya,East Java,Indonesia,video,captured,adult cat,Nob,uninterested,climbing,playful,interaction,adorable,laid-back,disinterested,heat,cute,feline,companionship</media:keywords>
             <media:city> Surabaya, East Java</media:city>
             <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
             <media:category>Animals</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2273</guid>
             <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 10:01:42 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/3373da86-e072-437b-8e23-d1e70763b914.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/cb801c74-28b3-4864-9efc-3800d0259c90.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Floral finesse: man and dog make a majestic entrance at Sagala 2023 parade</media:title>
             <media:description>In a captivating display of creativity and unconventional companionship, a viral video captured by @babygingerblog on May 1st, 2023, showcased a remarkable scene during the Sagala 2023 parade in Lucban, Quezon, Philippines. Amidst the grandeur and traditional splendor of the parade of saints, a man was seen elegantly strolling through the streets with a dog comfortably nestled in a baby stroller adorned with vibrant flowers. This unique sight added a touch of whimsy and enchantment to the procession, as the man and his canine companion gracefully moved along, capturing the attention and admiration of onlookers. The beautifully decorated stroller created an exquisite backdrop for this charming duo, epitomizing the spirit of the Sagala tradition and leaving a lasting impression on all who witnessed this extraordinary display.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>parade,saints,philippines,sagala,video,man,dog,baby stroller,flowers,majestic,capture,viral,creativity,unconventional,companionship,lucban,quezon,enchantment,whimsy,procession</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Lucban Quezon</media:city>
             <media:country>Philippines</media:country>
             <media:category>Cool</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Mon, 1 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2272</guid>
             <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 18:17:03 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/436a2e34-604d-4a4f-83aa-d5139e188d35.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/3c858772-df11-491c-a5f7-87af541fe489.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Wild wine mishap: when Wiley the dog chased a bunny at Willows Lodge</media:title>
             <media:description>On June 8, 2023, an incident took place at the scenic Willows Lodge in Woodinville, Washington, USA. A video captured by @dustingalipeau_ showcased a lady named @salcomptonn, who had intended to relax with a glass of wine in the outdoor seating area. However, her plans took an unexpected turn when her energetic dog, Wiley, decided to chase after a bunny.

As the lady attempted to settle down on a chair, holding Wiley's leash, the determined canine spotted the furry creature and abruptly pulled her towards the nearby bush. In the video, one can witness the moment as Wiley's sudden movement nearly caused the lady to lose balance and topple over her chair.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>wine,dog,leash,bunny,outdoor,hotel,Willows Lodge,Woodinville,Washington,USA,video,seat,glass,Wiley,funny,mishap,laughter,adventure,amusing,serene,spontaneous</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Woodinville, Washington</media:city>
             <media:country>United States</media:country>
             <media:category>Animals</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Thu, 8 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2269</guid>
             <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 17:35:45 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/5b89c363-a235-4934-80b6-fb75cc15c847.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/545ccf8e-8abd-4d90-ae71-323a4448ff3f.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Adorable Mia: the bathroom buddy who loves bath time and hair dryers!</media:title>
             <media:description>In a heartwarming video captured by @miiafam in Rivne, Ukraine on May 24, 2023, her dog Mia stole the spotlight as she stood patiently in the bathroom while her owner dried her hair. The spontaneous and natural moment showcased Mia's undeniable love for bathing and the post-bath ritual. With an evident fondness for water, Mia spends ample time in the bath, relishing the soothing experience as the author describes. </media:description>
             <media:keywords>dog,bath,bathroom,hair,drying,spontaneous,natural,love,Mia,pet,video,owner,Ukraine,Rivne,adorable,joyful,camera,grooming,petcare,bath time</media:keywords>
             <media:city> Rivne</media:city>
             <media:country>Ukraine</media:country>
             <media:category>Animals</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Wed, 24 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2268</guid>
             <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 17:07:54 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/88dcba7f-c041-4637-9e0a-bb06dc27b84e.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/bddafddd-4760-4312-9513-0f5e623027ca.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Lola's love for hide and seek: a playful pup's secret hideaway</media:title>
             <media:description>In a heartwarming video captured by @dutchandlola on June 1st, 2020, in Pasadena, California, USA, a playful dog named Lola was caught engaging in a game of Hide and Seek. As the camera approached the couch, Lola skillfully maneuvered herself to stay hidden, displaying her impressive hiding skills. The adorable pup eventually revealed her furry head from beneath the couch, showcasing her playful nature.

According to the author, Lola quickly picked up on various tricks shortly after being adopted. Among her favorite games, Hide and Seek quickly became a cherished pastime for the energetic canine. Lola's enthusiasm for the game remains unwavering even to this day.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>dog,hideandseek,playful,video,couch,Pasadena,California,USA,tricks,games,adorable,pet,love,joy,furry,energetic,pastime,heartwarming,capture,Lola,video</media:keywords>
             <media:city> Pasadena, California</media:city>
             <media:country>United States</media:country>
             <media:category>Animals</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Mon, 1 Jun 2020</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2267</guid>
             <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 16:47:08 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/e4267ec1-9e61-4ffe-9372-e4e2b006c570.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/93362622-ecc8-4113-b650-54781ec6ad25.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Adorable Kemaman kitten caught napping skyward in cute pose!</media:title>
             <media:description>In a heartwarming scene captured in Kemaman, Malaysia on January 31, 2023, @eymanrazak has shared an adorable video of a sleepy kitten caught in a unique nap position. The video showcases the tiny feline comfortably snoozing while looking up at the world, standing on all fours. The irresistible sight of the drowsy kitten's pose has melted hearts across social media, captivating viewers with its cuteness. </media:description>
             <media:keywords>sleepy,kitten,nap,adorable,Kemaman,Malaysia,video,cute,pose,feline,snooze,drowsy,social media,heartwarming,tiny,furry,companion,peaceful,moments,captured</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Kemaman</media:city>
             <media:country>Malaysia</media:country>
             <media:category>Animals</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2266</guid>
             <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 13:41:39 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/76197da7-6a9a-4f67-94c1-db239f0c0c7f.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/f90399e6-9403-4a97-9155-a460aa1c0c49.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Close call: cyclist narrowly escapes collision with truck at Xuân Mai crossing, Hanoi</media:title>
             <media:description>
In a heart-stopping moment captured by @trananhmobile116 on 21st March, 2023 in Xuân Mai, Chuong My District, Hanoi, Vietnam, a video shows a near miss between a cyclist and a green truck at a crossing. The footage reveals the truck driver hitting the brakes suddenly, accompanied by screeching tires, just in the nick of time to avoid a potentially catastrophic accident. An unidentified lady on a bike can be seen crossing the road when the truck unexpectedly approaches full speed. Thanks to the quick reflexes of the truck driver, disaster was averted. </media:description>
             <media:keywords>cycling,truck,near miss,crossing,Hanoi,Vietnam,video,cyclist,green truck,brakes,screeching,accident,whisker,reflexes,safety,awareness,pedestrians,caution,Xuân Mai,Chuong My District</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Xuân Mai, Chuong My District, Hanoi</media:city>
             <media:country>Vietnam</media:country>
             <media:category>News</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2262</guid>
             <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 18:59:35 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/bc9d1af9-7e23-4fb3-8ec6-0a95cdc3cdba.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/25931c88-7d54-4583-90d5-e45456a544de.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Unleashing love: a groomer's encounter with howling wieners</media:title>
             <media:description>In a heartwarming video captured by @sydnee_michael on June 10th, 2023, in Simi Valley, California, USA, the love and joy of a dog groomer's job were on full display. As the author attended to the dogs in her care, she took a moment to greet two adorable wiener dogs. However, her friendly introduction was swiftly interrupted by a sudden howl from one of the pups. The unexpected interruption only added to the charm of the scene, showcasing the lively personalities and vocal nature of these lovable companions.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>dog grooming,love,wiener dogs,video,job,capture,moment,howling,Sydnee Michael,Simi Valley,California,USA,dogs,affection,bond,pets,companionship,joy,connection,happiness,furry friends</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Simi Valley, California</media:city>
             <media:country>United States</media:country>
             <media:category>Animals</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2259</guid>
             <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 12:11:44 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/51b31fb3-5f6f-4d07-9ec2-650dfbac744f.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/f994f2a9-de26-4e3b-9651-f7435160ba73.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Heartwarming tale: woman becomes mother figure to orphaned goat, creating a hilariously adorable bond</media:title>
             <media:description>In a heartwarming incident captured on video on March 17, 2023 by @rhisst from Tegalombo, Pacitan Regency, East Java, Indonesia, is seen carrying a young goat on her back. The touching moment is made even more significant as she reveals that she took on the role of a surrogate mother to the goat when its own mother passed away just an hour after its birth. Over the course of two months, she has cared for the little goat as her own child, spoiling it with love and attention. The goat has become quite fond of being carried, often requesting to be held like a small child. </media:description>
             <media:keywords>goat,surrogate,mother,bond,love,caring,animals,connection,Indonesia,Pacitan,Tegalombo,orphan,funny,adorable,video,heartwarming,small,child,two months,young</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Tegalombo, Pacitan Regency</media:city>
             <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
             <media:category>Animals</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2258</guid>
             <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 10:37:27 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/58115784-4675-4766-820d-7529a7012ce1.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/bc5760a4-488b-4b3c-9e59-2803ae2a6cc7.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Riverside serendipity: a fisherman's close encounter with buffalos</media:title>
             <media:description>In a spontaneous turn of events on May 19, 2023, in Klaten, Indonesia, @rangn.r  and his friend found themselves amidst a unique encounter while trying to catch some fish. Frustrated by his unsuccessful attempts, he persisted in his pursuit. Suddenly, the tranquil riverside scene was disrupted as buffalos were released from their cages, making their way into the river. To his surprise, one buffalo approached from his left. The author quickly decided to record the extraordinary sight. The buffalos peacefully meandered through the river, oblivious to the fisherman's presence. Sensing the need for caution, he slowly stood up and moved away. </media:description>
             <media:keywords>fishing,buffalos,encounter,riverside,Indonesia,recording,frustration,persistence,unique,tranquil,surprise,meander,nature,caution,phone,fisherman,cages,release,convergence,unforgettable</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Klaten</media:city>
             <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
             <media:category>Animals</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Fri, 19 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2257</guid>
             <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 10:21:58 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/f0a1f15b-d52e-4bec-b05a-e3b77d4ba218.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/3653a681-d0ea-444c-94ec-d4f499c02c4e.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Rare heavy rainstorm engulfs Jinzhou causing flash floods </media:title>
             <media:description>Jinzhou, a city in Northeast China, experienced an extraordinarily rare weather event on June 12th, 2023. Heavy rain mixed with hail transformed the city into a waterlogged maze, causing disruption throughout. The unprecedented downpour resulted in flash floods that submerged the streets, leaving cars driving through water that reached tire height.

For a city unaccustomed to such extreme rainfall, the deluge came as a shock to residents and authorities alike. A video captured by @Eloquent showcased the magnitude of the situation, revealing the sight of vehicles struggling through the flooded streets. The heavy rainstorm overwhelmed the drainage systems, leading to rapid accumulation of water on the road surfaces.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>rare,heavy,rainstorm,hail,water,road,surface,accumulation,city,northeast,China,weather,flash floods,cars,tire high,video,chaos,unprecedented,Jinzhou,waterlogged</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Jinzhou</media:city>
             <media:country>China</media:country>
             <media:category>Weather</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2256</guid>
             <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 09:58:32 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/ebd156c8-971a-40d3-bbbb-9c3925563b1d.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/f6f221a1-2ac7-4e27-b804-a562dc624ee2.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item></channel>
           </rss>