<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
            <rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
            xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
            xmlns:openSearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearchrss/1.0/"
            xmlns:dfpvideo="http://api.google.com/dfpvideo"
            xmlns:tms="http://data.tmsapi.com/v1.1"
            version="2.0">
              <channel>
                <title>ViralBear videos</title>
                <dfpvideo:version>2</dfpvideo:version>
                  
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Explosions in Kyiv during a girl's stream</media:title>
                          <media:description>On March 21, 2023, an alarming event unfolded in Kyiv. The city was attacked by Russian missiles. It coincided with a live stream on TikTok  launched by @lily_m96.The girl was very scared by what happened, and the stream attracted more than 300 viewers.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>Kyiv,Ukraine,Shelling,TikTok,Live Stream,Social Media,Citizen Journalism,Crisis Reporting,Awareness,Resilience,Adversity,@lily_m96,Global Events,Support,Humanitarian,Conflict,Emergency,Courage,Solidarity</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Kyiv</media:city>
                          <media:country>Ukraine</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>UA</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>CWP</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>3110</guid>
                          <pubDate>Sat, 23 Sep 2023 09:26:58 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/3110.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/3110.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Mother's hoverboard stroller ride takes a dangerous turn in Yekaterinburg</media:title>
                          <media:description>In Yekaterinburg, Russia, a mother's attempt to combine modern mobility with parenting took a perilous turn on August 16, 2023. While riding a Segway hoverboard and pushing her baby's stroller simultaneously, things initially seemed to be going smoothly. However, in a sudden and dramatic twist of events, the mother lost her balance, leading to a harrowing fall. As she tumbled backward, the stroller tilted dangerously, causing concern among onlookers. Swift action from eyewitnesses prevented what could have been a tragic accident, as they rushed to assist the distressed mother and her child. </media:description>
                          <media:keywords>mother,segway,hoverboard,stroller,accident,yekaterinburg,russia,fall,witnesses,assistance,video,balancing,parenting,perilous,dramatic,caution,safety,incident,modern,mobility</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Yekaterinburg</media:city>
                          <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>3094</guid>
                          <pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2023 11:46:09 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/3094.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/3094.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Caught on camera: phone robbery brawl at Córdoba traffic lights</media:title>
                          <media:description>In a dramatic incident captured by @nicolasebbio on August 9, 2023, at a busy intersection in Córdoba, Argentina, two men were caught in a heated altercation. The video footage depicts a brief but intense struggle, with one of the men's phones tumbling to the ground during the scuffle. In a shocking turn of events, he retrieved his fallen phone only to kick his opponent, who retaliated by striking him with what appeared to be a cloth. It was later revealed that the two men were engaged in a dispute over the attempted theft of each other's mobile phones. </media:description>
                          <media:keywords>fight,altercation,phone,theft,brawl,Córdoba,Argentina,traffic lights,video,footage,incident,scuffle,mobile,dispute,dramatic,confrontation,street,altercation,smartphone,clash</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Córdoba</media:city>
                          <media:country>Argentina</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>AR</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Wed, 9 Aug 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>3084</guid>
                          <pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2023 11:42:44 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/3084.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/3084.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Dramatic turn of events: fire engulfs Lamborghini Aventador during Moscow photoshoot</media:title>
                          <media:description>On August 6, 2023, in the heart of Moscow, Russia, a routine photoshoot took an unexpected turn as @harleydavidson700 captured a thrilling moment on camera. While photographing their 1967 Mustang for a blogger's feature, a Lamborghini Aventador made a stylish entrance into Khilkov Lane. However, what started as a picturesque moment quickly transformed into a dramatic scene when smoke billowed from the Lamborghini's rear. Quick-thinking @harleydavidson700 and their friends rushed to alert the driver, who initially didn't grasp the urgency. Despite swift response from firefighters, the car succumbed to flames due to water shortages in the area. Fortunately, everyone emerged unscathed, leaving behind an unforgettable day captured on video.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>moscow,russia,video,car,flames,photoshoot,mustang,lamborghini,fire,blogger,lane,smoke,drama,photographer,unexpected,moment,firefighters,water,incident,safety</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Moscow</media:city>
                          <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Sun, 6 Aug 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>3041</guid>
                          <pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2023 09:39:29 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/3041.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/3041.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Rain and strong winds send food cart flying, ending in shattering disaster</media:title>
                          <media:description>In a surprising turn of events on July 17, 2023, in Soc Trang Province, Southern Vietnam, a video captured by @beut_668 documented a fierce combination of rain and strong winds that sent a food cart hurtling away from its owner near a roadside. The cart's owner valiantly attempted to give chase, but the violent gusts proved too formidable, causing the cart to overturn. The impact resulted in the shattering of the cart's glass components, leaving a scene of unexpected destruction in its wake.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>rain,wind,food cart,disaster,Soc Trang Province,Vietnam,video,accident,overturn,glass,shattering,weather,strong,chase,owner,unexpected,destruction,July 17,2023,@beut_668</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Soc Trang Province</media:city>
                          <media:country>Vietnam</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>VN</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Weather,Accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>3031</guid>
                          <pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2023 09:10:48 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/3031.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/3031.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Mobile food vendor's cart catches fire, bystanders help to put out the fire</media:title>
                          <media:description>In a dramatic incident captured on video by @romadhon_03_ on August 10, 2023, in Magetan, East Java, Indonesia, a mobile food vendor's cart was engulfed in flames. The vendor, riding a motorbike with his cart attached on top, found himself in a perilous situation as the fire raged within the compartment at the back of his vehicle. Fortunately, quick-thinking bystanders rushed to his aid, taking swift and coordinated action to extinguish the flames and prevent a potentially disastrous outcome. </media:description>
                          <media:keywords>fire,vendor,mobile,cart,rescue,heroes,incident,video,Magetan,East Java,Indonesia,motorbike,flames,bystanders,emergency,dramatic,community,swift,action,perilous</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Magetan, East Java</media:city>
                          <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>ID</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>2990</guid>
                          <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 08:29:47 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2990.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2990.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Portable charger explosion prompts evacuation at St. Petersburg school on Vasilyevsky Island</media:title>
                          <media:description>In a startling incident at a school on Vasilyevsky Island in St. Petersburg, Russia, on September 6, 2023, a portable charger exploded inside a student's backpack, triggering the evacuation of students and staff. The incident occurred in the 4th building of the gymnasium located on Morskaya Embankment. Video footage from the scene captured smoke billowing from the backpack, which had been placed on the corridor floor. Fortunately, no injuries were reported, and emergency responders swiftly ensured the safety of all individuals involved. Investigations into the cause of the charger explosion are currently underway, as both school officials and local authorities work to prevent any such incidents from occurring in the future.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>school,explosion,charger,backpack,evacuation,incident,St. Petersburg,Russia,student,safety,gymnasium,smoke,corridor,video,Morskaya Embankment,Vasilyevsky Island,emergency,responders,investigation,authorities.</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>St. Petersburg</media:city>
                          <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>News,Accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Wed, 6 Sep 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>2953</guid>
                          <pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 11:57:31 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2953.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2953.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Medieval monastery in Georgia's Mtskheta threatened as rock collapses on its territory </media:title>
                          <media:description>A significant incident unfolded on August 27, 2023, as a rock collapse sent shockwaves through the serene surroundings of the medieval Shio-Mgvime Monastery in Mtskheta, Georgia. This historic monastic architectural complex, nestled within a narrow limestone gorge along the Mtkvari River, faced an unforeseen landslide, prompting visitors to hastily evacuate the premises. Fortunately, initial reports indicated no immediate casualties, allowing the focus to shift towards search and rescue efforts. The dramatic event was captured on video, revealing a massive cloud of dust that billowed into the air, shrouding the entire gorge in a veil of particles. The monastery, located approximately 30 km from the capital city of Tbilisi, now stands as a testament to the unpredictability of nature's force and the resilience of human heritage.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>monastery,landslide,collapse,Georgia,Mtskheta,rock,incident,medieval,Shio-Mgvime,visitors,evacuation,rescue,dust,gorge,Tbilisi,heritage,nature,architectural,complex,video</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Mtskheta</media:city>
                          <media:country>Georgia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>GE</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>News,Accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>2895</guid>
                          <pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2023 18:17:17 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2895.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2895.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Rostov blogger survives near-fatal fall after roof to roof car stunt goes wrong</media:title>
                          <media:description>Rostov-on-Don, Russia - August 29, 2023 - Blogger Evgeny Chebotarev was hospitalized after falling from a roof while attempting a dangerous car stunt. @bednie.oligarhi and @chebotarev_life were filming a video in which @chebotarev_life would drive a Niva car from one roof to another. However, the stunt went wrong and the car crashed into the side of the building, causing Chebotarev to fall from the roof. The car was badly damaged, but Chebotarev survived with only minor injuries. He was taken to the hospital and released a few hours later.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>stunt,video,car,accident,crash,danger,rooftop,fall,Niva,disaster,hospital,survival,team,filming,failed,smashed,roof,blogger,North Ossetia,Evgeny Chebotarev</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>North Ossetia</media:city>
                          <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>News,Accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>2894</guid>
                          <pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2023 18:15:07 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2894.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2894.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Terrifying lightning strike amidst rainy joy: tragedy strikes tourist spot in North Sumatra</media:title>
                          <media:description>In a shocking turn of events on April 26, 2023, at the picturesque Mandala Sena in Silangkitang, South Labuhan Batu Regency, North Sumatra, Indonesia, what began as a tranquil rainy day turned into a harrowing ordeal. A video captured by @dedisatria56 showcased the moment when a lightning bolt tore through the sky, shattering the peaceful ambiance. Amidst the rain, individuals could be seen enjoying themselves in the water, completely unaware of the imminent danger. Tragically, the lightning strike left 8 people injured and claimed one life. </media:description>
                          <media:keywords>rain,video,meal,lightning,water,incident,tourist spot,people,danger,tragedy,Sumatra,Indonesia,safety,nature,vigilance,leisure,shock,unpredictable,capture,ambiance</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>South Labuhan Batu Regency, North Sumatra</media:city>
                          <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>ID</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>2892</guid>
                          <pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2023 11:03:25 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2892.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2892.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 10:03:01 GMT</dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Amusing trampoline mishap: laughter and support amidst slippery fun</media:title>
                          <media:description>In a lighthearted moment captured by @jefriesa on July 1, 2023, in Bekasi, Indonesia, a group of women engaged in an exercise session on a trampoline found themselves in a comical situation. The video depicts a woman performing her routine jumps when the trampoline suddenly slips beneath her feet, causing her to teeter momentarily. Amidst a burst of laughter from one of her companions, another friend rushes to her aid, preventing what could have been a tumble. </media:description>
                          <media:keywords>exercise,trampoline,slip,laughter,support,mishap,friends,fun,workout,camaraderie,Indonesia,Bekasi,video,women,jumps,amusement,feet,sore,moment,group</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Bekasi</media:city>
                          <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>ID</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Fails and Funnies,Accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Sat, 1 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>2873</guid>
                          <pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2023 19:53:23 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2873.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2873.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>6-year-old boy injured in car accident in Ufa</media:title>
                          <media:description>A 6-year-old boy was injured in a car accident in Ufa, Russia on August 9, 2023. The boy was riding a scooter in the courtyard of a house when he was hit by a car driven by a 45-year-old man. The boy was taken to the hospital with injuries, but his condition is not known. The traffic police are investigating the accident.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>accident,car,child,courtyard,datsun,driver,injured,knocked down,6-year-old,police,scooter,street,ufa,video,vehicle,yard,hit,traffic,investigation,hospitalized,emergency,rescue</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Ufa</media:city>
                          <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>News,Accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Wed, 9 Aug 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>2871</guid>
                          <pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2023 15:13:48 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2871.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2871.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Brave child outsmarts pack of stray dogs, escapes tragic fate in Makhachkala chase</media:title>
                          <media:description>In a heart-stopping incident on August 27, 2023, in the Reduktorny settlement microdistrict of Makhachkala, Russia, a pack of ten stray dogs nearly turned a day of play into tragedy for a young child. The unfolding scene, captured by alert eyewitnesses, revealed the harrowing chase as the barking dogs closed in on the terrified child along the coast. In a split-second decision that showcased remarkable ingenuity, the quick-thinking boy made a daring dash for the safety of the water. The strategy paid off, sparing him from what could have been a devastating outcome. Despite his narrow escape, the dogs managed to inflict bites before he reached the water's refuge.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>beach,chase,survival,bravery,danger,dogs,child,Makhachkala,escape,ingenuity,water,incident,stray,pack,coastal,courage,alert,bite,eyewitnesses,refuge,play</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Makhachkala</media:city>
                          <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Animals,News,Accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>2867</guid>
                          <pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2023 11:36:26 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2867.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2867.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Storm-driven collision: P&amp;O Britannia and oil transport ship clash in Palma, Mallorca</media:title>
                          <media:description>In a dramatic maritime incident off the coast of Palma, Mallorca, Spain, a powerful storm unleashed its fury on August 27, 2023, causing a cruise ship to collide with an oil transport tanker. The vessel in question, P&amp;O Britannia, found itself at the mercy of relentless winds that snapped its mooring ropes, propelling it towards the neighboring tanker and ultimately onto the unforgiving rocks. The force of the collision was captured on video by @millermanuk, an eyewitness aboard the ship. Despite the harrowing encounter, reports indicate that the integrity of the cruise ship remained intact, and a team of tugboats swiftly maneuvered to guide it back into position. </media:description>
                          <media:keywords>storm,collision,ship,tanker,Palma Mallorca,Spain,video,moorings,rocks,winds,gales,maritime,incident,eyewitness,tugs,nature,seafarers,power,challenges</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Palma, Mallorca</media:city>
                          <media:country>Spain</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>ES</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Accidents,News,Weather</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>2861</guid>
                          <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 10:06:50 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2861.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2861.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 11:13:08 GMT</dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Father's heroic catch: baby saved mid-air as stroller falls on bus ride in Kaliningrad Oblast</media:title>
                          <media:description>In a heart-stopping incident on August 22, 2023, in Kaliningrad Oblast, Russia, a father's quick reflexes averted a potential disaster as his six-month-old baby fell out of a stroller on a moving bus. Eduard, accompanied by his wife and five-year-old child, was carefully holding the stroller against the bus wall while gripping a handrail. However, a sudden sharp turn at a roundabout proved too much to counter, sending both Eduard and the stroller off-balance. In a split second, the stroller tipped over, and baby Mark tumbled out. Displaying astonishing agility, Eduard managed to catch his son mid-air, although Mark's face met the bus window, causing minor injuries. The incident left the family in shock, and while the bus driver displayed an odd demeanor following the accident, Eduard has taken the matter to the police with hopes of pursuing legal action. Medical examinations revealed injuries to both father and son, and authorities are investigating the incident through eyewitness accounts and surveillance footage.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>baby,stroller,bus,catch,father,incident,reflexes,Kaliningrad,Russia,family,shock,injuries,police,legal,examination,witnesses,surveillance,quick,route,danger</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Kaliningrad Oblast</media:city>
                          <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>News,Accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>2847</guid>
                          <pubDate>Fri, 25 Aug 2023 16:08:20 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2847.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2847.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Tragic plane crash claims lives of PMC Wagner founder Yevgeny Prigozhin and commander Dmitry Utkin in Tver Region, Russia</media:title>
                          <media:description>In a devastating incident on August 23, 2023, a business jet identified as an Embraer-135 (EBM-135BJ) crashed near the village of Kuzhenkino in the Bologovsky district of Russia's Tver region. The plane, en route from Moscow to St. Petersburg, was reported to be carrying Yevgeny Prigozhin, the founder of PMC Wagner, and Dmitry Utkin, the PMC's commander, as stated by the airline. Tragically, all individuals on board, including Prigozhin and Utkin, lost their lives in the crash, according to preliminary information from the Russian Ministry of Emergency Situations. The wreckage of the aircraft was depicted engulfed in flames in video footage. The crash site's location, northwest of Tver and halfway between Tver and Veliky Novgorod, marks a somber event that has shaken the region and beyond.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>crash,tragedy,plane,incident,wreckage,fire,victims,PMC Wagner,Yevgeny Prigozhin,Dmitry Utkin,Russia,Tver,Kuzhenkino,Bologovsky district,Embraer-135,St. Petersburg,Moscow,devastation,investigation,loss</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Kuzhenkino, Bologovsky district</media:city>
                          <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>News,Accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>2825</guid>
                          <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 07:17:06 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2825.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2825.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Unfortunate departure: motorbike mishap captured on camera in Nghe An, Vietnam</media:title>
                          <media:description>In a candid and unfortunate incident captured on a home camera in Nghe An province, Vietnam, on July 18, 2023, a family member, presumed to be on their way out, encountered a mishap while departing. The camera footage, credited to @haisan_0978899822, reveals the individual setting off with a loaded motorbike, only to lose balance and topple over shortly after. The load they were carrying also fell as the motorbike fell and slid towards the fallen rider. The video does not provide clear information on whether the person sustained any injuries. This incident highlights the unpredictable nature of daily life and serves as a reminder of the unforeseen challenges that can arise at any moment.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>accident,departure,mishap,motorbike,topple,fall,load,family,member,camera,footage,balance,spill,rider,unpredictable,challenges,incident,home,Vietnam,injuries</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Nghe An province</media:city>
                          <media:country>Vietnam</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>VN</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>2797</guid>
                          <pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 08:00:48 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2797.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2797.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Home fire scare: quick-thinking husband extinguishes socket blaze in Nam Dinh, Vietnam</media:title>
                          <media:description>In a startling incident on June 27, 2023, a home camera owned by @thuphuong160201 documented a potentially catastrophic event in Nghia Hung district, Nam Dinh province, Vietnam. The footage captured a socket erupting into flames while the homeowner's husband was relaxing in a chair, his legs casually resting on the table. Acting swiftly, he managed to avert disaster by using his own breath to douse the flames before rushing to deactivate the electricity via the circuit breaker. </media:description>
                          <media:keywords>fire,socket,explosion,safety,home,camera,husband,chair,table,danger,quick thinking,electricity,circuit breaker,incident,hazard,disaster,alert,prevention,household,Vietnam</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Nghia Hung district, Nam Dinh province</media:city>
                          <media:country>Vietnam</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>VN</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>2795</guid>
                          <pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 07:57:40 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2795.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2795.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Elderly woman suffers serious injury after falling from bus in Nalchik: investigation underway</media:title>
                          <media:description>In a concerning incident that occurred on August 1, 2023, in Nalchik, Kabardino-Balkarian Republic, Russia, local authorities have opened a criminal case after a 78-year-old woman fell out of a bus. The investigative department of the TFR in the region reported that the incident transpired as the bus was in motion, with its doors unexpectedly opening, causing the elderly resident to lose her balance and tumble out. The woman sustained a traumatic brain injury and her condition is currently regarded as critical by medical professionals. Disturbing video footage captured the unfortunate incident, revealing the moment the pensioner fell from the bus, which subsequently came to a halt as two individuals rushed to her aid. As investigations are underway, questions regarding the circumstances leading to the incident remain unanswered.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>bus,incident,fall,elderly,woman,injury,investigation,Nalchik,Russia,doors,traumatic,brain,serious,video,footage,aid,local,residents,case,TFR</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Kabardino-Balkarian Republic</media:city>
                          <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Accidents,News</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Tue, 1 Aug 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>2786</guid>
                          <pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2023 09:34:24 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2786.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2786.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Ignition hazard: deadly electric chair-like structure erupts in Moscow courtyard</media:title>
                          <media:description>On July 25, 2023, a startling incident shook the tranquility of the Mir Mitino residential complex in Moscow, Russia, as a hazardous structure resembling an electric chair suddenly emerged in one of its courtyards. The eerie structure, uncannily resembling a deadly contraption, came to light after builders inadvertently struck an underground electric cable during landscaping efforts. The consequences proved perilous, as public utility workers proceeded to install outdoor seating just above the exposed wire, unsuspectingly creating a potential danger zone. The situation took a turn for the worse when moisture made contact with the cable, causing one of the seats to burst into flames before astonished residents. Billowing smoke and a chair launched skyward echoed scenes of demolition, all of which mercifully occurred without any unfortunate occupants. The incident was captured on video by a resident, showcasing the unsettling sight of fire erupting from beneath the seat. Now, the complex's residents anxiously await the intervention of public utility authorities, hoping for a swift resolution to this alarming oversight.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>electric chair,hazard,courtyard,Moscow,Russia,deadly,structure,underground cable,landscaping,builders,outdoor seats,danger,ignition,residents,emergency,public utilities,smoke,demolition,video,oversight</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Moscow</media:city>
                          <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>News,Accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>2765</guid>
                          <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 11:34:05 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2765.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2765.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Miraculous escape: father's slip on slippery walkway sends chills as son watches in tears</media:title>
                          <media:description>In a heart-stopping moment captured on video by @hnv_93 on July 19, 2023, in Xuan Hoa Ward, Phuc Yen Town, Vinh Phuc Province, Vietnam, a father narrowly averted a potential disaster as he slipped and nearly hit his head on the stairs outside his house. The incident unfolded as he was making his way toward the entrance, the smooth tiles beneath his feet proving treacherously slippery. Despite his quick reflexes, he lost his balance and tumbled precariously. His young son, perched on the doorstep, burst into tears at the sight of his father's fall. Fortunately, a man from the house, witnessing the accident, rushed to the father's aid, helping him up and ensuring he was unharmed. The incident serves as a stark reminder of the importance of vigilance, even on familiar ground, and the unpredictability of split-second moments.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>slippery,fall,video,father,stairs,house,tiles,accident,son,tears,passerby,aid,treacherous,balance,entrance,moment,near-miss,vigilance,unharmed,unpredictability</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Xuan Hoa Ward, Phuc Yen Town, Vinh Phuc Province</media:city>
                          <media:country>Vietnam</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>VN</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>2652</guid>
                          <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 10:37:17 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2652.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2652.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Unforeseen plunge: Bryansk woman survives unexpected water-filled roadway hole</media:title>
                          <media:description>In a surprising and harrowing incident on August 10, 2023, in Bryansk, Russia, a local resident had a narrow escape after inadvertently falling into a concealed water-filled hole on the road. The unsuspecting woman was crossing the street during a heavy downpour when the mishap occurred. The hole, which had formed due to ongoing road repairs, was obscured by the rainwater that had accumulated, making it invisible to pedestrians. Video footage of the incident captures the woman's ordeal as she navigates through deep puddles with an umbrella, only to suddenly plunge into the submerged pit. Remarkably, she resurfaced after a few tense seconds, appearing relatively unscathed. Despite the alarming incident, the woman regained her footing and continued her journey, seemingly without sustaining significant injuries.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>rain,accident,roadway,hole,water,fall,Bryansk,Russia,pedestrian,video,umbrella,plunge,rescue,incident,escape,surface,injuries,unexpected,passersby,repair</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Bryansk </media:city>
                          <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Accidents,News</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>2754</guid>
                          <pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 09:41:24 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2754.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2754.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Tragedy strikes Makhachkala: gas station explosion claims 27 lives, including 3 children</media:title>
                          <media:description>In a devastating incident that unfolded on August 14, 2023, in Makhachkala, Dagestan, Russia, a gas station explosion claimed the lives of 27 individuals, leaving the local community reeling in shock. The Dagestan Center for Disaster Medicine confirmed the grim death toll, with an additional 75 people reported as victims. Heartbreakingly, among the deceased were three children, amplifying the tragedy's somber impact. The sequence of events leading to the catastrophic explosion began with a car service catching fire along a highway in Makhachkala, subsequently engulfing the adjacent gas station and culminating in the devastating blast. Authorities, including First Deputy Minister of Health of Russia Viktor Fisenko, swiftly mobilized to provide medical care to the injured, with plans in place to transfer victims to Moscow hospitals for specialized treatment. As the community grapples with this unprecedented loss, Dagestan's Head, Sergei Melikov, emphasized the importance of both material and psychological support for the victims' families. The incident has prompted an official investigation, with the Investigative Committee initiating a criminal case under relevant sections of the Criminal Code. In remembrance of the lives lost, August 15 has been declared a day of mourning in Dagestan.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>explosion,tragedy,gas station,Makhachkala,Dagestan,Russia,death toll,victims,children,emergency,investigation,mourning,community,shock,blast,authorities,medical care,support,criminal case,remembrance</media:keywords>
                          <media:city> Makhachkala, Dagestan </media:city>
                          <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>News,Accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>2729</guid>
                          <pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 16:32:21 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2729.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2729.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Tragic training flight: Su-30 fighter jet crashes in Kaliningrad Region</media:title>
                          <media:description>A devastating incident unfolded on August 12, 2023, in the Kaliningrad region of Russia as a two-seat Su-30 fighter jet crashed during a routine training flight. The Western Military District's press service confirmed the grim news, stating that the aircraft went down in an uninhabited area, with the unfortunate loss of the entire crew's lives. The flight had been conducted without any ammunition on board. Preliminary investigations indicate that a technical malfunction precipitated the emergency, highlighting the potential risks inherent in complex aviation machinery even during non-combat operations. </media:description>
                          <media:keywords>crash,su-30,fighter jet,training,Kaliningrad,Russia,crew,tragedy,technical malfunction,aviation,incident,military,loss,emergency,ammunition,investigation,danger,skills,security,somber</media:keywords>
                          <media:city> Kaliningrad region </media:city>
                          <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>News,Accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>2715</guid>
                          <pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 14:53:15 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2715.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2715.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Torrential rainstorm unleashes fury: container tossed by powerful winds in Borovlyany, Belarus</media:title>
                          <media:description>A dramatic rainstorm wreaked havoc in Borovlyany village, Belarus on July 8, 2023, as captured in a compelling video by @zvansky. The footage showcases the intensity of the downpour, with rain lashing against the pavement and buildings on 40 Years of Victory Street. As the author patiently waited for the rain to subside near the Euroopt building, the weather took an abrupt turn. The wind's strength escalated noticeably, prompting him to start recording. In an astonishing turn of events, the tempestuous wind forcefully sent a sizeable container hurtling onto the street. </media:description>
                          <media:keywords>rain,storm,Borovlyany,Belarus,video,wind,container,weather,intensity,pavement,buildings,Euroopt,street,@zvansky,downpour,dramatic,footage,lashing,unpredictability,nature</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Borovlyany</media:city>
                          <media:country>Belarus</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>BY</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Accidents,Weather</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Sat, 8 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>2686</guid>
                          <pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 13:38:18 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2686.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2686.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Thrilling mishap: Audi drift attempt ends in guardrail collision at Suzhou GTshow </media:title>
                          <media:description>During the annual Suzhou GTshow on July 22, 2023, a highly anticipated automotive cultural event in China, a heart-pounding incident occurred as an Audi car attempted a daring drift maneuver. The vehicle lost control and collided with a guardrail, sending shockwaves through the crowd of car enthusiasts. Thankfully, no one was injured in the dramatic collision. The video captured by @ShanghaiUPAutomotiveTechnicalService shows the intensity of the moment, serving as a reminder of the risks involved in high-speed automotive displays. Despite the unexpected mishap, the event continued, showcasing a spectacular display of Custom cars and Supercars to the delight of the attendees.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>drift,audi,collision,guardrail,suzhou,china,g t show,automotive,event,enthusiasts,custom,supercar,annual,mishap,excitement,car,culture,display,injured,risk</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Suzhou</media:city>
                          <media:country>China</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>CN</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>2603</guid>
                          <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 13:19:39 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2603.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2603.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Close call: Voronezh woman narrowly escapes injury as fan falls from balcony</media:title>
                          <media:description>A harrowing incident occurred on August 12, 2023, in Voronezh, Russia, leaving a resident shaken but miraculously unharmed. Angelina Adam, a 36-year-old woman, was out for a morning walk along a footpath when a fan plummeted from a sixth-floor balcony just behind her. Startled by the sudden rumble and lightning pain as the fan's wire grazed her arm and leg, Angelina's shock quickly turned to fear. She had narrowly escaped a potentially fatal accident by mere luck. Despite the close call, she pressed on, returning to the scene and promptly notifying the police about the incident. Surveillance footage captured the heart-stopping moment as the fan descended, prompting the authorities to launch an investigation. Angelina, a mother herself, expresses concern for the safety of young families in the area and hopes that justice will be served to the individual responsible for the reckless act.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>walk,balcony,fan,incident,escape,luck,shock,police,investigation,danger,resident,Voronezh,Russia,Angelina Adam,surveillance,narrow,fear,safety,reckless,justice</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Voronezh </media:city>
                          <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Accidents,News</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>2755</guid>
                          <pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 09:32:51 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2755.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2755.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Tragedy strikes Makhachkala: gas station explosion claims 27 lives, including 3 children</media:title>
                          <media:description>A devastating explosion at a gas station in Makhachkala, Dagestan, Russia, has left a grim toll of 27 fatalities, including three children, as confirmed by the Dagestan Center for Disaster Medicine. The incident, which occurred on August 14, 2023, resulted in a total of 75 reported victims, with 66 individuals in hospitals in Makhachkala, 10 of them in serious condition. The catastrophe was triggered by a fire that originated at a car service on the highway and quickly spread to the adjacent gas station, culminating in a powerful explosion. The First Deputy Minister of Health of Russia, Viktor Fisenko, has flown to Dagestan to oversee medical care for the wounded, who will be transported by a special aircraft of the Ministry of Emergency Situations to hospitals in Moscow. In response to the tragedy, August 15 has been declared a day of mourning in Dagestan, with both material and psychological support being extended to the families of the victims. An investigation has been launched by the Investigative Committee under charges of negligence that led to the tragic loss of life. A harrowing video footage depicts the gas station engulfed in towering flames, capturing the magnitude of the disaster that has shaken the region.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>explosion,gas station,tragedy,Dagestan,Russia,casualties,children,fire,investigation,mourning,support,victims,hospitalization,wreckage,negligence,grief,impact,devastation,emergency,flames</media:keywords>
                          <media:city> Makhachkala, Dagestan </media:city>
                          <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Accidents,News</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>2728</guid>
                          <pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 16:31:44 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2728.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2728.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Frontline valor: BRAVO team's harrowing battle for Pyatikhatka village amidst Russian air assault</media:title>
                          <media:description>In a relentless display of courage and determination, a video captured on June 16, 2023, brings to light the harrowing assault on Pyatikhatka village, Ukraine by the "BRAVO Team" detachment from the 130th ORB. Amidst the ongoing conflict between Ukraine and Russia, this courageous detachment embarked on a perilous mission to advance deep into the village, engaging in a fierce battle against units of the Russian Air Force, known as "Storm Z." The relentless barrage of enemy artillery, tanks, and mortars provided a formidable backdrop to their efforts, pushing the soldiers to their limits. In the midst of the chaos, a poignant moment arose as a soldier was struck by searing debris from their own weapon, underscoring the unyielding challenges faced by those who valiantly defend their homeland on the frontlines.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>battlefield,conflict,valor,bravery,video,assault,detachment,village,Ukraine,Russia,BRAVO Team,130th ORB,frontline,courage,mission,enemy,artillery,tanks,mortars,debris</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Pyatikhatka village</media:city>
                          <media:country>Ukraine</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>UA</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>WAR</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>News,Accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>2738</guid>
                          <pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 07:39:44 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2738.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2738.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Crane catastrophe: dramatic bridge damage caught on video in Brooklyn</media:title>
                          <media:description>On July 19th, 2023, in Brooklyn, New York, USA, a shocking incident occurred during which a crane collided with the lower side of a bridge. A witness, identified as @thisismathieu, captured the dramatic moment on video. As he was out for his morning run, he noticed the tall crane approaching the bridge but did not expect the disastrous outcome. The crane struck the bridge with a loud bang, causing significant damage as it dragged along the bottom. In the brief recording, the extent of the destruction became apparent.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>brooklyn,new york,usa,crane,bridge,damage,video,incident,witness,collision,morning,run,loud,bang,destruction,authorities,accident,investigate,damages,caught</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Brooklyn, New York</media:city>
                          <media:country>United States</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>US</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>2525</guid>
                          <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 21:04:22 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2525.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2525.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Tragic clash in Nerekhta: intoxicated foreign car driver hits pedestrian girl and crashes into building</media:title>
                          <media:description>A horrific incident occurred in Nerekhta, Kostroma region, Russia, as reported by the press service of the UGIBDD of the Ministry of Internal Affairs. On June 29th, 2023, a foreign car driver, under the influence of alcohol, recklessly crashed into a young girl before colliding into a residential building. Shocking video footage from CCTV cameras circulated on social media, capturing the car speeding towards the helpless victim. The impact was mitigated slightly by bushes, possibly saving the girl's life. Urgently hospitalized, she now fights for recovery, while the driver will be held accountable for his actions according to the law.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>accident,clash,nerekhta,kostroma,russia,foreign car,pedestrian,girl,building,video footage,cctv,social media,intoxicated,driver,hospitalization,bushes,speeding,accountable,law,tragic</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Nerekhta, Kostroma region</media:city>
                          <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>2467</guid>
                          <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/f50935ab-19a9-4134-9232-d6071d0d4327.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/801973da-a173-4cce-98bb-3a5004f60820.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Blaze breaks out on Panama-registered car carrier Fremantle Highway off Netherlands coast</media:title>
                          <media:description>A fire broke out on the Panama-registered car carrier, Fremantle Highway, off the coast of the Netherlands near Ameland on July 26, 2023, as it was transporting 2,857 cars from Bremerhaven, Germany, to Port Said, Egypt. The blaze resulted in the evacuation of all 23 crew members, with seven rescued from the water and the rest airlifted by helicopter. Tragically, one crew member lost their life, and several others were injured during the incident. The fire, originating from one of the 25 electric cars onboard, proved difficult for the crew to control, and the vessel continued to burn approximately 27 nautical miles north of the Dutch island of Ameland, close to a major environmental and UNESCO heritage site. Images showed scorched areas and billowing smoke along the ship's side as emergency responders battled to contain the flames. @NicoGuud captured a video of smoke still coming from the vessel.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>fire,blaze,car carrier,Netherlands,coast,Fremantle Highway,smoke,evacuation,rescue,injuries,crew,incident,electric cars,tragedy,Ameland,environmental,UNESCO,scorched,emergency,responders</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Ameland</media:city>
                          <media:country>Netherlands</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>NL</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>2552</guid>
                          <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023 20:11:03 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2552.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2552.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Rail rampage: freight train mishap causes havoc at Matveevskaya Station in Moscow</media:title>
                          <media:description>On July 18, 2023, at Moscow's Matveevskaya station in Russia, a freight train transporting rails experienced a serious accident. During transportation, one of the rails shifted and obstructed the train's path, causing extensive damage to everything in its way. The incident resulted in the destruction of the platform's pavilion and the damage of the driver's cab in an oncoming train. Fortunately, no injuries were reported among the people at the station. Despite the chaos caused by the runaway rail, there were no traffic delays along the route. </media:description>
                          <media:keywords>rail,accident,freight,train,platform,Moscow,Russia,transportation,damage,pavilion,oncoming,driver's cab,mishap,knockdown,path,havoc,delay,people,repairs,footage</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Matveevskaya, Moscow </media:city>
                          <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>2494</guid>
                          <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 12:14:26 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2494.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2494.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Su-25 training flight ends in disaster: engine failure causes crash over sea of Azov, pilot survives ejection</media:title>
                          <media:description>On July 17th, 2023, a Su-25 attack aircraft crashed near the coast of Yeysk, Krasnodar Territory, Russia, while conducting a training flight over the Sea of Azov. The preliminary investigation points to an engine failure as the cause of the incident. Disturbingly, the crash occurred in close proximity to people who were resting on the coast at the time. Fortunately, the pilot successfully ejected from the aircraft before the impact and was rescued by emergency services. Currently, specialists from the Ministry of Defense of the Russian Federation and other relevant agencies are on-site, investigating the accident.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>crash,su-25,yeysk,krasnodar territory,russia,engine failure,training flight,sea of azov,incident,emergency services,pilot,eject,rescuers,ministry of defense,special services,scene,coast,rest,investigation,accident</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Yeysk, Krasnodar Territory</media:city>
                          <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>2490</guid>
                          <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 09:40:33 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2490.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2490.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Nine-year-old boy hospitalized after tree collapse at Samara playground</media:title>
                          <media:description>On July 10, 2023 evening in the Oktyabrsky district of Samara, Russia, a harrowing incident occurred on a playground when a tree unexpectedly fell on a nine-year-old boy. Despite initial fears, authorities determined that the tree was still alive and showed no signs of decay, raising questions about the cause of the collapse. The young victim was rushed to Seredavina Hospital, where medical professionals confirmed his condition to be stable and satisfactory. The child is currently under close observation by doctors as they work to ensure his recovery. Authorities are conducting a thorough investigation into the incident to understand the circumstances leading to the tree's collapse, offering insights to prevent similar accidents in the future.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>hospitalized,playground,tree,collapse,samara,russia,nine-year-old,incident,oktyabrsky,alive,decay,investigation,authorities,stable,satisfactory,doctors,observation,recovery,child,district</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Samara</media:city>
                          <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>2559</guid>
                          <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 06:58:05 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2559.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2559.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Tragedy strikes: pedestrian bridge collapse in Luga claims one life, leaves three injured</media:title>
                          <media:description>In a devastating incident on July 22, 2023, a pedestrian bridge in the city of Luga, Leningrad Region, Russia, collapsed, resulting in one person losing their life and three others sustaining injuries. The regional Investigative Committee confirmed the tragic event, and harrowing video footage captured the moment when numerous people were standing on the bridge just before it gave way. The collapse has sent shockwaves through the community, prompting concerns about the safety and maintenance of such structures.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>tragedy,pedestrian,bridge,collapse,Luga,Russia,death,injury,incident,Investigative Committee,video,footage,community,safety,maintenance,structure,investigation,authorities,shockwaves,concerns</media:keywords>
                          <media:city> Luga, Saint Petersburg region</media:city>
                          <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>2554</guid>
                          <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 07:29:36 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2554.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2554.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Action-packed movie filming in Chisinau takes a dramatic turn as car rams parked bus!</media:title>
                          <media:description>In a stunning turn of events in Chisinau, Moldova, a movie filming session took a thrilling and unexpected twist as a car intentionally rammed into a parked bus. The dramatic scene, captured by @nazligian_ on July 23, 2023, showcased the heart-pounding moment when the car, utilizing a purpose-built ramp, accelerated towards the stationary bus. With precision and skill, the car collided with the bus, creating a breathtaking spectacle that left onlookers in awe. Fortunately, there were no reported injuries as the filming was conducted in a closed-off area in the city center. The incident occurred as part of the action-packed movie production, adding an authentic touch to the adrenaline-filled scenes being brought to life on the silver screen.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>movie,filming,chisinau,moldova,car,bus,ramp,action,thrilling,unexpected,dramatic,spectacle,onlookers,injury-free,closed-off,center,adrenaline,scenes,silver screen,production</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Chisinau </media:city>
                          <media:country>Moldova</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>MD</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Sun, 23 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>2563</guid>
                          <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 07:49:50 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2563.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2563.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Su-25 aircraft crashes into sea of Azov during training flight in Yeysk, Russia, due to engine failure</media:title>
                          <media:description>On July 17th, 2023, a Su-25 aircraft crashed into the Sea of Azov near Yeysk, Krasnodar Territory, Russia, during a training flight. The incident occurred around 15:00, and according to the press service of the Southern Military District, the preliminary cause of the crash was attributed to engine failure. Fortunately, there were no reported casualties, and specialists from the Ministry of Defense and special services are currently investigating the accident on-site.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>crash,aircraft,sea,training,Yeysk,Russia,engine failure,incident,casualties,specialists,Ministry of Defense,special services,investigation,coast,Su-25,Azov,preliminary cause,spot,press service,Southern Military District</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Yeysk, Krasnodar Territory</media:city>
                          <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>2489</guid>
                          <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 09:42:11 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2489.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2489.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Sanitary felling mishap: poplar collapses on residential building</media:title>
                          <media:description>In the Tyukhtet region of Russia, an incident occurred on July 5th, 2023, during a sanitary felling operation. Workers cut down a poplar tree, but it unexpectedly collapsed onto a residential building that also housed a pharmacy and a shop. Fortunately, local authorities reported that the damage was minor, and the house was promptly repaired on the same day. According to the first deputy head of the Tyukhtetsky municipal district, Vladimir Napryushkin, the poplar tree only touched a part of the roof with one of its branches, causing damage to several sheets. However, no injuries were reported in the incident. The tree felling is a preventive measure taken in the region to remove old trees that pose potential dangers to people and buildings. No one was injured as a result of the incident.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>residential,building,pharmacy,shop,poplar,collapse,incident,Tyukhtet,Russia,workers,tree,damage,repaired,roof,pediment,felling,danger,authorities,minor,no injuries</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Tyukhtet</media:city>
                          <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Wed, 5 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>2487</guid>
                          <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/b615cfb9-6dbd-42ac-968d-ea39c34fd49c.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/dca43876-b4c9-41fc-88c8-4178f529b1e9.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Near disaster at North Morowali's wooden bridge: motorbikes overload nearly causes collapse!</media:title>
                          <media:description>On June 27th, 2023, a heart-stopping incident occurred in North Morowali, Indonesia, when a wooden bridge came close to collapsing under the weight of multiple motorbikes. The alarming scene was captured on video by @srcyayaaa, who witnessed the incident unfold. Instead of crossing the bridge one by one as recommended, the riders decided to pass together, causing an overwhelming strain on the aging structure. Miraculously, the bridge managed to hold on, preventing a potentially catastrophic accident. </media:description>
                          <media:keywords>wooden,bridge,collapse,motorbike,weight,North Morowali,Indonesia,video,nearly,one by one,together,fall,repaired,incident,captured,@srcyayaaa,danger,structure,safety,guidelines</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>North Morowali</media:city>
                          <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>ID</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>2472</guid>
                          <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/626d8c53-00bd-4110-afc2-335d637a3843.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/8bafe67d-273c-44bc-a53a-82fe7c7888ac.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Hit-and-run incident in Novosibirsk: child survives as driver flees the scene</media:title>
                          <media:description>In a distressing incident that occurred on October 30, 2022, in the Novosibirsk region of Russia, a child was struck and run over by a RAV4 driver. Shocking video footage captured the incident, revealing that the driver initially attempted to lift the injured boy before abruptly fleeing the scene in his vehicle. According to reports from the AST-54 group on the VKontakte social network, which cited eyewitnesses, the young victim, aged 6, miraculously survived the accident and is currently receiving medical treatment at a local hospital.

Authorities have yet to comment on the incident, as a request for information has been sent to the press service of the Main Directorate of the Ministry of Internal Affairs for the Novosibirsk Region. Meanwhile, speculation has arisen on social media that the driver involved may be a deputy working as a director of a municipal institution. However, there is no official confirmation of this allegation at the time of writing.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>accident,hit-and-run,Novosibirsk,Russia,RAV4,child,video,driver,hospital,survival,investigation,authorities,eyewitnesses,social media,speculation,deputy,municipal institution,press service,community,updates</media:keywords>
                          <media:city> Novosibirsk region</media:city>
                          <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2022</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>2207</guid>
                          <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 09:22:21 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/1c408366-4764-4bef-a715-2d3ca421e52f.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/c60c9865-aea0-436a-8ee5-e5fc1de88a1b.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Terrifying gas explosion at family party leaves dishes shattered </media:title>
                          <media:description>In a shocking incident that unfolded during a family party in Chon Thanh town, Binh Phuoc province, Vietnam on October 12, 2022, a gas explosion sent shockwaves through the gathering, leaving dishes shattered. The explosion occurred without warning, while everyone was enjoying a meal prepared by the author. Amidst the joyous atmosphere, the sudden blast sent pieces of meat flying towards the ceiling, causing chaos and panic among the attendees.

The cause of the explosion is believed to be an old mini gas tank that had been repainted and repaired to appear brand new by the seller. @n07071990 who captured the video  recounts that there were no visible signs of leaks or any other indications of trouble prior to the incident. The force of the explosion was so intense that it took more than two hours for one person, dressed in a blue shirt, to regain mobility after being struck by one of the materials shattered by the gas. The aftermath of the incident left the guests traumatized, with many hesitant to use mini gas stoves in the future.
</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>explosion,gas,party,guests,dishes,bacon,grilled,stove,old,repaired,brand new,witnesses,fear,chaos,panic,injuries,shattered,leaks,intense,trauma</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Chon Thanh town, Binh Phuoc province</media:city>
                          <media:country>Vietnam</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>VN</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2022</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>2260</guid>
                          <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 20:31:50 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/6de1372d-4bb2-4424-a2d6-71fe88782b42.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/c19ed9e3-0190-41ac-b8f6-d1c76aa35f81.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Terrifying moment: motorbike plunges into water as floating bridge swings wildly</media:title>
                          <media:description>In a heart-stopping incident captured on video by @ferdipratamaa, a man's motorbike plummeted into the water after the floating bridge he was crossing swung violently due to strong winds. The dramatic footage, filmed on April 24, 2023, in Gunung Megang, South Sumatra, Indonesia, shows the man losing control of his bike as it teeters on the swaying bridge. Despite his desperate efforts to regain balance, he ultimately succumbs to the uncontrollable forces, toppling into the water below.

 Fortunately, the man escaped the incident with no serious injuries. The strong winds that day created a treacherous situation, causing the bridge to sway violently and making it nearly impossible for the motorist to maintain control.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>floating bridge,motorbike,incident,video,strong winds,swinging,dramatic,control,water,balance,danger,unpredictable,weather,risk,injuries,caution,preparedness,structure,adverse conditions,Indonesia</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Gunung Megang, South Sumatra</media:city>
                          <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>ID</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>2190</guid>
                          <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 20:48:59 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/374b5994-6b55-416e-a875-a3d8bca3b4c4.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/9c20e511-d7af-4cb3-883a-00765728c6d0.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Unexpected pitfall: friend's close call during inflatable pool adventure</media:title>
                          <media:description>In a bizarre incident captured on video by @anjarsuzu, a day of fun turned into a close call for a friend in Muko Regency, Bengkulu Province, Indonesia on July 18, 2022. The video shows a friend, unknowingly, stepping into a hole pit while moving backward, moments after helping tie the children's pool on the car. The friend quickly regained his balance and lifted himself out of the hole.

The incident occurred when the author decided to inflate a children's pool and secure it on top of a car. With his friend's assistance, he successfully tied the pool to the vehicle. However, as the friend stepped back, he failed to notice the nearby pit and accidentally slid into it. Fortunately, his reflexes kicked in, allowing him to swiftly lift himself out of harm's way.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>pit,fall,video,friend,inflatable,pool,air,tying,car,hole,leg,quick,close call,adventure,incident,Muko Regency,Bengkulu Province,Indonesia,funny,captured,unaware</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Muko Regency, Bengkulu Province</media:city>
                          <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>ID</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2022</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>2191</guid>
                          <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 20:49:36 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/136a1d01-99c4-4d56-a76d-6b67f2c3c56c.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/6ab75d3b-050f-4de3-9580-ae72da1c0acc.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Driver flees after Lada Priora crashes at toll booth on M-4 Don Highway in Voronezh Region, Russia</media:title>
                          <media:description>A Lada Priora crashed into a fence and broke the barrier at a toll booth on the M-4 Don highway in the Voronezh region of Russia on May 4th, 2023. The incident was reported by the Telegram channel "Atypical Pavlovsk". According to the public, the accident occurred on the 636th km of the highway near the village of Shestakovo in the Bobrovsky district.

Eyewitnesses reported that the driver of the car fled the scene after the accident. It is not known what caused the accident or if there were any injuries or fatalities as a result.

The M-4 Don highway is one of the major highways in Russia and connects Moscow with the southern regions of the country, including Rostov-on-Don and Krasnodar.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>car,crash,toll,booth,highway,Voronezh,Russia,Lada,Priora,fence,barrier,accident,driver,flee,scene,investigation,charges,safety,driving,responsibility</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Voronezh Region</media:city>
                          <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Thu, 4 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>2011</guid>
                          <pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 18:21:46 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2011.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2011.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Fiery blaze engulfs foam board truck in Linyi: driver escapes unharmed</media:title>
                          <media:description>A truck carrying foam boards caught fire in Linyi, Shandong province, China, causing a dramatic scene captured on video by @Anquanshengchan on May 25th, 2023. The incident occurred at 6 o'clock in the morning when the driver suddenly detected a burning odor. To his horror, he realized that the foam boards on the top of the truck were engulfed in flames. Despite his quick efforts to unload the cargo, his attempts proved futile, and he could only stand helplessly as the foam boards burned on the ground. Thankfully, the driver managed to drive the truck away from the area, ensuring that no injuries were reported.

The video footage showcases the intense nature of the fire, with billowing smoke and bright orange flames consuming the foam boards. The driver's prompt action to remove the truck from potential danger was crucial in preventing any further complications. </media:description>
                          <media:keywords>burning,foam,boards,truck,fire,video,incident,Linyi,Shandong,China,driver,smell,top,unloaded,useless,watch,ground,offloaded,fortunate,injured</media:keywords>
                          <media:city> Linyi of Shandong province</media:city>
                          <media:country>China</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>CN</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Thu, 25 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>2233</guid>
                          <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 11:29:08 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/835177d6-f84b-464a-9fda-b503181c42e5.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2233.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Unattended gear mishap: car rolls out and damages neighbor's house</media:title>
                          <media:description>In Bandung, Indonesia, a car mishap occurred when a driver, Yuda Aminurahman, experienced an unfortunate incident on May 20, 2023. Yuda had washed his car and intended to warm up the engine. However, in a moment of carelessness, he failed to check the gears before starting the ignition. As a result, the car unexpectedly rolled out of its parking spot and came to a halt against his neighbor's house.

A video he captured showcased his desperate attempts to prevent the car from colliding with the neighboring property. Despite his efforts from outside, he was unable to halt the car's momentum. Fortunately, the car itself sustained minimal damage. However, the neighbor's house was not as fortunate, it suffered damage.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>car,mishap,video,roll,ignition,gears,damage,neighbor,house,incident,Bandung,Indonesia,morning,wash,engine,careless,stop,outside,minimal,attention</media:keywords>
                          <media:city> Bandung</media:city>
                          <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>ID</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Sat, 20 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>2188</guid>
                          <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 19:53:15 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2188.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2188.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Bridge of peril: tales of survival in Uttara Kannada's waterfall adventure"</media:title>
                          <media:description>In a heart-stopping incident during a waterfall exploration in the Uttara Kannada district of Karnataka, India, a small wooden bridge meant to span a gentle river met an unexpected fate. With three intrepid adventurers on it, the bridge suddenly gave way, plunging them into a perilous situation. Gripped by fear and struggling to stay afloat in the swift waters, they instinctively clung to one another, to fight against the current's relentless pull. the video footage was captured by  @_traveleen_ on 21st of April, 2023. 

Fellow adventurers who had been trailing behind swiftly rushed to their aid. Braving the treacherous currents themselves, these courageous individuals extended a lifeline to the stranded trio, ensuring they okay and safe. </media:description>
                          <media:keywords>waterfall,exploration,bridge,collapse,survival,adventurers,river,danger,unity,compassion,rescue,panic,courage,teamwork,nature,unpredictability,preparedness,bonds,triumph,chaos</media:keywords>
                          <media:city> Uttara Kannada District, Karnataka</media:city>
                          <media:country>India</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>IN</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>2109</guid>
                          <pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2023 09:56:51 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2109.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2109.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Unintentional collision: young girl in mosque runs into pillar while being recorded</media:title>
                          <media:description>The footage, recorded by a user with the handle @syafiqikhwannnnn on 17th April, 2023, shows a young girl playing in a mosque in Bachok, Kelantan, Malaysia. However, things take a turn for the worse when the girl notices that she is being recorded and runs straight into a nearby pillar.

In the video, the little girl can be seen standing against the wall, playing with her hands. She appears to be lost in her own world, enjoying the peaceful atmosphere of the mosque. However, as soon as she notices that she is being recorded, she runs away from the camera without looking where she is going.

Unfortunately, the girl's carelessness leads to a painful collision with the pillar. She bumps into it with considerable force. The girl is fine.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>girl,mosque,playing,wall,accident,carelessness,impulsive,safety,parents,children,social media,recording,sharing,online,privacy,consent,cautionary,reminder,awareness,environment</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Bachok, Kelantan</media:city>
                          <media:country>Malaysia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>MY</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>2050</guid>
                          <pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2023 09:56:51 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2050.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2050.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Acrobatic mishap: high-flying stunt goes wrong</media:title>
                          <media:description>In a heart-stopping incident in Jiangsu Province, East China, a high-altitude acrobatic stunt took a dangerous turn, leading to a colleague's neck injury. The incident, captured on video by @dragondragon on May 18th, 2023, showcased the acrobat's colleague practicing daring maneuvers on a springboard. However, concerns arose among the group as they worried he might miss the sponge pad meant to cushion his fall.

In an attempt to reduce the risk, another colleague quickly placed an extra sponge in front of the acrobat's expected landing site. Fortunately, this movement softened the fall of the acrobat. Everything could have ended much worse.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>acrobat,high-altitude,springboard,colleague,practice,movement,sponge pad,fall,twist,neck,injury,video,stunt,Jiangsu Province,East China,worry,risk,landing,head,safety</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Jiangsu Province</media:city>
                          <media:country>China</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>CN</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Thu, 18 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>2134</guid>
                          <pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 07:36:06 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/bfa7f4d8-6ee4-4dca-969b-8747a1e0abde.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/b1549029-1798-4bd6-b892-1c34b6ea5e51.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Storm in Ufa: ventilation duct collapse crushes parked car</media:title>
                          <media:description>A severe storm in Ufa, Russia on 29th May, 2023, wreaked havoc in the Sosny residential complex as a ventilation duct from a high-rise building was demolished, resulting in a parked car being crushed under the debris. The alarming incident was captured on surveillance cameras, and images circulated on social media showing the extent of the damage. Fortunately, the Ufa Civil Protection Department confirmed that there were no casualties as a result of the incident.

In response to the incident, representatives from the Office of Civil Protection of Ufa and the administration of the Leninsky district swiftly arrived at the scene to assess the situation. Their primary objective is to determine the causes and circumstances that led to the ventilation duct's collapse. </media:description>
                          <media:keywords>storm,Ufa,Russia,Sosny residential complex,ventilation duct,demolished,debris,car,surveillance cameras,crushed,Civil Protection Department,no casualties,Office of Civil Protection,Leninsky district,causes,circumstances,investigation,incident,fallen,high-rise building,social media</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Ufa </media:city>
                          <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Mon, 29 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>2144</guid>
                          <pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 12:41:33 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/da1341f5-5543-452e-82d4-faf619f1689d.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/89f87dd8-a932-4b44-bef0-ef185fef52a4.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Motorcycle mishap: video captures rider's tumble on Indonesian Road</media:title>
                          <media:description>A video filmed by @dhony_bagas on August 10, 2022, in Banyuwangi, Indonesia, captured the moment a person riding an extended motorcycle veered off the road and toppled over.

The video, which has since been widely shared on social media, shows the person driving in front of @dhony_bagas before suddenly losing control of the motorcycle and crashing to the ground beside the road. It is not clear from the video whether the person sustained any injuries.

In Indonesia, where motorcycles are a common form of transportation, road safety is a major concern. According to data from the Indonesian Ministry of Transportation, there were over 128,000 motorcycle accidents in the country in 2020, resulting in more than 29,000 fatalities.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>motorcycle,mishap,Indonesia,Banyuwangi,road,safety,driving,accident,vulnerability,risk,enforcement,regulations,infrastructure,awareness,social media,video,transportation,fatalities,injuries,reminder</media:keywords>
                          <media:city> Banyuwangi</media:city>
                          <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>ID</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2022</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>2049</guid>
                          <pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2023 09:56:51 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2049.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2049.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Brave biker's close call: dismantled motorbike catches fire during test run</media:title>
                          <media:description>In a harrowing incident captured on video, @rohadysajiedin of Serdang Deli, North Sumatra, Indonesia, narrowly escaped disaster when the engine of his dismantled motorbike caught fire during a test run on April 29, 2023. The heart-stopping footage shows him riding the bike before stopping for a moment when suddenly  flames engulf the engine. Reacting swiftly, the author brought jumped off the motorbike. 

Risking his own safety, he wasted no time in attempting to extinguish the growing flames. Everything ended well.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>video,testing,motorbike,dismantled,fire,engine,caught,flames,stopped,extinguish,Serdang Deli,North Sumatra,Indonesia,close,call,bravery,danger,quick thinking,safety,courageous,incident</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Serdang Deli, North Sumatra</media:city>
                          <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>ID</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Sat, 29 Apr 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>2187</guid>
                          <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 20:45:42 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/04a13c6d-18ad-4dd4-ac23-c488c20c1e4e.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/d8515096-6195-4be7-b38f-a5663ceffdac.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Night market mishap: woman falls from 'banyu wave' ride in Sragen, Indonesia</media:title>
                          <media:description>A woman had a terrifying accident at a night market in Cembreng, Sragen, Indonesia. The incident occurred on May 15, 2023, when everyone was in the process of getting off the "Banyu Wave" ride. It is believed that the woman fell due to nervousness or a lack of focus, possibly resulting in her holding on less tightly and suddenly losing her balance. the video footage was captured by @rian.sanjaya931. 

The victim, whose identity remains undisclosed, is currently receiving medical treatment at a hospital. The extent of her injuries has not been disclosed, but it is clear that the incident was serious enough to require immediate attention.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>accident,night market,woman,fall,ride,Banyu Wave,Sragen,Indonesia,nervousness,lack of focus,tight grip,balance,hospital,treatment,investigation,safety,precautions,mechanical failure,amusement park,attractions</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Cembreng, Sragen</media:city>
                          <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>ID</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Mon, 15 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>2178</guid>
                          <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 17:53:23 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/bc0dcde2-678c-4bc5-9147-e0c84b7161f8.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/9d52f2d2-b987-4be0-aaaf-812d71f8afaa.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Quick thinking saves the day: daughter's cool response stops stove fire</media:title>
                          <media:description>In a remarkable display of composure and quick thinking, a young girl in Thái Bình province, Vietnam, averted a potential disaster when a fire broke out in her kitchen. The incident, captured by @ngothanhlam123456789 on April 8th, 2023, showcased the bravery and level-headedness of the daughter as she handled the situation with remarkable poise.

As the video footage reveals, the girl was cooking alone when the stove suddenly burst into flames. Instead of panicking, she immediately started looking for a way to put out the fire. Demonstrating her resourcefulness, she swiftly sought out a nearby fan to disperse the smoke and prevent the flames from spreading further. Miraculously, thanks to her calm and decisive actions, the fire was contained, with only the food falling victim to the incident.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>cooking,fire,stove,daughter,home,calm,quick-thinking,safety,protection,bravery,composure,resourcefulness,fan,smoke,emergency,incident,food,camera,thái bình,vietnam</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Quỳnh Phụ, Thái Bình province</media:city>
                          <media:country>Vietnam</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>VN</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Fri, 7 Apr 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>2167</guid>
                          <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 18:21:58 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/cbe312de-92d8-4a3c-8ce3-d03f397363cc.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/18dedc10-1680-47cc-b710-a59d6aa14968.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Fire erupts during well repair at Severo-Labatyuganskoye field in Russia</media:title>
                          <media:description>An explosion rattled the Severo-Labatyuganskoye field in the Surgut district of the Khanty-Mansiysk Autonomous region, Russia, as repair work was underway on a well. The incident occurred on 30th May, 2023, during which a fire broke out, damaging the body of the lifting unit of a car. Fortunately, the oil workers at the site managed to extinguish the fire before the arrival of the fire service, averting any casualties or injuries.

The Ministry of Emergency Situations reported that the fire had engulfed an area measuring approximately 0.5 square meters. Although the flames were successfully brought under control, investigators are now working diligently to establish the cause of the fire. The Severo-Labatyuganskoye field, being developed by Surgutneftegaz, is known for its significant oil reserves and plays a crucial role in Russia's energy sector.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>explosion,repair,well,fire,damage,car,workers,extinguished,arrival,firefighters,Ministry,Emergency Situations,cause,investigators,Severo-Labatyuganskoye,field,Surgutneftegaz,Khanty-Mansi,Autonomous Okrug,Russia</media:keywords>
                          <media:city> Khanty-Mansiysk autonomous region</media:city>
                          <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Tue, 30 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>2174</guid>
                          <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 10:13:17 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/c945f894-5d73-40df-bbe5-bef926de87e7.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/df9ebb47-e472-4bb5-a3d5-338f8ff6aa36.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Unstoppable lady rider's calmness amidst chaos: a remarkable incident at a general store</media:title>
                          <media:description>In a small village in Masaran, Sragen, Central Java, Indonesia, a remarkable incident unfolded at a local general store. On May 12, 2023, a CCTV camera captured the astonishing actions of a lady motorbike rider who found herself in an unexpected predicament.

The video footage reveals that the motorbike experienced a malfunction, causing the gas to remain engaged, rendering it impossible for the vehicle to come to a stop. Unfazed by the situation, the determined rider made her way into the general store, the motorbike's engine still roaring.

With remarkable skill and composure, she navigated through the narrow spaces between the shelves. Onlookers were left in awe.

However, as fate would have it, the motorbike eventually collided with one of the shelves, causing both the rider and the bike to fall. Astonishingly, the lady remained calm and composed throughout the incident, never displaying a hint of panic. On the other hand, the onlookers were left bewildered, unable to comprehend the rider's intentions.

As the dust settled, the store owner and the concerned spectators gathered around the lady rider. To everyone's surprise, the owner did not demand compensation for the damaged mop or any other potential losses incurred during the incident. 

As news of this incident spread on social media, the video shared by @Yunitaardiva2 quickly went viral. </media:description>
                          <media:keywords>motorbike,rider,store,incident,gas problem,unstoppable,composure,chaos,shelves,determination,precision,astonishment,onlookers,mystery,generosity,speculation,resilience,calmness,viral,unconventional</media:keywords>
                          <media:city> Masaran, Sragen, Central Java</media:city>
                          <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>ID</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Fri, 12 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>2071</guid>
                          <pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 18:21:46 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2071.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2071.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Terrifying escape: surviving the devastating landslide in Palapay, Gingoog city</media:title>
                          <media:description>In a heart-stopping turn of events, a group of individuals narrowly escaped a catastrophic landslide while driving through Palapay, Gingoog City, Philippines. The incident occurred on a 26th March, 2023, as @DanteSalang captured the harrowing event on video. Travelling at a moderate speed of 50 to 60 kilometers per hour, their pickup truck suddenly encountered falling stones at the mountainside. Within seconds, a massive landslide ensued, prompting the driver to slam the brakes and swiftly retreat to safety.

As they hastily turned back, the scene unfolded before their eyes, painting a picture of sheer chaos and terror. A house, caught in the landslide's wrath, was swiftly washed away, leaving behind a devastated landscape. Amidst the chaos, a mother desperately clutched her baby and fled from the collapsing dwelling, fear etched on her face. A teenage girl, displaying tremendous courage and resilience, carried an infant in her arms as she sprinted for safety. Children, their innocence shattered by the calamity, sprinted with all their might, desperate to outrun the advancing destruction.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>landslide,escape,danger,survival,Palapay,Gingoog City,video,driving,pickup truck,stones,mountain,house,mother,baby,teenager,infant,children,chaos,resilience,nature</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Palapay Gingoog city</media:city>
                          <media:country>Philippines</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>PH</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Sun, 26 Mar 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>2091</guid>
                          <pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2023 11:56:17 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2091.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2091.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Powerful explosion rocks gas supply station in Samarkand, Uzbekistan</media:title>
                          <media:description>A powerful explosion has rocked a gas supply station in the Samarkand region of Uzbekistan, leaving one person injured. The incident occurred on May 10th, 2023, and was reportedly caused by a violation of safety techniques during the draining of fuel from a gas tanker into the reserve tank.

Eyewitnesses reported that the explosion was preceded by a fire that broke out in a truck at the gas supply station. The fire then spread to several LNG cylinders, causing a series of explosions that shook the area and sent plumes of smoke billowing into the sky.

Emergency services were quickly dispatched to the scene, and the injured person was taken to a nearby hospital for treatment.

The cause of the explosion is currently under investigation, and authorities have warned that it is too early to speculate on the exact cause. However, initial reports suggest that the accident was caused by a failure to follow proper safety protocols when transferring fuel from the gas tanker to the reserve tank.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>explosion,gas,supply,station,Samarkand,Uzbekistan,truck,fire,LNG,cylinders,injured,safety,techniques,violation,draining,fuel,reserve,tank,accident,investigation</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Samarkand region</media:city>
                          <media:country>Uzbekistan</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>UZ</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Wed, 10 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>2058</guid>
                          <pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 11:25:53 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2058.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2058.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Unusual catfish deluge: road accident unleashes aquatic chaos</media:title>
                          <media:description>In a bizarre incident that unfolded on the Sragen-Jogoro route in Central Java, Indonesia, a road accident led to a remarkable sight of live catfish scattered across the asphalt. The incident was captured on video by @choiiiikayuuu on November 20, 2020, who transporting the catfish through the area. The footage shows numerous catfish wriggling and flopping around on the road, while a group of people swiftly gathered to help collect the disoriented fish.

According to @choiiiikayuuu, the mishap occurred when his pickup truck, loaded with a cargo of catfish stored in white drums, experienced a tire explosion. The sudden impact caused the vehicle to sway, resulting in the scattering of the slippery cargo onto the road. Fortunately, the accident didn't lead to a more disastrous outcome, as the fish managed to avoid falling into nearby ditches filled with water. The unexpected scene attracted the attention of bystanders and passersby who lent a hand in the rescue efforts, working diligently to gather the stranded catfish and return them to safety.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>catfish,scattered,road,alive,waggling,video,people,collecting,Grobogan,Sragen-Jogoro,pick up,white drum,tire,exploded,accident,swayed,ditch,water,Indonesia,unusual</media:keywords>
                          <media:city> Glonggong, Sragen, Central Java</media:city>
                          <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>ID</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Fri, 20 Nov 2020</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>2228</guid>
                          <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 16:56:46 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/0596d608-c539-4c06-b873-f615d597864a.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/3fb40772-9ab4-42b5-ab4e-4ec8086eb350.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Mother's swift action: a heart-stopping moment captured in Bali</media:title>
                          <media:description>In a heart-stopping moment captured on home camera footage, a mother's swift actions saved her children from a potentially dangerous situation in Karangasem, Bali, Indonesia. The video, recorded by @aryawiryaatmaja on April 9, 2023, showcases a scene where the mother is tending to her two young kids in front of their house.

The incident unfolded when the older child suddenly skidded and fell, resulting in a loud cry. The mother instinctively shifted her attention to attend to the fallen toddler, momentarily leaving the other child in a baby walker unattended. Little did she know that a shallow pit, a remnant of a religious ceremony, lay dangerously close to the path the baby walker was traversing.

As the child in the baby walker pushed it around, unaware of the potential danger, disaster seemed imminent. However, luck was on their side that day. The mother, displaying remarkable reflexes and agility, swiftly intercepted the baby walker just in the nick of time. She pulled both children closer to her, providing solace and comfort to the one who had fallen.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>mother,children,home camera,Bali,Indonesia,incident,rescue,swift,danger,toddler,fallen,baby walker,pit,religious ceremony,attention,love,vigilance,safety,parenting,social media</media:keywords>
                          <media:city> Karangasem, Bali</media:city>
                          <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>ID</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Sun, 9 Apr 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>2156</guid>
                          <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 07:40:55 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/8c1ac402-7344-4666-b3a2-3a54ec547fa7.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/cca6dd9a-df17-4f00-835a-3bb9944a0557.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Gravity's harvest: a fruitful climb turns into a tumbling adventure</media:title>
                          <media:description>In a incident that unfolded in East Luwu, South Sulawesi, Indonesia, a simple task of plucking rambutan fruit from a tree turned into a memorable sudden fall. @jentitorlawyer96, who happened to be present at the scene, captured the entire escapade on video.

On the 9th of December, 2022, East Luwu's a rambutan tree served as the backdrop for an impromptu expedition. Fueled by a craving for the delectable tropical fruit, @jentitorlawyer96's ex-girlfriend embarked on a daring quest to collect the rambutans above a wall.

As she delicately plucked a ripe rambutan, fate intervened, and an unexpected loss of balance ensued. The ladder, serving as both a stepping stone and an unfortunate catalyst, teetered precariously, sending her and the ladder on a chaotic descent. A mix of surprise, amusement, and concern filled the air as she tried to regain her balance during the tumble.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>exgirlfriend,rambutan,tree,wall,ladder,balance,fall,video,capture,adventure,laughter,unexpected,EastLuwu,SouthSulawesi,Indonesia,mishap,amusement,suspense,comedy,moment</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>East Luwu, South Sulawesi</media:city>
                          <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>ID</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Fri, 9 Dec 2022</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>2055</guid>
                          <pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2023 09:56:51 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2055.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2055.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Large fire along Virgin River in St. George contained after threatening 100 structures</media:title>
                          <media:description>Firefighters battled a large fire along the Virgin River in St. George, Utah, USA, on May 9th, 2023. The fire broke out around 3 p.m. near a residential area at 2580 E. Waters Edge Circle, just south of the Virgin River near Mall Drive. Fire departments from across Washington County responded to the scene to fight the blaze.

Although the cause of the fire is currently unknown, it is suspected to have been a controlled burn that got out of control. The fire spread quickly, covering an estimated 40 acres and threatening more than 100 structures. Some residents in nearby condos were urged to voluntarily evacuate, but no mandatory evacuations were ordered.

State fire managers reported that the fire was mostly contained within two hours of firefighters being called to the scene. By 8 p.m., the fire was 100% contained, and there were no injuries or structures lost.

St. George Fire Chief Robert Stoker warned that this fire season could be tough in southern Utah due to the wet winter and rainy spring, which have created new vegetation growth on top of years of dead fuels just beneath the surface. @cairochris who captured a clip of the fire commented "Fire along the Virgin River currently…about a half mile from my place."</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>fire,firefighters,Utah,St. George,Virgin River,blaze,evacuation,response,spectators,danger,containment,investigation,structures,vegetation,controlled burn,resources,crowds,residential,police,tough season</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Virgin River, St. George</media:city>
                          <media:country>United States</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>US</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Tue, 9 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>2042</guid>
                          <pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 20:33:21 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2042.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2042.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Drone strike suspected as cause of fire at oil depot in Krasnodar Territory, Russia</media:title>
                          <media:description>A fire that broke out at an oil depot in the Krasnodar Territory of Russia on May 3, 2023, has sparked suspicions that it may have been caused by a drone strike.

Eyewitnesses reported seeing a drone flying over the oil depot just before the fire started, followed by two loud explosions. While authorities have not yet confirmed whether the fire was indeed caused by a drone strike, the incident has raised concerns about the use of unmanned aerial vehicles (UAVs) for malicious purposes.

The fire, which broke out in the village of Volna in the Temryuk District, caused a thick black column of smoke that was visible from the Crimean coast of the Kerch Strait. Emergency services were immediately dispatched to the scene, and employees of the port next to the burning tank were evacuated.

Despite the severity of the fire, there were no reported casualties or injuries. The governor of the Krasnodar Territory, Veniamin Kondratiev, assured residents that the situation was under control and that there was no need for a complete evacuation of the village.

According to Fyodor Babenkov, the head of the Temryuk district, 85 firefighters were deployed to put out the blaze. The fire was given the highest difficulty level, and emergency services were working around the clock to prevent it from spreading further.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>fire,oil depot,drone,strike,Krasnodar Territory,Russia,evacuation,emergency services,firefighters,smoke,UAV,explosion,investigation,security,regulations,technology,threats,vigilance,danger,accessibility</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Krasnodar</media:city>
                          <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Wed, 3 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>1981</guid>
                          <pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 18:21:46 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/1981.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/1981.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Man robs store and throws money in the street to go to jail in Nizhny Novgorod, Russia"</media:title>
                          <media:description>
In Nizhny Novgorod region, a very specific type of robber has appeared who robs stores not for profit but also puts on a show at the crime scene. One such incident occurred in the village of Buturino on April Fool's Day and turned out to be no joke. On that Saturday, an unknown man burst into an alcohol market on Lenin Street. Like in an action movie, the perpetrator instantly found himself at the cash register and began threatening a strong-looking man standing at his workplace with a knife. The store employee did not resist and obediently took out money from the cash register. At that moment, other employees and customers were in the store, but none of them dared to stop the armed man. As soon as the attacker went outside, the frightened seller called the police.

The police arrived at the scene and detained the perpetrator who did not try to hide. After committing the crime, he went out into the street, threw away the money and stayed to wait for the police. While talking to the police, the man admitted that he had decided to commit a crime because he wanted to go to jail.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>robber,store,profit,show,crime,Buturino,April Fool's Day,joke,alcohol market,Lenin Street,action movie,cash register,knife,money,employees,customers,police,perpetrator,jail</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Nizhny Novgorod</media:city>
                          <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>ODD</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Sat, 1 Apr 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>1937</guid>
                          <pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2023 11:06:30 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/1937.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/1937.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Woman with machete attacks car in Vladivostok!</media:title>
                          <media:description>On Wednesday, April 5th, 2023, residents of Vladivostok, Russia witnessed a shocking scene. An unknown woman with a large machete attacked cars on the streets near the waste incineration plant. The woman aggressively shouted as she struck one of the cars with her machete. It is unclear what provoked her to commit this strange act.

Later, the police found the woman who had attacked the car with a machete the previous evening. According to her, she was provoked by others to commit this act.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>Vladivostok,Russia,woman,machete,attack,car,unknown,large,streets,waste,incineration,plant,aggressively,shouted,struck,police</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Vladivostok</media:city>
                          <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Wed, 5 Apr 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>1931</guid>
                          <pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 18:21:46 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear2.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/1931.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear2.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/1931.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Two elderly women caught in snow avalanche in Kuzbass, Russia - miraculously uninjured</media:title>
                          <media:description>In a shocking incident that occurred on February 24th, 2023, two elderly women in the city of Taiga, located in Kuzbass, Russia, found themselves caught in the midst of a snowstorm. However, by a stroke of luck, both women managed to escape unharmed.

The incident took place on Savinova street as the two women were calmly walking along the road. Suddenly, a snow avalanche descended from the roof of a nearby building, knocking them off their feet. The entire incident was caught on a video surveillance camera.

Judging by the footage, the victims had noticed the snowstorm coming towards them. However, they were unable to move out of the way, and were consequently buried in the snow. Fortunately, passersby came to their rescue. In the video, it can be seen that a man and a woman rushed to their aid and helped them up.

Following the incident, the Kuzbass prosecutor's office launched an investigation into the matter. The supervisory agency will examine the compliance of the building owner with the legislation on improving the area, and assess their actions in clearing the roof of snow and ice on time.

The two elderly women, who were 73 and 76 years old, were lucky to have escaped with just a fright. The incident serves as a reminder of the importance of timely snow removal from rooftops during winter months, especially in areas with heavy snowfall.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>snowstorm,Kuzbass,Russia,surveillance camera,elderly women,avalanche,passersby,investigation,snow removal,kindness</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Kuzbass</media:city>
                          <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>undefined</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>undefined</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>1777</guid>
                          <pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 18:21:46 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/1777.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/1777.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>18 Fishermen Rescued After Being Carried Away on Ice Floe in Sakhalin, Russia</media:title>
                          <media:description>On March 5, 2023, a group of 18 fishermen were carried away on an ice floe off the coast of Sakhalin, Russia. The incident occurred as almost two dozen fishermen were capturing fish along the coast from the village of Starodubskoye to Vzmorye, and the ice broke suddenly.

As soon as the authorities were informed, the Main Directorate of the Ministry of Emergency Situations for the Sakhalin Region took immediate action. The GIMS, doctors, and law enforcement agencies quickly moved to the scene, and rescuers left the regional center to assist the fishermen.

After some time, the 18 fishermen were successfully removed from the torn-off ice floe, and they were reunited with their families. This was a significant relief to both the authorities and the fishermen's loved ones, who were no doubt anxious and worried during the ordeal.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>Sakhalin,Russia,fishermen,ice floe,emergency,rescue,safety,caution,winter,conditions</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Sakhalin</media:city>
                          <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>undefined</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>undefined</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Sun, 5 Mar 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>1682</guid>
                          <pubDate>Invalid Date</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1682.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1682.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Massive explosion at metal plant during night shift in Zlatoust, Russia </media:title>
                          <media:description>On March 9th, 2023, a massive explosion occurred at a metal plant in Zlatoust, Russia during the night shift. According to eyewitness accounts, the incident took place in the second electric arc furnace shop of the metal plant while loading a charge consisting of metal pipes.

Fortunately, no one was injured in the explosion, although the metal pipes were scattered for tens of meters. One of the pipes even reached the overhead crane, which is located more than 10 meters high. Witnesses suggest that the cause of the explosion may have been the remnants of ice and snow that had gotten into the charge.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>Zlatoust,Russia,metal plant,explosion,shavings,witnesses,night shift,safety,incident,investigation</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Zlatoust</media:city>
                          <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>undefined</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>undefined</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Thu, 9 Mar 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>1753</guid>
                          <pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 18:21:46 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/1753.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/1753.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>MiG-31 military aircraft crashes in Murmansk region: fate of crew and causes of accident unknown</media:title>
                          <media:description>In a tragic incident that occurred on April 26th, 2023, a MiG-31 military aircraft crashed in Monchegorsk, a town in the Murmansk region of Russia. The fate of the crew and the causes of the accident are still unknown, but according to unconfirmed reports, the plane fell into a lake near the village of Rizh-Guba, and the pilots ejected.

The MiG-31 is a Soviet-era supersonic high-altitude all-weather long-range fighter-interceptor, designed to destroy air targets in the border and inland areas of the country. Developed at OKB-155 based on the MiG-25 in the 1970s, the MiG-31 has been in service with the Russian Air Force since the early 1980s.

According to witnesses, the fighter caught fire in the air and then began to fall. A video of the incident shows the aircraft spiraling out of control before crashing into the lake. Rescue teams rushed to the scene immediately after the incident, but the search for the crew and the wreckage of the aircraft was hindered by the difficult weather conditions and the remote location of the crash site.

The MiG-31 has been involved in several accidents in the past, and the Russian Air Force has been criticized for its aging fleet of military aircraft. However, the cause of this latest incident is yet to be determined.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>military,aircraft,crash,Russia,MiG-31,tragedy,Murmansk,pilots,investigation,supersonic,interceptor,border,all-weather,long-range,fire,rescue,remote,aging,fleet,aviation</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Monchegorsk</media:city>
                          <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>1957</guid>
                          <pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 18:57:11 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/1957.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/1957.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Man falls from 19th floor and survives with minor injuries</media:title>
                          <media:description>A man fell from the 19th floor of a building in Voronezh, Russia and survived with minor injuries. The incident occurred on April 3rd on Kolesnichenko Street when a man born in 1982 fell onto the roof of a Nissan X-Trail SUV. He was hospitalized with head and spinal injuries.

The man reportedly suffered only minor injuries despite falling from such a height. According to doctors at the Voronezh hospital where he was treated, patients who suffer such falls usually go home immediately. The man had a mild skull-brain injury and one small bone fracture. However, doctors decided to keep him in the hospital “because such blows do not pass without a trace.”

After being rescued by firefighters, the man even began singing a song.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>Voronezh,19th floor,minor injuries,Nissan X-Trail SUV,head injury,spinal injury,hospital,man,fail</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Voronezh</media:city>
                          <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>undefined</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>undefined</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Mon, 3 Apr 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>1790</guid>
                          <pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 18:21:46 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/1790.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/1790.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Drunken Man Opens Fire from Apartment Window in Vyatskiye Polyany, Russia</media:title>
                          <media:description>In the city of Vyatskiye Polyany, located in the Kirov region of Russia, an alarming incident occurred on the 15th of March, 2023. A 47-year-old man by the name of Alexander Alyoshin opened fire from his apartment window, while under the influence of alcohol.

According to eyewitnesses, the man was armed with two shotguns and appeared to be heavily intoxicated. It is reported that Alyoshin had not consumed any alcohol for the past 16 years, however, on this fateful day, he decided to drink and got untied. Unfortunately, his body reacted inadequately to the alcohol, resulting in the dangerous and potentially fatal decision to fire his weapons from his apartment window.

Fortunately, there were no other people present in the apartment, and the police quickly arrived on the scene, cordoning off the surrounding area to prevent any further harm. Although the situation was tense, the police were able to arrest Alyoshin without any injuries or casualties.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>Vyatskiye Polyany,Kirov region,Drunken Man,Fire,Apartment Window,Shotguns,Arrest,Police,Alcohol</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Vyatskiye Polyany</media:city>
                          <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>undefined</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>undefined</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>1705</guid>
                          <pubDate>Invalid Date</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1705.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1705.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Devastating Hurricane in Norilsk: Roofs of Houses Torn Off During Bad Weather</media:title>
                          <media:description>On March 16th and 17th, 2023, the city of Norilsk in Russia experienced severe weather conditions that resulted in the roofs of several apartment buildings being damaged. The hurricane wind was so strong that it caused significant damage to the buildings, leaving residents in shock and disbelief.

In response to the damage, the prosecutor's office organized an inspection to assess the extent of the damage and ensure that the necessary measures were taken to address the situation. </media:description>
                          <media:keywords>Norilsk,Russia,hurricane,wind,roofs,apartment buildings,damage,prosecutor's office,inspection,emergency services</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Norilsk</media:city>
                          <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>undefined</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>undefined</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>1729</guid>
                          <pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2023 11:06:30 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1729.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1729.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Man wanted for letting boa constrictor crawl in a subway in St. Petersburg</media:title>
                          <media:description>In a shocking incident on 12th April, 2023 in St. Petersburg, a young man has been caught on video letting a boa constrictor crawl in a subway. The reptile was seen slithering in the subway, causing alarm among the passengers.

Authorities are now searching for the man responsible for bringing the wild animal onto the subway. The imperial boa constrictor is a protected species, listed in Appendix II of the Convention on International Trade in Endangered Species of Wild Flora and Fauna.

Moreover, it is prohibited to keep this species as a pet. The man's actions have sparked outrage and concern for the safety of both the animal and the public.

Boa constrictors are powerful snakes that can grow up to 13 feet in length and weigh over 100 pounds. They are known to be non-venomous but can still pose a danger to humans, especially when provoked.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>st. petersburg,subway,snake,manhunt,endangered,species,protection,illegal,pet,danger,public,safety,regulation,enforcement,video,viral,socialmedia,outcry,search,responsibility</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Saint Petersburg</media:city>
                          <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>undefined</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>undefined</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>1873</guid>
                          <pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 18:21:46 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/1873.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/1873.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Inadequate man kicks Karaganda resident down escalator, identified and placed in psycho-neurological dispensary</media:title>
                          <media:description>A 25-year-old resident of Karaganda, Kazakhstan, was subjected to an unprovoked attack while descending an escalator in a shopping center on April 18th, 2023. The victim was kicked in the back by a 31-year-old man who was reportedly in an inadequate state.

According to police the victim was sent flying down the stairs and suffered bodily harm as a result. The police were alerted to the incident and subsequently registered a criminal case under Article 293 of Part 1 of the Criminal Code of the Republic of Kazakhstan, which pertains to hooliganism.

The perpetrator was identified by the police and placed in a psycho-neurological dispensary due to his alleged inadequate condition at the time of the attack. The Karaganda Region Police Department issued a statement on the matter, confirming the status of the case.

It is unclear what motivated the attacker to commit such a violent act.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>karaganda,kazakhstan,shopping center,attack,victim,escalator,hooliganism,criminal case,police,inadequate,psycho-neurological,dispensary,bodily harm,perpetrator,violence,law enforcement,justice,community,trauma,mental health</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Karaganda</media:city>
                          <media:country>Kazakhstan</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>KZ</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Tue, 18 Apr 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>1929</guid>
                          <pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 18:21:46 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear2.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/1929.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear2.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/1929.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Cargo ship carrying Alumina sinks off Sakhalin coast despite repair efforts</media:title>
                          <media:description>A cargo ship carrying alumina has sunk off the coast of Sakhalin, Russia. The ship had encountered 10-point ice and gave a distress signal on February 23. The 21 crew members, all Chinese citizens, were forced to abandon ship and went onto the ice before being rescued by another vessel.

Specialists were deployed to the site to repair the hole in the ship's hull and stop other leaks. However, despite their best efforts over several days, the ship continued to take on water and eventually sank on the morning of March 1, 2023. The vessel now lies at a depth of 253 meters.

Alumina is a crucial material used in the production of aluminum. The cargo aboard the sunken ship is estimated to be worth several million dollars. The environmental impact of the incident remains unclear, as it is not yet known if any of the cargo has spilled into the sea.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>cargo ship,alumina,Sakhalin,sinking,distress signal,Chinese crew,Arctic,extreme weather,ice,hole,repair,leakage,investigation,environmental impact,shipping,Northern Sea Route,risks,remote environment,salvage operation,maritime accident</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Sakhalin</media:city>
                          <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>undefined</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>undefined</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Wed, 1 Mar 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>1887</guid>
                          <pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 18:21:46 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/1887.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/1887.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Garbage truck causes collision with car and endangers passengers!</media:title>
                          <media:description>In a shocking incident in Tomsk, a garbage truck without a driver crashed into a passenger car, putting the occupants in danger. The incident occurred on April 9, 2023, when the driver of the truck left the cab without taking the necessary measures to keep the vehicle from moving.

Several onlookers can be seen running toward the accident site to check whether the people in the car are safe. A woman and a child were in the passenger car at the time of the accident. The woman was not injured, the child received one-time medical assistance

According to eyewitnesses, the garbage truck moved in reverse, slamming into the car and causing significant damage. The incident highlights the importance of ensuring that vehicles are properly secured before leaving them unattended.

The local authorities have launched an investigation into the incident to determine the cause of the accident and to identify any potential safety lapses</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>garbage,truck,unmanned,accident,car,passengers,danger,onlookers,safety,measures,driver,cab,moving,reverse,damage,investigation,public,debate,renewed,importance.</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Tomsk</media:city>
                          <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>undefined</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>undefined</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Sun, 9 Apr 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>1856</guid>
                          <pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2023 11:06:30 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/1856.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/1856.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Car overturns at intersection in Volgograd due to sudden swerve, lack of road markings</media:title>
                          <media:description>In Volgograd, Russia, an unfortunate incident occurred on April 30th, 2023, at the intersection of Rokossovsky Street and Zhukov Avenue. A Volkswagen Polo overturned, injuring the driver's hand. The incident happened on a section of the road where repairs are underway, and a safety island has been allocated. However, there were no signs or markings indicating an obstacle.

Eyewitnesses reported that the car in front of the Volkswagen Polo swerved suddenly, causing the driver to lose control and land on the roof of the car. Fortunately, the driver survived the accident, but the incident has raised concerns among Volgograd residents about the lack of road markings and signage in the area.

The Main Directorate of the Ministry of Internal Affairs for the Volgograd Region is currently investigating the incident. However, locals who came to the aid of the injured driver are worried that similar incidents could happen again if the necessary road markings and signage are not installed promptly.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>volgograd,russia,accident,overturned,car,swerve,driver,injury,hand,road,repairs,safety,island,markings,signage,warning,authorities,investigation,eyewitnesses,locals</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Volgograd</media:city>
                          <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>1991</guid>
                          <pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 11:27:14 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/1991.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/1991.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Explosion in Belgorod: shocking footage of Su-34 bomber ammo mishap on street intersection!</media:title>
                          <media:description>On April 20, 2023, residents of Belgorod, Russia were caught off guard by a sudden and violent explosion that rocked the intersection of Gubkin and Vatutin streets. 

The video begins with a bomb plummeting onto the road, followed by a massive blast that sends debris and earth soaring several meters into the air. It is reported that the explosion was triggered by an "unscheduled ammunition release" from a Su-34 bomber, as confirmed by the Ministry of Defense. The force of the blast was so intense that it propelled a parked car into the air, slamming it onto the roof of a nearby building.

Three people were injured, and several vehicles were damaged. The blast shattered windows in multiple nearby high-rise buildings, sending shards of glass raining down on the streets.

Authorities quickly responded to the incident, cordoning off the area and launching an investigation into the cause of the mishap. The incident left residents of Belgorod shaken and in disbelief, as the video footage circulated widely on social media, capturing the sheer force and destructive power of the explosion.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>Explosion,Belgorod,Russia,Su-34,Bomber,Ammo,Mishap,Street,Intersection,Video,Footage,Shocking,Chaos,Damage,Injuries,Investigation,Safety,Security,Protocol,Recovery</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Belgorod</media:city>
                          <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>undefined</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>undefined</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>1925</guid>
                          <pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 18:21:46 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/1925.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/1925.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Scientists trapped in a powerful ash and rock fall on Kamchatka expedition to study active volcano</media:title>
                          <media:description>On April 11th, 2023, a group of six scientists found themselves trapped in a powerful ash and rock fall while on an expedition to study the active volcano Bezimyanny on Kamchatka, Russia. The scientists had set out to conduct a survey of the volcano's activity and perform aerial photography. The video of this incident was filmed by Petr Krinkin.

Bezimyanny had been actively erupting since the end of March, with lava flowing from its crater and ash clouds billowing into the air. The edges of the crater were also prone to collapse. Despite these warning signs, the group of scientists departed from the Apakhonchich base station on April 7th to reach Ambon Rock, which was relatively close to the volcano. Their plan was to collect samples and install gas analyzers and mobile stations.

As the group approached the volcano, a sudden ash and rock fall occurred, trapping them in their location. The scientists were not able to move due to the heavy ash fall and the danger of further rockslides. They immediately contacted the authorities for help, but due to the remote location, rescue efforts were hindered.

The scientists were able to establish a communication line and update the rescue team on their situation. However, the rescue team was unable to reach them until the following day due to the harsh weather conditions and the difficult terrain. The scientists were equipped with survival gear and managed to keep themselves warm and sheltered through the night.

When the rescue team arrived, they were able to safely evacuate the scientists. Although the group had suffered minor injuries, they were all in stable condition and received medical attention.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>Scientists,Kamchatka,Russia,volcano,expedition,ash,rock fall,Bezimyanny,eruption,lava,ash clouds,collapse,Ambon Rock,gas analyzers,mobile stations,rescue,safety protocols,Shiveluch,risks,research</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Kamchatka</media:city>
                          <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>undefined</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>undefined</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>1872</guid>
                          <pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 18:21:46 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/1872.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/1872.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Skateboarding wipeout: man falls on steep rail but gets back up</media:title>
                          <media:description>Skateboarding is an exciting and thrilling sport that requires balance, skill, and courage. Skaters often perform daring stunts and tricks that require precision and practice. However, even the most experienced skaters can have a wipeout every now and then, as evidenced by a recent video captured by @rays__hell in Warm Springs, Oregon, USA on 18th of April, 2023.

The video shows a man attempting to skateboard down a steep and elevated rail surface. As he gained momentum, he lost his balance and fell flat on his stomach. The impact of the fall is jarring, although the man was not wearing protective gear, he was able to get up and walk away unharmed.

Despite the wipeout, the skater quickly regained his composure and got back on his board to continue skating. This resilience and determination are characteristic of many skaters, who often face falls and injuries in their pursuit of the sport.

Skateboarding is not just a sport, but a culture and community that has grown in popularity over the years. From the early days of skateboarding in California in the 1960s to the modern-day X Games and skate parks, the sport has evolved and become more mainstream.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>skateboarding,wipeout,resilience,determination,sport,community,culture,safety,injury,prevention,helmets,pads,wristguards,designated areas,skate parks,stunts,tricks,passion,dedication,thrill</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Warm Springs, Oregon</media:city>
                          <media:country>United States</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>US</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Tue, 18 Apr 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>1976</guid>
                          <pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 09:45:34 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/1976.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/1976.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Surviving a crevasse fall: a mountain dweller's tale of calm and preparedness</media:title>
                          <media:description>In the world of mountain sports, there is always an element of danger that comes with the thrill of adventure. It's the reason why people love skiing, snowboarding, mountain biking, hiking, climbing, and other outdoor activities. But as much as we prepare and try to be safe, accidents can still happen. One such incident occurred in La Grave/Meije, France, on April 26, 2022, when a group of mountain dwellers called the Powtos experienced a close call with a crevasse according to a video clip captured by @lespowtos.

The Powtos are a group of outdoor enthusiasts based in Grenoble, France, who love mountain biking, hiking, climbing, skiing, and other outdoor activities. On the day of the incident, they were doing a lot of descents and having a great time. However, things took a turn for the worse when one of their friends got caught in a crevasse at the last moment and fell in.

The group of friends had a lot of experience and were well-prepared for such situations. They all had the necessary equipment, including a probe, shovel, ARVA (an avalanche transceiver), harness, ice screw, and ice axes. The fall was about 15 meters, but thankfully their friend was able to stop before hitting a large boulder.

The group was a bit lower than their friend, so it took them about 15-20 minutes to reach him. During this time, they were all worried about his condition and unsure of what had happened. But they quickly sprang into action, using their skills and equipment to secure the area and bring their friend to safety.

Their friend, despite the fall, remained calm and composed. He was able to put on his crampons and slowly make his way out of the crevasse. The group joined him and secured the exit with a rope before helping him climb out. Credit to: @lespowtos</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>powtos,mountain,biking,hiking,climbing,skiing,crevasse,safety,preparedness,equipment,adventure,experience,composure,rescue,rope,ice,avalanche,transceiver,adrenaline,teamwork</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Grenoble</media:city>
                          <media:country>France</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>FR</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2022</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>1946</guid>
                          <pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 18:21:46 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/1946.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/1946.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Motorcyclist knocked down by horse during holiday celebration in Dagestan</media:title>
                          <media:description>A festive day turned into a nightmare for a motorcyclist who was hit by a horse rider in the village of Khuchada, Dagestan, Russia. The incident happened on April 24th, 2023, during the celebration of the first furrow “Ots Bai”, a traditional holiday that marks the beginning of spring and agricultural work.

According to eyewitnesses, the motorcyclist was standing across the road behind a crowd of people who were watching the parade of horses and riders. At that moment, three riders were moving in their direction at high speed. One of them did not notice the motorcyclist and crashed into him.

The motorcyclist fell into the mud after the collision, and the rider hit the fence and flew out of the saddle. The video shows the shocked reactions of the spectators and the other riders who stopped to help.

It is not clear whether anyone was injured as a result of the incident. The local authorities have not commented on the situation yet.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>horse,motorcyclist,holiday,celebration,accident,video,Dagestan,Russia,Khuchada,riders,collision,mud,fence,injured,Kuzbass,Audi,passengers,comma,sequence</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Dagestan</media:city>
                          <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>1945</guid>
                          <pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 18:21:46 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/1945.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/1945.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Russian freight train derails after explosive device detonates on rail tracks in Bryansk region, Russia</media:title>
                          <media:description>A freight train in the western region of Bryansk in Russia derailed on Monday, the 1st of May, 2023 after an "explosive device" detonated on the rail tracks, according to local governor Alexander Bogomaz. The incident occurred just one day after a Ukrainian strike killed four people in a Russian village in the Bryansk region, and as Kyiv prepared for a widely expected counter-offensive.

Bogomaz confirmed that there were no casualties, but the device went off "on the 136th kilometer" of the railroad between regional hub Bryansk and the town of Unecha, towards the border with Ukraine. Russian Railways stated that the front locomotive and seven wagons derailed "after the intervention of unauthorized persons." The company also said that the fire had been put out by 12.30 pm local time and that passengers of two Moscow-bound trains in the area would be taken by bus to the regional capital Bryansk.

Footage on social media showed the front of the train and several cargo carriages on fire and lying on the grass next to the tracks. There have been reports of sabotage acts on railroads in Russia and its ally Belarus throughout Moscow's more than year-long Ukraine offensive.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>russian,freight train,derailment,explosive,device,ukraine,border,strike,casualties,sabotage,railroads,belarus,offensive,social media,instability,negotiations,transportation,vulnerability,safety,security</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Bryansk region </media:city>
                          <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Mon, 1 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>1970</guid>
                          <pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 18:21:46 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/1970.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/1970.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Russian shoplifter gets kicked out by store clerk: caught on camera</media:title>
                          <media:description>A video surfaced on March 26th, 2023, of an unusual incident that occurred in Naberezhnye Chelny, Russia. A man attempted to steal a bottle of alcohol from a liquor store, but his actions quickly caught up with him. The store clerk noticed the theft and approached the man, kicking him in the backside before he could make his escape.

The entire incident was caught on a surveillance camera, and the video quickly went viral on social media.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>Russia,Shoplifter,Liquor Store,Caught on Camera,Surveillance,Video,Viral,Social Media,Theft,Consequences,Naberezhnye Chelni,Incident,Kicked Out,Alcohol,Clerk,Controversy,Swift Kick,Attempted Theft,Consequences,Actions</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Naberezhnye Chelny</media:city>
                          <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>undefined</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>undefined</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Sun, 26 Mar 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>1821</guid>
                          <pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2023 11:06:30 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/1821.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/1821.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Powerful earthquake strikes Kamchatka, Russia: home security camera captures chaos</media:title>
                          <media:description>On April 3rd, 2023, a powerful earthquake with a magnitude of 6.9 struck Kamchatka, Russia, causing widespread chaos and panic throughout the region. The earthquake was felt most strongly in the city of Petropavlovsk-Kamchatsky, where people have been sharing photos and videos on social media in the aftermath of the quake.

One such video was captured by a home security camera in a private residence, which shows the violent shaking and destruction caused by the earthquake. Furniture can be seen swaying and falling, while objects are sent flying across the room. A poor cat can be seen frantically trying to navigate its way through the chaos.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>earthquake,Kamchatka,Russia,magnitude,Petropavlovsk-Kamchatsky,damage,aftershocks,epicenter,seismic,instability</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Petropavlovsk-Kamchatsky</media:city>
                          <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>undefined</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>undefined</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Mon, 3 Apr 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>1784</guid>
                          <pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 18:21:46 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/1784.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/1784.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Scooter crash at Bali restaraunt: guy escapes with minor injuries</media:title>
                          <media:description>A guy on a scooter lost control and crashed into a local café in Bali, Indonesia on February 16, 2017. The incident left behind a trail of destruction as the scooter smashed into tables and chairs, causing a commotion in the area. Fortunately, no one was hurt, as the calmly sitting visitors managed to avoid the out-of-control scooter. The rider was lucky to escape with only minor injuries.

Eyewitnesses stated that the incident happened suddenly and that the rider had no control over the scooter. The café staff and visitors were quick to react and helped the rider, who was dazed after the accident</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>Bali,Indonesia,scooter accident,local cafe,minor injuries,escaped,lost control,tables,chairs,visitors</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Bali</media:city>
                          <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>undefined</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>undefined</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2017</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>1780</guid>
                          <pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2023 09:56:51 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/1780.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/1780.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Massive Dome Collapse in Ufa, Russia Due to Strong Winds During Construction</media:title>
                          <media:description>On March 13, 2023, strong winds caused the dome of a mosque under construction in Ufa, Russia, to fall, damaging the scaffolding. The main department of the Ministry of Emergency Situations for the Republic of Bashkortostan confirmed the incident, reporting that the building's integrity was not violated, and there were no casualties.

The cause of the incident is still under investigation, and it is not clear what specific factors contributed to the dome's collapse. However, it is known that the mosque in Ufa has been under construction for over a decade, and the height of the structure is supposed to reach 77 meters upon completion.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>Ufa,Russia,strong winds,mosque,construction,dome,scaffolding,Ministry of Emergency Situations,investigation,completion</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Ufa</media:city>
                          <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>undefined</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>undefined</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>1689</guid>
                          <pubDate>Invalid Date</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1689.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1689.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>A young woman saves a 7-year-old boy who has fallen through ice in Russia</media:title>
                          <media:description>On February 16, 2023, a young woman named Leyla Abdulazimova became a hero in Perm Krai, Russia. The 28-year-old realtor was on her way to pick up her car when she saw something lying on the snow-covered ice of a river. At first, she didn't realize it was a child, but then she heard his cries and knew she had to act fast.

The child in question was a 7-year-old boy who had fallen through the ice while walking home from school with a classmate and her mother. The children had been playing and running ahead, and at some point, the situation got out of control. The girl's mother, who was pregnant, saw what was happening but was unable to rush onto the ice herself because of her condition. Instead, she stopped passing cars in a panic, hoping someone would be able to help.

Luckily, Leyla was in one of those passing cars. When she saw the boy in the river, she asked her driver to stop and got out of the car. A man ran up to her, and she asked him how much he weighed, knowing that the ice was fragile and could break at any moment. Then she suggested that he hold her legs while she crawled out onto the ice. The plan worked, and Leyla was able to reach the boy and pull him to safety.

The boy was quite wet, up to his shoulders, but Leyla and the others who helped him were able to get him into a car and take him home. His father was waiting for him there, and they were able to warm him up quickly with hot tea and a change of clothes. The boy didn't even get sick, much to the relief of his worried mother.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>hero,rescue,ice,river,child,danger,bravery,Russia,quick,fragile,school</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Perm Krai</media:city>
                          <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>undefined</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>undefined</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>1641</guid>
                          <pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 18:21:46 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1641.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1641.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>An animal trainer was attacked by a lion during a circus performance in Russia</media:title>
                          <media:description>African lions, the stars of a New Year's program called "Star Cruise" at the Sochi circus in Russia, turned violent during a performance on January 4, 2023. The incident was captured on video and has since been circulating online. The couple, Alexei Makarenko and Olga Borisova, were taming the lions when the animals refused to obey and began to destroy the props.

At one point during the performance, one of the predators approached Alexei from behind, jumped up, and bit him. The trainer fell from the attack, and Olga quickly ran to help him. She drove the animal away and helped the victim get up.

After the incident, the lions were quickly herded into an enclosure. Alexei was rushed to a medical facility, where he received treatment for the numerous bite and claw marks left on his back by the predator.

It is believed that two young lions were on stage during the performance and got into a conflict. When the tamers tried to calm the animals down, one of them attacked the man. The reason for the attack is still unknown, but it has been speculated that it was due to stress caused by the performance or a territorial dispute between the animals.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>Trainer,Lion,Attack,Circus,Performance,Russia,African Lions,Star Cruise,Taming,Animals,Pet,Trained</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Sochi</media:city>
                          <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>undefined</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>undefined</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Wed, 4 Jan 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>1612</guid>
                          <pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 18:21:46 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1612.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1612.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>A drunk driver crashed into a convenience store in Russia.</media:title>
                          <media:description>On the 15th day of January, the city police began investigating the collision that occurred in Ryazan when a Chevrolet Lacetti lost control and crashed into a convenience store. According to sources, the car was driven by a 36-year-old citizen who was positively drunk. and the man who was in the store at the time of the accident was injured and sought medical attention. The shop has suffered serious damage. The car crashed through the trading floor, overturning merchandise racks and shattering shop windows.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>car,drunk,driver,crashed,convenience store,police,Chevrolet,damage,injured</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Ryazan</media:city>
                          <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>undefined</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>undefined</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>1518</guid>
                          <pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 18:21:46 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1518.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1518.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>The explosion and collapse occurred as a result of a fire in the shopping center "Mega Khimki"</media:title>
                          <media:description>The explosion and collapse occurred in the Obi hypermarket in the Mega Khimki shopping center in the Moscow region.

The fire was reported to rescuers on the morning of Friday, December 9. At 07:05, the fire was assigned the fourth number of difficulty out of five.

According to the Ministry of Emergency Situations, the fire area was 7,000 square meters.

Video with explosions in the shopping center - in emergency services they explain with cans of paint and aerosols. The Ministry of Emergency Situations told about one deceased - a security guard of a hypermarket.

The cause of the fire is said to be welding work in the annex of the OBI hypermarket, which was carried out in violation of safety rules.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>explosion,russia,moscow,fire,hypermarket,accident</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Moscow</media:city>
                          <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>undefined</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>undefined</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Invalid date</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>1381</guid>
                          <pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2022 14:51:04 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1381.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1381.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Skiers miraculously escaped after an avalanche in Sheregesh</media:title>
                          <media:description>Two skiers were covered by a snow avalanche at the Sheregesh resort in the Kemerovo region. One man fell asleep so much that he simply could not get out of the "white captivity" on his own. Fortunately, a friend came to his aid in time.

The footage shows how extreme people ride on the mountain slopes and soon one of them is covered with an avalanche. The man remains under the rubble until his comrade saves him: raking the snow with his hands, he pulled out his friend in trouble in a matter of seconds. Well, when everything ended safely, the man began to thank the savior.

Skier Sergei Filippov said that at the time of the incident he really experienced a strong panic.

The man said that before the incident, he met local guys on the descent, who are very good at skiing. They took a ride together, and then one of Filippov's new acquaintances suggested that he go to another place where no one had been before. Moreover, the skier initially noticed that on this descent "small avalanches were cut."

“Well, that’s how it happened. Yes, the panic is very strong. And a very strong push, that is, it has so much strength, this avalanche. It was really scary,” Sergey said.

Credit to: Filippov Sergey</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>ski,Skiers,avalanche,Sheregesh,russia,snow,winter,ski resort,incident</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Kemerovo region</media:city>
                          <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>undefined</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>undefined</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Invalid date</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>1449</guid>
                          <pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 12:41:15 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1449.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1449.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>The girl fell into the ditch upside down!</media:title>
                          <media:description>The incident was recorded by the CCTV of a resident's house, which showed the street area. A woman wearing a blue shirt, riding her automatic motorcycle, stops slowly at a red light. Suddenly, the woman fell to the side without being touched or hit by another vehicle. Sadly, the woman fell upside down into a ditch on the side of the road. The woman is fine.

Credit to: @johansuhandri</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>Incident. fall,ditch,girl,CCTV,motorcycle,upside down,house,Indonesia</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Jakarta</media:city>
                          <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>undefined</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>undefined</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Sun, 14 Aug 2022</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>1450</guid>
                          <pubDate>Invalid Date</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1450.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1450.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>The woman spent more than a day in a trap between the wall and the closet.</media:title>
                          <media:description>Rescuers helped a resident of Troitsk get out from under the rubble in her own house. The woman was crushed by a closet, and in this position she spent more than a day. The alarm was sounded by her colleagues when she did not come to work.

Worried colleagues went to her house and saw a shocking picture there: the house of a neat and disciplined woman was literally crammed with a pile of various rubbish. It turned out to be so much that they could not find the mistress among the large dump and called rescuers.

As a result, specialists evacuated the victim, she showed signs of severe hypothermia and prolonged circulatory disorders in the limbs. The woman was taken to the hospital. Now the patient is under the supervision of doctors in the hospital.

Credit to: Search and Rescue Service of the Chelyabinsk Region</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>incident,woman,incident,trap,rescue</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Troitsk </media:city>
                          <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>undefined</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>undefined</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Invalid date</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>1405</guid>
                          <pubDate>Invalid Date</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1405.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1405.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>The girl saved the schoolboy, who nearly fell under the wheels of the bus</media:title>
                          <media:description>It all happened on the morning of December 8 at a pedestrian crossing near the house number 36 on Avanesov Street. A townswoman was crossing the road and, approaching the sidewalk, a schoolboy ran out to meet her at the pedestrian crossing. The girl grabbed the child and thereby saved him from the bus, which rushed along the second lane.

The girl's name is Yana. The girl told what she experienced at the moment when she saved the life of this boy.

“I was late for school. At the time when I was crossing the road, the bus was moving slowly, but when I walked a little further, I saw that it was picking up speed. Then I saw a boy who ran from the square. There was a car, because of which it was not visible. I was afraid that the bus driver might simply not see him, because the boy was short, he looked about seven or eight years old. When he ran past me, I grabbed him. I was very scared for him, I didn’t say anything to the boy, I was just shocked by this incident, ”she said.

A few days after the incident, the traffic police awarded the girl for her act.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>accident,russia,schoolboy,children,safety,girl,road,car,bus driver,pedestrian,lucky</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Barnaul</media:city>
                          <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>undefined</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>undefined</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Invalid date</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>1411</guid>
                          <pubDate>Invalid Date</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1411.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1411.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Semeru volcano erupts on East Java, Indonesia caught by CCTV</media:title>
                          <media:description>Highest volcano, Mount Semeru, spewed a column of volcanic ash into the air in a dramatic eruption on Sunday, December 4. Indonesia raises an alert, prompting evacuations of nearby residents.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>volcano,eruption,indonesia,East Java,Semeru</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>East Java</media:city>
                          <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>undefined</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>undefined</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Invalid date</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>1362</guid>
                          <pubDate>Invalid Date</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1362.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1362.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>A man beat a woman because of a parking space in the center of Tula</media:title>
                          <media:description>In the video, a person, most likely waiting for someone, stands on the roadway and does not allow anyone to park. One woman still managed to put the car in a free place. The man did not like it, and he decided to figure it out - he went up to the motorist and tore off her hat. She responded with a blow, and the attacker was also left without a headdress.

The girl tried to defend herself from the blows of an adult large man, but he hit her head on the roof of the car. And all this happened in front of the child who was sitting in the car.

A passer-by intervened and dragged the man aside. Now the victim is in the hospital in the neurosurgical department. Immediately after the attack, the woman called the police, from which her offender tried to escape. The assailant is believed to have held a seat for the bailiff. He himself witnessed the massacre of his assistant over the woman after he parked the car in another place.

An administrative case has been initiated on this fact of beatings.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>incident,car,parking,fight,beat,woman,russia,road</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Tula</media:city>
                          <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>undefined</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>undefined</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Invalid date</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>1416</guid>
                          <pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2022 09:31:21 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1416.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1416.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Bike running on road without rider</media:title>
                          <media:description>There was an accident at that time, then the motorbike was out of control and ran by itself, it stopped when it hit a wall. The victim suffered broken bones and abrasions.

Credit to: @chalismahardika</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>Bike,accident,wall,hit,Indonesia,broken,victim,motorbike</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Yogyakarta</media:city>
                          <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>undefined</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>undefined</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Sun, 25 Sep 2022</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>1343</guid>
                          <pubDate>Invalid Date</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1343.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1343.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>The guard doesn't let the student's mother into the school!</media:title>
                          <media:description>14 October 2022, Michurinsk, Russia
The guard was ordered not to let inside the school, due to terrorist acts. But woman still tries to break through, fights with the guard and swears!</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>school,guard,student,mother,swearing,invasion,lesson,learning</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Michurinsk</media:city>
                          <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>undefined</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>undefined</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2022</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>1205</guid>
                          <pubDate>Invalid Date</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/73c70ddf-97a2-487b-8b34-aa0fb8552a51.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/7ce906aa-fcda-4759-aae5-8bc90e686e6b.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Fire and explosions in Moscow in the Mega shopping center </media:title>
                          <media:description>The explosion and collapse occurred in the Obi hypermarket in the Mega Khimki shopping center in the Moscow region. The fire was reported to rescuers on the morning of Friday, December 9. At 07:05, the fire was assigned the fourth number of difficulty out of five. According to the Ministry of Emergency Situations, the fire area was 7,000 square meters. Video with explosions in the shopping center - in emergency services they explain with cans of paint and aerosols. The Ministry of Emergency Situations told about one deceased - a security guard of a hypermarket. The cause of the fire is said to be welding work in the annex of the OBI hypermarket, which was carried out in violation of safety rules.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>accident,explosion,fire,moscow,hypermarket,russia</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Moscow</media:city>
                          <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>undefined</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>undefined</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Invalid date</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>1382</guid>
                          <pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2022 15:05:34 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1382.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1382.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>The train fell off the jack during repairs in Tokyo!</media:title>
                          <media:description>17 November 2022, Tokyo, Japan
At the railway crossing in Tokyo the train derailed near Kisei-takasago station, Katsusika-ku. Workers diligently lifted it back onto the rails, but the train fell off the jack. Luckily no one was hurt! Eventually the train was successfully put back on the line!
Credit to: @beikoku_tanmouand</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>train,accident,repairs,Tokyo,Japan,railway,station,rails</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Tokyo</media:city>
                          <media:country>Japan</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>undefined</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>undefined</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2022</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>1267</guid>
                          <pubDate>Invalid Date</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/8108364a-24e3-4915-a75d-4d94a8cc4768.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/bce41d3a-8b01-4b5d-bcdb-a438565b4f76.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Pensioner tried to beat her neighbor with a piece of plinth because of the noise in the entrance</media:title>
                          <media:description>An elderly woman from St. Petersburg attacked a neighbor with a piece of plinth because of the noise in the entrance. The incident took place in Kupchino.

The pensioner waited for the girl near the entrance of a residential building on Malaya Balkanskaya and tried to hit her with a long object. She accompanied her actions with cries of “you can’t hammer.”

The victim recognized the brawler as a neighbor from below. She explained that her apartment has been empty for months and no one can make noise there.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>Pensioner,incident,woman,attack,neighbor,russia</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Saint Petersburg</media:city>
                          <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>undefined</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>undefined</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Invalid date</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>1421</guid>
                          <pubDate>Invalid Date</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1421.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1421.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>A fight between a buyer and sellers in a Russian store in Samara</media:title>
                          <media:description>The fight took place in a store on Dachnaya Street. Customers claim the man tried to steal food from the store, but was caught. 4 people had a hard time dealing with a potential thief.

People's opinions about the actions of store employees are divided: in social networks, some residents write that some people are already "tired of stealing in supermarkets." Others believe that the sellers had no right to do so.

The police are investigating the circumstances of the incident.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>accident,fight,russia,store,thief,incident</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Samara</media:city>
                          <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>undefined</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>undefined</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Invalid date</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>1397</guid>
                          <pubDate>Invalid Date</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1397.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1397.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                         </channel>
                      </rss>
                    