<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
        <rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
        xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
        xmlns:openSearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearchrss/1.0/"
        xmlns:dfpvideo="http://api.google.com/dfpvideo"
        xmlns:tms="http://data.tmsapi.com/v1.1"
        version="2.0">
          <channel>
            <title>ViralBear videos</title>
            <dfpvideo:version>2</dfpvideo:version>
              
                  <item>
                  <media:title>First-time rider's mishap: girl's scooter adventure ends with a bump!</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a candid video captured by @wkmzxuk_ on July 15, 2023, in the City of Soligorsk, Minsk region, Belarus, a young girl's first-time experience with an electronic scooter took an unexpected turn. With enthusiasm and excitement, she hopped onto the scooter but found herself struggling to control its speed. Unaware of the gears and unfamiliar with braking, she careened toward a stationary sign near a building, unable to halt her momentum. The result was a comical yet cautionary collision, reminding viewers of the importance of learning the basics before embarking on new adventures. While the girl's misadventure might have left her a little shaken, it undoubtedly served as a valuable lesson for both her and others who dare to ride the scooters for the first time.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>scooter,mishap,video,girl,first-time,adventure,excitement,gears,braking,collision,cautionary,comical,lessons,learning,electronic,speed,sign,building,Belarus,Soligorsk</media:keywords>
                  <media:city> City of Soligorsk, Minsk region</media:city>
                  <media:country>Belarus</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>BY</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Fails and Funnies</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2594</guid>
                  <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 10:53:05 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2594.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2594.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Cake mishap: hilarious family moment in Ankara, Turkey</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a heartwarming yet comical family moment captured in Ankara, Turkey, a video shared by @amywinehouzze on July 15, 2023, showcased their little one indulging in a cake while kneeling on a dining chair. The child's innocent delight was infectious as they merrily savored the cake in one hand, but alas, laughter ensued as the sweet treat slipped from their grasp while trying to juggle it with the other hand. Surrounding family members couldn't help but burst into fits of laughter, turning the mishap into an unforgettable memory. This endearing scene reminds us of the simple joys and shared laughter that bring families together, creating cherished moments to be cherished for years to come.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>cake,kid,dining,table,Ankara,Turkey,video,laughter,family,moment,comical,mishap,sweet,treat,delight,memorable,joy,shared,precious,memory</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Ankara</media:city>
                  <media:country>Turkey</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>TR</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Fails and Funnies</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2581</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023 17:45:47 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2581.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2581.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Autonomous appliance anomaly: the mysterious moving fan in Manila!</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a bizarre and comical incident that unfolded on May 17, 2023, in Quezon City, Manila, Philippines, a peculiar electric fan caught the attention of @sindefelt. The fan seemed to have a mind of its own, making spontaneous movements while set to speed 3, prompting the astonished owner to exclaim, "It seems like the newly bought electric fan has its own life, at speed 3 it moves on its own." The situation took a humorous turn as a voice-over in the captured video expressed frustration, declaring, "I don't know what to do with you, I'm having a hard time dealing with you." With the scorching summer heat making speed 1 insufficient, and speed 3 causing the fan to mischievously distance itself from its user, @sindefelt found solace in the middle ground, claiming speed 2 to be the optimal choice. </media:description>
                  <media:keywords>electric,fan,autonomous,movement,speed,comical,incident,video,capture,summer,Manila,Philippines,@sindefelt,quirky,frustration,amusing,mystery,internet,heat,optimal</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Quezon City, Manila</media:city>
                  <media:country>Philippines</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>PH</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Fails and Funnies</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Wed, 17 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2570</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 08:07:33 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2570.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2570.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Spooky encounter on Pasipit Road: terrified drivers mistake chilling figure for a ghost!</media:title>
                  <media:description>On July 15, 2023, a chilling encounter took place in Silang, Cavite, Philippines, when a group of friends driving to Tagaytay found themselves on an unknown road due to a navigation mishap with the Waze app. As they ventured down Pasipit Road, their headlights illuminated a figure by the roadside, sending them into a panic. Screams filled the car as they initially believed they had come across a ghost. However, it turned out to be a guy leisurely relaxing beside the road. The eerie moment, captured on video by @ljculalic_, became a spooky tale for the adventurers, who eventually found their way back on track. </media:description>
                  <media:keywords>silang,cavite,philippines,waze,navigation,lost,pasipit road,ghost,chilling,encounter,tagaytay,headlights,panic,screams,video,@ljculalic_,driving,spooky,laughter,relief</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Silang, Cavite</media:city>
                  <media:country>Philippines</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>PH</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Fails and Funnies</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2567</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 07:54:50 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2567.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2567.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Startling mishap at Bontea milk tea shop: little girl's unfortunate slip and bump</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a distressing incident captured by @nguyntttrang4 on June 11, 2023, at Bontea milk tea shop in Hoan Son, Tien Du, Bac Ninh, Vietnam, a small girl suffered an unfortunate slip and fall. As she was heading out, the little girl lost her footing and bumped her head on the glass door, leaving the seated patrons startled. Despite the impact, the brave child quickly got back on her feet and made her way to her mother, who promptly comforted her as she burst into tears.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>slip,fall,accident,Bontea,milk tea,shop,Hoan Son,Tien Du,Bac Ninh,Vietnam,girl,glass door,mother,crying,startled,patrons,cautious,vigilant,incident,video</media:keywords>
                  <media:city> Hoan Son, Tien Du, Bac Ninh</media:city>
                  <media:country>Vietnam</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>VN</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Fails and Funnies</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2540</guid>
                  <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 15:07:13 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2540.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2540.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Makeup prank turns tears to smiles: a tale of fake eyebrows and sweet relief</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a surprising turn of events during a makeup session on July 10, 2023 in Toronto, Canada, @artisanglow pulled off an eyebrow prank on her unsuspecting client who had come for makeup on her anniversary. Capturing the whole ordeal on video, the client's smile quickly faded into tears as she was appalled by the fake eyebrows. Unaware that it was all just a prank, the client's distress was evident. However, @artisanglow swiftly revealed the truth and corrected the brows, leading to a sigh of relief and a beaming smile from the client.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>anniversary,makeup,prank,client,eyebrows,video,Toronto,Canada,smile,tears,relief,artisanglow,fake,surprise,session,distress,correction,beaming,small,tags</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Toronto </media:city>
                  <media:country>Canada</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>CA</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Fails and Funnies</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2522</guid>
                  <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 20:52:21 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2522.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2522.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Manila mayhem: emotional ball game takes a comical turn as man bowls and falls!</media:title>
                  <media:description>In an amusing incident captured on video in Manila, Philippines, on July 9, 2023, an emotional ball game took an unexpected turn when a man, identified as @itzyoboymigi, fell while bowling. The video shows the man clutching the bowling ball, seemingly ready to throw it, when he lost his balance and tumbled onto his stomach. The hilarious moment quickly spread on social media, garnering plenty of laughs and reactions from netizens worldwide. </media:description>
                  <media:keywords>bawling,manila,philippines,video,falling,comical,emotional,ball game,@itzyoboymigi,laughter,social media,hilarious,unexpected,balance,stomach,netizens,worldwide,ordinary,activities,lighthearted</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Manila </media:city>
                  <media:country>Philippines</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>PH</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Fails and Funnies</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sun, 9 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2520</guid>
                  <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 15:10:30 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2520.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2520.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Joy amidst the rain: a child's playful adventure at Quiapo church</media:title>
                  <media:description>On July 4, 2023, at Quiapo Church in Manila, Philippines, a heartwarming scene unfolded amidst the rain. Captured by @karlalleeen, a video showcased a child joyfully playing with water in the downpour. While others sought shelter under their umbrellas, this carefree youngster found delight in sliding under rails using the rainwater. His infectious happiness served as a reminder of the simple joys in life, even in the midst of adverse weather conditions.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>playful,rain,child,video,water,joy,Quiapo Church,Manila,Philippines,sliding,rails,fun,umbrellas,happiness,carefree,downpour,weather,@karlalleeen,July 4,2023,adventure,delightful</media:keywords>
                  <media:city> Manila</media:city>
                  <media:country>Philippines</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>PH</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Fails and Funnies</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Tue, 4 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2519</guid>
                  <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 07:18:14 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2519.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2519.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Whimsical toy vendor takes flight: a hilarious surprise in Santa Rosa, Laguna!</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a heartwarming and unexpected moment, a toy vendor in Santa Rosa, Laguna, Philippines, captured the attention and laughter of onlookers as he showcased his playful spirit. The vendor was seen passing by, holding a small plane toy aloft with a stick, pretending to soar through the skies as if he were flying the toy himself. The crowd couldn't help but be amused by his delightful antics, and the video shared by @masterbaehub on June 11, 2023, quickly went viral, spreading joy and smiles across social media. Sometimes, the simplest gestures can bring the greatest joy, and this charming toy vendor's playful spirit certainly brightened the day for many.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>joyful,playful,vendor,toy,plane,stick,flying,video,laughter,surprise,heartwarming,Santa Rosa,Laguna,Philippines,crowd,amused,social media,viral,simple,joyful,charming</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Santa Rosa, Laguna</media:city>
                  <media:country>Philippines</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>PH</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Fails and Funnies</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2512</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 08:51:39 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2512.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2512.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Joyful puddle escapade: a father's hilarious chase in Minsk</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a heartwarming and lighthearted moment captured on June 21, 2023, on Nemiga Street in Minsk, Belarus, @tema_rai1986 shared a delightful video of a young boy's playful adventure. While out for a stroll, the boy's eyes lit up at the sight of a puddle, and he couldn't resist the temptation to run around in it. Amused and determined, his father tried to catch up, but the boy's splashing antics made it a challenging pursuit, as the father aimed to avoid getting soaked. Eventually, with a smile on his face, the father managed to scoop up his playful child, just as the boy reached the puddle's edge. </media:description>
                  <media:keywords>boy,puddle,running,Minsk,Nemiga Street,Belarus,video,walking,splashing,water,father,catch,wet,joy,playful,adventure,chase,moment,smile,heartwarming.</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Minsk</media:city>
                  <media:country>Belarus</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>BY</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Fails and Funnies</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2511</guid>
                  <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 06:56:54 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2511.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2511.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Thrills and tumbles: nighttime sign climbing adventure turns into chaos in Russia</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a daring escapade caught on camera in Russia, a group of friends attempted to climb a signpost at night with the aid of another companion. However, the adventure took a disastrous turn when the sign suddenly collapsed, sending the friend tumbling to the ground. The shocking video, captured by @nihuya_sebe_struya_ on July 15th, 2023, showcases the exhilarating yet perilous consequences of their reckless undertaking.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>nighttime,russia,adventure,friends,climbing,sign,video,risky,assistance,collapse,chaos,thrill,excitement,caution,safety,stunt,authorities,capture,fall,daring</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Kaluga</media:city>
                  <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Fails and Funnies</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2510</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 08:46:31 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2510.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2510.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Unique kitchen troubles: the gunshot sink that keeps dishwashing lively!</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a peculiar incident on May 7, 2023, in Halang, Calamba, Philippines, @pinunongjanjannn captured an amusing yet baffling video of his broken kitchen sink. The sink emitted gunshot-like sounds whenever opened, prompting the homeowner to comically mimic firing a gun. With shaking hands and a hint of humor, he declared, "You wouldn't get lazy washing your dishes if you have a sink like this." The peculiar and lively sink has undoubtedly brought a unique twist to the mundane task of dishwashing, leaving viewers both amused and curious about its mysterious malfunction.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>sink,kitchen,broken,gunshot,sounds,shaking,hands,shooting,dishes,lazy,amusing,video,Halang,Calamba,Philippines,homeowner,humor,malfunction,unique,curious.</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Halang, Calamba</media:city>
                  <media:country>Philippines</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>PH</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Fails and Funnies</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sun, 7 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2509</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 08:43:48 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2509.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2509.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Unconventional test of faith: a surprising gesture at Tondo church</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a surprising incident at Tondo Church in Manila, Philippines, a video captured by @zyramijares on January 6th, 2023, showcased a child making an unconventional gesture during a religious service. The child, believed to be her nephew, was seen directing the middle finger at her while inside the church. The video's caption, "the lord tests us everyday," added an intriguing twist to the situation, leaving viewers with questions about the child's intentions and the significance of such an act within the sacred space.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>church,video,nephew,gesture,test,faith,Tondo,Manila,Philippines,surprise,religious,service,unconventional,capture,January,2023,@zyramijares,incident,sacred,space,worship</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Tondo, Manila</media:city>
                  <media:country>Philippines</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>PH</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ODD</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Fails and Funnies</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Fri, 6 Jan 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2507</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 08:41:30 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2507.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2507.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Lipstick adventures: a colorful tale of playful parenting in Batam, Indonesia</media:title>
                  <media:description>In Batam, Indonesia, a heartwarming video captured by @inifency on June 9, 2023, showcases a small daughter's face covered in lipstick, bringing a smile to everyone's face. The mother reveals that her child often plays with her lipstick, leading her father to make light-hearted jokes in hopes of discouraging the behavior. Nevertheless, the young one's playful spirit remains unfazed. The video portrays a touching moment of parenthood, reminding us of the joyous innocence and carefree nature of childhood. </media:description>
                  <media:keywords>playful,parenting,video,daughter,lipstick,Batam,Indonesia,father,toys,fun,child,face,micellar,water,colorful,innocence,joyous,motherhood,rosy,cheeks</media:keywords>
                  <media:city> Batam</media:city>
                  <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>ID</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Fails and Funnies</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Fri, 9 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2499</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 08:39:42 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2499.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2499.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Acts of kindness unfold: motorbike rider rushes 'tatay' in Mawab, Philippines</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a heartwarming display of compassion and community spirit, a video captured by @DexieLexi on June 23, 2023, in Mawab, Davao De Oro, Philippines, showcased a motorbike rider's selfless act. The rider, in a hurry to assist a cart bicycle driver locally known as "tatay," parked his motorbike and rushed to lend a helping hand. However, in his eagerness, his own motorbike accidentally toppled over. Undeterred, he quickly returned to lift his fallen ride. Meanwhile, another kind-hearted individual joined forces with the cart bicycle driver to help pull the "tatay" and his cargo up a steep slope on the road. </media:description>
                  <media:keywords>motorbike,rider,parked,hurry,help,cart bicycle,tatay,fell,assistance,community,compassion,selfless,kindness,video,Mawab,Davao De Oro,Philippines,slope,road,solidarity</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Mawab, Davao De Oro</media:city>
                  <media:country>Philippines</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>PH</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Fails and Funnies</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2493</guid>
                  <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 12:37:13 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2493.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2493.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Caught on camera: two boys' epic grad party adventure foiled by mom</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a viral video capturing a memorable July 9th, 2023, night in New Jersey, USA, user @nverdesco_ shared an unforgettable moment when two boys' well-planned graduation party took an unexpected turn. The footage shows the boys caught red-handed by their mother after sneaking out to enjoy their long-awaited celebration. One of the boys explained that they had meticulously planned the event for an entire year, pooling their savings to make it a reality, fully aware that getting caught was a possibility. Despite their earnest attempts to explain, their mother remained firm, insisting they leave the party immediately.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>party,graduation,sneaking,caught,video,viral,New Jersey,USA,celebration,planned,savings,mother,determined,risks,social media,adventure,milestone,unforgettable,youthful,firm</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>New Jersey</media:city>
                  <media:country>United States</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>US</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Fails and Funnies</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sun, 9 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2492</guid>
                  <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 09:38:49 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2492.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2492.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Fear of the unknown: a son's dance with a glass floor in San Pedro Nuevo Leon</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a heartwarming yet fearful moment captured by @osvaldawg on May 27th, 2023, in San Pedro Nuevo Leon, Mexico, a young boy was confronted with a see-through glass floor. Terrified of the unknown depths below, he hesitated to take a step, frozen in his fear. The boy's concerned father gently pushed him onto the glass, but the overwhelming anxiety caused the child to quickly retreat.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>afraid,glass,floor,fear,son,video,Mexico,San Pedro,hesitation,unknown,depths,anxiety,father,push,retreat,courage,face,step,capture,moment</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>San Pedro Nuevo Leon</media:city>
                  <media:country>Mexico</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>MX</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Fails and Funnies</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sat, 27 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2473</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/a3d8050a-f5d4-41e9-a51e-fb96d93acd3d.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/79efb5d8-f6fa-47f0-ac04-a3b6f76b3ea3.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Disastrous auto repair mishap: Mercedes Benz plummets off forklift, front bumper lost!</media:title>
                  <media:description>On July 1st, 2023, in Zhejiang province, China, @ObligationXingaoAutomobileMaintenance documented a shocking incident at their repair shop. A video captured the moment a damaged Mercedes Benz, which was being lifted off a tow truck using a forklift, tragically plummeted to the ground. The unfortunate incident resulted in the car's front bumper falling off, compounding the initial damage. The vehicle's owner had entrusted it to the shop for repairs, only to face an unexpected and costly setback.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>mercedes,benz,repair,shop,forklift,accident,tow,truck,bumper,damage,incident,china,zhejiang,province,automobile,maintenance,video,owner,mishap,investigation</media:keywords>
                  <media:city> Zhejiang province</media:city>
                  <media:country>China</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>CN</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Fails and Funnies</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sat, 1 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2463</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/d5e866e5-dda6-4e97-86bc-281fa1269e38.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/1f47109b-42b2-4790-b10a-bff8a7a61203.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Heartwarming rescue: a father's swift response as baby takes a tumble in Quy Hoa Village, Vietnam</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a heartwarming moment captured by @dungthiem on May 27th, 2023, in Quy Hoa Village, Vietnam, a baby's playful adventure took an unexpected turn. Seated on a stroller, the little one gleefully played with it until a sudden loss of balance caused the stroller to tip forward, making the baby fall. The scene unfolded in a flash, but the baby's caring father rushed to the rescue, swiftly picking him up and offering comforting words as tears flowed. The baby is fine.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>playful,baby,stroller,fall,balance,father,rush,rescue,comforting,tears,love,protection,parents,mishap,adorable,village,Vietnam,cute,family,parenting</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Quy Hoa Village, Yen Hoa Commune, Cam Xuyen District</media:city>
                  <media:country>Vietnam</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>VN</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Fails and Funnies</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sat, 27 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2461</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/85e68d81-c06b-4e88-8e66-9cc0999d883c.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/74645571-c2cd-4d99-a61c-2001e1154fd9.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>A serene stumble: when aesthetic dreams meet a slippery reality</media:title>
                  <media:description>On July 9, 2023, in Malang city, Indonesia, a videographer known as @rikoclok_03 attempted to create an aesthetic video while walking on a wooden staircase surrounded by a lush green environment, holding a cup of his favorite drink. However, his intentions took an unexpected turn when the wet stairs caused him to tumble and fall. The man is fine.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>aesthetic,videographer,stairs,green,serene,environment,cup,drink,wet,tumble,fall,unexpected,mishap,life,pursuit,beauty,nature,unpredictable,reminder,video</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Malang city</media:city>
                  <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>ID</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Fails and Funnies</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sun, 9 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2459</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/28e4b2a9-2348-499f-b358-ab650cf0b358.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/854d0bd7-fad0-4c7b-94cc-7079efdb7abb.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Overloaded motorbike sends friend tumbling in Yogyakarta, Indonesia</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a video captured by @ka_wula_alit on June 6th, 2023, in Yogyakarta, Indonesia, a friend's attempt to ride an overloaded motorbike and ended up in a comical mishap. The video shows the rider struggling to maintain balance as the motorbike's weight proves to be too much. After a few meters, the inevitable happens, and the friend takes a tumble.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>village,mishap,overloaded bike,falling,balance,Yogyakarta,Indonesia,video,friend,riding,comedy,accident,bike,weight,safety,rural,load management,humor,stumble,capture</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Yogyakarta</media:city>
                  <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>ID</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Fails and Funnies</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Tue, 6 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2435</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/cd21c59d-5b07-4098-9f09-60ad72c69ec4.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2435.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Thrill-seeker's narrow escape at Skytropolis Indoor Theme Park</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a funny moment at Skytropolis Indoor Theme Park in Bentong, Malaysia, a thrill-seeker was about to board suddenly rolled and toppled. The incident was captured on video by @itznxshy on March 20th, 2023. The footage shows the courageous individual preparing to embark on the ride, only to be caught off guard as the chair unexpectedly tumbled sideways. Fortunately the author emerged from the incident unscathed, avoiding any injuries.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>roller coaster,mishap,thrill-seeker,escape,Skytropolis,indoor,theme park,Bentong,Malaysia,video,ride,chair,rolled,toppled,okay,not hurt,social media,incident,safety,precautions</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Bentong</media:city>
                  <media:country>Malaysia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>MY</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Fails and Funnies</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Mon, 20 Mar 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2434</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/46b9f903-9a5c-4168-801e-403539654c46.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2c0b515f-5ab3-47fc-a843-78a442a185f3.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Unexpected swing mishap: couples' joy turns to a shocking fall!</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a surprising turn of events, a video captured by @agilcuyy_ on June 24th, 2023, in Sukabumi, West Java, Indonesia, showed a seemingly innocent swinging adventure take a dramatic and unexpected twist. The footage featured the author and his girlfriend joyfully swinging together until disaster struck. Without any prior warning, one of the swing supports suddenly snapped, causing both individuals to plummet to the ground. The couple is fine!</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>video,swing,mishap,fall,surprise,capture,girlfriends,adventure,twist,disaster,warning,support,snap,plummet,ground,shocking,incident,dangers,enjoyment,unexpected</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Sukabumi, West Java</media:city>
                  <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>ID</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Fails and Funnies</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2429</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/e5d10922-2d22-44ca-9ac7-c51df09d153b.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/3888655c-bf90-4b0b-aa70-3f480001c759.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Boxing fails turn into hilarious triumph: laughter echoes at Kudus City Mall</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a video captured by @bang_loong123 on May 13th, 2023, at Kudus City Mall in Central Java, Indonesia, a moment of amusement unfolded during a boxing session. As his friend took a swing, he missed his target and nearly stumbled. The mishap brought laughter from their companions, but undeterred, he gathered himself and tried again. This time, his efforts paid off as he successfully landed a hit. </media:description>
                  <media:keywords>boxing,mall,video,friend,hit,laughter,incident,amusement,swing,stumble,companions,fluff,target,perseverance,success,capture,moment,failure,light-hearted,triumph</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Central Java</media:city>
                  <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>ID</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Fails and Funnies</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sat, 13 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2424</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/15c9e340-2a4d-4154-88e1-a022dd3abbb5.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/f4d044ec-d503-4603-8fe7-2f664ff904f1.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Unexpected mishap: model's dramatic fall steals the spotlight at Pekanbaru's fashion show</media:title>
                  <media:description>In an unfortunate turn of events at a fashion show held in Pekanbaru, Indonesia, a model took a sudden tumble off the stage, capturing the attention of onlookers. The incident, caught on video on April 23rd, 2023, by @babangg_r and shared on social media, showcased the model's unexpected fall. Concerned individuals quickly rushed to her aid, ensuring her safety and well-being. </media:description>
                  <media:keywords>fashion,show,model,fall,stage,incident,Pekanbaru,Indonesia,video,@babangg_r,attention,onlookers,social media,unexpected,aid,safety,well-being,live events,resilience,support</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Pekanbaru</media:city>
                  <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>ID</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Fails and Funnies</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sun, 23 Apr 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2421</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/7faaac9e-44e9-4e29-be47-470e79fccdbf.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2421.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Hilarious billiards blunder leaves players in stitches!</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a comical turn of events, a video captured by @bankhoa on June 22nd, 2023, in Hanoi, Vietnam, has gone viral. The footage shows a man engrossed in a game of billiards when he accidentally struck his friend right in the manhood with the cue ball. The unexpected mishap resulted in a burst of laughter from everyone present. The incident serves as a lighthearted reminder that even the most innocent of games can lead to unexpected hilarity.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>billiards,video,viral,mishap,laughter,comical,friends,accident,funny,unexpected,game,cue,ball,manhood,Hanoi,Vietnam,@bankhoa,Thai Ha Street,Dong Da District,lighthearted</media:keywords>
                  <media:city> Dong Da District, Hanoi</media:city>
                  <media:country>Vietnam</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>VN</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Fails and Funnies</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2416</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/00961765-8fd4-4598-9d7f-b5435489f1f2.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/0bdcd5a3-e320-44de-9ff4-9e1ab436124c.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Frantic plea for creation: a son's cry unleashes chaos</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a candid moment captured on camera on June 28th, 2023, a heartfelt plea for a piece of paper and pen escalated into an unexpected scene of chaos. @anhbee197, and her son were captured on their home camera in Hai Duong province, Vietnam. As the son relentlessly cried for the desired stationery, frustration mounted when his plea went unanswered. In a moment of frustration, he forcefully pushed the bedside table, causing it to crash to the ground and scatter its contents. Despite the mother's efforts to prevent the mishap, her attempts proved futile. With the debris settled, she sat in contemplation, gazing at her son, as the aftermath of his outburst unfolded before them.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>crying,paper,pen,chaos,frustration,camera,home,table,bed,mother,son,plea,push,falling,scattering,failed,looking,candid,captured,aftermath</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Hai Duong province</media:city>
                  <media:country>Vietnam</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>VN</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Fails and Funnies</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2415</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/1d919518-1477-4c9f-add7-711b13643db9.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/c3a9dd97-9746-4b95-b61b-8d416b4f711b.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Swinging mishap on Nirwana beach: laughter-filled tumble takes center stage</media:title>
                  <media:description>A hilarious incident unfolded on the picturesque Nirwana Beach in Padang, West Sumatra, Indonesia, as captured in a video by @sukmajla_ on May 29, 2023. While attempting to ride a swing, both the author and her friend accidentally took an unexpected tumble. The recording, seemingly intentional at first, showcased their laughter-filled mishap. With no harm done, the friends couldn't contain their amusement as they embraced the joyous moment.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>beach,swing,falling,laughter,mishap,video,friends,fun,accident,recording,joy,moment,hilarious,playful,unexpected,tumble,candid,outdoors,coastal,bonding</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Padang, West Sumatra</media:city>
                  <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>ID</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Fails and Funnies</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Mon, 29 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2411</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/8170ef24-1646-4311-b74c-02ac9d4e920a.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/7d61eabd-e82d-4e81-9c07-006ccc477e05.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Rescued from a bucked headache: young boy's misadventure in Kundasang</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a heart-stopping incident captured on video by @pakej_bajet_kundasang on April 17th, 2023, a small boy in Kundasang, Sabah, Malaysia found himself in a precarious situation. Despite being warned not to play with a bucket, the boy managed to get his head stuck between the bucket handle and the rim. Distressed and crying, he jumped around while desperately being helped to remove the bucket. Thankfully, the bucket was eventually freed, and the child emerged unharmed. Once liberated, the boy flung the bucket away, perhaps learning a valuable lesson about heeding warnings.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>bucket,mishap,Kundasang,Sabah,Malaysia,video,small,boy,stuck,handle,crying,help,warning,heed,removed,unharmed,incident,relieved,lesson,learn</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Kundasang, Sabah</media:city>
                  <media:country>Malaysia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>MY</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Fails and Funnies</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2396</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/134b8b68-1f8f-48bb-b4ca-dad8dbdf6aa5.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/294a0872-8421-4517-ba57-49212f298b3e.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Kids turn idle paint into whimsical art on mom's motorbike!</media:title>
                  <media:description>Bandung, Indonesia - In an unexpected turn of events, @nengrenii68 found her motorbike transformed into a mess of white paint, courtesy of a group of playful children. On June 24th, 2023, while the author was at home with her own child, her neighbor's kids had come over for a playdate. Little did they know that a container of idle paint, leftover from her husband's décor project, had been left on the terrace. Seizing the opportunity, the children unleashed their creativity and used the paint to not only decorate the terrace but also give her motorbike an impromptu makeover. The chaos came to light when her child excitedly rushed inside to inform her about the unexpected transformation. Surprised and likely amused, the author found herself facing an unconventional and colorful motorbike.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>bandung,indonesia,motorbike,paint,kids,video,white,home,neighbor,play,idle,terrace,surprise,mess,creativity,decoration,makeover,chaos,amused,colorful</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Bandung</media:city>
                  <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>ID</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Fails and Funnies</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2385</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2cd51397-09f8-473d-bf60-e49ee783a91f.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2385.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Unveiling Pompeii's enigma: Antonio's silent encounter with the naked marble man</media:title>
                  <media:description>On June 9th, 2023, in the ancient city of Pompeii, Italy, a captivating video was captured by @shileenoelle_. The footage featured @antoniomusicisme, her boyfriend, passionately explaining the intricate details of the marble carvings that surrounded them. However, their exploration took an unexpected turn when Antonio stumbled upon a naked man marble sculpture. Instantly, he fell into silence, unable to articulate the profound significance of this enigmatic artwork. </media:description>
                  <media:keywords>pompeii,italy,video,boyfriend,girlfriend,marble,carvings,exploration,unexpected,silence,naked,man,sculpture,artwork,enigma,history,ancient,captivate,significance,mysterious</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Pompeii</media:city>
                  <media:country>Italy</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>IT</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Fails and Funnies</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Fri, 9 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2378</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/6d79429c-d3cf-4aac-9f43-14df4b5675ac.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/6a6c9334-3560-4707-bb36-769c83944a2a.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Laughing off ignored warnings: unforgettable chair tumble in East Kutai, Indonesia</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a video captured by @ayufebrinaaaa on April 5th, 2023, from East Kutai, Indonesia, an unexpected chair mishap takes center stage. Despite repeatedly warning others about the chair's instability, the author was met with indifference and ignored. However, her prophetic words came true when she attempted to sit down, only to find herself falling hilariously. Despite the unexpected tumble, the author maintains a lighthearted spirit and continues to find amusement in the incident.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>chair,fall,video,home camera,warning,ignored,laughter,mishap,East Kutai,Indonesia,amusement,lighthearted,incident,hilarious,sitting,captured,complained,shared,@ayufebrinaaaa,April 5th</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>East Kutai</media:city>
                  <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>ID</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Fails and Funnies</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Wed, 5 Apr 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2340</guid>
                  <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 08:16:49 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/b0335fb4-69df-4e17-a294-1c77d2de977e.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/5399cd66-d126-4c17-84fe-43dc61df0b2e.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Sibling sour sensations: hilarious reactions to mega sour raspberry drops!</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a hilarious video captured on March 28th, 2022, by @tomdibbens of Adelaide, Australia, he and his sister took on the challenge of trying mega sour raspberry drops, known for their intense sourness. The video showcases his sister's priceless reactions as she pops the candy into her mouth, only to drop it instantly, exclaiming that it felt "hot." Clearly, this duo has a penchant for sour lollies and their entertaining taste-test moments are not to be missed.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>video,sour,lollies,reactions,priceless,siblings,challenge,candy,drops,intense,Adelaide,Australia,hilarious,hot,taste-test,duo,tom dibbens,raspberry,captured,mouth</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Adelaide</media:city>
                  <media:country>Australia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>AU</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Fails and Funnies</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Mon, 28 Mar 2022</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2364</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/652855e9-c7de-4681-84f5-40f0a0d1c025.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/99800709-026d-42c3-8d14-0cb0c7da1eca.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Truck head spontaneously detaches and takes a startling solo stroll</media:title>
                  <media:description>On June 17th, 2021, in Trenggalek, Indonesia, a puzzling incident occurred when a parked truck's head suddenly disconnected from its body and began moving autonomously. The event was captured on video by @kepalajenggot_official, who witnessed a man inadvertently touching the truck head as it sprung to life. Fortunately, no injuries were reported, as the truck head came to a halt just a few steps away. </media:description>
                  <media:keywords>truck,incident,disconnected,moving,autonomous,video,Trenggalek,Indonesia,head,man,touch,lucky,hurt,stopped,steps,parked,puzzling,witnessed,bystanders,awe,unexplained</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Trenggalek</media:city>
                  <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>ID</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Fails and Funnies</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Thu, 17 Jun 2021</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2346</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/960bac20-2620-4cbb-8944-8e062004044a.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2346.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Unforgettable graduation moment as boy mistakes canvas for Wall and takes a tumble</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a heartwarming yet amusing incident captured on video on June 17th, 2023 during a school children's graduation ceremony in Sidoarjo, Indonesia, two kids stole the spotlight unintentionally. The footage, courtesy of @azizahzindy, shows a boy and a girl holding hands as they make their way across the stage. However, in an unexpected turn of events, the boy leaned onto what he thought was a solid wall—a hanging canvas board—but to his surprise, it gave way, resulting in a comical tumble. </media:description>
                  <media:keywords>kids,graduation,ceremony,video,mishap,school,children,boy,girl,holding hands,canvas board,fall,funny,accident,Sidoarjo,Indonesia,laughter,unexpected,joyous,lightheartedness</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Sidoarjo</media:city>
                  <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>ID</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Fails and Funnies</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2332</guid>
                  <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 11:54:26 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/600dbfd0-2813-4430-b6ca-6838a009cc1a.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/0ce1539d-23e5-48fb-a679-0e6fd87af308.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Daring rescue attempt ends in hilarious tumble!</media:title>
                  <media:description>A hilarious incident unfolded in Sukomakmur Village, Magelang, Indonesia, on May 28, 2023, as captured by @aamriinnnn. In a video shared by her, two friends, a male and a female, found themselves in an unexpected tumble. According to the author, the female friend had dismounted from a motorbike but couldn't control her momentum, leading her to start running. In a valiant attempt to help her stop, the male friend grabbed her hands. However, to everyone's surprise, the female friend's strength proved to be too much, causing the male friend to roll over her and  land in a nearby ditch beside the path. </media:description>
                  <media:keywords>motorbike,friends,tumble,mishap,hilarious,video,Indonesia,Magelang,Sukomakmur,village,running,brake,male,female,strength,ditch,unexpected,incident,capture,fun</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Sukomakmur Village, Magelang</media:city>
                  <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>ID</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Fails and Funnies</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sun, 28 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2353</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/a1edf19b-ebb7-4377-8b63-0032eaf74fa8.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/fa7740b7-4206-442a-9268-73ee888525b5.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Captivating sibling food illusion: laughter, bond, and hilarity unveiled in Seagrove, Florida!</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a delightful and comical video that emerged on June 15th, 2023, captured by @j.stone19 in Seagrove, Florida, USA, a unique food illusion took place between a brother and sister. Seated at a table, the brother appeared to be enjoying a meal, but there was a twist - he was using his sister's hands instead of his own! With his sister positioned behind him, her hands emerging from his armpits, creating the illusion that they were his own. As she attempted to feed him, both siblings burst into laughter. The brother skillfully played along, commenting on the food as if he were his sister. The heartwarming video showcased the bond and lightheartedness shared between these siblings, leaving viewers in stitches.

</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>seagrove,florida,usa,video,brother,sister,food,illusion,hands,laughter,feed,armpits,bond,lightheartedness,hilarious,comical,captured,seated,table,unique</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Seagrove, Florida</media:city>
                  <media:country>United States</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>US</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Fails and Funnies</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2371</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/bb8f2439-cb24-4675-a08d-0c44a8868d6f.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/5aab8bf4-e712-40a7-97bc-a9abae4c18ae.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Unforeseen splash: a fishing expedition in Borneo takes an unexpected turn</media:title>
                  <media:description>In an unforeseen turn of events during a fishing expedition in Borneo, Indonesia, recorded by @keluargabakumpai on April 15, 2023, as he was filming his friend who was fishing as usual. The author's friend found himself taking an unexpected plunge into the river. While standing on a wooden structure at the riverbank, having his fishing adventure, a missed step led to an unfortunate fall into the water. Fortunately, the friend managed to emerge from the incident unharmed.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>fishing,expedition,borneo,indonesia,recording,river,plunge,wooden structure,mishap,resilience,balance,unexpected,unscathed,reflexes,composure,memorable,vigilance,friend,splash,caution</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Borneo</media:city>
                  <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>ID</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Fails and Funnies</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sat, 15 Apr 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2252</guid>
                  <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 19:55:21 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/395c27c4-61c9-47e4-bc0e-eb30657eeea1.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/595cca6e-d6c6-4930-81b3-eb7937836d67.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Gallon mishap: unfortunate accident shatters drinking water quest</media:title>
                  <media:description>In an unfortunate incident captured on video by @_anggitadstyaa on 25th February, 2023, a resident of Samarinda, Indonesia, a simple task turned into a clumsy mishap. The video initially intended to showcase a friend lifting a gallon of drinking water quickly took a turn for the worse. As the author's friend confidently embarked on the short journey into the house, disaster struck. With only a few strides taken, the gallon slipped from her grip, crashing onto the ground, spilling the water on the floor. </media:description>
                  <media:keywords>samarinda,indonesia,video,friend,lifting,gallon,mishap,accident,water,recording,fall,broke,house,strides,shattered,plastic,spilled,unexpected,twists,life</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Samarinda</media:city>
                  <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>ID</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Fails and Funnies</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2244</guid>
                  <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 19:56:59 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/65098378-6588-4390-b30c-acdd9214e35e.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/4adcec68-9c86-47f2-95cc-b50aed80cbf2.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Funny mishap: toddler gets drink in her eyes, dad can't stop laughing!</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a heartwarming yet hilarious moment captured on video, a father from St. George, Utah, USA, found himself in a comical mishap while fixing a drink for his young daughter. The footage, shared by @callmedivajustice on May 16, 2023, shows the dad playfully asking his daughter if she wanted to try the drink after vigorously shaking it in a drinking bottle. However, things took an unexpected turn as he opened the lid for his daughter, causing the drink to gush out from the straw and enter the toddler's eyes. Despite the momentary surprise, the brave little girl reassured her dad that she was okay. Unable to contain his laughter, the dad's amusement at the situation was evident.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>video,father,daughter,drink,mishap,laughter,St. George,Utah,USA,toddler,eyes,funny,captured,moment,shake,bottle,gushing,okay,comical,amusement,family</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>St. George, Utah</media:city>
                  <media:country>United States</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>US</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Fails and Funnies</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Tue, 16 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2304</guid>
                  <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 10:56:09 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/64fb124a-800a-4c01-9b11-9cd61d7dcca3.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/dd66a7b4-3eee-4b89-9a04-3d82ce60d72a.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Golden mistake: hilarious prank goes wrong </media:title>
                  <media:description>In a lighthearted turn of events, a playful prank took an unexpected twist for a couple in Perth, Western Australia. @sita.mann, an avid social media user, captured the hilarious moment on video as her boyfriend attempted to prank her but ended up spraying her face with gold hairspray instead of silly string.

The comical video, posted by @sita.mann on June 9th, 2023, shows the unsuspecting boyfriend confidently ready to surprise his girlfriend. However, to his dismay, he soon realized his mistake as he unintentionally doused the author's face with a dazzling spray of golden color.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>prank,video,couple,laughter,mistake,hilarious,socialmedia,unexpected,twist,gold,hairspray,silly,string,face,boyfriend,girlfriend,capture,moment,popular,tags</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Perth</media:city>
                  <media:country>Australia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>AU</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Fails and Funnies</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Fri, 9 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2251</guid>
                  <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 20:13:46 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/a0d94654-6acf-4e77-b646-5c62faf0ff19.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/4e7e6394-9848-4f58-8d21-f279bd6ad791.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Ship mishap: friend's misstep leads to dramatic plunge</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a dramatic turn of events, a filming session on a ship in Medan City, North Sumatra, Indonesia took a sudden and unexpected twist. @dandy_lubiis was capturing a video of his friend on 6th May, 2023 when a misstep on the stairs turned disastrous. Without warning, his friend stumbled and plummeted through the staircase, crashing to the bottom. The shocking incident left onlookers in a state of shock and concern. The author's friend however, quickly got up at the end of the incident.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>ship,mishap,filming,friend,stairs,fall,Medan City,North Sumatra,Indonesia,accident,dramatic,plunge,filming session,unexpected,twist,misstep,disastrous,onlookers,video footage,heart-stopping</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Medan City</media:city>
                  <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>ID</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Fails and Funnies</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sat, 6 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2247</guid>
                  <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 20:08:57 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/d647675f-845c-4a6b-a0b7-52666b3f4570.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/321ce756-d67b-42e1-9d7b-5971f27db0ea.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Close call: worker's near-death slip on wet floor caught on camera</media:title>
                  <media:description>A heart-stopping moment was caught on camera as a worker in Saint-Jérôme, Quebec, Canada narrowly escaped a potentially fatal accident. In a video captured by @karellevarin on June 21st, 2023 the worker can be seen carrying plates of food from the kitchen when she suddenly slips on a wet floor. The dramatic footage shows her nearly losing her balance, but miraculously manages to regain control just in time.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>worker,slip,wet floor,CCTV,video,near-death,accident,Saint-Jérôme,Quebec,Canada,kitchen,food,plates,balance,danger,workplace,safety,reminder,incident,footage,control</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Saint-Jérôme, Quebec</media:city>
                  <media:country>Canada</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>CA</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Fails and Funnies</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2313</guid>
                  <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 11:22:21 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/1868592e-0e3b-481e-b907-7e8a72627749.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/eb6fb124-9aed-46e4-a6ab-e55766663bfa.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Unforeseen wardrobe mishap: sister's skirt drops mid-performance, caught on camera!</media:title>
                  <media:description>In an unexpected turn of events at a school event in Kediri, Indonesia, a video captured by @risazizah on June 15, 2023, showcased a girl's skirt falling during a performance. What made this incident even more surprising was the fact that the girl in question was none other than the sister of the author herself. As a teacher at the same school, the author had recorded the entire event, unaware that her sister would be the one experiencing a wardrobe malfunction. Fortunately, the girl had worn black leggings underneath, ensuring that she was not left completely exposed. </media:description>
                  <media:keywords>school,event,video,skirt,fall,performance,sister,unexpected,captured,incident,leggings,permission,teacher,wardrobe,malfunction,exposure,Kediri,Indonesia,viral,twist</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Kediri</media:city>
                  <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>ID</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Fails and Funnies</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2309</guid>
                  <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 10:46:44 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/6977856a-62b4-4474-965f-1cf394fdc86e.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/ef49dfa7-fc7f-455d-97ee-a38b00918596.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Unforgettable bachelorette fun: hilarious raft tumble at beer olympics afterparty!</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a memorable bachelorette party celebration in Collingwood, Ontario, Canada, a group of friends found themselves in fits of laughter and screams after a day of Beer Olympics. The jovial atmosphere was captured on video by @jordan.ash.t on May 24, 2023. The highlight of the day came when one of the friends ingeniously hopped onto a wooden raft by lying flat on her stomach and clutching onto its sides. As the raft tilted to one side, her companions couldn't maintain their balance, plunging into the water with a symphony of shrieks. Luckily, everyone emerged unscathed, floating near the raft on the serene water body. It was an unforgettable moment of joy and camaraderie, capturing the essence of an epic bachelorette celebration. </media:description>
                  <media:keywords>beer,olympics,bachelorette,party,friends,video,wooden raft,hilarious,tumble,water,screams,serene,Canada,Collingwood,Ontario,fun,adventure,capture,memories,laughter</media:keywords>
                  <media:city> Collingwood, Ontario</media:city>
                  <media:country>Canada</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>CA</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Fails and Funnies</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Wed, 24 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2308</guid>
                  <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 10:52:50 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/94d1f8d6-7067-4cc0-8e05-be1f07e40423.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/c1097b14-f72a-4eee-bd0d-cf143bd60c70.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Unforgettable Bali getaway: an expected encounter with a playful wave</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a heart-stopping moment captured on video, a family vacationing on Batu Belig Beach in Bali, Indonesia had an expected encounter with a powerful wave on May 03, 2023. @cesarrohedi, the father, had been enjoying the sunny day with his wife and children, playing in the water and capturing memories with a waterproof-cased cell phone. One particularly vigorous wave rose engulfing the family. The author says that they are okay and its not scary as shown in the video. </media:description>
                  <media:keywords>vacation,beach,Bali,Indonesia,family,wave,video,shores,water,cell phone,waterproof casing,conditions,fine,thrilling,encounter,unexpected,captured,hurt,anticipated,unforgettable</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Batu Belig Beach, Bali</media:city>
                  <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>ID</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Fails and Funnies</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Wed, 3 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2225</guid>
                  <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 21:08:44 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/670a844b-2072-45db-bf93-2a3e9cbf9260.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/9aba9fcf-372e-4497-9351-defeaf061585.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Unforgettable barefoot ride: sandal mishap captured in hilarious video</media:title>
                  <media:description>A recent video captured in Tasikmalaya, West Java, Indonesia, has taken the internet by storm. The footage, shot by @alwidivraja on January 4th, 2023, shows him driving barefoot after his sandal accidentally fell off and got stuck in another motorbike passing by. In the video, the author can be heard laughing, while the oblivious owner of the other motorbike continues riding, seemingly unaware of the unusual situation.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>driving,barefoot,sandal,mishap,video,laughter,motorbike,stuck,hilarious,capture,Tasikmalaya,West Java,Indonesia,amusing,unexpected,carefree,social media,viral,joy,lighthearted</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Tasikmalaya, West Java</media:city>
                  <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>ID</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Fails and Funnies</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Wed, 4 Jan 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2185</guid>
                  <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 20:40:20 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/98013694-a007-4f14-b5f6-1865a6d09b9c.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/6c76aee7-e75d-4b22-ae86-afc25b30e53b.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Prankster's surprise: hen wakes man with pants-pecking feat!</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a hilarious video captured by @tatak_jodhipati in Temanggung, Central Java, Indonesia, on March 24, 2023, a clever prankster managed to wake a sleeping man in the most unexpected way. The footage shows the man peacefully dozing off while a chicken roams nearby. Seizing the opportunity for mischief, someone off-screen starts sprinkling rice grains on the slumbering man, specifically targeting his pants.

The chicken, quick to spot the free meal, wastes no time and begins pecking at the rice grains scattered on the man's pants. Surprised by the unexpected sensation, the man stirs awake, seemingly unfazed by the situation.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>hen,chicken,grains,prankster,video,sleeping,laughter,wake-up,pants,calmness,surprise,Temanggung,Central Java,Indonesia,mischief,pecking,amusement,unpredictable,moment,capture</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Temanggung, Central Java</media:city>
                  <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>ID</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Fails and Funnies</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Fri, 24 Mar 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2186</guid>
                  <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 20:44:02 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/d543617c-24d1-4c2f-810a-9011bc20cea0.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/ae91f9f1-f95d-4eea-988f-77c3a366e94b.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Cart-tastrophe in Boyolali: hilarious overload lifts cart and spirits!</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a comical turn of events that left onlookers in stitches, a recent video captured in Boyolali, Indonesia has gone viral. The footage, recorded by @ariwibowo7224 on December 24, 2022, showcases a light-hearted incident involving an overloaded hand-pulled cart . Fortunately, no one was harmed during the incident, and the unexpected turn of events resulted in uncontrollable laughter from the amused bystanders. The traditional cart, which was overloaded with wood, lifted up the author's friend as he tried to pull it.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>overloaded,cart,wood,hand-pulled,lifted,friend,video,mishap,laughter,incident,humor,Boyolali,Indonesia,lighthearted,unexpected,hilarious,bystanders,amused,noharm,laughter</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Boyolali</media:city>
                  <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>ID</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Fails and Funnies</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sat, 24 Dec 2022</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2173</guid>
                  <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 10:14:08 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2a7dde6e-b6f6-49af-9640-22a8ea07d6c3.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2e36dc55-9644-4c10-9906-ce3911ae2653.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Beachside fun turns into a sticky situation: friend's head gets stuck in anchor rock!</media:title>
                  <media:description>A leisurely day at the beach took a surprising turn of events when a group of friends encountered a rather sticky situation.  @arulbinhamid12, found himself filming a video that would soon go viral. In Buton Regency, South East Sulawesi, Indonesia, specifically in the Pasarwajo district, their recreational trip took an unexpected twist when one of his friends playfully attempted to stick his head into an unused anchor rock on January 8, 2023.

What began as a harmless joke quickly transformed into a nerve-wracking predicament. The friend's head became wedged tightly within the anchor rock. After several trials to free him, their efforts paid off, and their friend was finally freed from the anchor rock's clutches, much to everyone's relief.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>recreation,beach,waves,friends,video,stuck,anchor rock,Buton Island,Pasarwajo district,fun,adventure,viral,prank,panic,relief,peril,unexpected,predicament,capture,moments</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Buton Island, Pasarwajo district</media:city>
                  <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>ID</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Fails and Funnies</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sun, 8 Jan 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2201</guid>
                  <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 09:13:35 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/f8996a9e-44c4-4283-8a61-8e81c213f01f.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/d03cbd25-0912-4606-9e6d-3b92ec966361.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                     </channel>
                  </rss>
                