<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
        <rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
        xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
        xmlns:openSearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearchrss/1.0/"
        xmlns:dfpvideo="http://api.google.com/dfpvideo"
        xmlns:tms="http://data.tmsapi.com/v1.1"
        version="2.0">
          <channel>
            <title>ViralBear videos</title>
            <dfpvideo:version>2</dfpvideo:version>
              
                  <item>
                  <media:title>First-time rider's mishap: girl's scooter adventure ends with a bump!</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a candid video captured by @wkmzxuk_ on July 15, 2023, in the City of Soligorsk, Minsk region, Belarus, a young girl's first-time experience with an electronic scooter took an unexpected turn. With enthusiasm and excitement, she hopped onto the scooter but found herself struggling to control its speed. Unaware of the gears and unfamiliar with braking, she careened toward a stationary sign near a building, unable to halt her momentum. The result was a comical yet cautionary collision, reminding viewers of the importance of learning the basics before embarking on new adventures. While the girl's misadventure might have left her a little shaken, it undoubtedly served as a valuable lesson for both her and others who dare to ride the scooters for the first time.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>scooter,mishap,video,girl,first-time,adventure,excitement,gears,braking,collision,cautionary,comical,lessons,learning,electronic,speed,sign,building,Belarus,Soligorsk</media:keywords>
                  <media:city> City of Soligorsk, Minsk region</media:city>
                  <media:country>Belarus</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>BY</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Fails and Funnies</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2594</guid>
                  <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 10:53:05 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2594.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2594.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Intense hailstorm hits Central Ottawa: golf ball sized hail pummels the city for 5 minutes!</media:title>
                  <media:description>On July 28, 2023, residents of Ottawa, Canada, experienced an intense hailstorm that left them astonished and wary. The event was captured on video by @paulajroy, who shared the gripping footage of the hailstorm outside her house. Lasting for approximately five minutes, the hailstones reached nearly the size of golf balls, causing significant concern for property damage and potential risks to individuals caught outdoors. The severe weather phenomenon swept through central Ottawa, leaving a trail of destruction in its wake.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>hailstorm,ottawa,canada,weather,intense,video,paulajroy,golfball,sized,hail,central,astonishment,damage,risk,outdoors,severe,phenomenon,destruction,warnings,precautions</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Ottawa </media:city>
                  <media:country>Canada</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>CA</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Weather</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2579</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023 17:39:58 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2579.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2579.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Playful corgi's adorable 'poof' act delights internet in St. Petersburg, Russia!</media:title>
                  <media:description>In an endearing and amusing video that captured hearts on social media, a Corgi named Leo from St. Petersburg, Russia, showcased his unique talent for playing "dead." The video, shared by @prokopenkokate on April 29, 2023, depicts Leo sitting peacefully on the floor before his owner mimics a shooting gesture with her hands. Surprisingly, the adorable pup immediately flops down, pretending to be "shot" as part of a playful command he has mastered. As a reward for his impressive performance, Leo eagerly awaits a treat, proving that his favorite command is the delightful and harmless "poof," leaving viewers charmed by this clever and lovable canine's antics.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>playful,corgi,leo,video,internet,acting,dog,Russia,St. Petersburg,pet,owner,gun,pretend,cute,charm,humor,social media,adorable,command,sweet</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>St. Petersburg</media:city>
                  <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sat, 29 Apr 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2595</guid>
                  <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 10:53:38 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2595.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2595.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Nature's fury unleashed: lightning strikes and flames explode in Shijiazhuang</media:title>
                  <media:description>On July 24, 2023, in Shijiazhuang, northern China, a startling and unintentional event was captured on video by @HomelessYuanyuan. As she stood in front of her apartment window with her mobile phone, attempting to capture a street scene during a rainstorm and thunder, lightning struck the transformer below her building. The intense impact caused sparks of flames to erupt, scattering fiery fragments in all directions. Nature's fury was unleashed, and in a split second, the author found herself witnessing a breathtaking display of raw power and danger.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>lightning,sparks,flames,explosion,rainstorm,thunder,Shijiazhuang,China,video,mobile,window,street,nature,fury,power,danger,unpredictability,awe,humbled,@HomelessYuanyuan</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Shijiazhuang</media:city>
                  <media:country>China</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>CN</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>News</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2604</guid>
                  <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 13:16:50 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2604.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2604.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Terrifying Yokohama guerrilla rainstorm unleashes chaos with its fierce winds and torrential downpour</media:title>
                  <media:description>In Yokohama, Japan, on August 1, 2023, @Tomo_YNU captured a chilling video of a rainstorm known as Guerrilla. This local phenomenon is characterized by an unpredictable formation of cumulonimbus clouds, resulting in a short but intense downpour of over 100 mm per hour of rain. The video showcases the fury of the Guerrilla rainstorm, with powerful winds swaying trees in its path. The dangerous nature of this event highlights the need for caution and preparedness during such occurrences in Yokohama.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>rainstorm,guerrilla,yokohama,japan,video,downpour,cumulonimbus,clouds,intense,winds,trees,dangerous,unpredictable,weather,phenomenon,local,short,mm,hour,rain</media:keywords>
                  <media:city> Yokohama</media:city>
                  <media:country>Japan</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>JP</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Weather</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Tue, 1 Aug 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2601</guid>
                  <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 13:12:08 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2601.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2601.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Playful and obedient: Khryapa's impressive 'swim' command!</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a heartwarming video captured by @mokryi_nosik_ on June 17, 2020, in Voronezh, Russia, her beloved dog, Khryapa, stole the spotlight with her incredible obedience and playful nature. The footage shows @mokryi_nosik_ talking to Khryapa in one of the rooms, when suddenly, the clever canine dashes off towards the bathroom. Without hesitation, Khryapa leaps into the bathtub, showcasing her impressive execution of the "swim" command. The three-year-old furry friend proves to be not only obedient but also full of joy and enthusiasm. Her charming antics have won the hearts of viewers worldwide, leaving a lasting impression of her delightful personality and the strong bond between her and her owner.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>playful,obedient,dog,swim,command,video,Khryapa,Voronezh,Russia,bathtub,bathroom,three years old,pet,canine,joy,love,bond,clever,cute,charming</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Voronezh</media:city>
                  <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2598</guid>
                  <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 10:57:32 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2598.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2598.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Tenacious twig tug-of-war: a dog's unyielding affair with nature's bounty</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a delightful and amusing scene captured by @chelseareject on May 21, 2023, in Jersey City, New Jersey, USA, her four-legged companion exhibited an unshakeable determination during a playful encounter with nature. The video showcased the adorable pup clenching onto a sizable twig of a tree, despite the owner's best efforts to convince it otherwise. With @chelseareject's voice gently coaxing the dog to release its prized find, the resilient canine remained unyielding, steadfastly refusing to let go. Undeterred, they strolled along together, the furry protagonist proudly showcasing its prized possession in an endearing tug-of-war with the forces of nature. The heartwarming display of canine spirit and persistence resonated with viewers worldwide, capturing the essence of a special bond between humans and their loyal companions.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>tree,dog,twig,nature,Jersey City,USA,May,2023,video,pet,playful,determined,adorable,owner,walk,bonding,persistence,loyalty,companionship,endearing,capture</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Jersey City, New Jersey</media:city>
                  <media:country>United States</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>US</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sun, 21 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2586</guid>
                  <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 09:23:40 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2586.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2586.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Tokyo's sideways rain: nature's dance of wind and water</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a mesmerizing spectacle captured on August 1, 2023, from the heart of Tokyo, Japan, @4H6M8u0YmemZwmj shared a breathtaking video of sideways rain cascading down window panes. As nature's elements collided, the wind's mighty force compelled the raindrops to dance sideways, creating a captivating display of nature's power and beauty. The video serves as a vivid reminder of the unpredictable yet awe-inspiring wonders of the natural world, leaving viewers in awe of the harmonious choreography between wind and water. </media:description>
                  <media:keywords>wind,rain,sideways,video,Tokyo,Japan,nature,spectacle,mesmerizing,window,panes,dance,elements,force,beauty,power,display,awe,urban,landscape</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Tokyo </media:city>
                  <media:country>Japan</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>JP</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Weather</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Tue, 1 Aug 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2600</guid>
                  <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 13:12:22 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2600.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2600.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Resourceful feline masters the art of door-opening: a fascinating tale from Jepara, Indonesia!</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a captivating video captured by @muktafil on April 24, 2023, in Jepara, Indonesia, an astonishing feat unfolded as their clever cat showcased its ingenuity. The footage showcases the feline effortlessly opening the door to the house, by jumping on the door handle leaving its owner in awe of its newfound talent. Expressing his astonishment, the author stated, "I was surprised that the cat opened the door by itself, now if you put it outside, it will open the door. Don't know where it learned from." The video has since captured the hearts of viewers worldwide, as they marvel at the resourceful cat's ability to conquer the seemingly insurmountable obstacle. This extraordinary tale serves as a reminder of the intelligence and adaptability possessed by our feline companions.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>clever,cat,door,opening,video,Jepara,Indonesia,surprise,talent,resourceful,ingenuity,amazement,owner,outside,learn,astonishment,heartwarming,intelligence,adaptability,feline</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Jepara</media:city>
                  <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>ID</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2578</guid>
                  <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 07:29:30 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2578.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2578.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Love blossoms at a birthday party: tender smiles of a toddler</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a heartwarming moment captured by @ayreeeshh_ on March 12, 2023, at a birthday party in Las Piñas, Manila, Philippines, a two-year-old boy named Drei melted hearts as he looked tenderly at a little girl named Aliah. The usually quiet and well-behaved toddler seemed to be smitten with Aliah, flashing sweet smiles and even raising his eyebrows at her, giving the impression of a young love in the making. Drei's mother shared the adorable video, describing how her son became seemingly interested in Aliah, and it quickly became a viral sensation, spreading joy and warmth across the internet. This endearing encounter serves as a reminder of the innocent and pure connections that can blossom even among the youngest of hearts.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>love,toddler,birthday,party,smiles,tender,falling,in,young,children,innocence,adorable,viral,internet,connections,heartwarming,Manila,Philippines,Aliah,Drei,@ayreeeshh_</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Las Piñas, Manila</media:city>
                  <media:country>Philippines</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>PH</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Heartwarming</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2592</guid>
                  <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 10:51:48 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2592.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2592.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Bathroom bliss: Indonesian cat's unique way to beat the heat</media:title>
                  <media:description>In Yogyakarta, Indonesia, a heartwarming video captured by @bagus_muhammad_ on March 28, 2023, showcases the adorable antics of his feline companion during a hot day. The short clip features his cat lying flat on its stomach in the cool confines of the bathroom, delightfully spreading its hind legs for ultimate relaxation. As temperatures rise, it seems this clever kitty has found its perfect oasis for beating the heat. With a contented expression on its face, it's evident that the bathroom has become the preferred spot for the cat to seek respite from the sweltering weather. </media:description>
                  <media:keywords>cat,bathroom,Indonesia,Yogyakarta,video,pet,feline,hot,heat,adorable,antics,relaxation,hind legs,oasis,cool,weather,comfort,pets,content,warmer days</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Yogyakarta</media:city>
                  <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>ID</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2577</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 08:17:01 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2577.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2577.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Cake mishap: hilarious family moment in Ankara, Turkey</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a heartwarming yet comical family moment captured in Ankara, Turkey, a video shared by @amywinehouzze on July 15, 2023, showcased their little one indulging in a cake while kneeling on a dining chair. The child's innocent delight was infectious as they merrily savored the cake in one hand, but alas, laughter ensued as the sweet treat slipped from their grasp while trying to juggle it with the other hand. Surrounding family members couldn't help but burst into fits of laughter, turning the mishap into an unforgettable memory. This endearing scene reminds us of the simple joys and shared laughter that bring families together, creating cherished moments to be cherished for years to come.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>cake,kid,dining,table,Ankara,Turkey,video,laughter,family,moment,comical,mishap,sweet,treat,delight,memorable,joy,shared,precious,memory</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Ankara</media:city>
                  <media:country>Turkey</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>TR</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Fails and Funnies</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2581</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023 17:45:47 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2581.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2581.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Tranquil moments: Tokyo's beloved dog relishes in shallow creek at favorite park</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a heartwarming scene captured on June 24, 2023, in Tokyo, Japan, @mr.donbei_inu shared a delightful video of his beloved dog finding sheer bliss in a small, slow creek at their favorite park. The four-legged companion appeared completely at ease, comfortably resting its head on the surface of the shallow water, joyfully savoring the gentle flow around it. Unlike most dogs, this furry friend chose not to swim but found pure contentment in merely basking in the refreshing water. With a serene expression, the canine seemed to have discovered a little piece of paradise amidst the bustling city, making this tranquil spot its most cherished destination in the park.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>dog,creek,park,Tokyo,Japan,chilling,water,shallow,serene,bliss,favorite,video,pet,companion,contentment,relaxation,joy,tranquility,peaceful,happiness</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Tokyo</media:city>
                  <media:country>Japan</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>JP</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2593</guid>
                  <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 10:52:42 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2593.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2593.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Devastating wildfire strikes near Volos, Greece</media:title>
                  <media:description>On July 27, 2023, a destructive wildfire ravaged the area near Volos, Greece, causing significant damage to an ammunition depot situated in the coastal town of Nea Aghialos. The depot, belonging to the Greek air force, was engulfed in flames, leading to powerful explosions that echoed through the region. Local media reported on the incident, and officials took immediate action, ordering the evacuation of several communities in the severely impacted Magnesia area along the northern coast of Athens. As the fires continued to spread, @peterjaygood captured a video showcasing smoke billowing from a distance from the fires near Volos. The situation remained critical, with authorities and emergency services working tirelessly to contain the blaze and protect the affected communities.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>wildfire,volos,greece,ammunition,depot,explosions,evacuation,magnesia,coastal,nea aghialos,greek air force,damage,smoke,fires,video,@peterjaygood,media,officials,communities,Athens</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Volos</media:city>
                  <media:country>Greece</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>GR</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>News</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2575</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 07:26:05 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2575.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2575.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Skyscraper fire and crane collapse: dramatic scene unfolds at 41st and 10th Ave, New York</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a harrowing incident on the 26th of July, 2023, at the intersection of 41st and 10th Ave in New York City, USA, a devastating fire broke out on top of a skyscraper, accompanied by a catastrophic crane collapse. The intense scene was captured by @akofink, who shared a chilling video showcasing smoke billowing from the building's pinnacle. The social media post was captioned, "Crane collapse and fire! 41st and 10th Ave. First responders on the scene." The incident prompted an immediate response from first responders who rushed to the location to combat the raging blaze and assess the extent of the damage. </media:description>
                  <media:keywords>skyscraper,fire,crane,collapse,New York,USA,video,smoke,41st,10th Ave,incident,responders,damage,investigation,social media,tragedy,authorities,intersection,billowing,chilling</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>New York City</media:city>
                  <media:country>United States</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>US</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>News</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2551</guid>
                  <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023 18:25:43 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2551.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2551.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Enchanting encounter: friendly dolphin delights swimmer at Suishohama Beach, Japan</media:title>
                  <media:description>On July 17th, 2023, at Suishohama Beach in Mihama, Mikata District, Japan, a remarkable scene unfolded as a curious dolphin made a surprise appearance near the shore. @Ooo_MEN_ captured the heartwarming moment on video, showing the dolphin playfully interacting with a lone swimmer using a floater. The extraordinary encounter left beachgoers in awe as they witnessed the gentle marine creature approaching and engaging with the delighted individual. </media:description>
                  <media:keywords>dolphin,beach,interaction,swimmer,floater,video,Japan,Mihama,Mikata District,Suishohama Beach,nature,wildlife,encounter,playful,surprise,curious,harmony,awe,enchanting,filmed</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Mihama, Mikata District</media:city>
                  <media:country>Japan</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>JP</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2481</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/401402ff-22eb-4a49-9a06-dfbde13add42.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/cef347b0-35ba-4fd5-bd4e-6ef4fc575661.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Massive blaze strikes Changzhou food processing factory</media:title>
                  <media:description>On June 28th, 2023, a massive fire broke out in a food processing factory in Changzhou, China, causing thick smoke to billow from the scene and the fire to rapidly expand. @ChangzhouXinbeiPhysicalChemistryTeacher captured this video footage of the raging inferno while passing by the area. The cause of the fire is still under investigation, but officials have confirmed that there were no casualties resulting from the incident.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>fire,factory,changzhou,china,smoke,blaze,video,footage,accident,investigation,officials,casualties,inferno,nearby,raging,food,processing,thick,billowing,expanding</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Changzhou</media:city>
                  <media:country>China</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>CN</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>News</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2452</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/ba2676b5-b683-4842-b9c2-b654355ffb33.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/bfa4d7bf-92bc-4a13-8d48-f1622e36d1f3.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Unexpected mishap: model's dramatic fall steals the spotlight at Pekanbaru's fashion show</media:title>
                  <media:description>In an unfortunate turn of events at a fashion show held in Pekanbaru, Indonesia, a model took a sudden tumble off the stage, capturing the attention of onlookers. The incident, caught on video on April 23rd, 2023, by @babangg_r and shared on social media, showcased the model's unexpected fall. Concerned individuals quickly rushed to her aid, ensuring her safety and well-being. </media:description>
                  <media:keywords>fashion,show,model,fall,stage,incident,Pekanbaru,Indonesia,video,@babangg_r,attention,onlookers,social media,unexpected,aid,safety,well-being,live events,resilience,support</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Pekanbaru</media:city>
                  <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>ID</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Fails and Funnies</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sun, 23 Apr 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2421</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/7faaac9e-44e9-4e29-be47-470e79fccdbf.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2421.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Michigan's skyline vanishes: Detroit engulfed in smoke as Canadian wildfires blanket the region</media:title>
                  <media:description>Detroit, Michigan, USA - A video captured by @Michigameman313 on June 27th, 2023, reveals a disquieting sight as Michigan becomes shrouded in dense smoke originating from the ongoing wildfires in Canada. With the wildfires raging for several months now, more than a third of the US population, stretching from the Midwest to the East Coast, finds themselves under air quality alerts due to the pervasive reach of the Canadian wildfire smoke. The skyline of Detroit disappears behind a haze, casting an eerie atmosphere over the city as the impacts of the wildfires make their presence felt across the region.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>smoke,video,Detroit,Michigan,Canada,wildfires,air quality,alerts,Midwest,East Coast,USA,sight,shrouded,haze,skyline,eerie,atmosphere,impacts,region</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Detroit, Michigan </media:city>
                  <media:country>United States</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>US</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>News</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2333</guid>
                  <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 11:51:14 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/462bf183-d2c6-405d-9566-0b611444c92d.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/f91c84a9-efc3-4579-b07a-49e02a604201.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Dirty surprise: cat returns home with sewage water makeover!</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a surprising turn of events, a video captured by @ayumispa from Madiun, Indonesia on May 2, 2023, revealed the unanticipated return of her cat, sporting a face covered in dirty sewage water. Despite having groomed the feline just the day before, it seemed that mischievous curiosity had led the adventurous cat to an unexpected encounter with the unpleasant liquid.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>sewage,water,dirty,cat,face,groomed,video,captured,@ayumispa,Madiun,Indonesia,surprising,unanticipated,adventurous,curiosity,mischievous,encounter,messy,makeover,attention</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Madiun</media:city>
                  <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>ID</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Tue, 2 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2356</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/1abc7114-68f8-4ac1-ac99-cbf5d30b4de3.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/39903d9d-202a-42c4-9282-60b37cded5da.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Action-packed movie filming in Chisinau takes a dramatic turn as car rams parked bus!</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a stunning turn of events in Chisinau, Moldova, a movie filming session took a thrilling and unexpected twist as a car intentionally rammed into a parked bus. The dramatic scene, captured by @nazligian_ on July 23, 2023, showcased the heart-pounding moment when the car, utilizing a purpose-built ramp, accelerated towards the stationary bus. With precision and skill, the car collided with the bus, creating a breathtaking spectacle that left onlookers in awe. Fortunately, there were no reported injuries as the filming was conducted in a closed-off area in the city center. The incident occurred as part of the action-packed movie production, adding an authentic touch to the adrenaline-filled scenes being brought to life on the silver screen.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>movie,filming,chisinau,moldova,car,bus,ramp,action,thrilling,unexpected,dramatic,spectacle,onlookers,injury-free,closed-off,center,adrenaline,scenes,silver screen,production</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Chisinau </media:city>
                  <media:country>Moldova</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>MD</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sun, 23 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2563</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 07:49:50 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2563.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2563.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Raccoon's Miron misadventures: a heartwarming birthday surprise!</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a heartwarming tale of misadventures, @raccoon_miron from St. Petersburg, Russia, captured a touching video while searching for her beloved raccoon pet, Miron on April 27, 2023. The furry troublemaker had managed to scatter her belongings all over the apartment on the eve of his birthday, leaving her in tears, fearing he had escaped through the window. However, to her relief, Miron was just being mischievous and had fallen asleep amidst her things. The emotional rollercoaster of worry and joy unfolded in the video.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>raccoon,miron,video,pet,birthday,surprise,misadventures,St. Petersburg,Russia,apartment,balcony,work,order,sobbing,window,smart,boy,asleep,things,love,joy.</media:keywords>
                  <media:city> St. Petersburg</media:city>
                  <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2558</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 07:43:53 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2558.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2558.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Startling encounter: snake dangles and vanishes in Ho Chi Minh city home</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a harrowing incident captured on a home camera in Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam, a resident, @congdonghoainhon, had an unsettling surprise. On May 12, 2023, the camera alerted him to movement in his bedroom, and upon checking the footage, he was startled to see a snake dangling near the camera. Moments later, the snake fell out of sight, leaving him alarmed. Rushing back home, he searched his room diligently but found no trace of the elusive serpent. Speculating that it might have taken refuge inside the air conditioner, the resident remains on edge, unable to locate the reptile.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>snake,camera,bedroom,video,home,work,warn,movement,shocked,rummage,find,air conditioner,Vietnam,Ho Chi Minh City,resident,encounter,alert,elusive,reptile,tags</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Ho Chi Minh City</media:city>
                  <media:country>Vietnam</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>VN</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Fri, 12 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2528</guid>
                  <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 20:58:54 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2528.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2528.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Makeup prank turns tears to smiles: a tale of fake eyebrows and sweet relief</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a surprising turn of events during a makeup session on July 10, 2023 in Toronto, Canada, @artisanglow pulled off an eyebrow prank on her unsuspecting client who had come for makeup on her anniversary. Capturing the whole ordeal on video, the client's smile quickly faded into tears as she was appalled by the fake eyebrows. Unaware that it was all just a prank, the client's distress was evident. However, @artisanglow swiftly revealed the truth and corrected the brows, leading to a sigh of relief and a beaming smile from the client.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>anniversary,makeup,prank,client,eyebrows,video,Toronto,Canada,smile,tears,relief,artisanglow,fake,surprise,session,distress,correction,beaming,small,tags</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Toronto </media:city>
                  <media:country>Canada</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>CA</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Fails and Funnies</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2522</guid>
                  <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 20:52:21 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2522.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2522.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Fierce yet gentle: Russian serval cat's playful encounter with watchful dog</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a captivating video captured by @mainecoonnhaching on July 8th, 2023, in Dau Mot city, Binh Duong province, Vietnam, a serval cat imported from Russia displayed a striking mix of ferocity and tenderness. The video shows the cat enthusiastically chasing after an object thrown towards their glass door, revealing the curious dog outside. The cat runs straight to the door and, though fierce in appearance, slumps its head while retrieving the toy. The dog, kept outside to prevent accidents indoors, remains safe behind a fenced gate, thanks to careful guarding.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>cat,video,serval,Russia,fierce,gentle,dog,play,glass,door,chase,curious,outside,safe,fenced,gate,guarding,harmony,environment,adorable</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Dau Mot city, Binh Duong province</media:city>
                  <media:country>Vietnam</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>VN</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sat, 8 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2498</guid>
                  <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 13:13:12 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2498.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2498.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Paws-itively independent: clever canine takes treat shopping to new heights!</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a heartwarming display of intelligence and independence, a remarkable dog named LeeRoy has stolen the hearts of locals in Tuckerman, Arkansas, USA. A video captured by @mikey35232 on April 7th, 2023, shows LeeRoy confidently strolling in a mart with its owner, carefully selecting his favorite treat, and astonishingly making his way to the counter with its owner. According to his proud owner, Mikey, this impressive feat is a testament to their strong bond, as he has been taking LeeRoy everywhere since he was a mere 4 weeks old. Last year, LeeRoy began demonstrating his incredible ability to choose his own treats.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>dog,mart,treat,shopping,independence,intelligence,bond,video,Arkansas,Tuckerman,LeeRoy,owner,favorite,pay,confidence,remarkable,awe,loyalty,capture,heartwarming</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Tuckerman, Arkansas</media:city>
                  <media:country>United States</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>US</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Fri, 7 Apr 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2440</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/8384c6d8-bb0a-4b78-be59-5860b954b152.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/d42f7d6e-76c5-4cb0-8612-81466a1ac76f.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Dramatic scene in Binh Duong: cutter crumbles under torrential rainfall!</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a captivating video captured by @dung_200895 on June 29th, 2023, in Binh Duong province, Vietnam, a gut-wrenching incident unfolded as a heavy downpour took its toll on a residential house. The video shows the shocking moment when a gutter succumbed to the weight of the pouring rain, detached itself from the roof, and crashed onto the ground below. The sheer force of the rainfall proved to be too much for the gutter. The man in the video is very lucky and he is fine.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>gutter,falling,rain,heavy,video,Binh Duong,province,Vietnam,weather,incident,house,downpour,weight,pouring,detached,roof,ground,intense,nature,infrastructure</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Binh Duong province</media:city>
                  <media:country>Vietnam</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>VN</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Weather</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2419</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/d0776845-1d06-4e3f-b894-980ad03bf96b.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/915d99ca-f843-4f9a-b531-2010f7293195.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Adorable surprise: little Valentina's birthday dance with cat melts hearts worldwide!</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a heartwarming moment captured on camera, a small girl named Valentina stole the internet's heart as she danced with a cat at her mom's birthday party in Lancaster, Texas, USA. The adorable video, filmed by @rockysoto74 on  October 1, 2022 and shared on TikTok, showcased Valentina holding the cat by its fore legs, as if they were hugging, while dancing to her sister's favorite song. Little did the author know that the innocent video would go viral overnight, garnering immense love and attention from people around the world. Despite being an unintended surprise, Valentina's delightful dance with her feline friend resonated with viewers, spreading joy and warmth in a single, heartfelt moment.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>dance,cat,girl,viral,heartwarming,birthday,party,Texas,USA,video,TikTok,hug,favorite,song,surprise,love,attention,joy,warmth,moment</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Lancaster, Texas</media:city>
                  <media:country>United States</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>US</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Heartwarming</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sat, 1 Oct 2022</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2322</guid>
                  <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 07:45:47 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/69e155e9-a4fb-49de-b050-19fed0a49fbd.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/af8b06eb-b934-44a6-ae4b-543d06426ff2.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Captivating lightning illuminates Fredericksburg's night sky, creating a dazzling display</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a captivating video captured by @thegavinwhite24 on June 26th, 2023, in Fredericksburg, Virginia, USA, the night sky was momentarily transformed into a breathtaking spectacle. As the author drove through the darkness, a bolt of bright streak lightning shattered the tranquility, illuminating the surroundings with an intensity that rivaled daylight. Lasting a mere five seconds, this incredible display left the author in awe, capturing the attention of viewers worldwide. </media:description>
                  <media:keywords>lightning,night,Fredericksburg,Virginia,USA,video,driving,bright,streak,sky,day,moment,captivating,intense,power,awe,wonder,nature,raw,spectacle</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Fredericksburg, Virginia</media:city>
                  <media:country>United States</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>US</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Weather</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2327</guid>
                  <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 13:56:15 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/04c6f5a9-23cf-4cdc-94cd-25f934369613.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/3a12df32-fd41-4f1c-b6e9-e320859c7403.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Runaway cow wreaks havoc on parked motorbikes</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a surprising turn of events, chaos unfolded outside a hospital entrance in Balikpapan, Indonesia, on June 28th, 2023 when a cow dashed through the area and collided with parked motorbikes. A quick-thinking individual, who goes by the name @myselfmyenemy, managed to capture the bizarre incident on video. Fear gripped him as he watched the cow hurtling toward him, prompting him to swiftly record the scene on his phone. Fortunately, the motorbikes emerged unscathed.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>cow,motorbikes,incident,video,Balikpapan,Indonesia,chaos,hospital,entrance,@myselfmyenemy,fear,collision,parked,unexpected,astonished,moment,captured,unscathed,injuries,turn of events</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Balikpapan</media:city>
                  <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>ID</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2361</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/4fa1c59a-7447-4973-94aa-8d5d4714a91a.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/ee139c81-052c-4891-b39b-51d951c723d0.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Catnap couture: adorable feline caught napping in boutique's pink mavin!</media:title>
                  <media:description>In the city of Borisov, Belarus, on July 16, 2023, a heartwarming scene unfolded in a second clothes boutique. Local resident @ugimaster stumbled upon a delightful sight as he entered the store - a contented cat fast asleep amidst the clothes. Its furry head was cozily nestled on a soft pink mavin, adding an extra touch of cuteness to the scene. The video captured by @ugimaster quickly went viral, spreading smiles and warming hearts across the internet.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>cat,sleeping,clothes,boutique,Borisov,Belarus,@ugimaster,video,peaceful,pink,mavin,adorable,feline,nap,city,viral,internet,heartwarming,cozy,cute</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Borisov</media:city>
                  <media:country>Belarus</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>BY</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2562</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 07:47:37 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2562.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2562.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Massive moth invasion: swarms of flying creatures fill the night skies in Yelets, Russia</media:title>
                  <media:description>On the night of Monday, July 24, 2023, the city of Yelets in the Lipetsk region, Russia, experienced a bizarre phenomenon as drivers encountered a massive invasion of insects. Thousands of flying creatures, identified as moths, enveloped the road lights, creating "swarm clouds" that obstructed the path on the Karakum bridge. Disturbing footage recorded by a driver showcased the surreal scene, where the insects swarmed around vehicles, making navigation challenging. </media:description>
                  <media:keywords>insects,invasion,Yelets,Russia,night,Monday,July 24,Lipetsk,drivers,filmed,massive,flying,creatures,swarm,clouds,Karakum,bridge,moths,video,way,drove</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Yelets, Lipetsk region</media:city>
                  <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ODD</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2556</guid>
                  <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 14:56:15 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2556.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2556.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Severe flooding wreaks havoc in Akita Prefecture, Japan</media:title>
                  <media:description>As of July 15, 2023, Akita Prefecture, Japan, is facing ongoing disruptions due to severe flooding caused by heavy downpours. The Japan Meteorological Agency (JMA) has issued orange-level heavy rain and landslide warnings, along with yellow flood advisories across the region. The storms, accompanied by strong winds, lightning, hail, and potential tornadoes, have led to dangerous river levels and widespread transportation disruptions. Several cities and towns, including Akita, Daisen, Noshiro, Oga, Fujisato, Gojome, and Hachirogata, are under evacuation orders. The Babame and Uchikawa rivers have overflowed, causing significant flooding and damage to properties in affected areas. Tragically, one person has already lost their life due to the heavy rain. The Akita Shinkansen has been suspended between Morioka and Akita stations, further exacerbating the situation. @be5b48tgmailcom captured a video showing flooding in Akita station east exit rotary.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>flooding,akita,japan,weather,disruptions,heavyrain,landslides,warnings,evacuation,storms,strongwinds,lightning,hail,tornadoes,riveroverflow,transportation,propertydamage,poweroutages,meteorologicalagency,rainfall</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Akita Prefecture</media:city>
                  <media:country>Japan</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>JP</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Weather</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2476</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/4e66ff04-2157-4f3d-89c2-7ca8f905ef47.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/ecc272bb-73a1-44ff-bbd0-08aac593cb30.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Retired military working Dog's instinct shines through: a playful encounter with a puffy jacket</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a heartwarming video captured by @boepeepk9 on May 27th, 2023, in Crestview, Florida, USA, her 10-year-old retired Military Working Dog named Gina displayed her training instincts. While trying on a puffy jacket resembling the bite suit tops used in Controlled Aggression training, the author noticed Gina eyeing the jacket intently. Curious to test her response, she jerked her arm, expecting Gina to bite. True to her training, Gina gently bit the jacket, demonstrating her obedience and quick reflexes. With a soft verbal correction, the author reassured Gina, who immediately showed remorse. </media:description>
                  <media:keywords>retired,military,working dog,video,dogs,puffy jacket,bite suit,training,controlled aggression,eyeing,bite,instincts,obedience,reflexes,verbal correction,remorse,love,affection,commands,capture</media:keywords>
                  <media:city> Crestview, Florida</media:city>
                  <media:country>United States</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>US</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sat, 27 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2438</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/55726dec-a97e-49d6-8f33-28effcccf647.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/3ce0ec3f-93df-4e12-ae64-57cd1de0bbcd.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Intense rainfall unleashes torrential river in West Point, New York</media:title>
                  <media:description>On July 9th, 2023, @MikeGriff76 captured a captivating video in West Point, New York, USA, showcasing a river swollen with raging waters.  The mesmerizing footage portrayed the result of incredible rainfall in the region, where an astonishing 8-10 inches of rain poured down within a few short hours.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>devastating,flooding,damage,West Point,NY,rains,river,video,incredible,hours,more rain,dangerous,situation,captivated,assumption,mesmerizing,footage,rainfall,region,power</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>West Point, New York</media:city>
                  <media:country>United States</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>US</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Weather</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sun, 9 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2422</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/06c04219-d895-43e8-abc2-8711ecbbd3e3.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/f94e5fb1-ccae-48ac-b784-dbd9b13deacc.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Frantic plea for creation: a son's cry unleashes chaos</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a candid moment captured on camera on June 28th, 2023, a heartfelt plea for a piece of paper and pen escalated into an unexpected scene of chaos. @anhbee197, and her son were captured on their home camera in Hai Duong province, Vietnam. As the son relentlessly cried for the desired stationery, frustration mounted when his plea went unanswered. In a moment of frustration, he forcefully pushed the bedside table, causing it to crash to the ground and scatter its contents. Despite the mother's efforts to prevent the mishap, her attempts proved futile. With the debris settled, she sat in contemplation, gazing at her son, as the aftermath of his outburst unfolded before them.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>crying,paper,pen,chaos,frustration,camera,home,table,bed,mother,son,plea,push,falling,scattering,failed,looking,candid,captured,aftermath</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Hai Duong province</media:city>
                  <media:country>Vietnam</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>VN</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Fails and Funnies</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2415</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/1d919518-1477-4c9f-add7-711b13643db9.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/c3a9dd97-9746-4b95-b61b-8d416b4f711b.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Playful pursuit: Sasuke the dog's hilarious chase with a clever crow</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a delightful scene captured by @sasuke_2017.0808 on June 14th, 2023, in Tokyo, Japan, a video showcased the amusing encounter between a persistent dog named Sasuke and a clever black crow. The canine's excitement was sparked as it spotted the crow perched on the balcony. However, instead of flying away, the mischievous bird continuously relocated to different parts of the balcony, keeping Sasuke in a constant pursuit. The author, found great amusement in witnessing this comical interaction between his dog and the crafty crow, creating a moment filled with laughter and joy.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>dog,crow,chase,balcony,Tokyo,Japan,video,Sasuke,amusement,laughter,pets,animals,funny,entertaining,playful,clever,mischievous,owner,encounter,joy</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Tokyo </media:city>
                  <media:country>Japan</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>JP</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2328</guid>
                  <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 11:51:52 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/7c1bad1f-9d05-4c66-bca4-754b7fa5d8d5.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/77ce2601-f34d-4050-a660-13c350ae6a0b.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Nature's chameleon: a mesmerizing lake camouflage makeup transformation</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a captivating video captured by @GoldieYabes on  November 26th, 2020 at Burnham Park in Baguio City, Philippines, she takes viewers on a mesmerizing journey of transformation. With deft brushstrokes and a keen eye for detail, Goldie skillfully applies makeup to blend seamlessly with the stunning lake background. Using paints that perfectly match the colors of the water, she effortlessly camouflages herself, becoming a living chameleon amidst nature's beauty. The video showcases each step of her artistic process, revealing the gradual metamorphosis into a harmonious blend with the surroundings. </media:description>
                  <media:keywords>lake,camouflage,makeup,transformation,video,beauty,art,nature,chameleon,mesmerizing,Baguio,Philippines,brushstrokes,colors,water,background,artist,surroundings,process,wonders</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Baguio City</media:city>
                  <media:country>Philippines</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>PH</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Cool</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Thu, 26 Nov 2020</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2354</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/c2f206ef-825e-465b-bdb8-c022b3afebb7.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2354.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Intense storms ravage Northern Italy: Monza and Milan on high alert as heavy rain and strong winds unleash havoc</media:title>
                  <media:description>On July 24th, 2023, Monza, Italy, experienced the wrath of an intense rainstorm accompanied by powerful winds, as captured in a video by @ylesweet666. The heavy downpour and strong gusts wreaked havoc on parts of northern Italy, leading to an orange alert in Monza and Milan on July 25th. The region faced challenging weather conditions, with the video depicting the impact on Monza.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>rainstorm,winds,northern Italy,Monza,Milan,intense,orange alert,weather,video,July 24th,2023,@ylesweet666,car,trees,havoc,disruptions,caution,storms,weather event,powerful,heavy rain</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Monza</media:city>
                  <media:country>Italy</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>IT</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Weather</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2538</guid>
                  <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 14:18:52 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2538.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2538.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Slippery shenanigans: Fatty the dog's hilarious underground parking adventure!</media:title>
                  <media:description>In Jiangxi province, China, on June 9th, 2023, a playful dog named Fatty found himself in a comical situation at the underground parking lot. His owner, Fatty, captured the moment on video as the excited canine ran towards her, only to slip on the wet floor. With a quick recovery, Fatty tried to hide his embarrassment by looking forward, creating a humorous and endearing scene. Thankfully, no harm was done, and Fatty's misadventures added a touch of laughter to an otherwise ordinary day at the parking lot.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>june 9th,2023,jiangxi province,china,fatty,dog,video,running,sliding,wet floor,underground parking,car,water,slip,embarrassment,owner,playfulness,comical,recovery,laughter,misadventure</media:keywords>
                  <media:city> Jiangxi province</media:city>
                  <media:country>China</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>CN</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Fri, 9 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2527</guid>
                  <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 21:01:29 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2527.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2527.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Bra brawl: furry guardians turn fashion feud in Selangor, Malaysia!</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a surprising and amusing spectacle captured by @rita_roslie in Selangor, Malaysia on June 28, 2023, two dogs were caught on camera engaging in a hilarious tug-of-war over a bra. The canines seemed to have stumbled upon the lingerie in question and were passionately tugging at each end, playfully bickering over their newfound treasure. As one dog clenched its teeth onto one side of the bra, the other dog stubbornly held onto the opposite end, creating a comical fashion feud. The author, the eyewitness, revealed that one of the dogs involved was her loyal garden guardian, but she was clueless about where they had discovered the bra.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>dogs,fighting,bra,tugofwar,hilarious,spectacle,Malaysia,Selangor,video,canines,fashion,feud,treasure,comical,viral,pets,quirky,antics,animals,guardians</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Selangor</media:city>
                  <media:country>Malaysia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>MY</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2500</guid>
                  <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 14:26:17 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2500.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2500.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Snake's surprise: when a reptile acts like a cat!</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a surprising and adorable video captured by @children.of.loki on June 13th, 2023, in Texas, USA, a snake displayed remarkably cat-like behavior. The footage shows the snake slithering around the house until its owner scratches its back. Astonishingly, the reptile bends the area where it receives the scratch, seemingly relishing the affectionate gesture. Captioned as "My snake is a cat," this extraordinary behavior showcases the fascinating and unexpected similarities between these two vastly different creatures.
</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>snake,reptile,pet,Texas,USA,video,cat-like,behavior,adorable,surprising,scratch,slithering,house,owner,affectionate,gesture,fascination,creature,similarities,captivating</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Texas</media:city>
                  <media:country>United States</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>US</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2484</guid>
                  <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 09:35:26 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/dccfb477-e6cb-4f39-a2e9-be93aaab4eff.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/30a86124-8fc3-4dc2-89dc-ffb246cfc1f3.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Doggie oasis: Beha finds refreshing relief from the heat by the shore</media:title>
                  <media:description>On June 17th, 2023, in Balashikha, Moscow, Russia, a heartwarming video captured the attention of many as @nemez_bexa shared a delightful moment with her dog. The scorching heat couldn't keep Beha away from cooling off in the water near the shore. In the short clip, the dog is seen seated in the water, content and relaxed. </media:description>
                  <media:keywords>dog,water,shore,hot,Beha,play,video,Balashikha,Moscow,Russia,heat,pet,playful,refresh,summer,cool,socialmedia,cute,joy,happiness,retrieve</media:keywords>
                  <media:city> Balashikha, Moscow</media:city>
                  <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2477</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/ed8cd420-ed98-48df-9484-6be4d907eff5.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/9b1fdfa0-bae1-40b8-8d27-d41efc0aac8a.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Fearful furry friends: Ball the dog and a playful deer's zoo encounter in Beijing!</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a heartwarming yet cautious encounter at a zoo in Beijing, China, a dog named Ball had a surprising interaction with a curious deer. The moment was captured on video by @todaythemoonisnotopen on July 3rd, 2023. As Ball sat inside the car, a deer approached, seemingly eager to engage in a kiss. However, the dog's apprehension was evident, and it quickly retreated back into the safety of the vehicle. Despite the brief interaction, the endearing exchange between the two animals left a lasting impression, highlighting the beauty of unexpected connections in the animal kingdom.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>playful,deer,dog,zoo,Beijing,China,encounter,video,July3rd,2023,curious,kiss,car,interaction,animals,connection,heartwarming,cautious,moment,captured</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Beijing</media:city>
                  <media:country>China</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>CN</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Mon, 3 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2465</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/291686df-edaf-40a2-b29e-324e7310ae8e.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/59533475-0fb1-4a59-b179-39812ed84054.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Thrilling river adventure: brother's epic wakeboarding stunt delights all!</media:title>
                  <media:description>In an adrenaline-pumping video captured by @mr_valerian in Salihorsk, Belarus, on July 2nd, 2023, his brother showcased an impressive wakeboarding stunt. Tied to a car with a rope, he skillfully water-skied on the river near the road, all while avoiding potential hazards like posts along the way. As the video unfolds, it becomes apparent that the cable came close to catching on the posts, but @mr_valerian cleverly controlled the situation from the car's backseat, ensuring a smooth and exhilarating ride for his brother. Laughter and excitement filled the air as the brother stood up on the wakeboard, showcasing his enjoyment throughout the daring feat. With precise execution and a touch of thrill, the video captivated viewers worldwide, leaving them in awe of the daring waterskiing adventure.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>wakeboarding,river,stunt,car,rope,Belarus,adventure,water,road,posts,thrilling,excitement,laughter,skill,control,ride,video,brother,enjoy,daring</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Salihorsk</media:city>
                  <media:country>Belarus</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>BY</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Cool</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sun, 2 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2453</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/36984f91-3c1e-4780-acb8-beb6d6764df9.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/bf83c05e-baff-4f72-990e-20c2b480fafe.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Devastating tornado strikes Barrhaven, Ottawa: homes damaged, power outages reported</media:title>
                  <media:description>A powerful tornado struck the suburban area of Barrhaven in Ottawa, Canada, on July 13th, 2023, causing significant damage to homes and leaving a trail of destruction. A video captured by @TheShagtor showed the tornado trying to form near his house. David Sills, the executive director of the Northern Tornadoes Project, confirmed the tornado's occurrence, which hit approximately 25 kilometers south of downtown Ottawa. Reports indicated that around 125 homes in the affected area suffered various degrees of damage, ranging from roofs being torn off to broken windows and downed trees. Moreover, approximately 1,600 homes were left without power, with concerns of potential gas leaks due to the destruction. The impact of the tornado left residents in shock and authorities working diligently to restore normalcy and provide assistance to those affected by the incident.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>tornado,barrhaven,ottawa,canada,damage,homes,destruction,power outages,gas leaks,emergency,assistance,suburb,roofs,windows,trees,devastation,residents,authorities,recovery,Northern Tornadoes Project</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Barrhaven </media:city>
                  <media:country>Canada</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>CA</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>News</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2444</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/eb78110f-e301-42a2-983f-0e3e94641f4f.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/23469efd-d9fe-4693-8c06-f13d258b0925.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Overloaded motorbike sends friend tumbling in Yogyakarta, Indonesia</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a video captured by @ka_wula_alit on June 6th, 2023, in Yogyakarta, Indonesia, a friend's attempt to ride an overloaded motorbike and ended up in a comical mishap. The video shows the rider struggling to maintain balance as the motorbike's weight proves to be too much. After a few meters, the inevitable happens, and the friend takes a tumble.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>village,mishap,overloaded bike,falling,balance,Yogyakarta,Indonesia,video,friend,riding,comedy,accident,bike,weight,safety,rural,load management,humor,stumble,capture</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Yogyakarta</media:city>
                  <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>ID</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Fails and Funnies</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Tue, 6 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2435</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/cd21c59d-5b07-4098-9f09-60ad72c69ec4.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2435.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Quirky Yeti: cat asserts ownership over owner's resting foot in hilarious video!</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a heartwarming yet amusing video captured by @dymova_brows on December 14, 2022, in Zaporozhye, Ukraine, a 7-year-old cat named Yeti showcases its unique character. The footage shows Yeti attempting to keep its owner's foot still under the blanket while playfully growling like a dog when met with resistance. The quirky feline's predilections include strolls on the balcony and relishing wet food, but it fiercely guards its delicious meals from fellow feline companions. The short video captures Yeti's endearing and assertive personality, providing a delightful glimpse into the fascinating world of this furry friend.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>cat,yeti,video,quirky,owner,foot,bed,blanket,growl,dog,character,Zaporozhye,Ukraine,balcony,wet food,delicious,unique,feline,playful,adorable</media:keywords>
                  <media:city> Zaporozhye</media:city>
                  <media:country>Ukraine</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>UA</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2569</guid>
                  <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 07:20:35 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2569.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2569.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Emotional dilemma: heartwarming video shows child's tears turn into joy when offered money</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a touching video captured by @yhangespela on June 2, 2023, in San Mateo, Rizal, Philippines, a young child's conflicting emotions towards money were showcased. The footage depicted the child initially crying but quickly becoming quiet and even expressing a desire for more when presented with money. The heartwarming scene left viewers pondering the complexities of children's perceptions of money and the diverse range of emotions it can evoke in young minds.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>crying,money,child,emotions,video,touching,Philippines,San Mateo,young,tears,joy,desire,perception,mother,quiet,conflicting,heartwarming,captured,presented,note</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>San Mateo, Rizal</media:city>
                  <media:country>Philippines</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>PH</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Heartwarming</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Fri, 2 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2568</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 07:55:27 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2568.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2568.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Unique kitchen troubles: the gunshot sink that keeps dishwashing lively!</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a peculiar incident on May 7, 2023, in Halang, Calamba, Philippines, @pinunongjanjannn captured an amusing yet baffling video of his broken kitchen sink. The sink emitted gunshot-like sounds whenever opened, prompting the homeowner to comically mimic firing a gun. With shaking hands and a hint of humor, he declared, "You wouldn't get lazy washing your dishes if you have a sink like this." The peculiar and lively sink has undoubtedly brought a unique twist to the mundane task of dishwashing, leaving viewers both amused and curious about its mysterious malfunction.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>sink,kitchen,broken,gunshot,sounds,shaking,hands,shooting,dishes,lazy,amusing,video,Halang,Calamba,Philippines,homeowner,humor,malfunction,unique,curious.</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Halang, Calamba</media:city>
                  <media:country>Philippines</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>PH</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Fails and Funnies</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sun, 7 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2509</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 08:43:48 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2509.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2509.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                     </channel>
                  </rss>
                