<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
        <rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
        xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
        xmlns:openSearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearchrss/1.0/"
        xmlns:dfpvideo="http://api.google.com/dfpvideo"
        xmlns:tms="http://data.tmsapi.com/v1.1"
        version="2.0">
          <channel>
            <title>ViralBear videos</title>
            <dfpvideo:version>2</dfpvideo:version>
              
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Bear brawl at Guaipo Tiger Park: two black bears engage in fierce fight over food</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a thrilling and unexpected encounter at the Guaipo Tiger Park in Shenyang, Northeast China, two black bears engaged in a heated fight, captured on video by local resident @100millionfatballs on June 24, 2023. As she explored the living area of the black bears, the normally docile animals suddenly clashed, with their aggression escalating over a possible dispute for food. The shocking scene prompted the author to react quickly, loudly shouting in an attempt to intervene and put an end to the confrontation. Her bravery in the face of this intense encounter showcased the unpredictable nature of wildlife and served as a powerful reminder of the importance of respecting and preserving the delicate balance between humans and the animal kingdom.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>shenyang,china,black bears,fight,video,wildlife,park,encounter,food,aggression,shock,visitor,Guaipo Tiger Park,northeast,@100millionfatballs,nature,animals,conservation,bravery,balance</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Shenyang</media:city>
                  <media:country>China</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>CN</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2602</guid>
                  <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 13:12:52 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2602.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2602.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Playful and obedient: Khryapa's impressive 'swim' command!</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a heartwarming video captured by @mokryi_nosik_ on June 17, 2020, in Voronezh, Russia, her beloved dog, Khryapa, stole the spotlight with her incredible obedience and playful nature. The footage shows @mokryi_nosik_ talking to Khryapa in one of the rooms, when suddenly, the clever canine dashes off towards the bathroom. Without hesitation, Khryapa leaps into the bathtub, showcasing her impressive execution of the "swim" command. The three-year-old furry friend proves to be not only obedient but also full of joy and enthusiasm. Her charming antics have won the hearts of viewers worldwide, leaving a lasting impression of her delightful personality and the strong bond between her and her owner.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>playful,obedient,dog,swim,command,video,Khryapa,Voronezh,Russia,bathtub,bathroom,three years old,pet,canine,joy,love,bond,clever,cute,charming</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Voronezh</media:city>
                  <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2598</guid>
                  <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 10:57:32 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2598.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2598.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Playful corgi's adorable 'poof' act delights internet in St. Petersburg, Russia!</media:title>
                  <media:description>In an endearing and amusing video that captured hearts on social media, a Corgi named Leo from St. Petersburg, Russia, showcased his unique talent for playing "dead." The video, shared by @prokopenkokate on April 29, 2023, depicts Leo sitting peacefully on the floor before his owner mimics a shooting gesture with her hands. Surprisingly, the adorable pup immediately flops down, pretending to be "shot" as part of a playful command he has mastered. As a reward for his impressive performance, Leo eagerly awaits a treat, proving that his favorite command is the delightful and harmless "poof," leaving viewers charmed by this clever and lovable canine's antics.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>playful,corgi,leo,video,internet,acting,dog,Russia,St. Petersburg,pet,owner,gun,pretend,cute,charm,humor,social media,adorable,command,sweet</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>St. Petersburg</media:city>
                  <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sat, 29 Apr 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2595</guid>
                  <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 10:53:38 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2595.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2595.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Tranquil moments: Tokyo's beloved dog relishes in shallow creek at favorite park</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a heartwarming scene captured on June 24, 2023, in Tokyo, Japan, @mr.donbei_inu shared a delightful video of his beloved dog finding sheer bliss in a small, slow creek at their favorite park. The four-legged companion appeared completely at ease, comfortably resting its head on the surface of the shallow water, joyfully savoring the gentle flow around it. Unlike most dogs, this furry friend chose not to swim but found pure contentment in merely basking in the refreshing water. With a serene expression, the canine seemed to have discovered a little piece of paradise amidst the bustling city, making this tranquil spot its most cherished destination in the park.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>dog,creek,park,Tokyo,Japan,chilling,water,shallow,serene,bliss,favorite,video,pet,companion,contentment,relaxation,joy,tranquility,peaceful,happiness</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Tokyo</media:city>
                  <media:country>Japan</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>JP</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2593</guid>
                  <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 10:52:42 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2593.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2593.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Tenacious twig tug-of-war: a dog's unyielding affair with nature's bounty</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a delightful and amusing scene captured by @chelseareject on May 21, 2023, in Jersey City, New Jersey, USA, her four-legged companion exhibited an unshakeable determination during a playful encounter with nature. The video showcased the adorable pup clenching onto a sizable twig of a tree, despite the owner's best efforts to convince it otherwise. With @chelseareject's voice gently coaxing the dog to release its prized find, the resilient canine remained unyielding, steadfastly refusing to let go. Undeterred, they strolled along together, the furry protagonist proudly showcasing its prized possession in an endearing tug-of-war with the forces of nature. The heartwarming display of canine spirit and persistence resonated with viewers worldwide, capturing the essence of a special bond between humans and their loyal companions.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>tree,dog,twig,nature,Jersey City,USA,May,2023,video,pet,playful,determined,adorable,owner,walk,bonding,persistence,loyalty,companionship,endearing,capture</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Jersey City, New Jersey</media:city>
                  <media:country>United States</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>US</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sun, 21 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2586</guid>
                  <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 09:23:40 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2586.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2586.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Cat burglar in Buenos Aires: feline filches cash and cuddles up!</media:title>
                  <media:description>In an amusing incident in Buenos Aires, Argentina, on July 6, 2023, a mischievous cat turned into a daring thief. A video captured by @gaston__joaquin showed the feline delving into a handbag and snatching a bundle of money before darting off towards the bedroom. The curious owner followed the sneaky cat's trail to find it lounging on the bed with the stolen cash. This lighthearted escapade left everyone amused and highlighted the unpredictable antics of our four-legged companions.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>cat,thief,money,video,Buenos Aires,Argentina,handbag,bed,owner,amusing,feline,daring,curious,sneaky,trail,lounging,stolen,cash,lighthearted,antics</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Buenos Aires</media:city>
                  <media:country>Argentina</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>AR</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Thu, 6 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2585</guid>
                  <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 09:24:40 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2585.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2585.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Resourceful feline masters the art of door-opening: a fascinating tale from Jepara, Indonesia!</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a captivating video captured by @muktafil on April 24, 2023, in Jepara, Indonesia, an astonishing feat unfolded as their clever cat showcased its ingenuity. The footage showcases the feline effortlessly opening the door to the house, by jumping on the door handle leaving its owner in awe of its newfound talent. Expressing his astonishment, the author stated, "I was surprised that the cat opened the door by itself, now if you put it outside, it will open the door. Don't know where it learned from." The video has since captured the hearts of viewers worldwide, as they marvel at the resourceful cat's ability to conquer the seemingly insurmountable obstacle. This extraordinary tale serves as a reminder of the intelligence and adaptability possessed by our feline companions.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>clever,cat,door,opening,video,Jepara,Indonesia,surprise,talent,resourceful,ingenuity,amazement,owner,outside,learn,astonishment,heartwarming,intelligence,adaptability,feline</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Jepara</media:city>
                  <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>ID</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2578</guid>
                  <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 07:29:30 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2578.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2578.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Bathroom bliss: Indonesian cat's unique way to beat the heat</media:title>
                  <media:description>In Yogyakarta, Indonesia, a heartwarming video captured by @bagus_muhammad_ on March 28, 2023, showcases the adorable antics of his feline companion during a hot day. The short clip features his cat lying flat on its stomach in the cool confines of the bathroom, delightfully spreading its hind legs for ultimate relaxation. As temperatures rise, it seems this clever kitty has found its perfect oasis for beating the heat. With a contented expression on its face, it's evident that the bathroom has become the preferred spot for the cat to seek respite from the sweltering weather. </media:description>
                  <media:keywords>cat,bathroom,Indonesia,Yogyakarta,video,pet,feline,hot,heat,adorable,antics,relaxation,hind legs,oasis,cool,weather,comfort,pets,content,warmer days</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Yogyakarta</media:city>
                  <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>ID</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2577</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 08:17:01 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2577.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2577.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Adventurous Manda: a curious cat's high-rise escapades in Yogyakarta!</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a captivating moment caught on video by @a.youu_ on July 4, 2023, in Yogyakarta, Indonesia, a curious cat named Manda was spotted perched atop an unfinished building. The enigmatic feline appeared unsure of its surroundings, leaving viewers both amused and intrigued by its daring escapade. With a playful spirit, the author decided to record the charming scene, showcasing Manda's adventurous nature and uncertain demeanor as it surveyed the world from its lofty vantage point.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>cat,video,Yogyakarta,Indonesia,Manda,building,perched,curious,confused,fun,playful,adventurous,daring,charming,uncertain,climb,pet,antics,moment,heartwarming</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Yogyakarta</media:city>
                  <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>ID</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Tue, 4 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2573</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 08:15:12 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2573.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2573.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Adventurous boat dog: a joyful journey on the waters of Posadas, Argentina</media:title>
                  <media:description>In Posadas, Argentina, a heartwarming sight was captured by @fefu1408 on December 1, 2021. A video showcased a spirited dog perched confidently on the front of a speeding boat, appearing to relish every moment of the thrilling experience. As the author went rowing with a friend, they encountered this common occurrence of dogs joining the boating adventures. In this particular instance, the dog belonged to another boat that passed them by, showcasing the adventurous spirit and love for the water that these furry companions hold. </media:description>
                  <media:keywords>rowing,boat,dog,adventure,Posadas,Argentina,speed,waters,joyful,companions,video,water,front,perched,passing,friend,common,furry,capture,spirit</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Posadas</media:city>
                  <media:country>Argentina</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>AR</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Wed, 1 Dec 2021</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2572</guid>
                  <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 07:28:52 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2572.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2572.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Enchanting fur patterns: unique cat in Blitar delights in friendly affection</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a heartwarming scene captured on video by @polseksrengat on June 30, 2023, in Blitar, Indonesia, a cat with naturally polished fur became the center of attention among a group of friends. The cat sported a striking combination of white fur on its face and a mix of white and black fur on the rest of its body, making it truly unique. As the friends scratched the cat gently, it basked in their affectionate company, closing its eyes in contentment each time one of them touched its head. The endearing sight of this feline enjoying the camaraderie warmed the hearts of those who witnessed the adorable encounter, reminding us of the profound bond between humans and their feline companions.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>polished,fur,cat,white,black,unique,friends,affection,company,contentment,adorable,feline,bond,Indonesia,Blitar,video,captured,June30,2023,@polseksrengat</media:keywords>
                  <media:city> Blitar</media:city>
                  <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>ID</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2571</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 08:08:02 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2571.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2571.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Quirky Yeti: cat asserts ownership over owner's resting foot in hilarious video!</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a heartwarming yet amusing video captured by @dymova_brows on December 14, 2022, in Zaporozhye, Ukraine, a 7-year-old cat named Yeti showcases its unique character. The footage shows Yeti attempting to keep its owner's foot still under the blanket while playfully growling like a dog when met with resistance. The quirky feline's predilections include strolls on the balcony and relishing wet food, but it fiercely guards its delicious meals from fellow feline companions. The short video captures Yeti's endearing and assertive personality, providing a delightful glimpse into the fascinating world of this furry friend.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>cat,yeti,video,quirky,owner,foot,bed,blanket,growl,dog,character,Zaporozhye,Ukraine,balcony,wet food,delicious,unique,feline,playful,adorable</media:keywords>
                  <media:city> Zaporozhye</media:city>
                  <media:country>Ukraine</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>UA</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2569</guid>
                  <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 07:20:35 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2569.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2569.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Cat chaos: Minsk feline's hilarious morning escape from the mysterious carrier bag!</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a humorous yet chaotic scene captured by @vorobyov2021 on May 5, 2023, in Minsk, Belarus, a scared feline caused havoc as she ran around the house with a carrier bag caught on her back. The video showcases the frantic cat darting from room to room, desperately trying to escape the seemingly terrifying bag. According to the author, the unexpected morning commotion served as an amusing wake-up call, as the mischievous cat poked and prodded her way through the apartment in a comical attempt to be free from her unexpected accessory.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>cat,video,Minsk,Belarus,scared,carrier bag,back,running,banging,things,escape,hilarious,chaos,feline,apartment,wake-up,poke,capture,room,commotion</media:keywords>
                  <media:city> Minsk</media:city>
                  <media:country>Belarus</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>BY</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Fri, 5 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2566</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 07:53:24 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2566.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2566.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Catnap couture: adorable feline caught napping in boutique's pink mavin!</media:title>
                  <media:description>In the city of Borisov, Belarus, on July 16, 2023, a heartwarming scene unfolded in a second clothes boutique. Local resident @ugimaster stumbled upon a delightful sight as he entered the store - a contented cat fast asleep amidst the clothes. Its furry head was cozily nestled on a soft pink mavin, adding an extra touch of cuteness to the scene. The video captured by @ugimaster quickly went viral, spreading smiles and warming hearts across the internet.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>cat,sleeping,clothes,boutique,Borisov,Belarus,@ugimaster,video,peaceful,pink,mavin,adorable,feline,nap,city,viral,internet,heartwarming,cozy,cute</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Borisov</media:city>
                  <media:country>Belarus</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>BY</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2562</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 07:47:37 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2562.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2562.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Raccoon's Miron misadventures: a heartwarming birthday surprise!</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a heartwarming tale of misadventures, @raccoon_miron from St. Petersburg, Russia, captured a touching video while searching for her beloved raccoon pet, Miron on April 27, 2023. The furry troublemaker had managed to scatter her belongings all over the apartment on the eve of his birthday, leaving her in tears, fearing he had escaped through the window. However, to her relief, Miron was just being mischievous and had fallen asleep amidst her things. The emotional rollercoaster of worry and joy unfolded in the video.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>raccoon,miron,video,pet,birthday,surprise,misadventures,St. Petersburg,Russia,apartment,balcony,work,order,sobbing,window,smart,boy,asleep,things,love,joy.</media:keywords>
                  <media:city> St. Petersburg</media:city>
                  <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2558</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 07:43:53 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2558.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2558.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Record-breaking capture: the world's longest Burmese python defeated on US41</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a remarkable feat of courage and teamwork, a group of adventurers on US41 between Naples and Miami, USA, captured the world's longest Burmese python ever documented. The incredible event was documented in a video by @gladesboys on July 10, 2023. Braving the late-night encounter at 1 am, the author and his three inexperienced companions faced the massive serpent on the road. With nerves of steel, he expertly dodged the snake's strikes, finally managing to grasp its tail and secure the head. Despite the dangers, the skilled team managed the capture flawlessly, ensuring that no one was harmed during the process. </media:description>
                  <media:keywords>python,road,US41,Naples,Miami,USA,video,capture,longest,Burmese,record,encounter,hunters,tail,head,courageous,teamwork,adventure,wildlife,triumph,danger</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>US41 between Naples and Miami</media:city>
                  <media:country>United States</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>US</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2557</guid>
                  <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 14:58:10 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2557.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2557.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Massive moth invasion: swarms of flying creatures fill the night skies in Yelets, Russia</media:title>
                  <media:description>On the night of Monday, July 24, 2023, the city of Yelets in the Lipetsk region, Russia, experienced a bizarre phenomenon as drivers encountered a massive invasion of insects. Thousands of flying creatures, identified as moths, enveloped the road lights, creating "swarm clouds" that obstructed the path on the Karakum bridge. Disturbing footage recorded by a driver showcased the surreal scene, where the insects swarmed around vehicles, making navigation challenging. </media:description>
                  <media:keywords>insects,invasion,Yelets,Russia,night,Monday,July 24,Lipetsk,drivers,filmed,massive,flying,creatures,swarm,clouds,Karakum,bridge,moths,video,way,drove</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Yelets, Lipetsk region</media:city>
                  <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ODD</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2556</guid>
                  <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 14:56:15 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2556.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2556.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Silent expectations: a comical tale of leash mishaps and unspoken desires</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a heartwarming yet amusing video captured by @bentleyandfinnn on June 12, 2023, in Texas, USA, a dog's expressive response to an unexpected leash mishap left viewers in stitches. The dog, eagerly anticipating a walk, stood still as its owner accidentally dropped the leash. With a look of anticipation and confusion, the canine waited for the owner to pick it up and continue the outing, but to no avail. The silence spoke volumes as the dog's expressive eyes and hopeful demeanor conveyed its desires without a single bark. Eventually, the dog took matters into its paws and returned to the owner, as if to say, "Let's try this again, but get it right this time!" The video exemplified the unspoken bond between pets and their owners, evoking laughter and heartwarming feelings all at once.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>dog,leash,video,Texas,USA,cute,funny,owner,walk,expectation,confusion,expressive,eyes,paws,bond,outing,pet,laughter,heartwarming,silent,mishap</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Texas</media:city>
                  <media:country>United States</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>US</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2547</guid>
                  <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023 17:52:44 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2547.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2547.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Adorable new arrival: baby parrot dreams peacefully in loving hands</media:title>
                  <media:description>On June 8th, 2023, in Izmir, Turkey, a heartwarming video captured by @hknyilmaz35 showcased a newly hatched parrot in the gentle hands of its caretaker, Hakan. The tiny parrot, peacefully asleep, melted hearts with its undeniable cuteness. The short clip resonated with viewers worldwide, celebrating the beauty of new life and the bond between humans and animals.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>adorable,parrot,hatchling,video,Izmir,Turkey,hands,caretaker,asleep,cute,newlife,bond,humans,animals,heartwarming,tiny,love,peaceful,@hknyilmaz35,June8th2023</media:keywords>
                  <media:city> Izmir</media:city>
                  <media:country>Turkey</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>TR</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Thu, 8 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2546</guid>
                  <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023 18:03:14 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2546.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2546.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Raging cow causes chaos during Eid al-Adha in Belakang Padang, Indonesia</media:title>
                  <media:description>On June 29, 2023, in Belakang Padang, Kampung Baru, Indonesia, a dramatic incident unfolded during the celebration of Eid al-Adha. A video captured by @donieffendi98 showcased a cow running furiously through the streets just before its scheduled sacrifice. The animal went berserk, dashing into the houses of local residents, causing panic and chaos. Despite efforts to restrain it with a rope, the cow remained in a state of rage and lashed out by kicking a nearby parked motorcycle. The unexpected and intense encounter left the community startled, and the situation was eventually brought under control.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>rage,cow,sacrifice,berserk,houses,residents,panic,chaos,restrain,rope,motorcycle,intense,encounter,community,startled,control,video,Belakang Padang,Kampung Baru,Indonesia</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Belakang Padang, Kampung Baru</media:city>
                  <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>ID</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2543</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 07:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2543.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2543.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Unconventional cat and mouse chase: when the prey strikes back in Lviv, Ukraine!</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a comical scene captured by @bohdansereda on June 11, 2023, in Lviv, Ukraine, a cat found itself in an amusing predicament with a crafty mouse. The video showcased the mouse perched confidently on the cat's back, seemingly taunting the feline as it attempted to catch its elusive companion. Despite the mouse's daring trickery, the determined cat valiantly pursued the rodent, refusing to give up the chase. After a series of entertaining antics, the mouse's luck eventually ran out, and it tumbled from the cat's back, leading to a swift and triumphant pounce by the feline. </media:description>
                  <media:keywords>cat,mouse,lviv,ukraine,video,chase,trick,clever,funny,pursuit,adventure,pounce,whiskers,comical,scene,internet,sensation,playful,showdown,triumph,amusing</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Lviv</media:city>
                  <media:country>Ukraine</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>UA</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2534</guid>
                  <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 15:07:59 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2534.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2534.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Feathered frenzy: Loki the staffy takes on the seagull invasion in Hull, UK!</media:title>
                  <media:description>On June 3, 2023, in Hull, UK, @zaynetowe witnessed an amusing sight in her garden as her dog, Loki the Staffy, took charge against a swarm of seagulls. The video captured the moment when numerous seagulls invaded the garden, prompting Loki to dash into action. With unyielding determination, Loki fearlessly chased the seagulls away, leaving the garden free from the feathery invaders. It was a comical display of canine bravery, as the loyal pup swiftly returned to the safety of the house after successfully warding off the feathered intruders.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>garden,dog,Loki,staffy,seagulls,chase,video,Hull,UK,funny,brave,invasion,action,loyal,pup,feathered,intruders,June,@zaynetowe,house</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Hull, England </media:city>
                  <media:country>United Kingdom</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>GB</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sat, 3 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2529</guid>
                  <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 20:56:41 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2529.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2529.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Startling encounter: snake dangles and vanishes in Ho Chi Minh city home</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a harrowing incident captured on a home camera in Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam, a resident, @congdonghoainhon, had an unsettling surprise. On May 12, 2023, the camera alerted him to movement in his bedroom, and upon checking the footage, he was startled to see a snake dangling near the camera. Moments later, the snake fell out of sight, leaving him alarmed. Rushing back home, he searched his room diligently but found no trace of the elusive serpent. Speculating that it might have taken refuge inside the air conditioner, the resident remains on edge, unable to locate the reptile.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>snake,camera,bedroom,video,home,work,warn,movement,shocked,rummage,find,air conditioner,Vietnam,Ho Chi Minh City,resident,encounter,alert,elusive,reptile,tags</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Ho Chi Minh City</media:city>
                  <media:country>Vietnam</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>VN</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Fri, 12 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2528</guid>
                  <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 20:58:54 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2528.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2528.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Slippery shenanigans: Fatty the dog's hilarious underground parking adventure!</media:title>
                  <media:description>In Jiangxi province, China, on June 9th, 2023, a playful dog named Fatty found himself in a comical situation at the underground parking lot. His owner, Fatty, captured the moment on video as the excited canine ran towards her, only to slip on the wet floor. With a quick recovery, Fatty tried to hide his embarrassment by looking forward, creating a humorous and endearing scene. Thankfully, no harm was done, and Fatty's misadventures added a touch of laughter to an otherwise ordinary day at the parking lot.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>june 9th,2023,jiangxi province,china,fatty,dog,video,running,sliding,wet floor,underground parking,car,water,slip,embarrassment,owner,playfulness,comical,recovery,laughter,misadventure</media:keywords>
                  <media:city> Jiangxi province</media:city>
                  <media:country>China</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>CN</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Fri, 9 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2527</guid>
                  <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 21:01:29 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2527.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2527.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Charming canine shenanigans: dog delights in self-play on the couch!</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a heartwarming video captured by @mia.the.staffy on June 16, 2023, in Örebro, Sweden, a delightful canine showcased its unique form of entertainment. The dog Mia, which is a staffy breed, was seen playfully folding itself on the couch, engrossed in the amusing activity of nibbling at its own leg. The endearing display of self-play charmed viewers, highlighting the joyful and quirky nature of our beloved four-legged companions.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>playful,canine,video,couch,leg,nibbling,adorable,@mia.the.staffy,Sweden,Örebro,charming,self-play,entertaining,dog,folding,heartwarming,quirky,delightful,nature,beloved</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Örebro</media:city>
                  <media:country>Sweden</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>SE</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2524</guid>
                  <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 09:32:57 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2524.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2524.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Purrplexing playtime: cat domestic 'violence' or feline fun?</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a lighthearted and amusing video captured by @smallfox_kate on May 28, 2023, in Tyumen, Russia, her energetic feline companion named Kosik stole the spotlight with his mischievous antics. The playful cat delightedly engaged in what his owner jokingly referred to as "cat domestic violence," as he playfully attacked her head while she lay on her bed, toying with her hair. The author affectionately described Kosik as a restless and fast cat who had never before exhibited such behavior, leaving her both amused and slightly exasperated. </media:description>
                  <media:keywords>cat,playtime,video,Tyumen,Russia,smallfox_kate,hair,domestic,violence,jokingly,Kosik,restless,fast,amusing,playful,unpredictable,whimsical,joyful,feline,antics.</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Tyumen</media:city>
                  <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sun, 28 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2508</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 08:42:08 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2508.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2508.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Bird's-eye view: sky the budgie's playful encounter with glasses</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a heartwarming moment captured on May 22, 2023, in Worcester, UK, @sky.the_budgie shared a delightful video of her beloved bird pet, Sky. The endearing budgie was caught on camera perched on her glasses near her ear, playfully getting in the way of her eyes. Despite being not particularly fond of humans, Sky occasionally seeks attention from her owner. At three years old, she holds the special distinction of being her first pet, forging a unique and loving bond between them.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>bird,pet,budgie,glasses,eyes,attention,playful,Worcester,UK,Sky,owner,love,bond,first,capture,video,hoomans,perched,ear,view</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Worcester</media:city>
                  <media:country>United Kingdom</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>GB</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Mon, 22 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2506</guid>
                  <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 08:24:27 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2506.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2506.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Hilarious dinner table antics: dog seeks special treats in Baguio City!</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a delightful video captured by @maui_theeb on May 27, 2023, in Baguio City, Philippines, a comical dog stole the show with its amusing dinner table antics. The furry friend, seated on a chair atop the table, was seen hilariously tapping a gentleman on the shoulders, seemingly asking for a treat or some attention. The heartwarming interaction between the dog and the person brought smiles to viewers' faces, showcasing the bond between humans and their beloved pets in the most endearing way possible.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>funny,dog,interaction,dinner table,Baguio City,Philippines,video,tapping,gentleman,chair,adorable,pets,bond,cute,hilarious,canine,comedy,heartwarming,love,companionship,amusing</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Baguio City</media:city>
                  <media:country>Philippines</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>PH</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sat, 27 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2505</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 08:31:02 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2505.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2505.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Playful corgi interrupts exercise session in Sochi park: a hilarious surprise!</media:title>
                  <media:description>In Sochi, Russia, on July 13, 2023, two friends, @da.daa and her companion, were diligently exercising on their mats in the park when an unexpected visitor joined them. A lively corgi dog approached the pair, and despite its owner's attempts to retrieve it, the playful pup ran circles around them, bringing laughter and surprise to their workout. The adorable intruder even playfully scampered on their backs as they lay on their stomachs doing exercises. Eventually, the owner managed to take the dog away, leaving the friends amused by the delightful interruption to their exercise session.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>exercise,park,corgi,dog,Sochi,Russia,friends,mats,playful,owner,unexpected,visitor,laughter,workout,scamper,intruder,amusement,interruption,companions,circles</media:keywords>
                  <media:city> Sochi</media:city>
                  <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2504</guid>
                  <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 08:17:20 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2504.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2504.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Unlikely confrontation: tourist's dog faces fierce cat at Irganai reservoir</media:title>
                  <media:description>In an unexpected turn of events at the picturesque Irganai reservoir in Dagestan, Russia, a tourist's leisurely day took a surprising twist when their four-legged companion faced off against a disgruntled cat. On June 11, 2023, @dag.travel captured a video showing the intense encounter. The cat lunged at the dog, prompting the owner to swiftly intervene, pulling the dog away and moving to a safer distance. Despite the distance, the persistent cat continued its pursuit, leading the dog's owner to carry their pet to avoid further confrontation. The serene outing turned into an unusual showdown, leaving both the onlookers and the tourists in awe of the unexpected clash between these unlikely adversaries.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>dog,cat,attack,Irganai,reservoir,Dagestan,Russia,tourist,owner,atmosphere,video,confront,surprising,encounter,lunge,persistent,pursuit,carry,onlookers,clash</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Dagestan</media:city>
                  <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2503</guid>
                  <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 19:17:00 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2503.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2503.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Bra brawl: furry guardians turn fashion feud in Selangor, Malaysia!</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a surprising and amusing spectacle captured by @rita_roslie in Selangor, Malaysia on June 28, 2023, two dogs were caught on camera engaging in a hilarious tug-of-war over a bra. The canines seemed to have stumbled upon the lingerie in question and were passionately tugging at each end, playfully bickering over their newfound treasure. As one dog clenched its teeth onto one side of the bra, the other dog stubbornly held onto the opposite end, creating a comical fashion feud. The author, the eyewitness, revealed that one of the dogs involved was her loyal garden guardian, but she was clueless about where they had discovered the bra.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>dogs,fighting,bra,tugofwar,hilarious,spectacle,Malaysia,Selangor,video,canines,fashion,feud,treasure,comical,viral,pets,quirky,antics,animals,guardians</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Selangor</media:city>
                  <media:country>Malaysia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>MY</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2500</guid>
                  <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 14:26:17 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2500.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2500.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Fierce yet gentle: Russian serval cat's playful encounter with watchful dog</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a captivating video captured by @mainecoonnhaching on July 8th, 2023, in Dau Mot city, Binh Duong province, Vietnam, a serval cat imported from Russia displayed a striking mix of ferocity and tenderness. The video shows the cat enthusiastically chasing after an object thrown towards their glass door, revealing the curious dog outside. The cat runs straight to the door and, though fierce in appearance, slumps its head while retrieving the toy. The dog, kept outside to prevent accidents indoors, remains safe behind a fenced gate, thanks to careful guarding.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>cat,video,serval,Russia,fierce,gentle,dog,play,glass,door,chase,curious,outside,safe,fenced,gate,guarding,harmony,environment,adorable</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Dau Mot city, Binh Duong province</media:city>
                  <media:country>Vietnam</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>VN</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sat, 8 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2498</guid>
                  <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 13:13:12 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2498.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2498.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Amusing cat drama unfolds: playful feline duo turns kitchen mishap into entertainment!</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a heartwarming yet comical scene captured by @thanhtam8880 on June 14th, 2023, in Thanh Xuan district, Hanoi, Vietnam, two cats shared a playful moment in the kitchen. As one curious feline inadvertently stuck its tail between the cupboard door, its furry friend mistook the situation for a game and started playfully tugging at the trapped tail. While the incident might have seemed concerning at first, it quickly turned into a delightful display of camaraderie as the mischievous companion successfully freed its tail.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>cat,video,playful,kitchen,cupboard,tail,stuck,comical,companionship,feline,heartwarming,Hanoi,Thanh Xuan district,Vietnam,friends,entertaining,cooking,mishap,funny,moment</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Thanh Xuan district, Hanoi</media:city>
                  <media:country>Vietnam</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>VN</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2496</guid>
                  <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 12:28:49 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2496.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2496.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Conalie the playful puddle prancer: a horse's muddy adventure in Göthewitz, Germany</media:title>
                  <media:description>In Göthewitz, Germany, a delightful sight was captured by @frizziarnold on April 11th, 2021. The video showcased a horse named Conalie engaging in a playful activity. With a lady on its back, Conalie joyfully tapped the mud with its front legs, creating an endearing scene. The horse had discovered a small puddle and decided to embrace its mischievous side, playfully walking through the dirty water. The heartwarming moment captured the essence of the horse's carefree spirit and brought smiles to viewers' faces.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>horse,mud,playful,video,Göthewitz,Germany,Conalie,tapping,front legs,lady,puddle,dirty water,joy,mischievous,carefree,smiles,playful spirit,@frizziarnold,April 11th,2021</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Göthewitz</media:city>
                  <media:country>Germany</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>DE</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sun, 11 Apr 2021</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2485</guid>
                  <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 09:36:53 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/9d681a58-9032-422d-bce9-5166eb06806b.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/e79cc8ea-eeef-49ea-8f28-70add3daeb17.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Snake's surprise: when a reptile acts like a cat!</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a surprising and adorable video captured by @children.of.loki on June 13th, 2023, in Texas, USA, a snake displayed remarkably cat-like behavior. The footage shows the snake slithering around the house until its owner scratches its back. Astonishingly, the reptile bends the area where it receives the scratch, seemingly relishing the affectionate gesture. Captioned as "My snake is a cat," this extraordinary behavior showcases the fascinating and unexpected similarities between these two vastly different creatures.
</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>snake,reptile,pet,Texas,USA,video,cat-like,behavior,adorable,surprising,scratch,slithering,house,owner,affectionate,gesture,fascination,creature,similarities,captivating</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Texas</media:city>
                  <media:country>United States</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>US</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2484</guid>
                  <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 09:35:26 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/dccfb477-e6cb-4f39-a2e9-be93aaab4eff.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/30a86124-8fc3-4dc2-89dc-ffb246cfc1f3.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Enchanting Serpukhov slumber: meet Jim, the bed-loving pet raccoon!</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a heartwarming and endearing display of companionship, a captivating video emerged on June 2, 2023, from Serpukhov, Russia, showcasing the adorable bond between a pet raccoon and its owner. Shared by @enot_jim, the footage captured her furry friend, Jim, curled up cozily in bed. Jim, the affectionate pet raccoon, has won the hearts of netizens with his penchant for catching forty winks in the comfort of his owner's bed.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>sleeping,raccoon,pet,bed,Serpukhov,Russia,cute,video,Jim,adorable,bond,owner,cozy,heartwarming,furry,netizens,household,charming,relationship,companionship</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Serpukhov</media:city>
                  <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Fri, 2 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2483</guid>
                  <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 09:34:32 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/acd9474c-3f02-437f-b297-9ab3fe3fa3cf.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/ab95948d-d17b-41d7-803c-d929fc231b8f.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Enchanting encounter: friendly dolphin delights swimmer at Suishohama Beach, Japan</media:title>
                  <media:description>On July 17th, 2023, at Suishohama Beach in Mihama, Mikata District, Japan, a remarkable scene unfolded as a curious dolphin made a surprise appearance near the shore. @Ooo_MEN_ captured the heartwarming moment on video, showing the dolphin playfully interacting with a lone swimmer using a floater. The extraordinary encounter left beachgoers in awe as they witnessed the gentle marine creature approaching and engaging with the delighted individual. </media:description>
                  <media:keywords>dolphin,beach,interaction,swimmer,floater,video,Japan,Mihama,Mikata District,Suishohama Beach,nature,wildlife,encounter,playful,surprise,curious,harmony,awe,enchanting,filmed</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Mihama, Mikata District</media:city>
                  <media:country>Japan</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>JP</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2481</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/401402ff-22eb-4a49-9a06-dfbde13add42.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/cef347b0-35ba-4fd5-bd4e-6ef4fc575661.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Whiskered surprise: playful cat in a cute box captivates Siheung City</media:title>
                  <media:description>In Siheung City, Korea, a heartwarming incident occurred on June 3, 2023, as a video captured by @goarongggoo went viral. The clip featured a curious cat tucked away inside a cute box. The man behind the camera revealed that he was selling these delightful boxes when he stumbled upon the feline surprise. With a playful knock on the box resembling a door, he decided to unveil the mystery. Upon opening the box, a charming cat emerged. </media:description>
                  <media:keywords>cat,box,video,cute,Siheung City,Korea,surprise,viral,@goarongggoo,June 3,2023,knock,door,feline,playful,charming,joy,wonder,internet,community,moment</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Siheung City</media:city>
                  <media:country>South Korea</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>KR</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sat, 3 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2480</guid>
                  <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 09:31:32 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/71eed083-e8af-46f6-8c74-09a7128c2948.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2480.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Harv's chicken house harmony: cat and chickens live in paw-sitive coexistence!</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a heartwarming display of unexpected camaraderie, a captivating video captured by @harvs.gamla.skola on July 3rd, 2023 from Harv, Sweden, showcased a remarkable scene in her chicken house. The footage revealed her feline companion perched gracefully on one of the chicken trays while the feathered inhabitants remained surprisingly calm and at ease in the presence of their newfound friend. Captioned with a touch of amusement, "I'm not even surprised anymore...," the video serves as a testament to the harmonious coexistence between the cat and the chickens. </media:description>
                  <media:keywords>cat,chicken,harmony,coexistence,video,Sweden,Harv,pets,animals,friendship,unexpected,bond,companionship,feathers,tray,love,heartwarming,amusement,captivated,surprising,delightful</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Harv</media:city>
                  <media:country>Sweden</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>SE</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Mon, 3 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2479</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/bad55bf2-197f-4722-8387-d12a5844b496.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/86f6ba64-461f-4f45-922c-f0d129b95f61.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Resilient Weimaraner overcomes adversity: walking proudly with unlikely footwear amidst health challenges</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a heartwarming moment captured by @ms_zwaal on May 20th, 2023, in Port Hueneme, California, USA, her Weimaraner, Dutch, showed incredible resilience and adaptability. While hanging out and watching TV, they heard a peculiar "clack, clack" sound and discovered Dutch walking around with a slipper on his hind leg. Unbothered by the unusual situation, Dutch showcased his indomitable spirit despite his fragile appearance. The video's caption revealed that Dutch is an old guy battling a tumor in his spleen and liver, reassuring viewers that he is well taken care of.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>resilient,weimaraner,dog,slipper,hind leg,unbothered,California,USA,video,TV,clack,sandal,fragile,old,tumor,spleen,liver,pet,companion,bond</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Port Hueneme, California</media:city>
                  <media:country>United States</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>US</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sat, 20 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2478</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/9bb30096-7336-40e4-99b4-8a3c5f4777c6.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/ea2fe7dd-7907-44c2-b285-0aad8ec8c867.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Doggie oasis: Beha finds refreshing relief from the heat by the shore</media:title>
                  <media:description>On June 17th, 2023, in Balashikha, Moscow, Russia, a heartwarming video captured the attention of many as @nemez_bexa shared a delightful moment with her dog. The scorching heat couldn't keep Beha away from cooling off in the water near the shore. In the short clip, the dog is seen seated in the water, content and relaxed. </media:description>
                  <media:keywords>dog,water,shore,hot,Beha,play,video,Balashikha,Moscow,Russia,heat,pet,playful,refresh,summer,cool,socialmedia,cute,joy,happiness,retrieve</media:keywords>
                  <media:city> Balashikha, Moscow</media:city>
                  <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2477</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/ed8cd420-ed98-48df-9484-6be4d907eff5.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/9b1fdfa0-bae1-40b8-8d27-d41efc0aac8a.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Swan's protective standoff: a brave encounter with a curious canine</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a remarkable incident captured by @semenova_lena on June 3rd, 2023, in Novorossiysk, Russia, a serene family of swans by the Sudzhuk Spit estuary encountered an unexpected visitor. As onlookers observed the graceful swans, a dog, seemingly unaccompanied by its owner, approached the water's edge. The situation took a tense turn when one of the swans began hissing in defense. The quick-thinking observers promptly intervened, safely removing the curious canine from the swan's perceived territory. </media:description>
                  <media:keywords>swan,hissing,dog,family,water,shore,Novorossiysk,Sudzhuk Spit,Russia,video,captured,June 3rd,2023,estuary,protective,encounter,onlookers,curious,owner,wildlife,balance</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Novorossiysk</media:city>
                  <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sat, 3 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2474</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/8fad0eb7-2eda-4538-a056-4b6cd5ffc87f.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/6325c6fb-d9d6-49bc-9112-b05b145446fe.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Amusing misunderstanding: clever Shih Tzu eagerly eats treats after playful vet pretense</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a heartwarming and humorous video captured by @Fimmy_theshihtzu on May 31st, 2023, in Cavite, Philippines, a delightful Shih Tzu showcased its cleverness and sense of humor. The adorable pet initially refused to eat its treats, prompting the owner's dad to pretend to call the vet and humorously warn of an impending rear injection if the dog didn't eat. Surprisingly, the moment the word "injection" was mentioned, the furry companion quickly changed its mind and eagerly devoured the treats. Many viewers found the video entertaining, believing that the pet had genuinely understood the playful jest.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>adorable,shih tzu,pet,treats,funny,clever,video,Philippines,Cavite,eat,pretend,vet,injection,rear,amusement,understanding,heartwarming,owner,dad,humor</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Cavite</media:city>
                  <media:country>Philippines</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>PH</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Wed, 31 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2471</guid>
                  <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 12:50:58 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2471.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2471.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Fearful furry friends: Ball the dog and a playful deer's zoo encounter in Beijing!</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a heartwarming yet cautious encounter at a zoo in Beijing, China, a dog named Ball had a surprising interaction with a curious deer. The moment was captured on video by @todaythemoonisnotopen on July 3rd, 2023. As Ball sat inside the car, a deer approached, seemingly eager to engage in a kiss. However, the dog's apprehension was evident, and it quickly retreated back into the safety of the vehicle. Despite the brief interaction, the endearing exchange between the two animals left a lasting impression, highlighting the beauty of unexpected connections in the animal kingdom.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>playful,deer,dog,zoo,Beijing,China,encounter,video,July3rd,2023,curious,kiss,car,interaction,animals,connection,heartwarming,cautious,moment,captured</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Beijing</media:city>
                  <media:country>China</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>CN</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Mon, 3 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2465</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/291686df-edaf-40a2-b29e-324e7310ae8e.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/59533475-0fb1-4a59-b179-39812ed84054.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Troublemaker Prince: the mischievous parrot's love for cupboards!</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a charming video captured by @tamiaoveres in Vancouver, Canada, on November 15th, 2022, her mischievous parrot, Prince, found himself in a bit of a predicament after sneaking into a forbidden cabinet filled with delicate glass cups. As the author called out to her feathery companion, Prince seemed to revel in the adventure, hopping around and singing playfully. However, after a brief dance of mischief, the mischievous bird finally hopped back into author's arms. According to the amused owner, Prince's fascination with cupboards outweighed his interest in toys, making him an adorable troublemaker with a flair for exploring forbidden spaces.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>parrot,prince,video,Vancouver,Canada,cabinet,glass cups,mischief,forbidden,bird,arms,singing,dance,owner,fascination,toys,troublemaker,adorable,exploration,spaces</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Vancouver</media:city>
                  <media:country>Canada</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>CA</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2022</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2464</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/1995213b-d46f-47c5-8db5-d1a01e5dc6f0.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/b1493f6b-529d-4bdf-a0c1-d0256171dd97.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Birthday cake ambush: raccoon Patrick's sweet greed unleashed!</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a hilarious yet mischievous scene, @raccoon.patrick, on May 14th, 2023, in Dnipro, Ukraine, captured a video that showcased their raccoon, Patrick, in action. It was his birthday, and to celebrate, a delicious cake had been prepared for the guests. However, Patrick couldn't resist the temptation, and with nimble paws, he skillfully  began clawing at the cake with pure greed.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>cake,raccoon,Patrick,birthday,video,Dnipro,Ukraine,mischief,celebration,temptation,guests,clawing,nimble,cunning,playful,curiosity,appetite,funny,adorable,animals</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Dnipro</media:city>
                  <media:country>Ukraine</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>UA</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sun, 14 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2457</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/c93dd98d-7b83-4b15-83f4-e8c57bf3cdb6.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/d2ddc274-7130-42f9-9856-c3676b90096c.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Tenacious ferret's persistent pursuit: the wallet heist in Bytom, Poland</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a quirky incident captured by @ferret_fred on May 20, 2023, in Bytom, Poland, a mischievous ferret showcased its determined nature. The video shows the furry little creature retrieving a wallet from the top of a counter. According to the author, her ferret has a penchant for collecting things under the bed, and that day, it stumbled upon her boyfriend's wallet. Despite her efforts to return the wallet to its original position, the persistent ferret insisted on stealing it repeatedly.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>ferret,pet,Poland,Bytom,video,wallet,theft,mischievous,determined,collect,under,bed,boyfriend,persistent,stubborn,amusing,cute,curious,animal,hunt</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Bytom</media:city>
                  <media:country>Poland</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>PL</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sat, 20 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2456</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/25bac6f5-44dc-4a56-b291-1806ab4753ac.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/f209743e-d157-4f10-acf0-7c237e30ace3.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Miraculous animal bond: minke whale saves ailing boar in Saint Petersburg region</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a heartwarming incident captured on video by @PavelGlazkov in the Priozersky district of the Leningrad region, Russia on June 27th, 2023, a boar found itself in distress, struggling to stand on its feet. Its mother sensed the urgency and immediately took action, giving her ailing piglet a massage around the heart area with her sinewy heel. Despite her efforts, the baby showed no signs of life. However, a surprising turn of events unfolded as another minke whale rushed to the scene and took over the care. This compassionate whale diligently massaged the body of its sibling, and astonishingly, the piglet regained consciousness. Without hesitation, the piglet resumed eating, showcasing the remarkable bond between animals and their capacity for empathy and aid in the most unexpected circumstances.

Credit to: https://t.me/kazdoytvaripopare</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>boar,mother,massage,illness,consciousness,minke whale,Russia,Priozersky district,Leningrad region,baby,sibling,empathy,help,video,trap,heart,feet,eating,distress,remarkable,bond.</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Priozersky district of the Saint Petersburg region</media:city>
                  <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2455</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/c239ec24-bc12-4273-a7eb-f9c3314253d5.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2682e9db-1a8c-4e27-a201-c6cb1390260a.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Unusual playtime: fearless dog entertains itself with cockroach in Batangas, Philippines</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a peculiar video captured by @chiquito_boy on May 2nd, 2023, in Batangas, Philippines, his brave and vaccinated dog can be seen engaging in an unexpected playtime activity. The footage shows the dog fearlessly interacting with a cockroach, seemingly amused by the tiny creature. While some viewers might find the sight unusual, the author assures that his dog's health is protected.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>playtime,video,dog,cockroach,Batangas,Philippines,brave,vaccinated,amusing,unusual,interaction,socialmedia,attention,netizens,reactions,unconventional,pet,insect,entertainment,curious,playful</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Batangas</media:city>
                  <media:country>Philippines</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>PH</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Tue, 2 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2451</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/3c4e48dd-e74c-4d27-9bb2-dd67a3c154aa.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/8c2cdccd-fa90-4260-9b0e-999aed4df594.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Enthusiastic equine: the joyful journey of Tosha, the Bashkir breed Macintosh horse</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a heartwarming video captured by @mashak_b on May 4th, 2023, in Lobnya, Moscow, Russia, we witness an endearing moment between a skilled equestrian and his beloved horse, Tosha. The footage shows the author standing on a wooden stool as Tosha, a magnificent Bashkir breed Macintosh horse, gallops towards him with boundless enthusiasm. As the author reveals, this video showcases one of Tosha's favorite exercises, where he is asked to "park" at the end of their class. The genuine connection between the rider and his horse is evident, portraying the sheer joy and fulfillment that comes from this beautiful bond between man and equine companion.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>horse,video,Bashkir,Macintosh,Tosha,equestrian,enthusiasm,Moscow,Russia,Lobnya,wooden,stool,student,exercise,park,connection,rider,gallop,bond,joy,fulfillment</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Lobnya, Moscow</media:city>
                  <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Thu, 4 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2449</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/4d478e9e-fbb6-4a65-a9ca-e981b78a2bd5.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/aa9a8d10-7cea-4a7b-942a-d38594f519ce.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                     </channel>
                  </rss>
                