<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
        xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
        xmlns:openSearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearchrss/1.0/"
        xmlns:dfpvideo="http://api.google.com/dfpvideo"
        xmlns:tms="http://data.tmsapi.com/v1.1"
        version="2.0">
         <channel>
           <title>ViralBear videos</title>
           <dfpvideo:version>2</dfpvideo:version><item>
             <media:title>Unforeseen splash: a fishing expedition in Borneo takes an unexpected turn</media:title>
             <media:description>In an unforeseen turn of events during a fishing expedition in Borneo, Indonesia, recorded by @keluargabakumpai on April 15, 2023, as he was filming his friend who was fishing as usual. The author's friend found himself taking an unexpected plunge into the river. While standing on a wooden structure at the riverbank, having his fishing adventure, a missed step led to an unfortunate fall into the water. Fortunately, the friend managed to emerge from the incident unharmed.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>fishing,expedition,borneo,indonesia,recording,river,plunge,wooden structure,mishap,resilience,balance,unexpected,unscathed,reflexes,composure,memorable,vigilance,friend,splash,caution</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Borneo</media:city>
             <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
             <media:category>Fails and Funnies</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Sat, 15 Apr 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2252</guid>
             <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 07:34:17 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/395c27c4-61c9-47e4-bc0e-eb30657eeea1.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/595cca6e-d6c6-4930-81b3-eb7937836d67.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Feline fun: mischievous cat finds joy in dry leaves </media:title>
             <media:description>In a heartwarming scene captured by @avrianachacha in Alor Setar, Kedah, Malaysia, on December 26, 2022, a playful cat found sheer bliss amidst a pile of dry leaves. The video shows the cat frolicking in the yard as the author's friend diligently cleared the area, bundling up the fallen leaves. Undeterred by the cleaning process, the cat spotted an opportunity for amusement.

With a burst of energy, the feline dashed towards one of the leaf bundles. Moments later, it leaped into a nearby wheelbarrow that was also filled with dry leaves. The cat seemed unperturbed by the additional foliage being added by author's friend, choosing instead to bury its head deep within the comforting embrace of the leaves.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>playful,cat,leaves,yard,cleaning,bundles,wheelbarrow,unbothered,frolicking,joy,bliss,amusing,energy,hiding,contentment,happiness,present,innocent,delightful,animals</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Alor Setar, Kedah</media:city>
             <media:country>Malaysia</media:country>
             <media:category>Animals</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2022</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2249</guid>
             <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 19:30:26 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/b3269e12-31dd-41e3-a7c1-2df2c754d8e5.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2249.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Dancing yellow jackets: South African firefighters bring unity and rhythm to Edmonton's wildfire battle</media:title>
             <media:description>In a heartwarming display of solidarity and unity, a group of 200 firefighters from the renowned South African organization, Working on Fire, landed in Edmonton, Canada, on June 4, 2023, to lend their expertise in battling the raging fires. The arrival of this dedicated team was captured on video by @wo_fire and the footage has taken the internet by storm, quickly going viral. The remarkable scene shows a wave of yellow-clad firefighters dancing and singing in perfect harmony, creating an atmosphere of resilience and determination.

Their infectious energy and synchronized movements not only serve as a testament to their camaraderie but also highlight the power of music and dance in fostering unity amidst adversity.

As they join forces with local firefighters, the South African team's unwavering spirit and expertise promise to make a significant impact in combatting the wildfires that have plagued the region.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>firefighters,unity,solidarity,Edmonton,Canada,South Africa,Working on Fire,arrival,video,viral,dancing,singing,yellow jackets,wildfire,battle,resilience,determination,camaraderie,hope,support,impact</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Edmonton</media:city>
             <media:country>Canada</media:country>
             <media:category>Heartwarming</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Sun, 4 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2240</guid>
             <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2023 12:12:36 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/6ed62ca7-4cbc-49c6-98c3-e724646b4370.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/5a6b69eb-5cf3-4d6d-8d23-f4640de34754.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Innocence and assertiveness: a little girl stands up for herself in school</media:title>
             <media:description>In a heartwarming video captured by @lola_and_aria on 23rd May, 2023, a mother from Greenville, South Carolina, USA, her daughter, Aria, showcased both innocence and assertiveness as she recounted an incident at school. The young girl passionately explained how another student, who happened to be German, attempted to put their hands in her food, a behavior she found inappropriate. Unfazed, she confidently confronted the student, smirking and warning them not to repeat such actions.

Despite her mother's attempts to explain that it was not appropriate to respond in that manner, determined Aria remained stubborn, insisting that she had the right to stand up for herself. Her adorable demeanor and unwavering belief in her actions captured the hearts of viewers. </media:description>
             <media:keywords>adorable,innocence,assertiveness,school,incident,video,daughter,Greenville,South Carolina,USA,German,food,inappropriate,stubborn,explanation,mother,hands,smirk,warning,self-advocacy</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Greenville, South Carolina</media:city>
             <media:country>United States</media:country>
             <media:category>Heartwarming</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Tue, 23 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2255</guid>
             <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 09:40:26 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/0871ce1d-48e3-4256-ba4c-7eebe4f627d1.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/4742d174-51c0-4c9e-9f9f-805720b46f47.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Amidst poor air quality: New York City ignites with controversial fireworks display</media:title>
             <media:description>Despite the prevailing poor air quality caused by the Canadian wildfires, Chelsea Piers, New York City, USA showcased a dazzling fireworks spectacle on the evening of June 9, 2023. The event, captured on video by @MzBehaVIN164 and shared on social media, sparked skepticism among viewers. With the caption, "Our air quality is trash due to the fires in Canada...but hey, let's have fireworks," the post highlighted the contrasting decision to proceed with the fireworks show despite the concerning environmental conditions.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>air quality,fireworks,New York City,Canadian wildfires,video footage,skepticism,trash,display,controversy,poor,evening,social media,admiration,decision,environment,health risks,resilience,celebration,irresponsibility,hazy skies</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Chelsea Piers, New York City</media:city>
             <media:country>United States</media:country>
             <media:category>News</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Fri, 9 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2238</guid>
             <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2023 10:58:34 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2710fca2-8590-4785-925f-1086078e514c.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/60c8829c-e40e-46ed-bc44-dedab87353f0.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Close call: cyclist narrowly escapes collision with truck at Xu창n Mai crossing, Hanoi</media:title>
             <media:description>
In a heart-stopping moment captured by @trananhmobile116 on 21st March, 2023 in Xu창n Mai, Chuong My District, Hanoi, Vietnam, a video shows a near miss between a cyclist and a green truck at a crossing. The footage reveals the truck driver hitting the brakes suddenly, accompanied by screeching tires, just in the nick of time to avoid a potentially catastrophic accident. An unidentified lady on a bike can be seen crossing the road when the truck unexpectedly approaches full speed. Thanks to the quick reflexes of the truck driver, disaster was averted. </media:description>
             <media:keywords>cycling,truck,near miss,crossing,Hanoi,Vietnam,video,cyclist,green truck,brakes,screeching,accident,whisker,reflexes,safety,awareness,pedestrians,caution,Xu창n Mai,Chuong My District</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Xu창n Mai, Chuong My District, Hanoi</media:city>
             <media:country>Vietnam</media:country>
             <media:category>News</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2262</guid>
             <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 18:59:35 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/bc9d1af9-7e23-4fb3-8ec6-0a95cdc3cdba.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/25931c88-7d54-4583-90d5-e45456a544de.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Unleashing love: a groomer's encounter with howling wieners</media:title>
             <media:description>In a heartwarming video captured by @sydnee_michael on June 10th, 2023, in Simi Valley, California, USA, the love and joy of a dog groomer's job were on full display. As the author attended to the dogs in her care, she took a moment to greet two adorable wiener dogs. However, her friendly introduction was swiftly interrupted by a sudden howl from one of the pups. The unexpected interruption only added to the charm of the scene, showcasing the lively personalities and vocal nature of these lovable companions.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>dog grooming,love,wiener dogs,video,job,capture,moment,howling,Sydnee Michael,Simi Valley,California,USA,dogs,affection,bond,pets,companionship,joy,connection,happiness,furry friends</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Simi Valley, California</media:city>
             <media:country>United States</media:country>
             <media:category>Animals</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2259</guid>
             <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 12:11:44 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/51b31fb3-5f6f-4d07-9ec2-650dfbac744f.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/f994f2a9-de26-4e3b-9651-f7435160ba73.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Heartwarming tale: woman becomes mother figure to orphaned goat, creating a hilariously adorable bond</media:title>
             <media:description>In a heartwarming incident captured on video on March 17, 2023 by @rhisst from Tegalombo, Pacitan Regency, East Java, Indonesia, is seen carrying a young goat on her back. The touching moment is made even more significant as she reveals that she took on the role of a surrogate mother to the goat when its own mother passed away just an hour after its birth. Over the course of two months, she has cared for the little goat as her own child, spoiling it with love and attention. The goat has become quite fond of being carried, often requesting to be held like a small child. </media:description>
             <media:keywords>goat,surrogate,mother,bond,love,caring,animals,connection,Indonesia,Pacitan,Tegalombo,orphan,funny,adorable,video,heartwarming,small,child,two months,young</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Tegalombo, Pacitan Regency</media:city>
             <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
             <media:category>Animals</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2258</guid>
             <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 10:37:27 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/58115784-4675-4766-820d-7529a7012ce1.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/bc5760a4-488b-4b3c-9e59-2803ae2a6cc7.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Rare heavy rainstorm engulfs Jinzhou causing flash floods </media:title>
             <media:description>Jinzhou, a city in Northeast China, experienced an extraordinarily rare weather event on June 12th, 2023. Heavy rain mixed with hail transformed the city into a waterlogged maze, causing disruption throughout. The unprecedented downpour resulted in flash floods that submerged the streets, leaving cars driving through water that reached tire height.

For a city unaccustomed to such extreme rainfall, the deluge came as a shock to residents and authorities alike. A video captured by @Eloquent showcased the magnitude of the situation, revealing the sight of vehicles struggling through the flooded streets. The heavy rainstorm overwhelmed the drainage systems, leading to rapid accumulation of water on the road surfaces.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>rare,heavy,rainstorm,hail,water,road,surface,accumulation,city,northeast,China,weather,flash floods,cars,tire high,video,chaos,unprecedented,Jinzhou,waterlogged</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Jinzhou</media:city>
             <media:country>China</media:country>
             <media:category>Weather</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2256</guid>
             <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 09:58:32 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/ebd156c8-971a-40d3-bbbb-9c3925563b1d.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/f6f221a1-2ac7-4e27-b804-a562dc624ee2.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Charming encounter: king quail chicks mistake farmer as their mother!</media:title>
             <media:description>In a heartwarming video captured by @fathenfarms on May 3rd, 2023, in New Milford, Connecticut, USA a flock of adorable king quail chicks was seen dutifully following their caretaker around the house. The author, who has been raising birds since 2012, proudly shared that his farm is home to over 150 birds, consisting of more than 8 species.

The tiny quail chicks, known affectionately as buttons, were only a few days old when they imprinted on the farmer, considering him their mother. The endearing scene unfolded as the chicks trailed closely behind their human caregiver, demonstrating an innocent trust and a bond formed through constant care and nurturing. The author expressed his love for these feathered companions and emphasized that all the birds on his farm are raised solely as pets and for the pure joy of his hobby, with none being harmed or used for consumption.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>chicks,farmer,birds,quail,pets,hobby,imprinting,trust,caretaker,companions,farm,love,animals,connection,compassion,nurturing,bond,mistaken identity,kindness,video</media:keywords>
             <media:city>New Milford, Connecticut</media:city>
             <media:country>United States</media:country>
             <media:category>Animals</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Wed, 3 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2254</guid>
             <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 08:44:34 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/7f945fcf-926f-454e-94e5-a52e006aaf09.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/7b6110dc-1c42-44de-91b2-5446d8019ea1.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Unbelievable goal from corner kick leaves football fans in awe</media:title>
             <media:description>In an extraordinary football match held in Jambi, Indonesia, on March 12, 2023, an incredible goal from a corner kick left fans speechless. The breathtaking moment was captured by @mrival__ who shared the video on social media, instantly gaining viral attention. The footage shows a player confidently stepping up to take a corner kick, but what unfolded next was nothing short of astonishing. As the ball left the player's foot, it soared through the air with remarkable precision, curving towards the net. To the astonishment of everyone present, the ball sailed past defenders and found the back of the net, resulting in an unforgettable goal.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>goal,corner,football,rare,video,Jambi,Indonesia,kick,scoring,ball,player,high-five,fans,viral,astonishing,precision,excitement,unforgettable,unpredictable,skill</media:keywords>
             <media:city> Jambi</media:city>
             <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
             <media:category>Sport</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2243</guid>
             <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 08:27:18 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/98c3fddd-5387-43b4-a5ab-2c82e10f252f.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/1ae823c4-df7a-4c47-aa8c-b46f95cc7e00.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Startled success: Texas toddler's surprising reaction to mother's cheerful congratulation</media:title>
             <media:description>In a heartwarming moment captured on video, a toddler in Texas, USA, showcased his impressive hand-eye coordination while playing with a wooden cube and a ball. The video, shared by @camillesmiith on May 22, 2023, depicts the toddler successfully throwing the ball through the hole in the cube. As soon as he achieved this feat, his mother congratulated him. However, the suddenness of her voice startled the little one, creating an adorable reaction.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>wooden cube,ball,toddler,Texas,USA,video,playing,achievement,hand-eye coordination,surprise,startle,moment,joy,parenting,innocence,development,milestone,support,determination,encouragement,happiness</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Texas</media:city>
             <media:country>United States</media:country>
             <media:category>Heartwarming</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Mon, 22 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2241</guid>
             <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 07:36:19 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/7daa08c1-3e23-4848-8704-7e72260a37d1.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/e7a1bb2f-2742-471a-864b-c595d1658455.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Multiple explosions and fire rock construction site in Hamburg, Germany</media:title>
             <media:description>Multiple explosions and a raging fire engulfed a construction site in Hamburg, Germany, on 9th June, 2023 triggering an urgent response from emergency crews. The incident took place at the Westfield construction site in Hafer City, leaving authorities scrambling to contain the situation. The public has been advised to steer clear of the area, while those nearby have been instructed to remain indoors with windows and doors tightly shut.

The cause of the explosions and subsequent fire at the warehouse remains unclear at this time. Video footage captured by @RFromdablock shows thick plumes of smoke billowing from the site, heightening concerns about the extent of the damage. </media:description>
             <media:keywords>explosions,fire,construction,site,Hamburg,Germany,emergency,crews,Hafer City,smoke,warehouse,authorities,response,video,footage,billowing,damage,investigation,impact,incident</media:keywords>
             <media:city> Hamburg</media:city>
             <media:country>Germany</media:country>
             <media:category>News</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Fri, 9 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2237</guid>
             <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2023 06:50:12 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/1c7adb3e-76b5-435e-91f7-0994b1cf4f57.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2ce19a00-d180-41b0-9595-bc8dcd361516.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Goat's reflection fiasco: hilarious encounter caught on camera!</media:title>
             <media:description>In a humorous incident captured on video, an unsuspecting goat in South Tangerang, Indonesia mistook its own reflection for another goat. The footage, recorded by @tirunsmd on May 8th, 2023, showcases the goat's comical attempts to interact with the shiny metal sheet fence.

The curious goat happened to see the reflective surface of the fence. Mistakenly perceiving its own reflection as a fellow goat, the animal became fixated on the mysterious presence. Ignoring its peaceful surroundings, the determined goat began repeatedly ramming its head into the fence, seemingly attempting to make contact with the perceived "intruder."</media:description>
             <media:keywords>goat,reflection,fiasco,video,footage,hilarious,encounter,camera,South Tangerang,Indonesia,metal sheet fence,mistaken identity,curiosity,relaxation,house,ramming,head,confusion,behavior,entertainment</media:keywords>
             <media:city>South Tangerang</media:city>
             <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
             <media:category>Animals</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Mon, 8 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2246</guid>
             <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 13:10:12 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/14f5125f-4fbc-4c6f-bc2b-5ecbd24fbb1e.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/b8b32939-5d05-4316-b77b-05be1caf6dc8.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Sweets galore: the delicious delight of 'Sweet Harvest Show' engulfs Belagro-2023!</media:title>
             <media:description>At the agricultural exhibition held in Minsk, Belarus on June 10th, 2023, a unique and delightful event took place that left attendees with a sweet taste in their mouths. Organized by the forum of farmers, "Belagro-2023," the spectacle was aptly named the "Sweet Harvest Show." For a few minutes, people were called to gather beneath the pipe of a harvester, and to their surprise, an abundance of sweets came raining down upon them. With hats raised and anticipation in the air, visitors eagerly caught the delectable treats, savoring the moment with a resounding "yum-yum."</media:description>
             <media:keywords>agriculture,exhibition,Minsk,Belarus,farmers,forum,Belagro-2023,sweets,harvester,spectacle,event,unique,delightful,hats,yum-yum,joy,excitement,whimsy,innovation,celebration,respite</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Minsk</media:city>
             <media:country>Belarus</media:country>
             <media:category>News</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2253</guid>
             <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 07:52:12 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2253.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2253.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Children's kindness shines as they help fallen green doll rise again</media:title>
             <media:description>In a heartwarming incident captured on video, a person dressed as a green doll with a tail took a tumble and found themselves unable to get back on their feet. The incident, which occurred on April 2nd, 2023, in Baling, Kedah, Malaysia, attracted the attention of three compassionate children who rushed to lend a helping hand.

The video, filmed by @masyitahosman, shows the person inside the green doll struggling to regain their balance. With each attempt, they seemed to face further difficulties. However, their struggle did not go unnoticed. Three children, whose names remain unknown, quickly approached the fallen doll. With a remarkable display of empathy and kindness, they joined forces and worked together to lift the doll back onto its feet.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>green,doll,tail,fallen,struggle,feet,children,help,kindness,compassion,video,captured,Baling,Kedah,Malaysia,forces,heartwarming,empathy,selfless,connection</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Baling, Kedah</media:city>
             <media:country>Malaysia</media:country>
             <media:category>Heartwarming</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Sun, 2 Apr 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2250</guid>
             <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 19:44:56 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/7c0e8c45-a4d6-4c56-8857-c4bf68842c3e.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/e20f8d86-4d40-426c-86df-7691d27b8b69.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Serenity and brotherhood: two lions embrace in a playful manner in Kruger National Park</media:title>
             <media:description>In a heartwarming display of camaraderie, a captivating sight unfolded in Kruger National Park, South Africa. On April 23, 2023, wildlife enthusiast @louise.wilson.1 captured a remarkable moment between two male lions. The majestic creatures found themselves in the middle of the road, where one lion settled down for a peaceful slumber. Not wanting to miss out on the cozy spot, the second lion playfully climbed on top of its companion, joining in the embrace.

For a while, the two lions lay intertwined, their bodies forming a heartwarming tableau. Their bond was evident as they slept soundly, oblivious to the surrounding world. However, their playful nature soon surfaced, as they gently nudged and pushed each other. With playful shoves and nudges, they eventually settled into their own positions, each finding a comfortable spot.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>lions,wildlife,brotherhood,sleep,road,Kruger National Park,South Africa,companionship,embrace,playfulness,bond,majestic,slumber,nudges,affection,social,dynamics,survival,beauty,tenderness</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Kruger National Park</media:city>
             <media:country>South Africa</media:country>
             <media:category>Animals</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Sun, 23 Apr 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2242</guid>
             <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 08:08:35 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/f9304df7-b810-4a3e-96fb-5e0f0a152026.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/b2450b4f-6362-4e58-b04f-281e964f11b5.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Massive fire and explosions engulf Hamburg's HafenCity construction site</media:title>
             <media:description>Multiple explosions and a large fire erupted on the roof of a ten-storey building at a construction site in Hamburg's HafenCity, Germany, causing significant alarm on June 9, 2023 afternoon. The blaze sent a colossal cloud of black smoke billowing into the sky, visible from a distance as captured by @Ffleig. The police attributed the popping noises to nearby gas cylinders detonating during the fire.

Thankfully, there were no reported injuries, as confirmed by the Hamburg fire service. However, emergency responders did transport a crane operator to an ambulance for examination by a medical professional. As a precautionary measure, residents of HafenCity and the surrounding neighborhoods were instructed to keep their windows and doors closed due to the smoke. </media:description>
             <media:keywords>explosions,fire,roof,construction site,Hamburg,HafenCity,Germany,stir,black smoke,gas cylinders,no injuries,fire service,crane operator,ambulance,examination,emergency doctor,windows,doors,smoke,shopping center,investigation</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Hamburg, HafenCity</media:city>
             <media:country>Germany</media:country>
             <media:category>News</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Fri, 9 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2239</guid>
             <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2023 11:16:21 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/93ca4a67-a4be-40d1-a71e-52b99013089f.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/f1879d43-4680-42a8-ab68-ab2ab8fdfe9c.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Hilarious escape: friends playfully outrun dog in Malaysia</media:title>
             <media:description>On the 29th of April, 2023, in Johor, Malaysia, @itsmeyutt_ captured a video that showcased a lighthearted yet thrilling moment as her friends found themselves being chased by a dog. Just as the author was about to head home, laughter filled the air as her friends, screaming with joy, sprinted towards a nearby house, playfully evading the persistent canine. The chase came to an end when they reached the safety of the house, and the dog gave up, leaving them all laughing as they reflected on their exciting escapade.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>chase,dog,friends,video,laughter,running,Malaysia,near,house,escape,playfulness,joy,thrilling,safety,canine,lighthearted,sprinting,escapade,laughter-filled,persistent</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Johor City</media:city>
             <media:country>Malaysia</media:country>
             <media:category>Animals</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Sat, 29 Apr 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2245</guid>
             <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 11:42:59 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/7c015444-cd01-4865-a263-7dd0625cf41c.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/f8c230c1-72cf-44a3-a805-af50cdb4b549.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Gallon mishap: unfortunate accident shatters drinking water quest</media:title>
             <media:description>In an unfortunate incident captured on video by @_anggitadstyaa on 25th February, 2023, a resident of Samarinda, Indonesia, a simple task turned into a clumsy mishap. The video initially intended to showcase a friend lifting a gallon of drinking water quickly took a turn for the worse. As the author's friend confidently embarked on the short journey into the house, disaster struck. With only a few strides taken, the gallon slipped from her grip, crashing onto the ground, spilling the water on the floor. </media:description>
             <media:keywords>samarinda,indonesia,video,friend,lifting,gallon,mishap,accident,water,recording,fall,broke,house,strides,shattered,plastic,spilled,unexpected,twists,life</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Samarinda</media:city>
             <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
             <media:category>Fails and Funnies</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2244</guid>
             <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 09:02:09 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/65098378-6588-4390-b30c-acdd9214e35e.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/4adcec68-9c86-47f2-95cc-b50aed80cbf2.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Riverside serendipity: a fisherman's close encounter with buffalos</media:title>
             <media:description>In a spontaneous turn of events on May 19, 2023, in Klaten, Indonesia, @rangn.r  and his friend found themselves amidst a unique encounter while trying to catch some fish. Frustrated by his unsuccessful attempts, he persisted in his pursuit. Suddenly, the tranquil riverside scene was disrupted as buffalos were released from their cages, making their way into the river. To his surprise, one buffalo approached from his left. The author quickly decided to record the extraordinary sight. The buffalos peacefully meandered through the river, oblivious to the fisherman's presence. Sensing the need for caution, he slowly stood up and moved away. </media:description>
             <media:keywords>fishing,buffalos,encounter,riverside,Indonesia,recording,frustration,persistence,unique,tranquil,surprise,meander,nature,caution,phone,fisherman,cages,release,convergence,unforgettable</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Klaten</media:city>
             <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
             <media:category>Animals</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Fri, 19 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2257</guid>
             <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 10:21:58 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/f0a1f15b-d52e-4bec-b05a-e3b77d4ba218.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/3653a681-d0ea-444c-94ec-d4f499c02c4e.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Devastating landslide strikes South Bogor District, leaving railway line hanging and villagers trapped in debris</media:title>
             <media:description>A catastrophic landslide in South Bogor District, Bogor city, Indonesia has left a railway line hanging precariously and caused extensive damage to the surrounding village. The distressing scene was captured in a video by @fais_channel on March 15, 2023, revealing the magnitude of the disaster. The landslide not only disrupted the railway infrastructure but also trapped four villagers who were tragically buried under the debris.
</media:description>
             <media:keywords>landslide,railway,hanging,village,affected,debris,rescue,people,buried,video,four,Bogor,South Bogor District,Indonesia,tragedy,destruction,chaos,devastation,emergency,nature</media:keywords>
             <media:city>South Bogor District</media:city>
             <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
             <media:category>News</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2248</guid>
             <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 19:07:04 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/aca3a85f-3a13-4d98-a4e2-5210fe67b69c.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/ce23ea24-261a-46e7-a9af-a5b17e95a8e3.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Clever chalkboard challenge: a father-son pictorial game of wits!</media:title>
             <media:description>In a heartwarming display of intelligence and creativity, a recent video captured the delightful interaction between a father and his young son in Melbourne, Australia. Shared by @itsjoshmiller on May 8th, 2023, the video showcased a unique pictorial game that showcased the boy's exceptional abilities. Using a chalkboard, the father would draw various figures and ask his son to identify them. With astounding accuracy, the clever son always had the right answer, promptly erasing the figure with his chalkboard eraser after each response.

Despite being less than five years old, the young boy's remarkable knowledge and quick thinking shone through in this captivating game. </media:description>
             <media:keywords>father,son,pictorial,game,intelligence,creativity,Melbourne,Australia,video,clever,young,chalkboard,eraser,figures,knowledge,quick thinking,bond,nurturing,cognitive,education</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Melbourne</media:city>
             <media:country>Australia</media:country>
             <media:category>Cool</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Mon, 8 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2221</guid>
             <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 12:09:30 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/4e683411-736b-452a-8890-b8b59cb3c5d7.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/c7eaa500-c519-4418-9438-55ca0bab74b1.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Choked skies: Washington, D.C. enveloped in smoke as wildfire air pollution hits historic highs</media:title>
             <media:description>Washington, D.C., USA, is currently grappling with the most severe air pollution levels witnessed in recent years as smoke from Canadian wildfires engulfs the Mid-Atlantic and Northeast regions. On Thursday, the Metropolitan Washington Council of Governments (COG) issued a rare Code Purple air quality advisory, primarily due to the high concentration of harmful fine particulate matter originating from the wildfire smoke. This marks the first time the region has experienced such an advisory, with previous instances limited to ozone pollution in 2012.

As a result of the alarming air quality, COG has recommended that individuals with respiratory ailments and other sensitive groups refrain from engaging in any outdoor physical activities. Additionally, the general population is advised to limit or avoid prolonged and intense outdoor exertion. The smoky haze has significantly reduced visibility in the capital, as witnessed in a video captured by @starlitdazzle during an airplane landing on 9th June, 2023 morning. In the video, she comments on the challenge of recognizing Washington, D.C.'s iconic buildings due to the obscured skyline.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>wildfires,air pollution,smoke,Washington,D.C.,code purple,fine particulate matter,advisory,Canadian,Mid-Atlantic,Northeast,respiratory,visibility,haze,buildings,outdoors,physical activity,ozone,pollution,reduced,video</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Washington, D.C.</media:city>
             <media:country>United States</media:country>
             <media:category>News</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Fri, 9 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2227</guid>
             <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 08:50:20 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/6a936930-1b48-4aae-a97f-27c5f96cf1a8.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/1325336d-a96f-430b-964a-06863e190d68.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Catastrophe in Santa Barbara: a feline's floral fiasco unfolds</media:title>
             <media:description>In a moment of mischief and curiosity, a mischievous feline in Santa Barbara, California, USA, found itself at the center of a floral fiasco that left shattered pieces in its wake. The incident, captured by @tatyana_mironova_real_estate on November 29th, 2022, shows the daring cat playfully pushing a flower pot off the counter, only to watch it plummet to the ground, breaking into several pieces. With a swift turn of its head, the cat's gaze fixates upon the fallen flower pot, seemingly assessing the aftermath of its daring feat.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>mischief,curiosity,feline,floral,fiasco,shattered,pieces,daring,playfully,plummet,broken,aftermath,gaze,fallen,assess,social,media,amused,inquisitive,unpredictable</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Santa Barbara, California</media:city>
             <media:country>United States</media:country>
             <media:category>Animals</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2022</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2202</guid>
             <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 06:24:12 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/6c57cd27-e791-4dd5-bd08-9d851f79d144.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/12065ac0-f624-4b15-a575-5f65869e65a3.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Budgie bliss: Mere the spiraling star on a heart-shaped straw!</media:title>
             <media:description>In a delightful video captured by @mere.mere114 on March 1st, 2021, in Gifu, Japan, viewers were treated to a mesmerizing sight of a yellow budgerigar named Mere. The playful parrot joyfully spun round and round on a heart-shaped straw placed inside a cup. With vibrant feathers and endless energy, Mere showcased her youthful spirit, captivating the hearts of those who watched the footage.
At just two years old, Mere exuded a zest for life that was truly infectious.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>yellow,budgerigar,spinning,heart-shaped,straw,cup,video,parrot,playful,delightful,vibrant,feathers,energetic,joy,happiness,carefree,enchanted,smiling,youthful,whimsical</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Gifu</media:city>
             <media:country>Japan</media:country>
             <media:category>Animals</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Mon, 1 Mar 2021</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2220</guid>
             <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 11:33:41 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2624cfa7-de69-4ecc-8085-a3f5d10b79a0.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/cc664f58-a45d-45e2-92c4-c1adea854781.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Quebec wildfires engulf northeastern US, choking cities in hazardous smoke</media:title>
             <media:description>A monstrous cloud of smoke, originating from the wildfires in Quebec, has wreaked havoc in the northeastern United States. As a result, more than 75 million people in the region are under air quality alerts, forcing children to stay indoors and grounding flights in New York City. The smoke has enveloped iconic skylines, shrouding them in wafting orange fumes and causing visibility to vanish. The situation is expected to worsen as the heaviest smoke is projected to hit the Northeast, spanning from the mid-Atlantic down to the Carolinas. Air quality indexes in major metropolitan areas such as Philadelphia, Jersey City, and New Haven have reached dangerously high levels, classified as "very unhealthy" by AirNow.gov. New York City, in particular, recorded its highest level of air pollution since the 1960s, with an AQI of 484, placing it in the "hazardous" category. @KellyrKopp captured a video showing the smoke cloud over New York City near George Washington Bridge on 7th June, 2023.

The unprecedented levels of smoke have created a health crisis, with millions of residents at risk of breathing in unhealthy air. Authorities have urged people to remain indoors and take precautions to minimize exposure. Schools have enforced indoor recesses to protect children from the hazardous conditions outside. Flights have been grounded in New York City due to poor visibility caused by the smoke, causing disruptions in travel plans for many.

The smoke conditions are expected to persist at least until Thursday, as the wildfires in Quebec continue to rage.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>smoke,wildfires,air quality,Quebec,northeastern US,children,flights,New York City,residents,risk,unhealthy air,alerts,visibility,pollution,hazardous,crisis,precautions,grounded,disruptions,environment</media:keywords>
             <media:city>New York City</media:city>
             <media:country>United States</media:country>
             <media:category>News</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Wed, 7 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2215</guid>
             <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 07:25:11 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/51ddbff0-182b-4786-b7f4-5f8ab8ca2c80.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/18104127-d7df-461d-915d-217eaab838a5.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Destruction of hydroelectric dam sparks water emergency and escalating tensions between Ukraine and Russia</media:title>
             <media:description>In a catastrophic turn of events, the upper part of the hydroelectric dam in Russian-occupied Novaya Kakhovka, located in the Kherson region of Ukraine, was destroyed on 6th June, 2023. This destructive act led to an uncontrolled discharge of water, triggering a series of alarming consequences. As the blame game ensues, both Ukraine and Russia accuse each other of undermining the hydroelectric power station, further fueling the already heightened tensions between the two nations.

The immediate aftermath of the dam's destruction was the flooding of the hydroelectric power station area, forcing authorities to initiate mass evacuations in the Kherson region. The fear of water scarcity in Crimea looms large, as the region heavily relies on the reservoir's supply. Additionally, the Zaporozhye nuclear power plant had to be shut down due to the incident, compounding the already pressing water shortage crisis in southern Ukraine.

The severity of the situation was highlighted by reports indicating that the Kakhovka Hydroelectric Power Station is beyond repair, a sentiment echoed by both Ukrainian and Russian authorities. Disturbingly, the collapse of the hydroelectric dam continues, with sources suggesting that 14 of the station's 28 spans have already been destroyed, rendering the entire power station completely submerged.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>hydroelectric,dam,destruction,water,evacuation,tensions,Ukraine,Russia,blame,crisis,flood,scarcity,reservoir,power,station,collapse,submerged,geopolitical,aftermath,incident</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Novaya Kakhovka, Kherson</media:city>
             <media:country>Ukraine</media:country>
             <media:category>News</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Tue, 6 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2211</guid>
             <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 09:37:15 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/cfbc6c9c-ac68-4c1a-8444-af9babe61bf2.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/206ffa4c-a665-4ac7-8c94-8b61cff1b5f8.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Unprecedented wildfire smoke engulfs New York City: a choking reminder of Canada's inferno</media:title>
             <media:description>New York City finds itself enveloped in an unprecedented blanket of smoke and haze as wildfires ravage Canadian forests, causing air quality alerts to remain in effect across the Northeast of United States, the Ohio Valley, and the Mid-Atlantic. With the worst air quality in the world, New York ranked number one among cities grappling with this hazardous situation. As captured in a video by @westerley167 on 7th June, 2023, the smoke and smell of fire in New York from Canada have left residents astounded.

The Canadian province of Quebec is currently battling more than 160 out-of-control fires, while Alberta and British Columbia are also grappling with dozens of wildfires. This grim situation has led to Canada's worst wildfire season ever recorded, with approximately 240 active fires reported. The dire consequences of these fires are now being felt in the United States, as hazardous particles degrade air quality as far south as South Carolina. Even areas as distant as the Georgia-Florida border have experienced hints of smoke.

Authorities are urging residents to stay indoors and limit their exposure to the smoke as much as possible, including during exercise. Experts recommend closely monitoring local air quality and wearing masks capable of filtering out tiny particles, such as N95 or KN95 masks. While the smoke plumes are expected to somewhat disperse after Friday morning, the urgency to protect public health remains high. </media:description>
             <media:keywords>wildfires,smoke,haze,air quality,alerts,Northeast,Ohio Valley,Mid-Atlantic,Canada,Quebec,Alberta,British Columbia,New York,crisis,unprecedented,choking,health,masks,pollution,residents</media:keywords>
             <media:city>New York City </media:city>
             <media:country>United States</media:country>
             <media:category>News</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Wed, 7 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2216</guid>
             <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 07:39:37 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/4ca3e5e6-a858-473f-85fc-6767b41577b7.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/f610d60c-2d5b-43a8-96da-2652984bead8.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>West Ham's epic celebration in Prague: players party all night after Europa Conference League triumph</media:title>
             <media:description>West Ham United players extended their victorious celebrations into the night after their historic win in the Europa Conference League. Following their triumph at the final held in Prague, Czech Republic, the team opted to skip their initial flight back to London and continue reveling in the moment. The club had wisely arranged for two flights, allowing the players an additional four hours to bask in their achievement.

Captured by @MrMarkCorner on 8th June, 2023, a video from the festivities showcased the players back at their hotel, embracing the joyous atmosphere. The caption accompanying the video read, "Back at the hotel with the boys! Love you." It was a testament to the camaraderie and unity that fueled their success throughout the competition. </media:description>
             <media:keywords>party,celebration,West Ham,Europa Conference League,win,Prague,Czech Republic,players,flight,London,hotel,teammates,unity,camaraderie,victory,joy,revelry,memorable,unforgettable,championship,elation</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Prague </media:city>
             <media:country>Czechia</media:country>
             <media:category>Sport</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Thu, 8 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2226</guid>
             <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 08:11:50 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/85cd9f13-1605-4611-903b-b98a4dac7a67.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/fcf838cd-52a4-46ec-95ac-4f79ab59cd6d.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Adorable toddler's hilarious twist: moldy bun served at playtime store!</media:title>
             <media:description>In a heartwarming moment captured by @kyliecgray in Barrie, Ontario, Canada, her young son embarked on his first imaginative play as a storekeeper on  May 28th, 2023. Little did she expect the unexpected twist that awaited her when she placed an order for a cheeseburger and fries. Instead of the anticipated treat, the adorable toddler handed her a random moldy bun With a mischievous smile. 

</media:description>
             <media:keywords>store,toddler,playtime,moldy,bun,cheeseburger,fries,imagination,Barrie,Ontario,Canada,laughter,adorable,video,creativity,surprise,make-believe,joy,memory,chuckle</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Barrie, Ontario</media:city>
             <media:country>Canada</media:country>
             <media:category>Heartwarming</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Sun, 28 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2208</guid>
             <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 08:13:07 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/74e45764-8058-48c8-99f0-aa3219399bb3.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/1b78bd31-48ac-40be-9379-a974ec5ddc87.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Trapped in art: dramatic rescue as man stuck in Edmonton's Talus Dome Sculpture</media:title>
             <media:description>In a bizarre incident on April 10th, 2023, a man found himself trapped inside a unique piece of public art in Edmonton, Alberta, Canada. The sculpture in question was the Talus Dome, composed of large silver spheres. @cwks, an ultra runner who happened to be nearby, documented the incident on his phone and got a closer look at the trapped individual. The man inside the structure was reported to be in a state of panic, resembling a mouse trapped in a bucket.

Edmonton firefighters swiftly responded to the scene around 8:30 p.m. that evening. The stranded man was stuck within the mound of polished stainless steel balls with no apparent means of escape. Schwindt, intrigued by the commotion, approached the firefighters and inquired about the situation. Upon learning that it was indeed a person trapped inside, he began capturing the unfolding events on his phone. Observing the trapped man's distress, Schwindt likened the scene to witnessing a panicked creature in confinement.

The rescue operation unfolded as the firefighters diligently worked to extricate the trapped individual from the Talus Dome sculpture. With their expertise, they managed to free the man from his confining predicament. Following his rescue, the man was subsequently arrested, though specific details regarding the reasons for his detainment were not disclosed.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>trapped,art,sculpture,spheres,Edmonton,Alberta,Canada,firefighters,commotion,rescue,incident,silver,stainless steel,panic,documentation,surreal,arrest,public,unusual,bizarre,curiosity</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Edmonton, Alberta</media:city>
             <media:country>Canada</media:country>
             <media:category>Rescue</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2213</guid>
             <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 15:26:16 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/25e2b5a2-53e6-4b1e-a80e-666ea7a16b80.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/75eb58c8-5837-4022-a5fe-59f19d2ea886.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Cat chaos: Cuppa's tabletop tumble sends plate shattering!</media:title>
             <media:description>In a hilarious and unexpected turn of events, a live-streaming session captured an unforgettable moment between two mischievous cats named Cuppa and Berry. The incident took place on May 24, 2023, in Bekasi City, West Java, Indonesia, and left viewers in stitches. As Cuppa attempted to climb onto the table, a precarious plate teetering on the edge proved to be its downfall. In a split second, the plate crashed to the floor, shattering into countless pieces.

The video shared by @berrybellecat on social media showcased the playful antics of the two feline companions. Little did anyone expect that Cuppa's innocent attempt to reach higher ground would result in such comedic chaos. </media:description>
             <media:keywords>kittens,playfulness,live-streaming,antics,comedy,chaos,mishap,table,plate,breakage,Bekasi City,Indonesia,Cuppa,Berry,mischievous,adorable,curiosity,laughter,fragments,unpredictability.</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Bekasi City</media:city>
             <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
             <media:category>Animals</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Wed, 24 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2206</guid>
             <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 07:21:04 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/361d971e-592e-44a8-8394-8bbb9d243129.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/de3f10f9-f034-4d92-859c-4d7d59e0ce84.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Mission impossible: Phoebe the dog's foiled burrito heist caught on camera!</media:title>
             <media:description>In a surprising turn of events, a mischievous dog named Phoebe from San Francisco, USA, was caught red-handed in a hilarious video shared by @phoebeinsf on April 20th, 2023. The clip shows Phoebe with a foil-wrapped burrito clenched between her jaws, seemingly unfazed by the commotion around her. The delectable treat had been procured from the renowned La Taqueria in the heart of the Mission.

As the author tried to coax Phoebe into dropping the  burrito, the clever canine scampered under a table, determined to savor her newfound prize.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>dog,burrito,heist,video,Phoebe,Mission District,San Francisco,La Taqueria,mischief,hilarious,pet,companion,playful,misadventure,bond,unexpected,joy,canine,theft,indulgence</media:keywords>
             <media:city>San Francisco</media:city>
             <media:country>United States</media:country>
             <media:category>Animals</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2235</guid>
             <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 18:53:35 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/057b125d-3f2c-4b08-ab61-19fd52518a9d.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2235.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Brave resilience: unfazed individuals stay calm as boat sinks</media:title>
             <media:description>In a remarkable display of composure and survival instinct, two individuals were caught on camera as their boat, plagued by a severe leak, teetered on the verge of sinking near Nabire, Papua, Indonesia. The video, captured by @aswrdd on the 26th of February, 2023, showcases the astonishing calmness of the passengers as they remained seated in the deteriorating vessel. Instead of panicking or attempting a premature escape, the duo patiently awaited the boat's inevitable fate. Only after the boat had completely submerged did they initiate their escape by swimming away.

</media:description>
             <media:keywords>boat,sinking,leak,calm,passengers,video,capture,survival,instinct,remarkable,composure,escape,swimming,Nabire,Papua,Indonesia,bravery,resilience,danger,inspiring</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Nabire, Papua</media:city>
             <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
             <media:category>Cool</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Sun, 26 Feb 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2230</guid>
             <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 09:50:15 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/1672fd21-21a9-495a-b1c5-e7d0dff0aa2d.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/65ffe138-e057-4d75-b288-54e0fe99e2c0.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Tram derailment in Barnaul: tram collides with a car</media:title>
             <media:description>In a recent incident in Barnaul, Russia, a tram derailed and crashed into a foreign car, according to the regional traffic police. The accident took place on June 5th, 2023, at approximately 15:15 on Chelyuskintsev Street near house number 119b. As the tram veered off its tracks, it collided with a Toyota, causing significant damage to the vehicles involved.

Fortunately, no one was injured in the accident. However, the collision resulted in temporary roadblocks as the damaged car obstructed traffic. Authorities swiftly responded to the scene to ensure the safety of all individuals involved and to restore the flow of vehicles on the affected roadway.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>tram,derailment,collision,foreign car,Barnaul,Russia,Chelyuskintsev Street,accident,traffic police,no injuries,temporary,roadway,Toyota,derailed,crash,damaged,investigation,authorities,safety,obstruction</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Barnaul</media:city>
             <media:country>Russia</media:country>
             <media:category>Road accidents</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Mon, 5 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2222</guid>
             <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 12:28:19 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/f5069885-9c88-44cc-bbb4-357836f22adc.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2222.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Artistic dedication: from leaf art to crowned victory</media:title>
             <media:description>In a heartwarming display of admiration and creativity, @AldrenNazarenoQuintana, a resident of Caloocan in Metro Manila, Philippines, captured a captivating video on April 29th, 2023. The footage showcased his exceptional talent for leaf art as he crafted a stunning portrait of a contestant from Laguna vying for the title of Miss Earth Philippines. Little did he know that his heartfelt creation would play a role in shaping the destiny of his beloved contestant. To his sheer delight, she emerged victorious, wearing the coveted crown, and filling Aldren with an overwhelming sense of pride.

</media:description>
             <media:keywords>fan,leaf art,pageant,contestant,Miss Earth Philippines,Laguna,video,process,admiration,love,dedication,crown,victory,Caloocan,Metro Manila,Philippines,art,creativity,triumph,connection</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Caloocan, Metro Manila</media:city>
             <media:country>Philippines</media:country>
             <media:category>Cool</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Sat, 29 Apr 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2231</guid>
             <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 10:36:37 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/e017ca1d-9017-483d-8a2a-c34c9831f12c.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/4d382bbf-4a01-42c5-bb12-f76b2303b073.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Tragedy strikes Kherson region as Kakhovka hydroelectric power station collapse leaves seven missing and thousands affected</media:title>
             <media:description>Seven individuals are reported missing following the catastrophic destruction of the Kakhovka hydroelectric power station in the Kherson region of Ukraine on 7th June, 2023. Vladimir Leontiev, the head of the Russian administration in Nova Kakhovka, confirmed that these missing individuals included shepherds who were in the area at the time of the incident. The disaster has resulted in a dire situation, with an estimated 22,000 to 40,000 people currently residing within the affected zone.

Vladimir Saldo, the acting head of the Kherson region, disclosed the alarming figures, indicating the scale of the crisis. The Ukrainian administration reported that 1,852 houses on the right bank, which is under Kiev's control, have been flooded. On the left bank, which is now under the control of the Russian Federation, approximately 2,700 houses have been documented as flooded. This devastating event has disrupted the lives of thousands and plunged the region into a state of emergency.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>missing,flooded,shepherds,destruction,hydroelectric,power station,tragedy,Kherson,Ukraine,disaster,zone,houses,affected,crisis,emergency,rescue,assistance,property damage,recovery,reconstruction</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Kherson region</media:city>
             <media:country>Ukraine</media:country>
             <media:category>News</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Wed, 7 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2212</guid>
             <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 15:03:42 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/406585d3-9363-4315-982e-151c1d48edad.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/0a07fcca-3a14-4687-bc55-4b22165c3724.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Cats vs. mouse: hilarious encounter reveals feline cowardice!</media:title>
             <media:description>In a humorous and adorable video captured by @errsunday on May 5th, 2023, in Yogyakarta, Indonesia, two cats were caught in a rather comical situation. The video showcased the feline duo's intense fear of a tiny mouse perched on top of a box, while the cats themselves cowered behind a shopping bag near the door. It was a lighthearted reminder that even our furry friends can have moments of timidity.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>cats,mice,video,humor,adorable,fear,cowardice,Yogyakarta,Indonesia,pets,companions,vulnerability,hunters,shopping bag,door,timidity,amusing,intruder,lighthearted,capture</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Yogyakarta</media:city>
             <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
             <media:category>Animals</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Fri, 5 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2234</guid>
             <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 18:34:36 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/f48bfc33-42d1-495a-86b1-282c9635238e.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/c783b28e-7476-412c-8270-41e9e48f23e1.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Destructive fury unleashed: Fuxin City ravaged by terrifying tornado</media:title>
             <media:description>On June 1st, 2023, a terrifying tornado unleashed its destructive fury upon Fuxin City in Northeast China. Captured by a brave individual a video emerged, showcasing the raw power and devastation caused by this natural disaster. Filmed from the safety of a moving car, the footage revealed a large mass of circling winds and dirt, tearing through the city with relentless force.

As the video unfolded, it became evident that Fuxin City was under siege from the menacing tornado. The swirling winds and debris created a chaotic scene. </media:description>
             <media:keywords>tornado,devastation,Fuxin City,Northeast China,video,circling winds,dirt,destruction,brave,chaos,buildings,trees,debris,power,nature,unpredictable,storm,recovery,rebuilding,scars</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Fuxin City</media:city>
             <media:country>China</media:country>
             <media:category>Weather</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Thu, 1 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2203</guid>
             <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 06:53:31 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/499e4c1f-1d2c-4bc1-a8be-57442376d2b9.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/b7aa68b2-7c02-480d-b230-30b31ec8a83b.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Fury unleashed: a farmer's glimpse into Fuxin's terrifying tornado</media:title>
             <media:description>On June 1st, 2023, in Fuxin City, Northeast China, a farmer named had a harrowing encounter with an extreme weather phenomenona tornado. Engaged in his usual work in the field, the author was suddenly taken aback by a powerful gust of wind that swiftly intensified. Gripped by fear, he quickly sought refuge on the ground but managed to capture the awe-inspiring sight on video.

In a matter of moments, the tranquil landscape transformed into a scene of chaos and destruction. The swirling vortex of the tornado tore through the vicinity with unrelenting force.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>tornado,farmer,Fuxin,extreme weather,wind,fear,field,video,chaos,destruction,vortex,trees,debris,devastation,power,unpredictability,nature,fury,vulnerability,resilience</media:keywords>
             <media:city> Fuxin</media:city>
             <media:country>China</media:country>
             <media:category>Weather</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Thu, 1 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2205</guid>
             <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 07:05:33 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/935c7b17-a84f-4379-a3aa-fdb7212f7f0e.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/c1bf59be-6b3c-4868-b829-40a51d77837f.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Mayon volcano escalates to alert level 3: impending threat of hazardous eruption looms</media:title>
             <media:description>The Philippine Institute of Volcanology and Seismology (Phivolcs) has elevated the status of Mayon Volcano in Albay to Alert Level 3, citing an "increased tendency towards a hazardous eruption." This announcement comes after the institute had recently raised the alert level to 2 due to escalating unrest. Phivolcs warned of a magmatic eruption of a summit lava dome, with a heightened risk of lava flows and hazardous pyroclastic density currents impacting the upper to middle slopes of the volcano. They also expressed concerns about potential explosive activity within weeks or even days.

In a video captured by @SEANcharlord on June 8th, 2023, smoke can be seen emanating from the summit of Mayon Volcano, highlighting the severity of the situation. With the volcano now at Alert Level 3, the local population, particularly the residents of Bicol region, are urged to exercise caution and prioritize their safety. Phivolcs' bulletin serves as a stern reminder for everyone to stay vigilant and prepared for the possible eruption, which could have far-reaching consequences. Authorities will closely monitor the volcano's activity and provide timely updates to ensure the well-being of the affected communities.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>mayon volcano,alert level 3,eruption,hazard,volcanic activity,magmatic,lava flows,pyroclastic density currents,explosive,unrest,smoke,summit,danger,warning,bicol region,philippines,seismology,safety,monitoring,community</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Albay</media:city>
             <media:country>Philippines</media:country>
             <media:category>News</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Thu, 8 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2219</guid>
             <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 08:33:52 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/dbd4ce8f-0b20-472a-b5c7-1077cd791b4e.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/b2344e7d-858d-402e-897f-afbecb0dbcce.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Hydroelectric dam catastrophe in Novaya Kakhovka: Ukraine-Russia water crisis looming</media:title>
             <media:description>In a devastating turn of events, the upper part of the hydroelectric dam in Novaya Kakhovka, located in the Russian-occupied region of Kherson, Ukraine, was destroyed on 6th June, 2023. This resulted in an uncontrolled discharge of water, triggering a dire situation for the residents in the surrounding areas. Both Ukraine and Russia have been quick to accuse each other of undermining the hydroelectric power station, further escalating tensions between the two nations.

The consequences of this catastrophe have been severe. The flooding caused by the collapsed dam has forced the evacuation of residents in the Kherson region, who now fear the impending water shortage in Crimea. Additionally, the Zaporozhye nuclear power plant had to be disabled, compounding the already existing water scarcity in southern Ukraine. With the Kakhovka HPP deemed beyond repair by authorities from both sides, the situation continues to worsen. According to sources from TASS, 14 of the station's 28 spans have been destroyed, leaving the hydroelectric power station completely submerged. This disaster marks a critical moment in the ongoing water crisis between Ukraine and Russia.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>hydroelectric,dam,catastrophe,Novaya Kakhovka,Kherson,Ukraine,uncontrolled,discharge,water,evacuation,Crimea,Zaporozhye,nuclear,power plant,Russian-occupied,collapse,tension,scarcity,submerged,crisis</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Novaya Kakhovka, Kherson</media:city>
             <media:country>Ukraine</media:country>
             <media:category>News</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Tue, 6 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2210</guid>
             <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 09:17:33 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/ee91ef8b-61f7-401d-8af8-054c4245d3d0.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/e187860f-2b92-4c6c-9b35-5f81d9907ef7.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Interspecies encounter: squirrel startles seagull, revealing unfriendly neighborhood dynamics</media:title>
             <media:description>
In a fascinating video captured by @belka.ulya on May 24th, 2023, in St. Petersburg, Russia, an unexpected encounter unfolded between a squirrel and a seagull. Perched outside her window, with a glass pane separating the seagull and her squirrel, @belka.ulya decided to bring the squirrel closer to the window to observe the interaction. However, as she approached with the squirrel in hand, the seagull abruptly took flight, displaying signs of fear. The intriguing moment left the author contemplating the coexistence of squirrels and other large birds, as it became evident that they may not be the most friendly neighbors.

The video, captioned "something tells me they are not friendly neighbors," sheds light on the dynamics between these two species. Despite their physical separation by the window, the seagull's swift departure suggests an underlying tension or fear towards the squirrel.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>squirrel,seagull,window,video,encounter,coexist,neighbors,fear,curiosity,wildlife,St. Petersburg,Russia,animals,glass,tension,dynamics,observation,interaction,species,behavior</media:keywords>
             <media:city>St. Petersburg</media:city>
             <media:country>Russia</media:country>
             <media:category>Animals</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Wed, 24 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2194</guid>
             <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 17:54:06 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/84d99477-3253-4882-b2e2-90456f969e36.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2194.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Unforgettable barefoot ride: sandal mishap captured in hilarious video</media:title>
             <media:description>A recent video captured in Tasikmalaya, West Java, Indonesia, has taken the internet by storm. The footage, shot by @alwidivraja on January 4th, 2023, shows him driving barefoot after his sandal accidentally fell off and got stuck in another motorbike passing by. In the video, the author can be heard laughing, while the oblivious owner of the other motorbike continues riding, seemingly unaware of the unusual situation.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>driving,barefoot,sandal,mishap,video,laughter,motorbike,stuck,hilarious,capture,Tasikmalaya,West Java,Indonesia,amusing,unexpected,carefree,social media,viral,joy,lighthearted</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Tasikmalaya, West Java</media:city>
             <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
             <media:category>Fails and Funnies</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Wed, 4 Jan 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2185</guid>
             <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 07:14:02 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/98013694-a007-4f14-b5f6-1865a6d09b9c.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/6c76aee7-e75d-4b22-ae86-afc25b30e53b.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Terrifying encounter: polar bear narrowly misses attacking snowmobilers in Yakutia, Russia</media:title>
             <media:description>
In a heart-stopping incident in Yakutia, Russia, a polar bear nearly attacked a group of snowmobilers as they made their way to the village of Bykov. The encounter took place on the 31st of May, 2023, as the bear ran alongside the moving snowmobile, closely eyeing the people. Suddenly, it darted towards the sleigh where a passenger was seated, coming perilously close to biting him. The shocking moment was captured on video by a witness, who could only manage to shout out in alarm. Fortunately, the animal missed its target, leaving the snowmobilers shaken but unharmed.

Polar bears, known for their powerful land locomotion, can reach speeds of up to 40 km/h, making them formidable creatures capable of chasing down snowmobiles. Such encounters pose a significant risk to drivers and passengers, as demonstrated in this incident. While the motive behind the bear's actions remains unclear, it is speculated that the animal may have intended to frighten the people rather than actively attack them.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>polar bear,snowmobilers,Yakutia,Russia,Tiksi Bulunsky ulus,village,Bykov,chase,passenger,sleigh,attack,video,encounter,frightening,alarm,danger,remote,caution,wildlife,adrenaline</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Yakutia</media:city>
             <media:country>Russia</media:country>
             <media:category>Animals</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Wed, 31 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2170</guid>
             <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 03:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/814bafc6-05c6-4bbb-b43e-b73ebe43cbdc.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2170.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Intense duel: fierce canine clash over a chicken bone</media:title>
             <media:description>
In a captivating video captured by @richy_kira_thesalchis on May 3rd, 2023, in Santiago, Chile, two dogs engaged in a fierce growling battle over a single chicken bone. The dogs, both gripping one end of the bone, had their snouts touching as they vied for control. It all began when the author was in the process of cutting chicken for her beloved pets, and a chicken leg accidentally slipped from her grasp and fell. She realized that the dogs had taken the leg and had it in their mouths.

As soon as the author realized what had occurred, she quickly grabbed her camera to document the extraordinary scene unfolding before her eyes. The two dogs, determined not to let go of the precious bone, growled intensely at each other, their teeth clamped down firmly. Their fierce expressions and snarling noises painted a picture of rivalry and desire.

Realizing the potential danger and the need to intervene, the author bravely stepped in and took the bone away from the feuding canines. </media:description>
             <media:keywords>dogs,growling,chicken bone,rivalry,intense,video,capture,snouts,biting,duel,pets,instinct,domesticated,companions,confrontation,canines,fierce,gripping,determined,danger</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Santiago</media:city>
             <media:country>Chile</media:country>
             <media:category>Animals</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Wed, 3 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2175</guid>
             <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 05:24:42 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/8f8ca88a-6039-432f-aff8-e1487765bab6.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/aaf6d75d-31ad-4fe6-ba48-844ab6d32579.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Playful dog's spirited encounter with brother turns into a lively game in Buon Ma Thuot City</media:title>
             <media:description>In a captivating video captured by @le_xuanthao on April 11th, 2023, in Buon Ma Thuot City, Vietnam, a seemingly intense encounter between a dog and a person took an unexpected turn. As the person, who happened to be the owner's brother, entered the compound on a motorbike, the dog initially came running to the brother. The vigilant owner swiftly positioned himself between the dog and his brother, attempting to deter any harm. However, the dog persisted in its playful pursuit, circling around the person with uncontainable excitement.

To match the dog's exuberant antics, the brother displayed impressive agility, skillfully jumping from one side of the motorbike to the other. Although in the video the dog appeared hostile, the dog's intentions were not hostile, but rather a spirited invitation to play. Eventually, the dog's energy waned, and it joyfully disengaged from the interaction,</media:description>
             <media:keywords>dog,attack,video,Buon Ma Thuot City,Vietnam,owner,gate,motorbike,compound,deter,round,person,jumping,persistent,relent,protect,confrontation,fearless,footage,incident</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Buon Ma Thuot City</media:city>
             <media:country>Vietnam</media:country>
             <media:category>Animals</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2166</guid>
             <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 16:56:31 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/96e54591-1ef5-453b-82eb-c4ab17122b1b.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/37a362c5-990f-4097-bb38-8a3b14df0107.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Feline freedom fiesta: cats compete in treat-licking contest to celebrate Indonesia's Independence Day</media:title>
             <media:description>In a heartwarming display of feline patriotism, a viral video captured the spirited competition among cats to commemorate Indonesia's Independence Day. Filmed by @wulandapriliani on August 17, 2022, in Pauh, Sarolagun, Jambi, Indonesia, the footage showcases the playful yet competitive nature of these furry participants. The video reveals a unique contest where the cats engage in a treat-licking challenge, adding an adorable twist to the celebration.

With treats hanging enticingly in a line, the cats eagerly lick their treats, attempting to be the first to finish. </media:description>
             <media:keywords>cats,competition,treats,clicking,video,viral,patriotism,Indonesia,Independence Day,feline,contest,licking,Pauh,Sarolagun,Jambi,adorable,playful,unity,pets,celebration,bond</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Pauh, Sarolagun, Jambi</media:city>
             <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
             <media:category>Animals</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Wed, 17 Aug 2022</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2179</guid>
             <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 19:55:12 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/931447d1-9b79-4a35-8256-7bb02984dabf.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/b6fd8e7d-db7e-4caf-b45d-4ae2149e2058.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Falling camera: a serendipitous aesthetic mishap</media:title>
             <media:description>In a moment of uncertainty and against the backdrop of cloudy skies and a strong gust of wind in Wonosobo, Indonesia, @shierlya_ found herself capturing an unexpected and breathtaking video on  February 27, 2023. With initial hesitation, she pondered whether it was wise to proceed. However, succumbing to the thrill of the moment, she decided to hit the record button. Little did she know that fate had something extraordinary in store for her.

As the wind picked up, the unexpected occurred - her phone slipped from her grasp and began its descent, inadvertently continuing to record. In a split second, her friends' voices filled the air with a symphony of startled screams. The tumbling phone created a mesmerizing visual spectacle, capturing her friends' movements as if they were falling through the frame. </media:description>
             <media:keywords>cloudy,windy,video,aesthetic,uncertainty,friends,falling,mishap,serendipitous,moment,capture,thrill,descent,screams,spectacle,unexpected,mesmerizing,frame,captivate,awestruck</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Wonosobo</media:city>
             <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
             <media:category>Fails and Funnies</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2193</guid>
             <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 20:49:47 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/9c677eea-7585-42e6-8cdb-7778e8c4c6c9.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/cdf657b2-50a6-49aa-a2e6-2012d310aae8.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item></channel>
           </rss>