<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
        <rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
        xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
        xmlns:openSearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearchrss/1.0/"
        xmlns:dfpvideo="http://api.google.com/dfpvideo"
        xmlns:tms="http://data.tmsapi.com/v1.1"
        version="2.0">
          <channel>
            <title>ViralBear videos</title>
            <dfpvideo:version>2</dfpvideo:version>
              
                  <item>
                  <media:title>авпап</media:title>
                  <media:description>пав</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>пва</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>пав</media:city>
                  <media:country>American Samoa</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>AS</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>WAR</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Weather</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>exclusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Tue, 8 Aug 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2649</guid>
                  <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 15:02:29 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear2.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2649.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear2.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2649.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Sweet serenity: a head massage exchange between human and feline in General Santos City</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a heartwarming and endearing scene in General Santos City, South Cotabato, Philippines, a beautiful connection between a woman and her feline companion was captured on video by @jiannmay on July 29, 2023. The footage shows the remarkable bond between the two as the woman communicates with her cat, guiding it to massage her head gently using its delicate paws. The intimate exchange of affection and trust is a testament to the deep connection that can exist between humans and their beloved pets, showcasing the profound understanding and love that can transcend species boundaries. This heart-melting moment serves as a delightful reminder of the joy and comfort animals can bring into our lives.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>cat,massage,head,video,jiannmay,General Santos City,South Cotabato,Philippines,connection,bond,affection,trust,pets,love,animals,joy,comfort,feline,human,paws,endearing</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>General Santos City, South Cotabato</media:city>
                  <media:country>Philippines</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>PH</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2648</guid>
                  <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 15:33:08 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2648.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2648.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Adorable Shih Tzu puppy Miyo masters sit and stand commands with delight in Manila, Philippines!</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a heartwarming scene captured by @miyopuppy on November 12, 2022, in Manila, Philippines, her precious Shih Tzu puppy, Miyo, showcased her impeccable training skills by executing sit and stand commands with sheer joy. The video captured the endearing moments of Miyo gracefully obeying her owner's cues. Whenever instructed to sit, the puppy would happily curl up on her stomach, while on the command to stand, she would eagerly rise onto all fours. With an unmistakable look of happiness in her eyes, Miyo's enthusiasm for learning was evident, making the entire experience a delightful display of the loving bond between a pet and its owner.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>adorable,puppy,shih tzu,commands,video,miyo,sit,stand,Manila,Philippines,happy,training,obedience,joy,owner,love,cute,pet,bond,delightful</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Manila </media:city>
                  <media:country>Philippines</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>PH</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sat, 12 Nov 2022</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2647</guid>
                  <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 15:34:50 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2647.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2647.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Typhoon Dussuri aftermath: government trucks extracting water from flooded road tunnel in Fuzhou, Southeast China</media:title>
                  <media:description>In the aftermath of Typhoon Dussuri's devastating impact on Fuzhou, Southeast China, a resident known as @Tenglovehourglass captured a compelling video of government trucks diligently working to extract water from a flooded road tunnel on August 1, 2023. The typhoon's relentless heavy rainfall left the area inundated, and the roadways submerged in mud and standing water. Living nearby, The author witnessed the dire conditions firsthand, as the government staff tirelessly utilized specialized equipment to clean and restore the once-swamped road. As the community grapples with the aftermath of the natural disaster, these efforts serve as a testament to the resilience and determination of those involved in the recovery process.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>typhoon,dussuri,fuzhou,china,flood,rainfall,water,road,tunnel,mud,government,trucks,extraction,cleaning,aftermath,southeast,video,equipment,standing,window</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Fuzhou</media:city>
                  <media:country>China</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>CN</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>News</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Tue, 1 Aug 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2646</guid>
                  <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 15:31:51 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2646.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2646.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Devastating flash floods sever rural road in Zhuozhou, North China</media:title>
                  <media:description>In the aftermath of Typhoon Dussuri, the rural area of Zhuozhou in North China has been hit hard by continuous heavy rainfall, leading to flash floods that have wreaked havoc on the region. In a poignant video captured by @XiaoXiao on August 1, 2023, floodwaters can be seen having mercilessly cut a rural road into two, leaving the village isolated and vulnerable. The author, a resident of the affected village, witnessed firsthand the destructive power of nature as the torrential waters inundated the landscape, disrupting the lives of the local community. With the area bordering Beijing to the north, the impact of this natural disaster has been significant, raising concerns about the safety and well-being of the residents in the wake of this devastating flood event.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>floods,typhoon,rainfall,disaster,Zhuozhou,NorthChina,@XiaoXiao,video,rural,road,flashfloods,aftermath,impact,nature,isolated,community,Beijing,heavyrain,devastation,vulnerability</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Zhuozhou</media:city>
                  <media:country>China</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>CN</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>News</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Tue, 1 Aug 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2645</guid>
                  <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 15:31:31 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2645.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2645.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Frenzy in Gomel: throngs of youth storm second-hand store for bargains</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a stunning display of enthusiasm, young people in Gomel, Belarus, were captured in a video frenzy as they lined up outside a second-hand store, eagerly awaiting its opening. The footage, shot by @yyakirill on August 2, 2023, showcased the intensity of the crowd's eagerness, as they pushed and jostled to secure their positions at the store's entrance. The moment the doors finally opened, a whirlwind of excitement engulfed the scene, with each individual vying to be the first to enter. The author aptly captioned the video, "young people literally storm second-hand shops in Gomel. The crowd pushes into the store, and the strength of the doors can only be envied." This snapshot of consumer zeal underscores the allure of thrifting and the growing trend of sustainable shopping among the youth in the city.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>storm,second-hand,shop,gomel,belarus,frenzy,young,people,crowds,pushing,excitement,bargains,thrifting,sustainable,shopping,trend,@yyakirill,video,doors,enthusiasm</media:keywords>
                  <media:city> Gomel</media:city>
                  <media:country>Belarus</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>BY</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Fails and Funnies</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Wed, 2 Aug 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2644</guid>
                  <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 15:35:26 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2644.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2644.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Touching reunion: emotional dog embraces owner after time apart</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a heartwarming display of affection, a golden retriever named Timber captured the internet's attention with a touching video that showcased her emotional reunion with her owner. The video, shot by @timber.the.golden on July 27, 2023, in Chicago, Illinois, USA, depicted Timber eagerly embracing her owner as they were reunited after a few hours apart. The dog lovingly removed the cape from her owner and showered them with cries of joy, clearly showing how deeply she missed her human companion during their brief separation. According to the owner, Timber always gets emotional whenever they are separated and greets them with overwhelming happiness upon their return. The heartwarming footage quickly went viral, resonating with countless viewers who were moved by the undeniable bond between man and his best friend. </media:description>
                  <media:keywords>emotional,dog,reunion,video,Timber,owner,Chicago,Illinois,USA,embrace,cries,groomer,welcome,affection,bond,love,viral,bestfriend,heartwarming,connection,pets</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Chicago, Illinois</media:city>
                  <media:country>United States</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>US</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2643</guid>
                  <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 15:32:29 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2643.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2643.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Gas station brawl: shocking video goes viral as customers seek justice for dubious fuel</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a shocking incident at a gas station in Barabash, Primorsky Krai, Russia, on July 28, 2023, an aggressive altercation erupted after customers experienced engine troubles following a refueling with suspected low-quality fuel. The situation escalated when two cars failed to start immediately after refueling, and one of the vehicle owners confronted the gas station employee. Instead of addressing the issue, the gas station employee responded with violence, attacking the outraged customers with her fists. The entire episode was caught on camera and quickly spread across the internet, causing outrage among viewers. The affected motorists, determined not to let this go unnoticed, promptly reported the incident to the police in search of justice for their ordeal. Authorities are currently investigating the matter, and public sentiment is demanding appropriate action be taken against those responsible for this appalling act of aggression.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>gas,station,employee,customers,refueling,dubious,fuel,viral,internet,tanker,motorists,brawl,incident,Barabash,Primorsky,Krai,Russia,violence,police,justice</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Barabash, Primorsky</media:city>
                  <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>News</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2642</guid>
                  <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 09:26:09 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2642.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2642.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Beach brawl in Primorye: woman takes down two in fiery verbal skirmish</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a shocking incident near Vladivostok on the beach in Shamora Bay, Primorye, Russia, a woman wearing a black bikini unleashed a display of aggression and martial skill after a heated verbal altercation with her companions on July 27, 2023. Eyewitnesses reported that the women were drinking and quarreling when the woman in the black bikini decided to settle the matter physically. She swiftly attacked the offending woman, sending her sprawling to the floor, and then turned her fury towards a man who attempted to intervene. With precise boxing techniques, she swiftly subdued the man, hoisted him over her shoulder, and delivered a final blow, leaving him on the floor. The relentless attacker then returned to her group, seemingly unaffected by the intense brawl. As of now, it remains unclear whether any of the participants involved in the altercation have filed a complaint with the police.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>beach,brawl,primorye,russia,vladivostok,shamora bay,woman,black bikini,aggression,martial skill,verbal altercation,drinking,quarreling,attack,man,boxing techniques,intervention,relentless,group,police</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Primorye </media:city>
                  <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>News</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2641</guid>
                  <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 09:28:41 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2641.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2641.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Goat rescued after getting caught on electrical wires while being transported in Dagestan, Russia</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a heartwarming incident in the village of Kutih, Dagestan, Russia, a goat was saved from a perilous situation after it got entangled in electrical wires while being transported by truck. The incident, which occurred on July 31, 2023, was captured on video and later surfaced online, capturing the attention of netizens worldwide. According to a representative of the administration of the Charodinsky district, the unfortunate incident was a result of the truck's height being incompatible with the low-hanging wires in the area. Thankfully, concerned individuals came to the goat's rescue promptly. The animal was apparently being transported from the Levashinsky district to the Charodinsky district for sale. </media:description>
                  <media:keywords>goat,rescued,incident,video,online,Dagestan,Russia,truck,electrical,wires,village,Kutih,administration,Charodinsky,district,height,low,hanging,animals,transportation</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Dagestan</media:city>
                  <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Rescue</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2640</guid>
                  <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 09:34:11 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2640.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2640.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Enchanting moments: little boy joins the Yangko Dance, spreading joy in Heilongjiang Province, China</media:title>
                  <media:description>In the heartwarming province of Heilongjiang, China, a captivating scene unfolded during a traditional Yangko Dance activity. Local resident @happy captured a delightful moment on July 9, 2023, as a little boy couldn't resist joining the dancers while watching the mesmerizing performance. The Yangko Dance, renowned in northern China, saw its spirit come alive as the young boy wholeheartedly embraced the rhythmic moves, adding his own touch of innocence and joy to the age-old tradition. The video shared by the author quickly went viral, spreading smiles and warmth across social media platforms, reminding us all of the universal language of dance and the pure happiness it brings.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>happy,dance,yangko,china,heilongjiang,traditional,boy,video,viral,community,performance,northern,joy,heartwarming,moment,captivating,innocence,socialmedia,tradition,smiles</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Heilongjiang province</media:city>
                  <media:country>China</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>CN</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Heartwarming</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sun, 9 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2639</guid>
                  <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 08:10:17 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2639.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2639.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Rainy day joy: a hilarious puddle jump gone wrong!</media:title>
                  <media:description>In the picturesque landscapes of Heilongjiang Province, a heartwarming and comical scene unfolded on July 4, 2023. As captured by @sweetandsourplumspine, a father took his young son for a leisurely stroll after a refreshing rain shower. The boy's innocent eyes spotted a small puddle on the roadside, and with unwavering enthusiasm, he declared his intention to jump over it. Brimming with excitement, he took a brave leap, but fate had other plans. Alas, the little adventurer lost his footing, slipping right into the puddle, much to the amusement of his father and the video's viewers. Laughter erupted, and the adorable mishap turned into a heartwarming moment that encapsulated the joy and spontaneity of childhood.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>rain,walk,puddle,jump,slip,cute,laughter,joy,Heilongjiang,father,son,video,July,2023,roadside,adventure,innocence,amusement,childhood,landscapes</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Heilongjiang Province</media:city>
                  <media:country>China</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>CN</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Fails and Funnies</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Tue, 4 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2638</guid>
                  <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 07:49:12 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2638.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2638.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Driving triumph: conquering the flooded tunnel in Shandong's heavy downpour</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a daring and adrenaline-pumping feat, @3ThousandG found himself navigating through a tunnel submerged in water in Shandong province, China, on July 12, 2023. Caught in the midst of a torrential downpour that left the tunnel flooded, he resorted to using his dash cam camera to capture the nerve-wracking journey home. Braving the uncertain depths, he cautiously steered his vehicle through the water-laden tunnel, relieved to witness his car withstand the challenge without malfunctioning. The video serves as a testament to his determination and driving skills, showcasing his triumphant passage through the submerged tunnel amid the elements' fury.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>downpour,tunnel,water,dashcam,driving,flooded,Shandong,China,heavy,video,journey,brave,vehicle,triumph,adrenaline,challenge,weather,floodedtunnel,drivingtriumph,rain</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Shandong</media:city>
                  <media:country>China</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>CN</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Cool</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2637</guid>
                  <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 07:55:49 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2637.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2637.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>George Strait's Nashville stadium show: an abrupt end in the pouring rain sparks outrage among fans</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a highly anticipated event at Nissan Stadium, country music legend George Strait's performance in Nashville, Tennessee, USA, came to an abrupt halt as the rain poured down on July 29th, 2023. Despite efforts to fit in as much music as possible before impending storms, Strait's set was cut short, leaving fans disappointed and outraged. The decision not to offer refunds or reschedule the show infuriated concertgoers who expected a full performance from the iconic singer. With tickets for Strait's limited 2023 shows being highly priced and sought after, the disappointment was intensified. While safety concerns regarding lightning and severe weather were cited as reasons for the abrupt ending, fans questioned whether the show could have resumed later. As concert organizers become increasingly cautious about weather-related risks, this incident adds to the ongoing debate on balancing entertainment with safety at outdoor events. @magsd94 captured a video of with the stadium full f people despite the drizzling. </media:description>
                  <media:keywords>concert,music,country,legend,nashville,nissan stadium,george strait,rain,storm,disappointment,outrage,tickets,performance,abrupt,safety,lightning,outdoor,event,fans,iconic</media:keywords>
                  <media:city> Nashville, Tennessee</media:city>
                  <media:country>United States</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>US</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>News</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2636</guid>
                  <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 07:46:14 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2636.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2636.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Typhoon no. 6: from fun to forecast - Araha beach experience captured on video</media:title>
                  <media:description>On August 5th, 2023, @lycomoca captured a thrilling video of strong winds at Araha Beach in Chatan Town, Okinawa Prefecture, Japan. Playfully seeking to experience a typhoon's force, the videographer braved the intense gusts as Typhoon No. 6 raged across the area. Thankfully, the winds eventually subsided on the main island of Okinawa. However, authorities warn that the typhoon is expected to regain strength and move north along the west coast of Kyushu from August 8th to 9th. A forecast map revealed the trajectory, spanning from 12:00 on the 8th to 24:00 on the 9th. Despite the weakened force in the video, the strong winds showcased the awe-inspiring power of nature during this captivating encounter with Typhoon No. 6.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>typhoon,winds,video,experience,fun,Araha Beach,Chatan Town,Okinawa Prefecture,Japan,forecast,map,strength,north,west coast,Kyushu,August,gusts,nature,power,encounter,captivating</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Chatan Town, Okinawa Prefecture</media:city>
                  <media:country>Japan</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>JP</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Weather</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sat, 5 Aug 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2635</guid>
                  <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 07:45:32 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2635.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2635.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Miraculous escape: child unhurt as Lada Xray collides with bicycle and Subaru in Yekaterinburg</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a heart-stopping incident on July 13, 2023, in Yekaterinburg, Russia, a young boy on a bicycle narrowly escaped serious harm after being struck by a "Lada Xray" car. The accident occurred when the child unexpectedly entered the roadway of a residential passage. The collision mangled he bike, and the child tumbled to the pavement. However, by some stroke of luck, the child emerged from the ordeal without any injuries. Following the initial collision, the "Lada Xray" then careened into a parked Subaru, causing additional damage. Surprisingly, despite the severity of the accident, the city traffic police revealed that no one had reported the incident to them. Authorities are urging witnesses to come forward to assist with their investigation into the unsettling incident.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>bicycle,accident,Yekaterinburg,Russia,Lada Xray,boy,roadway,yard,passage,collision,Subaru,traffic,police,injury,bike,pavement,luck,witnesses,investigation,damage</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Yekaterinburg</media:city>
                  <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Road accidents</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2634</guid>
                  <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 07:56:33 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2634.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2634.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Trapped in flames: dramatic rescue of residents from Almaty apartment fire</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a devastating incident that shook Almaty, Kazakhstan, on August 1, 2023, an apartment on the fifth floor of a multi-storey building in the Akkent microdistrict caught fire. As panic spread among the residents, they resorted to desperate measures to escape the raging flames. In a heart-wrenching scene, parents threw their children out of windows in a bid to save them before jumping themselves. The heroic efforts of firefighters from the Ministry of Emergency Situations, however, proved crucial as they arrived within six minutes and swiftly initiated rescue operations. Braving the intense heat and danger, the firefighters skillfully used ladders to evacuate at least 290 people from the high-rise inferno, preventing further loss of life and mitigating the catastrophe's impact. The cause of the fire remains unknown, leaving the community to mourn the tragedy and reckon with the scars left behind.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>fire,almaty,kazakhstan,afternoon,apartment,fifth floor,multi-storey,blaze,evacuation,panic,children,rescue,firefighters,emergency,inferno,tragedy,heroic,ladders,community,impact</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Almaty</media:city>
                  <media:country>Kazakhstan</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>KZ</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Rescue</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Tue, 1 Aug 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2633</guid>
                  <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 08:07:52 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2633.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2633.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Playful corgi Jam from Belarus delights in dandelions</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a heartwarming video captured by @no_fans_only_plants on May 18, 2023, in St. Petersburg, Russia, a delightful corgi named Jam stole the spotlight as he frolicked in a field of dandelions. The playful pup, originally hailing from Belarus, exhibited his exuberance and love for life, embodying the typical corgi spirit. However, what sets Jam apart is his endearing habit of munching on dandelions, which his owner allows without any reservations. Emphasizing the importance of letting pets be themselves, the author expressed a deep understanding and appreciation for Jam's individuality. This heartening tale of a free-spirited corgi cherishing life's simple pleasures reminds us to embrace our loved ones for who they truly are.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>playful,corgi,jam,video,Belarus,dandelions,field,StPetersburg,Russia,pets,love,individuality,free-spirited,happiness,nature,adorable,canine,companionship,joy,outdoor,embrace</media:keywords>
                  <media:city> St. Petersburg</media:city>
                  <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Thu, 18 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2631</guid>
                  <pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 14:06:33 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2631.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2631.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Unexpected chair collapse turns dining mishap into laughter at Semarang restaurant</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a heartwarming yet amusing incident at a restaurant in Semarang, Indonesia, a woman had a lighthearted response to an unexpected mishap. On July 18, 2023, @sambel.pinuk.alisamu captured a video that quickly gained attention on social media. The footage showed the woman falling off her chair as it collapsed beneath her while she was eating. However, instead of being flustered or embarrassed, she laughed it off with good humor. The man she was dining with rushed to her aid and helped her back up. According to the author it seemed that the chair had shifted and hit a gap between the tiles, leading to the unexpected accident. The heartwarming display of laughter and camaraderie in the face of a minor mishap brought a smile to many as the video went viral, reminding us all to find joy in life's little moments.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>restaurant,semarang,indonesia,video,woman,chair,collapse,unexpected,help,dining,laughter,mishap,socialmedia,humor,viral,camaraderie,joy,permission,tiles,accident</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Semarang </media:city>
                  <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>ID</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Fails and Funnies</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2629</guid>
                  <pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 14:04:14 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2629.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2629.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Traffic police car collides with child in Bataysk, Russia: investigation underway</media:title>
                  <media:description>In an unfortunate incident on July 11, 2023, in Bataysk, Russia, a young boy was involved in a collision with a traffic police patrol car on Slavy Street, 7. The incident was caught on video by residents of the house and shared on social media. The footage shows the child being knocked down but managing to get back up and limping in shock towards the entrance of the house. Surprisingly, the inspector driving the patrol car did not approach the child after the accident but instead returned to the driver's seat. The Main Directorate of the Ministry of Internal Affairs of Russia for the Rostov Region stated that the child, born in 2014, suddenly ran out onto the road due to parked vehicles. An investigation into the circumstances surrounding the incident is currently underway.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>accident,bataysk,russia,boy,traffic,police,patrol,car,video,social,media,collision,pedestrian,investigation,shock,limping,entrance,inspector,parked,vehicles</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Bataysk</media:city>
                  <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Road accidents</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2628</guid>
                  <pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 14:02:51 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2628.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2628.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Enigmatic equine enigma: a horse's puzzled encounter with a horse coat</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a heartwarming yet amusing scene at @abbottsviewlivery in Aston Abbotts, UK, a delightful video captured by the account owner on June 11, 2023, showcased their horse donning a horse coat. The comical attire covered the horse entirely, except for two eye holes, leaving the majestic creature looking perplexed and inquiring about the peculiar get-up. As the laughter of the onlookers filled the air, the horse appeared to be seeking answers from its amused companions, making for an endearing moment that truly highlighted the unique bond between humans and their equine companions.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>horse,coat,confused,video,Aston Abbotts,UK,laughter,equine,companions,amusement,head-to-hoof,enigma,bond,unique,moment,animals,livery,eye holes,inquiring,delightful,June 11</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Aston Abbotts</media:city>
                  <media:country>United Kingdom</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>GB</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2626</guid>
                  <pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 14:00:21 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2626.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2626.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Reckless white SUV causes collision with street light: violation of traffic rules in Jiangxi Province, China</media:title>
                  <media:description>In Jiangxi Province, China, a recent traffic incident captured on video by @Jiangxitrafficpolice has brought attention to the dangers of reckless driving. On June 15, 2023, a driver was maneuvering their vehicle along a normal route when disaster struck. As they passed an uphill section, a white SUV suddenly appeared, overtaking on the hill and violating traffic regulations. The video shows the desperate attempt of the driver to avoid the SUV, but tragically, they collided with a street light post instead. The footage clearly highlights the white SUV's failure to adhere to road rules as the main cause of the accident. As a result, no one was hurt.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>accident,video,traffic,jiangxi,china,collision,streetlight,SUV,overtaking,hill,regulations,responsible,driving,safety,road,incident,reckless,footage,violation,driver</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Jiangxi</media:city>
                  <media:country>China</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>CN</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Road accidents</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2625</guid>
                  <pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 13:59:40 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2625.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2625.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Unusual collision in Jiangsu: scooters smile and carry on despite impact at crossing</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a peculiar incident captured by @trafficsafetyeveryday in Jiangsu Province, China, on July 24, 2023, two motorists collided in front of a moving car at a crossing area. The collision involved a woman driving an electric scooter and a delivery rider, both also on electric scooters. Surprisingly, despite the impact, the two parties showed an unexpected reaction. Instead of anger and frustration, they exchanged smiles after checking for injuries and continued on their way. The scene left the author intrigued, leading them to save the video. The incident serves as a unique reminder of how even in the midst of accidents, a moment of understanding and positivity can arise on the roads.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>collision,motorists,Jiangsu,China,video,crossing,traffic lights,electric bicycles,delivery rider,interesting,smile,accident,understanding,positivity,roads,@trafficsafetyeveryday,July 24,2023,intriguing,motorists,movement</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Jiangsu</media:city>
                  <media:country>China</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>CN</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Road accidents</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2624</guid>
                  <pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 13:57:46 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2624.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2624.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Friend's car narrowly avoids major collision with large truck on rural road in Heilongjiang Province</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a heart-stopping incident captured by @trafficsafetyeveryday on July 20, 2023, in Heilongjiang Province, China, a group of friends experienced a harrowing moment while driving to the countryside. As they were passing through a rural road, their friend's car, positioned in front of the author's vehicle, collided with the body of a large truck. The tense situation unfolded when the truck abruptly slammed on its brakes, causing the vehicle to lose control and veer towards the back of the truck. Fortunately, luck was on their side as the collision was not as severe as it could have been, considering it occurred just as they were nearly past each other. No harm done.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>accident,traffic,safety,video,friends,car,truck,collision,countryside,rural,road,Heilongjiang,China,brake,control,closecall,tense,vigilance,luck,reminder</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Heilongjiang Province</media:city>
                  <media:country>China</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>CN</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Road accidents</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2623</guid>
                  <pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 13:55:37 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2623.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2623.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Close call at the torch relay: commemorating Suro in South Jakarta</media:title>
                  <media:description>On the night of July 18, 2023, in South Jakarta, Indonesia, @kibojagoo captured a thrilling moment during a torch relay procession held to commemorate the first night of Suro, the Islamic New Year's Eve. In a video shared online, the author was seen walking alongside others holding fire torches when a close encounter almost turned into a disaster. As a fire torch came dangerously close to his hair, the end of his bun caught fire, prompting a quick reaction from him. Acting swiftly, he released the bun and managed to brush off the fire, averting any serious damage. Unfazed by the incident, the author continued recording the video, still engrossed in reading the sholawat, a prayer in Islamic tradition. He even humorously remarked that due to his frizzy and messy hair, no burn marks were visible. The event served as a poignant reminder of the significance of Suro and the importance of vigilance during such celebratory occasions.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>torch relay,procession,fire,hair,close call,Suro,Islamic New Year's Eve,South Jakarta,Indonesia,video,celebration,vigilance,frizzy,messy,safety,tradition,prayer,commemoration,community,culture,night</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>South Jakarta</media:city>
                  <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>ID</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Fails and Funnies</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2622</guid>
                  <pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 13:54:01 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2622.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2622.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Laughing in the face of disaster: Cotabato City's titanic-style flood adventure</media:title>
                  <media:description>In the midst of a devastating flood in Cotabato City, Philippines, @‌_kathlilies captured a heartwarming video that showcased the remarkable resilience and humor of the residents. Waist-high waters flooded their home, but one of them ventured inside, playfully recreating a scene from the movie "Titanic" in a lighthearted manner. The video, filmed on July 12, 2023, quickly went viral, spreading joy and inspiration worldwide. Despite the chaos and destruction caused by the flood, the residents' ability to find humor amidst adversity served as a powerful reminder of the human spirit's indomitable nature. </media:description>
                  <media:keywords>flood,resilience,humor,CotabatoCity,Philippines,video,Titanic,lighthearted,disaster,community,unity,inspiration,viral,chaos,destruction,adversity,laughter,camaraderie,uncertainty,positivity</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Cotabato City</media:city>
                  <media:country>Philippines</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>PH</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Fails and Funnies</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2621</guid>
                  <pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 08:00:43 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2621.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2621.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Ezro John's hilarious CPR lesson: from jokes to saving lives</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a video captured on July 21, 2023, at Saint Louis University in Baguio City, Philippines, a medical technologist student named Ezro, with the social media handle @‌ezrojohn_rmt, took part in Basic Life Support training. Amidst the CPR lesson, Ezro humorously slapped the mannequin patient, jokingly captioning the moment, "POV: You are saving lives but has anger issues. Doesn't want to wake up, sooo." However, as the training progressed, Ezro and his fellow students were taught the proper and serious way of performing CPR. Learning the vital techniques to potentially save lives, the lighthearted start of the session eventually transitioned into a valuable lesson on the importance of the life-saving skill.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>cpr,training,medical,technologist,student,mannequin,lesson,humor,serious,life-saving,skills,education,practice,Saint Louis University,Baguio City,Philippines,video,caption,CPR training,Basic Life Support</media:keywords>
                  <media:city> Baguio City</media:city>
                  <media:country>Philippines</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>PH</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Fails and Funnies</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2620</guid>
                  <pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 08:01:41 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2620.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2620.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Persistent feline pursuit: hilarious toilet time with a tenacious cat</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a comical and relatable scene, @badnotwolf from Vinnytsia, Ukraine, shared a video of his persistent cat, Roxy attempting to join him in the bathroom. On July 11, 2023, while seated in front of the camera, the cat made numerous unsuccessful leaps towards its owner, who was simply seeking a moment of relaxation on the toilet. With only the legs visible in the video, viewers were left amused by the feline's determined efforts to be part of the action.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>cat,toilet,video,legs,Ukraine,Vinnytsia,July,2023,hilarious,comical,pet,owner,persistent,attempts,relaxation,funny,feline,jump,bathroom,amusing,scene</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Vinnytsia</media:city>
                  <media:country>Ukraine</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>UA</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2618</guid>
                  <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 13:20:43 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2618.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2618.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Convicted thief escapes Blagoveshchensk pre-trial detention center through transmission window</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a daring escape, a young man convicted of theft managed to break free from a pre-trial detention center in Blagoveshchensk, Russia, through a transmission window on July 30, 2023. The incident occurred on Sunday during a visitation and transfer session, taking advantage of the warden's absence. After being on the run for a few hours, the fugitive was finally apprehended on the night of July 31st. According to the Russian Federal Penitentiary Service for the Amur Region, the escapee had been in detention since December 2022. Now facing severe consequences, the convict may be sentenced to forced labor or imprisonment for up to four years, as per Article 313 of the Criminal Code of Russia. Additionally, the court will charge him for the expenses incurred during the search operation. The Federal Penitentiary Service is currently conducting an internal audit to assess the security breach that allowed this escape to occur.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>escape,convict,theft,pretrial,detention,Blagoveshchensk,Russia,transmission,window,caught,criminal,penalty,fugitive,imprisonment,search,audit,warden,apprehended,visitation,expenses</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Blagoveshchensk</media:city>
                  <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>News</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2617</guid>
                  <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 13:22:11 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2617.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2617.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Adorable foster kittens indulge in a 'paws'-itively messy drink!</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a heartwarming scene captured by @emiliexfosters on July 18, 2023, in Milwaukee, USA, three adorable foster kittens were caught on video enjoying a drink from a bowl. However, one mischievous kitten had its legs dipped into the liquid as it drank, resulting in a cute yet messy moment. With quick reflexes, the author lifted the little one out of the bowl, revealing its front paws soaked in the brown liquid used for weaning them. Despite the adorable mishap, the sight of these tiny furballs brought smiles to viewers' faces, showcasing the joys of caring for foster animals.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>adorable,foster,kittens,video,drink,bowl,legs,soaked,weaning,messy,cute,moment,reflexes,furballs,caring,animals,pets,@emiliexfosters,Milwaukee,USA</media:keywords>
                  <media:city> Milwaukee </media:city>
                  <media:country>United States</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>US</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2615</guid>
                  <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 13:22:47 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2615.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2615.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Boomer's midnight mischief: possum party at home!</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a humorous and slightly mischievous incident captured by @ndnchic33 on June 17, 2023, in Chelsea, Alabama, USA, her adorable dog, Boomer, became the center of attention. The video shows Boomer lounging on the couch late at night, accompanied by an unexpected guest - possums! Apparently, Boomer had invited his possum friend over to join him indoors, much to his owner's surprise. In the video, we hear the author playfully scolding Boomer, reminding him that bringing friends into the house is not allowed. The adorable footage showcases Boomer's nocturnal adventures and his owner's delightful reaction to the unusual situation. It's a heartwarming reminder of the unexpected antics our furry friends can get up to when the world sleeps.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>night,dog,Boomer,possums,couch,house,video,Chelsea,Alabama,USA,friends,mischief,adorable,owner,surprise,nocturnal,antics,furry,funny,pets</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Chelsea, Alabama</media:city>
                  <media:country>United States</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>US</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2613</guid>
                  <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 08:13:17 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2613.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2613.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Enchanting double rainbow delights travelers in Rakov, Belarus</media:title>
                  <media:description>On July 30, 2023, a mesmerizing sight graced the city of Rakov, Belarus, as @lucyfer_da captured a stunning video of a rainbow during her return journey. After a trip to Nalibokskaya Pushcha, she noticed a remarkably bright and clear rainbow hovering over a distant lake. Throughout the drive, the rainbow remained elusive, often obscured by trees and buildings. However, as they ventured onto the track and turned a corner, the rainbow revealed its full splendor, stretching wider than the entire roadway. Onlookers were left in awe, with people pulling over to capture the spectacle with their cameras. Curiously, there was no rain preceding or following the rainbow, but within its vivid hues, a fine drizzle could be seen, akin to droplets from a spray bottle. As if one rainbow wasn't enough, a larger, fainter one appeared above the brilliant arc, adding to the enchantment of the moment. Nature's breathtaking display left a lasting impression on all who bore witness to this extraordinary occurrence.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>rainbow,rakov,belarus,video,lake,trees,buildings,travel,enchanting,double,stunning,splendor,onlookers,cameras,drizzle,nature,display,breathtaking,moment,occurrence</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Rakov</media:city>
                  <media:country>Belarus</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>BY</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Cool</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2612</guid>
                  <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 08:14:07 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2612.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2612.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Swaddle buddies: heartwarming video shows cat and baby bonding in Ciamis, Indonesia</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a heartwarming display of unlikely companionship, a video captured by @sheisseu malikeymouse on July 22, 2023, in Ciamis, Indonesia, has taken the internet by storm. The footage shows a swaddled baby peacefully lying next to a swaddled cat, with the feline seemingly unfazed by the tiny human's presence. According to the account owner, the cat has a penchant for disturbing the child, prompting the clever idea of swaddling them both together. </media:description>
                  <media:keywords>swaddle,baby,cat,companionship,bond,video,Indonesia,Ciamis,heartwarming,pets,harmony,unexpected,love,animals,internet,admiration,unique,clever,touching,footage</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Ciamis</media:city>
                  <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>ID</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Heartwarming</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2611</guid>
                  <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 08:15:55 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2611.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2611.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Playful pranks and paw popping: a kitten's hilarious reflexes!</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a heartwarming and humorous video captured by @pinkintotheblue on May 28, 2023, in Cikande, Banten, Indonesia, a playful kitten steals the show with its adorable reflexes. The feline's owner, @pinkintotheblue's boyfriend, gently held the little furball in his hands while playfully making popping sounds with his mouth. The kitten's reaction was priceless - as soon as it heard the sounds, it instinctively lifted all its tiny legs in surprise, only to settle back down again in his hands. With a house full of cats, the couple thoroughly enjoys creating these delightful moments on camera. This heartwarming video captures the joy and bond shared between humans and their feline companions, reminding us of the simple pleasures that brighten our lives.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>playful,kitten,reflexes,video,popping,adorable,hands,joy,cats,love,fun,pets,cute,surprise,bonding,moments,laughter,Indonesia,Banten,Cikande</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Cikande, Banten </media:city>
                  <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>ID</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sun, 28 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2610</guid>
                  <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 08:16:32 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2610.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2610.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Midnight motorbike melody: barking serenade by excited street dogs</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a captivating video captured by @abdullaev.222 on July 9, 2023, in Saratov Rakhova, Russia, a group of street dogs showcased their curious behavior towards a motorbike. As the rider turned on the engine, the dogs immediately came rushing towards him, barking excitedly. However, whenever the engine was switched off, they would retreat, only to return with renewed enthusiasm once it roared to life again. The intriguing scene unfolded during the night when the rider stopped to answer a phone call, catching the dogs' attention and prompting him to start recording the delightful encounter. It's a heartwarming reminder of the special bond between humans and their four-legged companions, even in unexpected and amusing circumstances.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>motorbike,dogs,street,night,Russia,Saratov,barking,excitement,video,capture,curious,engine,retreat,enthusiasm,phone,call,recording,bond,humans,companions</media:keywords>
                  <media:city> Saratov Rakhova</media:city>
                  <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sun, 9 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2609</guid>
                  <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 08:12:32 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2609.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2609.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Unsuspecting seaside silliness: a chair, a wave, and laughter in Banda Aceh!</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a moment of pure beachside amusement, an unexpected encounter with a massive wave turned into a hilarious spectacle for @aleshafamily_ on July 6, 2023, in Banda Aceh, Indonesia. Seated comfortably in her chair by the water's edge, little did she anticipate the waves reaching her spot. As if to playfully challenge her, a colossal wave surged forward just as she attempted to escape its reach with her chair. Instead of escaping unscathed, she found herself tumbling onto the sandy shore, bursts of laughter echoing around her. The video she captured quickly spread, showcasing the joyous mishap that made the internet chuckle along with her seaside antics.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>beach,waves,chair,laughter,video,unexpected,Banda Aceh,Indonesia,amusement,moment,water,edge,hilarious,encounter,summer,sea,shoreline,sand,mishap,internet</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Banda Aceh</media:city>
                  <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>ID</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Fails and Funnies</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Thu, 6 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2607</guid>
                  <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 08:03:37 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2607.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2607.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Intense firepower unleashed: Ukrainian forces train and prepare for confrontation between Donbass and Bakhmut</media:title>
                  <media:description>In the tense and war-torn between Donbass and Bakhmut, Ukraine, a harrowing video emerged on July 24, 2023, capturing the relentless firing of warheads by soldiers in the fields. The footage was attributed to @vladhalidov, shedding light on the activity of the Sheikh Mansour Battalion (BShM) and the Special Tactical Army Group LOM. Under the command of Muhammad-Aslan, the group conducted a strategic briefing on the impending storming of Russian positions, while also providing crucial training to the Ukrainian army. The conflict between Ukraine and Russia had persisted for over a year, with this latest display of firepower indicating the ongoing severity of the situation in the region. As tensions escalated, the international community remained on high alert, closely monitoring the developments in this volatile conflict zone.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>soldiers,firing,warheads,Donbass,Bakhmut,Ukraine,video,Sheikh Mansour Battalion,BShM,Special Tactical Army Group LOM,commander,Muhammad-Aslan,briefing,storming,Russian positions,training,armed conflict,tension,international community,escalation</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Donbass</media:city>
                  <media:country>Ukraine</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>UA</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>News</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2606</guid>
                  <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 08:28:15 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2606.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2606.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Adorable cashier's assistant: the beloved parking lot cat of Odessa, Ukraine</media:title>
                  <media:description>In the bustling city of Odessa, Ukraine, a heartwarming scene unfolded at a local parking lot on July 29, 2023. @40medok, an observant passerby, captured a heart-melting moment as a charming cat sat gracefully at the cashier's window, patiently awaiting attention. With affectionate pets and gentle caresses, the feline earned its rightful place as the "Cashier's Assistant." Customers and visitors passing by couldn't resist showering the cat with respect and tenderness, creating a sense of community around this adorable furball. This endearing sight has become a cherished part of the parking lot's atmosphere, leaving everyone with a smile as they complete their errands, knowing that a little feline guardian watches over them.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>adorable,cat,cashier,window,parking lot,Odessa,Ukraine,pet,picture,baby,cute,good,respect,tenderness,community,furball,atmosphere,guardian,smile,errands</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Odessa</media:city>
                  <media:country>Ukraine</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>UA</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2605</guid>
                  <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 07:59:28 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2605.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2605.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Nature's fury unleashed: lightning strikes and flames explode in Shijiazhuang</media:title>
                  <media:description>On July 24, 2023, in Shijiazhuang, northern China, a startling and unintentional event was captured on video by @HomelessYuanyuan. As she stood in front of her apartment window with her mobile phone, attempting to capture a street scene during a rainstorm and thunder, lightning struck the transformer below her building. The intense impact caused sparks of flames to erupt, scattering fiery fragments in all directions. Nature's fury was unleashed, and in a split second, the author found herself witnessing a breathtaking display of raw power and danger.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>lightning,sparks,flames,explosion,rainstorm,thunder,Shijiazhuang,China,video,mobile,window,street,nature,fury,power,danger,unpredictability,awe,humbled,@HomelessYuanyuan</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Shijiazhuang</media:city>
                  <media:country>China</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>CN</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>News</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2604</guid>
                  <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 13:16:50 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2604.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2604.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Thrilling mishap: Audi drift attempt ends in guardrail collision at Suzhou GTshow </media:title>
                  <media:description>During the annual Suzhou GTshow on July 22, 2023, a highly anticipated automotive cultural event in China, a heart-pounding incident occurred as an Audi car attempted a daring drift maneuver. The vehicle lost control and collided with a guardrail, sending shockwaves through the crowd of car enthusiasts. Thankfully, no one was injured in the dramatic collision. The video captured by @ShanghaiUPAutomotiveTechnicalService shows the intensity of the moment, serving as a reminder of the risks involved in high-speed automotive displays. Despite the unexpected mishap, the event continued, showcasing a spectacular display of Custom cars and Supercars to the delight of the attendees.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>drift,audi,collision,guardrail,suzhou,china,g t show,automotive,event,enthusiasts,custom,supercar,annual,mishap,excitement,car,culture,display,injured,risk</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Suzhou</media:city>
                  <media:country>China</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>CN</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2603</guid>
                  <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 13:19:39 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2603.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2603.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Bear brawl at Guaipo Tiger Park: two black bears engage in fierce fight over food</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a thrilling and unexpected encounter at the Guaipo Tiger Park in Shenyang, Northeast China, two black bears engaged in a heated fight, captured on video by local resident @100millionfatballs on June 24, 2023. As she explored the living area of the black bears, the normally docile animals suddenly clashed, with their aggression escalating over a possible dispute for food. The shocking scene prompted the author to react quickly, loudly shouting in an attempt to intervene and put an end to the confrontation. Her bravery in the face of this intense encounter showcased the unpredictable nature of wildlife and served as a powerful reminder of the importance of respecting and preserving the delicate balance between humans and the animal kingdom.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>shenyang,china,black bears,fight,video,wildlife,park,encounter,food,aggression,shock,visitor,Guaipo Tiger Park,northeast,@100millionfatballs,nature,animals,conservation,bravery,balance</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Shenyang</media:city>
                  <media:country>China</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>CN</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2602</guid>
                  <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 13:12:52 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2602.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2602.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Terrifying Yokohama guerrilla rainstorm unleashes chaos with its fierce winds and torrential downpour</media:title>
                  <media:description>In Yokohama, Japan, on August 1, 2023, @Tomo_YNU captured a chilling video of a rainstorm known as Guerrilla. This local phenomenon is characterized by an unpredictable formation of cumulonimbus clouds, resulting in a short but intense downpour of over 100 mm per hour of rain. The video showcases the fury of the Guerrilla rainstorm, with powerful winds swaying trees in its path. The dangerous nature of this event highlights the need for caution and preparedness during such occurrences in Yokohama.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>rainstorm,guerrilla,yokohama,japan,video,downpour,cumulonimbus,clouds,intense,winds,trees,dangerous,unpredictable,weather,phenomenon,local,short,mm,hour,rain</media:keywords>
                  <media:city> Yokohama</media:city>
                  <media:country>Japan</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>JP</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Weather</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Tue, 1 Aug 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2601</guid>
                  <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 13:12:08 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2601.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2601.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Tokyo's sideways rain: nature's dance of wind and water</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a mesmerizing spectacle captured on August 1, 2023, from the heart of Tokyo, Japan, @4H6M8u0YmemZwmj shared a breathtaking video of sideways rain cascading down window panes. As nature's elements collided, the wind's mighty force compelled the raindrops to dance sideways, creating a captivating display of nature's power and beauty. The video serves as a vivid reminder of the unpredictable yet awe-inspiring wonders of the natural world, leaving viewers in awe of the harmonious choreography between wind and water. </media:description>
                  <media:keywords>wind,rain,sideways,video,Tokyo,Japan,nature,spectacle,mesmerizing,window,panes,dance,elements,force,beauty,power,display,awe,urban,landscape</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Tokyo </media:city>
                  <media:country>Japan</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>JP</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Weather</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Tue, 1 Aug 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2600</guid>
                  <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 13:12:22 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2600.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2600.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Playful and obedient: Khryapa's impressive 'swim' command!</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a heartwarming video captured by @mokryi_nosik_ on June 17, 2020, in Voronezh, Russia, her beloved dog, Khryapa, stole the spotlight with her incredible obedience and playful nature. The footage shows @mokryi_nosik_ talking to Khryapa in one of the rooms, when suddenly, the clever canine dashes off towards the bathroom. Without hesitation, Khryapa leaps into the bathtub, showcasing her impressive execution of the "swim" command. The three-year-old furry friend proves to be not only obedient but also full of joy and enthusiasm. Her charming antics have won the hearts of viewers worldwide, leaving a lasting impression of her delightful personality and the strong bond between her and her owner.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>playful,obedient,dog,swim,command,video,Khryapa,Voronezh,Russia,bathtub,bathroom,three years old,pet,canine,joy,love,bond,clever,cute,charming</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Voronezh</media:city>
                  <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2598</guid>
                  <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 10:57:32 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2598.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2598.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Serene lake birthday circus: a decade of joyful dancing and balloon delight!</media:title>
                  <media:description>In the quaint town of Bakota, Ukraine, a mesmerizing birthday celebration unfolded on July 5, 2023. The talented dancer @annadellart, captured by @sykannushka's lens, graced the serene waterbody backdrop with her enchanting moves. Celebrating her 22nd birthday, she danced with legs elegantly up and spread straight, each leg adorned with a balloon forming the number 2 to signify her special age. The joyous spectacle unfolded in a circus setting, a fitting choice as the circus has been an integral part of her life for an entire decade. With graceful movements and a touch of whimsy, @annadellart's performance was a testament to a decade filled with joy, passion, and artistry.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>circus,birthday,celebration,dancing,waterbody,Bakota,Ukraine,@sykannushka,@annadellart,video,legs,balloons,22,joyful,enchanting,talented,serene,whimsy,passion,artistry</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Bakota </media:city>
                  <media:country>Ukraine</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>UA</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Cool</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Wed, 5 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2596</guid>
                  <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 07:58:40 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2596.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2596.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Playful corgi's adorable 'poof' act delights internet in St. Petersburg, Russia!</media:title>
                  <media:description>In an endearing and amusing video that captured hearts on social media, a Corgi named Leo from St. Petersburg, Russia, showcased his unique talent for playing "dead." The video, shared by @prokopenkokate on April 29, 2023, depicts Leo sitting peacefully on the floor before his owner mimics a shooting gesture with her hands. Surprisingly, the adorable pup immediately flops down, pretending to be "shot" as part of a playful command he has mastered. As a reward for his impressive performance, Leo eagerly awaits a treat, proving that his favorite command is the delightful and harmless "poof," leaving viewers charmed by this clever and lovable canine's antics.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>playful,corgi,leo,video,internet,acting,dog,Russia,St. Petersburg,pet,owner,gun,pretend,cute,charm,humor,social media,adorable,command,sweet</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>St. Petersburg</media:city>
                  <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sat, 29 Apr 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2595</guid>
                  <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 10:53:38 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2595.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2595.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>First-time rider's mishap: girl's scooter adventure ends with a bump!</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a candid video captured by @wkmzxuk_ on July 15, 2023, in the City of Soligorsk, Minsk region, Belarus, a young girl's first-time experience with an electronic scooter took an unexpected turn. With enthusiasm and excitement, she hopped onto the scooter but found herself struggling to control its speed. Unaware of the gears and unfamiliar with braking, she careened toward a stationary sign near a building, unable to halt her momentum. The result was a comical yet cautionary collision, reminding viewers of the importance of learning the basics before embarking on new adventures. While the girl's misadventure might have left her a little shaken, it undoubtedly served as a valuable lesson for both her and others who dare to ride the scooters for the first time.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>scooter,mishap,video,girl,first-time,adventure,excitement,gears,braking,collision,cautionary,comical,lessons,learning,electronic,speed,sign,building,Belarus,Soligorsk</media:keywords>
                  <media:city> City of Soligorsk, Minsk region</media:city>
                  <media:country>Belarus</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>BY</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Fails and Funnies</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2594</guid>
                  <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 10:53:05 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2594.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2594.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Tranquil moments: Tokyo's beloved dog relishes in shallow creek at favorite park</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a heartwarming scene captured on June 24, 2023, in Tokyo, Japan, @mr.donbei_inu shared a delightful video of his beloved dog finding sheer bliss in a small, slow creek at their favorite park. The four-legged companion appeared completely at ease, comfortably resting its head on the surface of the shallow water, joyfully savoring the gentle flow around it. Unlike most dogs, this furry friend chose not to swim but found pure contentment in merely basking in the refreshing water. With a serene expression, the canine seemed to have discovered a little piece of paradise amidst the bustling city, making this tranquil spot its most cherished destination in the park.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>dog,creek,park,Tokyo,Japan,chilling,water,shallow,serene,bliss,favorite,video,pet,companion,contentment,relaxation,joy,tranquility,peaceful,happiness</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Tokyo</media:city>
                  <media:country>Japan</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>JP</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2593</guid>
                  <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 10:52:42 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2593.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2593.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Love blossoms at a birthday party: tender smiles of a toddler</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a heartwarming moment captured by @ayreeeshh_ on March 12, 2023, at a birthday party in Las Piñas, Manila, Philippines, a two-year-old boy named Drei melted hearts as he looked tenderly at a little girl named Aliah. The usually quiet and well-behaved toddler seemed to be smitten with Aliah, flashing sweet smiles and even raising his eyebrows at her, giving the impression of a young love in the making. Drei's mother shared the adorable video, describing how her son became seemingly interested in Aliah, and it quickly became a viral sensation, spreading joy and warmth across the internet. This endearing encounter serves as a reminder of the innocent and pure connections that can blossom even among the youngest of hearts.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>love,toddler,birthday,party,smiles,tender,falling,in,young,children,innocence,adorable,viral,internet,connections,heartwarming,Manila,Philippines,Aliah,Drei,@ayreeeshh_</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Las Piñas, Manila</media:city>
                  <media:country>Philippines</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>PH</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Heartwarming</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2592</guid>
                  <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 10:51:48 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2592.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2592.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Stranded in the muddy ravine: military jeep's dramatic rescue in Bakhmut, Ukraine</media:title>
                  <media:description>In the rural outskirts of Bakhmut, Ukraine, an extraordinary scene unfolded on May 15, 2023, when a military jeep found itself trapped in the treacherous aftermath of a heavy rainstorm. Captured by @koshkarov_yarik, the vehicle was in the midst of pulling another stuck automobile when it succumbed to the thick mud, leaving its occupants in a precarious situation. As the hours passed and the sun began to set, tension mounted as the stranded group awaited assistance. To their surprise, it was an unexpected twist of fate that came to their aid. While waiting, a bizarre event occurred when their brother arrived to "shoot at the neighbor," causing an uproar of noisy birds. Remarkably, amid the chaos, a timely rescue operation led by fellow military personnel swooped in just in time, ensuring the safe extraction of both vehicles and their relieved occupants. The daring rescue, coupled with the unusual circumstances, left an unforgettable mark on the small community, showcasing the unwavering camaraderie and ingenuity of those serving in Ukraine's military.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>ravine,rain,stuck,jeep,evening,brother,shoot,neighbor,birds,lancet,rescue,mud,Bakhmut,Ukraine,military,daring,trapped,assistance,occupants,community</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Bakhmut</media:city>
                  <media:country>Ukraine</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>UA</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>News</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Mon, 15 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2591</guid>
                  <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 13:06:37 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2591.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2591.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                     </channel>
                  </rss>
                