<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
        <rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
        xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
        xmlns:openSearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearchrss/1.0/"
        xmlns:dfpvideo="http://api.google.com/dfpvideo"
        xmlns:tms="http://data.tmsapi.com/v1.1"
        version="2.0">
          <channel>
            <title>ViralBear videos</title>
            <dfpvideo:version>2</dfpvideo:version>
              
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Playful pups on a wild slide: adventures of Stavropol's Cane Corso and American Bully duo</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a charming woodland escapade captured by @naa2699 on November 7, 2021, in Stavropol, Russia, two lively dogs reveled in the simple joy of sliding down fallen tree foliage. The heartwarming video showcases the playful antics of a Cane Corso puppy named Pepsi, distinguished by a vibrant green collar. Chasing and frolicking, the young pup embarked on an impromptu slide down a steep incline, much to the amusement of its American Bully companions. The author, who proudly tends to a home kennel of Cane Corso and American Bully breeds, affectionately shared this delightful moment with the world, capturing the essence of carefree companionship and the boundless exuberance of four-legged friends.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>playful,dogs,video,woodland,slide,adventure,Cane Corso,American Bully,puppy,Stavropol,Russia,foliage,chase,collar,kennel,laughter,companionship,joy,escapade,antics</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Stavropol</media:city>
                  <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sun, 7 Nov 2021</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2667</guid>
                  <pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 11:21:25 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2667.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2667.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Joseph the berry-eating 'vacuum cleaner' dog</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a delightful scene captured by @iosif20.05.2020 on June 16, 2023, in St. Petersburg, Russia, a video showcases a furry culinary enthusiast named Joseph. The adorable dog found himself amidst an accidental spill of blueberries, creating a vibrant mess on the floor. Seizing the opportunity, Joseph channeled his inner vacuum cleaner, meticulously devouring the succulent blueberries one by one. </media:description>
                  <media:keywords>dog,berries,spill,St. Petersburg,Russia,video,Joseph,vacuum,homage,Brodsky,adorable,culinary,enthusiast,vibrant,mess,opportunity,munching,playful,exploration,literary</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>St. Petersburg</media:city>
                  <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2666</guid>
                  <pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 11:35:16 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2666.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2666.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Grass-adventurous feline: a playful afternoon romp leaves a messy surprise!</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a charming scene captured by @fahjrinagladysya on June 14, 2023, in Banyuwangi, Indonesia, a mischievous feline's afternoon escapade took an unexpected turn. The video showcases the cat, covered in patches of grass dirt, returning home after what seems to be a playful exploration through the lush grass bushes. The curious cat's fur is adorned with bits of grass, an evident testament to its outdoor adventures. Clearly, the allure of the natural world proved irresistible to this four-legged explorer. However, the aftermath required the owner's intervention, as the author lovingly tended to her pet's cleanliness, delicately removing the clinging grass. This endearing episode serves as a reminder of the simple yet profound joys that our feline companions find in the great outdoors.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>playful,cat,grass,dirt,adventure,exploration,outdoor,feline,curious,owner,intervention,cleanliness,video,bushes,fur,home,Banyuwangi,Indonesia,June 14,2023</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Banyuwangi </media:city>
                  <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>ID</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2665</guid>
                  <pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 11:36:57 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2665.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2665.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Kangaroo-inspired leap: Bull Arab and Catahoula mix masters the fence jump</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a remarkable display of agility and boundless energy, a video captured by @zoecarter_aus on July 11, 2023, in Victoria, Australia, showcases an extraordinary feat by his unique canine companion. The mixed breed dog, a fusion of Bull Arab and Catahoula, astounds viewers as it effortlessly leaps off a farm fence with a striking resemblance to a kangaroo in motion. With powerful hind legs propelling it skyward, the dog's graceful airborne maneuver and uncanny emulation of a kangaroo's iconic bounce leave a lasting impression. This captivating demonstration of athleticism not only highlights the remarkable abilities of our four-legged friends but also serves as a testament to the boundless wonders of the animal kingdom.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>kangaroo,leap,agility,canine,farm,fence,Victoria,Australia,Bull Arab,Catahoula,video,energy,motion,hind legs,bounce,athleticism,demonstration,animals,wonder,unique,captivating</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Victoria</media:city>
                  <media:country>Australia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>AU</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2664</guid>
                  <pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 11:39:46 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2664.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2664.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Frozen in feline hilarity: Maryland's playful mother and kitten duo stun the shelter!</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a heartwarming scene captured by veterinary technician @meo.cats on May 12, 2023, at the Cat's Life Rescue Shelter in Maryland, USA, two feline companions – a devoted mother cat and her adorable kitten – stole the show with their frozen yet utterly hilarious expressions. The video, which quickly went viral, showcased the pair seemingly caught in a moment of playful bewilderment. As the mother cat and her tiny offspring momentarily froze in their tracks, their comical and endearing facial expressions left viewers in stitches. </media:description>
                  <media:keywords>playful,adorable,heartwarming,viral,companions,expressions,shelter,feline,bewilderment,comical,endearing,glimpse,residents,joy,laughter,kittens,freeze,captivating,bonding,connection</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Maryland</media:city>
                  <media:country>United States</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>US</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Fri, 12 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2663</guid>
                  <pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 08:31:29 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2663.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2663.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Corn connoisseur cat: a hilarious tale of Coconut's seasonal delight</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a heartwarming and humorous scene captured by @plukchi__ on July 30, 2023, in Odesa, Ukraine, a feline friend named Coconut has become an internet sensation for his unique love of corn. The video depicts Coconut indulging in his favorite seasonal treat – corn on the cob – alongside the author's friend, @maks_elash. Previously known as Cosmos, the cat earned the endearing moniker Coconut due to his passion for the vegetable. Despite initial restrictions, Coconut's determination led him to master the art of opening a garbage drawer to savor corn cobs. The footage not only showcases Coconut's adorable corn-eating technique but also highlights the strong bond between the cat and his human. </media:description>
                  <media:keywords>corn,cat,coconut,friendship,humor,video,Odesa,Ukraine,TikTok,viral,pet,feline,delight,seasonal,treat,bond,quirky,munching,adorable,internet</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Odesa </media:city>
                  <media:country>Ukraine</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>UA</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2660</guid>
                  <pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 07:24:01 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2660.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2660.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Shared healing: a tale of compassion between man and dog in Maharashtra</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a touching moment captured by @ash_op_gamer on July 16, 2023, in Maharashtra, India, a heartwarming bond between a dog and its owner unfolded. The video shows the playful canine frolicking around the compound, its exuberance evident in every leap and dash. However, an unforeseen misstep resulted in a slight injury, causing the dog to limp over to its concerned owner. Undeterred by the setback, the owner's tender touch and soothing massage transformed the scene into a testament of unwavering companionship. With renewed vigor, the duo soon resumed their joyful play, showcasing the remarkable resilience of the bond between human and canine.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>dog,owner,play,Maharashtra,India,video,compound,hurt,foot,limping,massage,bond,companionship,resilience,joyful,exuberance,tender,touching,moment,duo</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Maharashtra</media:city>
                  <media:country>India</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>IN</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2659</guid>
                  <pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023 12:44:08 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2659.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2659.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Adorable attic antics: playful kittens' hilarious escapade in Bym Village!</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a heartwarming scene captured by @palinkagut on August 4, 2023, in Bym Village of the Kungursky district in Russia's Perm region, a delightful display of feline frolic unfolded. The video reveals a pair of playful kittens engaging in an endearing game within the confines of an attic. Amidst their lively play, one daring kitten leaped out of the attic space. However, its mischievous sibling promptly intervenes, swiftly and comically pulling the adventurous jumper right back to the attic's haven. The heartwarming interaction showcases the inseparable bond between the two siblings and offers a charming glimpse into the world of these furry companions.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>kittens,play,attic,siblings,village,Russia,video,capture,adorable,antics,hide-and-seek,leap,interaction,laughter,awe,companions,heartwarming,Bym,Kungursky,Perm</media:keywords>
                  <media:city> Bym village, Kungursky district, Perm region</media:city>
                  <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Fri, 4 Aug 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2655</guid>
                  <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 10:36:13 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2655.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2655.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Muddy adventures: Shiba the samurai girl finds refreshing escape near Narach Lake</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a charming scene captured by @siba_hani_ on June 18, 2023, near Narach Lake in Minsk Province, Belarus, a spirited dog named Shiba embraces the role of a playful samurai as it frolics in the cooling embrace of mud amidst the woodland. The video showcases Shiba's lighthearted antics as she indulges in the muddy terrain, dipping her snout and sauntering with abandon. With the sun's heat in the air, Shiba's instinctual cooling strategy draws a smile from onlookers as she revels in the joy of the moment, leaving a comical imprint of her adventurous escapade on both herself and her owner.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>playful,woodland,escapade,samurai,dog,mud,cooling,frolics,adventure,joy,antics,sun,Minsk,Belarus,Narach Lake,Shiba,snout,embrace,video,owner</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Minsk Province </media:city>
                  <media:country>Belarus</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>BY</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2654</guid>
                  <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 10:36:43 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2654.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2654.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Heartwarming canine companion: dog comforts "crying" owner in Can Tho City, Vietnam</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a touching display of empathy and companionship, a heartwarming video captured by @nhaco6conheooo on June 24, 2023, in Can Tho City, Vietnam, showcased the unwavering support of a loyal dog towards its owner. The footage featured a lady pretending to cry while sitting on the floor with her hand on her face, and her canine companion immediately rushed to her side. With gentle paws and a warm presence, the dog attempted to console the distressed owner, sliding under her arms and getting close to her face. Undeterred by the presence of another dog nearby, this compassionate furry friend proved that unconditional love knows no bounds. The poignant moment reached its climax when the lady ceased her pretense, rewarding the dog's comforting efforts with a tender scratch on its head, demonstrating the strong bond between human and canine. This heartening scene serves as a reminder of the extraordinary capacity for compassion that our furry companions bring into our lives.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>comfort,empathy,companionship,dog,crying,Can Tho,Vietnam,video,pawing,support,love,furry,bond,human,canine,pretend,touching,pets,affectionate,heartwarming</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Can Tho City</media:city>
                  <media:country>Vietnam</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>VN</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2651</guid>
                  <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 10:38:20 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2651.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2651.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Adorable Coco the Shih Tzu spins into sleepy delight chasing its tail!</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a heartwarming scene from San Mateo, Rizal, Philippines, captured by @coconabi_shihtzu on June 23, 2023, a delightful puppy named Coco found itself in a playful predicament on a cozy mat. As bedtime approached, the energetic little Shih Tzu couldn't resist the allure of its own tail. With excitement and determination, Coco spun around and around, trying to catch hold of the elusive target. The endearing video showcases the pure joy and innocence of a puppy at play, bringing smiles to the faces of viewers worldwide. It's moments like these that remind us of the simple pleasures in life and the unbreakable bond we share with our furry companions.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>puppy,coco,playing,tail,mat,floor,cute,adorable,San Mateo,Rizal,Philippines,video,joy,excitement,bedtime,shih tzu,spinning,delight,pet,fun,love</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>San Mateo, Rizal</media:city>
                  <media:country>Philippines</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>PH</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2650</guid>
                  <pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 11:20:09 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2650.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2650.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Sweet serenity: a head massage exchange between human and feline in General Santos City</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a heartwarming and endearing scene in General Santos City, South Cotabato, Philippines, a beautiful connection between a woman and her feline companion was captured on video by @jiannmay on July 29, 2023. The footage shows the remarkable bond between the two as the woman communicates with her cat, guiding it to massage her head gently using its delicate paws. The intimate exchange of affection and trust is a testament to the deep connection that can exist between humans and their beloved pets, showcasing the profound understanding and love that can transcend species boundaries. This heart-melting moment serves as a delightful reminder of the joy and comfort animals can bring into our lives.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>cat,massage,head,video,jiannmay,General Santos City,South Cotabato,Philippines,connection,bond,affection,trust,pets,love,animals,joy,comfort,feline,human,paws,endearing</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>General Santos City, South Cotabato</media:city>
                  <media:country>Philippines</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>PH</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2648</guid>
                  <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 15:33:08 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2648.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2648.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Adorable Shih Tzu puppy Miyo masters sit and stand commands with delight in Manila, Philippines!</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a heartwarming scene captured by @miyopuppy on November 12, 2022, in Manila, Philippines, her precious Shih Tzu puppy, Miyo, showcased her impeccable training skills by executing sit and stand commands with sheer joy. The video captured the endearing moments of Miyo gracefully obeying her owner's cues. Whenever instructed to sit, the puppy would happily curl up on her stomach, while on the command to stand, she would eagerly rise onto all fours. With an unmistakable look of happiness in her eyes, Miyo's enthusiasm for learning was evident, making the entire experience a delightful display of the loving bond between a pet and its owner.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>adorable,puppy,shih tzu,commands,video,miyo,sit,stand,Manila,Philippines,happy,training,obedience,joy,owner,love,cute,pet,bond,delightful</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Manila </media:city>
                  <media:country>Philippines</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>PH</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sat, 12 Nov 2022</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2647</guid>
                  <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 15:34:50 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2647.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2647.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Touching reunion: emotional dog embraces owner after time apart</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a heartwarming display of affection, a golden retriever named Timber captured the internet's attention with a touching video that showcased her emotional reunion with her owner. The video, shot by @timber.the.golden on July 27, 2023, in Chicago, Illinois, USA, depicted Timber eagerly embracing her owner as they were reunited after a few hours apart. The dog lovingly removed the cape from her owner and showered them with cries of joy, clearly showing how deeply she missed her human companion during their brief separation. According to the owner, Timber always gets emotional whenever they are separated and greets them with overwhelming happiness upon their return. The heartwarming footage quickly went viral, resonating with countless viewers who were moved by the undeniable bond between man and his best friend. </media:description>
                  <media:keywords>emotional,dog,reunion,video,Timber,owner,Chicago,Illinois,USA,embrace,cries,groomer,welcome,affection,bond,love,viral,bestfriend,heartwarming,connection,pets</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Chicago, Illinois</media:city>
                  <media:country>United States</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>US</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2643</guid>
                  <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 15:32:29 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2643.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2643.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Playful corgi Jam from Belarus delights in dandelions</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a heartwarming video captured by @no_fans_only_plants on May 18, 2023, in St. Petersburg, Russia, a delightful corgi named Jam stole the spotlight as he frolicked in a field of dandelions. The playful pup, originally hailing from Belarus, exhibited his exuberance and love for life, embodying the typical corgi spirit. However, what sets Jam apart is his endearing habit of munching on dandelions, which his owner allows without any reservations. Emphasizing the importance of letting pets be themselves, the author expressed a deep understanding and appreciation for Jam's individuality. This heartening tale of a free-spirited corgi cherishing life's simple pleasures reminds us to embrace our loved ones for who they truly are.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>playful,corgi,jam,video,Belarus,dandelions,field,StPetersburg,Russia,pets,love,individuality,free-spirited,happiness,nature,adorable,canine,companionship,joy,outdoor,embrace</media:keywords>
                  <media:city> St. Petersburg</media:city>
                  <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Thu, 18 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2631</guid>
                  <pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 14:06:33 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2631.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2631.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Oscar the cat's unconventional healing: a funny tale of biting plaster and broken leg</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a heartwarming yet peculiar display of feline caregiving, a cat named Oscar, belonging to @oskar_kitty_ from Kharkiv, Ukraine, was captured on video tenderly attacking his owner's broken foot and biting on the plaster. In the footage shared on July 17, 2023, Oscar's owner jokingly revealed that the cat's unusual behavior served as a form of treatment. Evidently, Oscar had developed a fondness for nibbling on his owner's leg, and the plaster provided a surprisingly effective and protective solution. The four-year-old feline's unexpected aid showcased the deep bond between pets and their owners, demonstrating how even in their playful antics, cats can express concern and offer comfort during times of need.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>cat,oscar,kitty,ukraine,kharkiv,video,attack,broken,foot,plaster,treatment,bites,healing,love,pets,owner,bonding,playful,caregiving,feline</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Kharkiv</media:city>
                  <media:country>Ukraine</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>UA</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2630</guid>
                  <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 08:09:39 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2630.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2630.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Enigmatic equine enigma: a horse's puzzled encounter with a horse coat</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a heartwarming yet amusing scene at @abbottsviewlivery in Aston Abbotts, UK, a delightful video captured by the account owner on June 11, 2023, showcased their horse donning a horse coat. The comical attire covered the horse entirely, except for two eye holes, leaving the majestic creature looking perplexed and inquiring about the peculiar get-up. As the laughter of the onlookers filled the air, the horse appeared to be seeking answers from its amused companions, making for an endearing moment that truly highlighted the unique bond between humans and their equine companions.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>horse,coat,confused,video,Aston Abbotts,UK,laughter,equine,companions,amusement,head-to-hoof,enigma,bond,unique,moment,animals,livery,eye holes,inquiring,delightful,June 11</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Aston Abbotts</media:city>
                  <media:country>United Kingdom</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>GB</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2626</guid>
                  <pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 14:00:21 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2626.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2626.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Meet the canine chauffeurs: Jack Russells take the wheel in Minsk's unconventional photo shoot!</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a captivating and unconventional photo shoot in Minsk, Belarus, Dmitry Zhilinsky, a talented trainer and owner of three Jack Russells, showcased his furry companions' incredible skills behind the wheel. Captured by @luckyshowby on August 1, 2021, the video featured Rick, Lucky, and Eva comfortably seated in the car, with one of them seemingly attempting to take the driver's role. Not only does Dmitry arrange corporate performances with his furry companions, but he also organizes delightful photo shoots that showcase the dogs' extraordinary abilities. This heartwarming display of intelligence and companionship between man and his loyal Jack Russells is sure to put a smile on anyone's face and highlight the incredible bond between humans and their four-legged friends.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>jack russells,dogs,car,driving,photo shoot,Minsk,Belarus,Dmitry Zhilinsky,canine,chauffeurs,talent,companions,intelligence,performance,video,pets,animals,wheel,corporate,@luckyshowby,August 1</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Minsk</media:city>
                  <media:country>Belarus</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>BY</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sun, 1 Aug 2021</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2619</guid>
                  <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 07:48:24 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2619.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2619.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Persistent feline pursuit: hilarious toilet time with a tenacious cat</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a comical and relatable scene, @badnotwolf from Vinnytsia, Ukraine, shared a video of his persistent cat, Roxy attempting to join him in the bathroom. On July 11, 2023, while seated in front of the camera, the cat made numerous unsuccessful leaps towards its owner, who was simply seeking a moment of relaxation on the toilet. With only the legs visible in the video, viewers were left amused by the feline's determined efforts to be part of the action.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>cat,toilet,video,legs,Ukraine,Vinnytsia,July,2023,hilarious,comical,pet,owner,persistent,attempts,relaxation,funny,feline,jump,bathroom,amusing,scene</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Vinnytsia</media:city>
                  <media:country>Ukraine</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>UA</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2618</guid>
                  <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 13:20:43 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2618.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2618.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Adorable foster kittens indulge in a 'paws'-itively messy drink!</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a heartwarming scene captured by @emiliexfosters on July 18, 2023, in Milwaukee, USA, three adorable foster kittens were caught on video enjoying a drink from a bowl. However, one mischievous kitten had its legs dipped into the liquid as it drank, resulting in a cute yet messy moment. With quick reflexes, the author lifted the little one out of the bowl, revealing its front paws soaked in the brown liquid used for weaning them. Despite the adorable mishap, the sight of these tiny furballs brought smiles to viewers' faces, showcasing the joys of caring for foster animals.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>adorable,foster,kittens,video,drink,bowl,legs,soaked,weaning,messy,cute,moment,reflexes,furballs,caring,animals,pets,@emiliexfosters,Milwaukee,USA</media:keywords>
                  <media:city> Milwaukee </media:city>
                  <media:country>United States</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>US</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2615</guid>
                  <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 13:22:47 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2615.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2615.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Boomer's midnight mischief: possum party at home!</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a humorous and slightly mischievous incident captured by @ndnchic33 on June 17, 2023, in Chelsea, Alabama, USA, her adorable dog, Boomer, became the center of attention. The video shows Boomer lounging on the couch late at night, accompanied by an unexpected guest - possums! Apparently, Boomer had invited his possum friend over to join him indoors, much to his owner's surprise. In the video, we hear the author playfully scolding Boomer, reminding him that bringing friends into the house is not allowed. The adorable footage showcases Boomer's nocturnal adventures and his owner's delightful reaction to the unusual situation. It's a heartwarming reminder of the unexpected antics our furry friends can get up to when the world sleeps.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>night,dog,Boomer,possums,couch,house,video,Chelsea,Alabama,USA,friends,mischief,adorable,owner,surprise,nocturnal,antics,furry,funny,pets</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Chelsea, Alabama</media:city>
                  <media:country>United States</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>US</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2613</guid>
                  <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 08:13:17 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2613.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2613.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Playful pranks and paw popping: a kitten's hilarious reflexes!</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a heartwarming and humorous video captured by @pinkintotheblue on May 28, 2023, in Cikande, Banten, Indonesia, a playful kitten steals the show with its adorable reflexes. The feline's owner, @pinkintotheblue's boyfriend, gently held the little furball in his hands while playfully making popping sounds with his mouth. The kitten's reaction was priceless - as soon as it heard the sounds, it instinctively lifted all its tiny legs in surprise, only to settle back down again in his hands. With a house full of cats, the couple thoroughly enjoys creating these delightful moments on camera. This heartwarming video captures the joy and bond shared between humans and their feline companions, reminding us of the simple pleasures that brighten our lives.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>playful,kitten,reflexes,video,popping,adorable,hands,joy,cats,love,fun,pets,cute,surprise,bonding,moments,laughter,Indonesia,Banten,Cikande</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Cikande, Banten </media:city>
                  <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>ID</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sun, 28 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2610</guid>
                  <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 08:16:32 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2610.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2610.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Midnight motorbike melody: barking serenade by excited street dogs</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a captivating video captured by @abdullaev.222 on July 9, 2023, in Saratov Rakhova, Russia, a group of street dogs showcased their curious behavior towards a motorbike. As the rider turned on the engine, the dogs immediately came rushing towards him, barking excitedly. However, whenever the engine was switched off, they would retreat, only to return with renewed enthusiasm once it roared to life again. The intriguing scene unfolded during the night when the rider stopped to answer a phone call, catching the dogs' attention and prompting him to start recording the delightful encounter. It's a heartwarming reminder of the special bond between humans and their four-legged companions, even in unexpected and amusing circumstances.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>motorbike,dogs,street,night,Russia,Saratov,barking,excitement,video,capture,curious,engine,retreat,enthusiasm,phone,call,recording,bond,humans,companions</media:keywords>
                  <media:city> Saratov Rakhova</media:city>
                  <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sun, 9 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2609</guid>
                  <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 08:12:32 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2609.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2609.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Adorable cashier's assistant: the beloved parking lot cat of Odessa, Ukraine</media:title>
                  <media:description>In the bustling city of Odessa, Ukraine, a heartwarming scene unfolded at a local parking lot on July 29, 2023. @40medok, an observant passerby, captured a heart-melting moment as a charming cat sat gracefully at the cashier's window, patiently awaiting attention. With affectionate pets and gentle caresses, the feline earned its rightful place as the "Cashier's Assistant." Customers and visitors passing by couldn't resist showering the cat with respect and tenderness, creating a sense of community around this adorable furball. This endearing sight has become a cherished part of the parking lot's atmosphere, leaving everyone with a smile as they complete their errands, knowing that a little feline guardian watches over them.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>adorable,cat,cashier,window,parking lot,Odessa,Ukraine,pet,picture,baby,cute,good,respect,tenderness,community,furball,atmosphere,guardian,smile,errands</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Odessa</media:city>
                  <media:country>Ukraine</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>UA</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2605</guid>
                  <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 07:59:28 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2605.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2605.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Bear brawl at Guaipo Tiger Park: two black bears engage in fierce fight over food</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a thrilling and unexpected encounter at the Guaipo Tiger Park in Shenyang, Northeast China, two black bears engaged in a heated fight, captured on video by local resident @100millionfatballs on June 24, 2023. As she explored the living area of the black bears, the normally docile animals suddenly clashed, with their aggression escalating over a possible dispute for food. The shocking scene prompted the author to react quickly, loudly shouting in an attempt to intervene and put an end to the confrontation. Her bravery in the face of this intense encounter showcased the unpredictable nature of wildlife and served as a powerful reminder of the importance of respecting and preserving the delicate balance between humans and the animal kingdom.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>shenyang,china,black bears,fight,video,wildlife,park,encounter,food,aggression,shock,visitor,Guaipo Tiger Park,northeast,@100millionfatballs,nature,animals,conservation,bravery,balance</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Shenyang</media:city>
                  <media:country>China</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>CN</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2602</guid>
                  <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 13:12:52 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2602.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2602.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Playful and obedient: Khryapa's impressive 'swim' command!</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a heartwarming video captured by @mokryi_nosik_ on June 17, 2020, in Voronezh, Russia, her beloved dog, Khryapa, stole the spotlight with her incredible obedience and playful nature. The footage shows @mokryi_nosik_ talking to Khryapa in one of the rooms, when suddenly, the clever canine dashes off towards the bathroom. Without hesitation, Khryapa leaps into the bathtub, showcasing her impressive execution of the "swim" command. The three-year-old furry friend proves to be not only obedient but also full of joy and enthusiasm. Her charming antics have won the hearts of viewers worldwide, leaving a lasting impression of her delightful personality and the strong bond between her and her owner.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>playful,obedient,dog,swim,command,video,Khryapa,Voronezh,Russia,bathtub,bathroom,three years old,pet,canine,joy,love,bond,clever,cute,charming</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Voronezh</media:city>
                  <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2598</guid>
                  <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 10:57:32 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2598.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2598.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Playful corgi's adorable 'poof' act delights internet in St. Petersburg, Russia!</media:title>
                  <media:description>In an endearing and amusing video that captured hearts on social media, a Corgi named Leo from St. Petersburg, Russia, showcased his unique talent for playing "dead." The video, shared by @prokopenkokate on April 29, 2023, depicts Leo sitting peacefully on the floor before his owner mimics a shooting gesture with her hands. Surprisingly, the adorable pup immediately flops down, pretending to be "shot" as part of a playful command he has mastered. As a reward for his impressive performance, Leo eagerly awaits a treat, proving that his favorite command is the delightful and harmless "poof," leaving viewers charmed by this clever and lovable canine's antics.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>playful,corgi,leo,video,internet,acting,dog,Russia,St. Petersburg,pet,owner,gun,pretend,cute,charm,humor,social media,adorable,command,sweet</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>St. Petersburg</media:city>
                  <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sat, 29 Apr 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2595</guid>
                  <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 10:53:38 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2595.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2595.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Tranquil moments: Tokyo's beloved dog relishes in shallow creek at favorite park</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a heartwarming scene captured on June 24, 2023, in Tokyo, Japan, @mr.donbei_inu shared a delightful video of his beloved dog finding sheer bliss in a small, slow creek at their favorite park. The four-legged companion appeared completely at ease, comfortably resting its head on the surface of the shallow water, joyfully savoring the gentle flow around it. Unlike most dogs, this furry friend chose not to swim but found pure contentment in merely basking in the refreshing water. With a serene expression, the canine seemed to have discovered a little piece of paradise amidst the bustling city, making this tranquil spot its most cherished destination in the park.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>dog,creek,park,Tokyo,Japan,chilling,water,shallow,serene,bliss,favorite,video,pet,companion,contentment,relaxation,joy,tranquility,peaceful,happiness</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Tokyo</media:city>
                  <media:country>Japan</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>JP</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2593</guid>
                  <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 10:52:42 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2593.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2593.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Tenacious twig tug-of-war: a dog's unyielding affair with nature's bounty</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a delightful and amusing scene captured by @chelseareject on May 21, 2023, in Jersey City, New Jersey, USA, her four-legged companion exhibited an unshakeable determination during a playful encounter with nature. The video showcased the adorable pup clenching onto a sizable twig of a tree, despite the owner's best efforts to convince it otherwise. With @chelseareject's voice gently coaxing the dog to release its prized find, the resilient canine remained unyielding, steadfastly refusing to let go. Undeterred, they strolled along together, the furry protagonist proudly showcasing its prized possession in an endearing tug-of-war with the forces of nature. The heartwarming display of canine spirit and persistence resonated with viewers worldwide, capturing the essence of a special bond between humans and their loyal companions.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>tree,dog,twig,nature,Jersey City,USA,May,2023,video,pet,playful,determined,adorable,owner,walk,bonding,persistence,loyalty,companionship,endearing,capture</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Jersey City, New Jersey</media:city>
                  <media:country>United States</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>US</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sun, 21 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2586</guid>
                  <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 09:23:40 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2586.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2586.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Cat burglar in Buenos Aires: feline filches cash and cuddles up!</media:title>
                  <media:description>In an amusing incident in Buenos Aires, Argentina, on July 6, 2023, a mischievous cat turned into a daring thief. A video captured by @gaston__joaquin showed the feline delving into a handbag and snatching a bundle of money before darting off towards the bedroom. The curious owner followed the sneaky cat's trail to find it lounging on the bed with the stolen cash. This lighthearted escapade left everyone amused and highlighted the unpredictable antics of our four-legged companions.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>cat,thief,money,video,Buenos Aires,Argentina,handbag,bed,owner,amusing,feline,daring,curious,sneaky,trail,lounging,stolen,cash,lighthearted,antics</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Buenos Aires</media:city>
                  <media:country>Argentina</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>AR</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Thu, 6 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2585</guid>
                  <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 09:24:40 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2585.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2585.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Loving Thai cat Luna: a tale of motherhood and her warrior kitten, Himars</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a heartwarming incident captured by @uvarova0304 on December 4, 2022 in Kyiv, Ukraine, a young mother cat named Luna, of the Thai breed, displayed her loving and protective nature towards her kittens. In particular, Luna's adventurous kitten, Himars, was spotted hanging on a rope, prompting his mother's immediate intervention. With great care and determination, Luna managed to rescue Himars and carried him to safety. The three kittens, Javelina, Khimars, and Bayroktarovna, grew up under Luna's watchful eye, venturing out of their box as they became more curious about the world. Despite their curiosity, Luna remained a vigilant and caring mother, keeping a close eye on her offspring to ensure their safety. Himars, playfully referred to as "child of war" by the author, seemed to embody a spirited nature, often prompting his mother's protective instincts. Now living with their owners, the kittens are showered with love and affection, with regular photo and video updates shared with their original caretakers. It's heartening to see such a strong bond between Luna and her kittens, and the incident with the rope underscores the loving protection she provides, even when the situation might not have posed a significant threat, given Himars' proximity to the floor.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>kittens,motherhood,love,rescue,cat,Luna,Himars,Javelina,Khimars,Bayroktarovna,curiosity,protective,care,owners,Ukraine,Kyiv,video,photos,affection,adorable</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Kyiv</media:city>
                  <media:country>Ukraine</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>UA</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sun, 4 Dec 2022</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2580</guid>
                  <pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 08:53:45 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2580.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2580.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Resourceful feline masters the art of door-opening: a fascinating tale from Jepara, Indonesia!</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a captivating video captured by @muktafil on April 24, 2023, in Jepara, Indonesia, an astonishing feat unfolded as their clever cat showcased its ingenuity. The footage showcases the feline effortlessly opening the door to the house, by jumping on the door handle leaving its owner in awe of its newfound talent. Expressing his astonishment, the author stated, "I was surprised that the cat opened the door by itself, now if you put it outside, it will open the door. Don't know where it learned from." The video has since captured the hearts of viewers worldwide, as they marvel at the resourceful cat's ability to conquer the seemingly insurmountable obstacle. This extraordinary tale serves as a reminder of the intelligence and adaptability possessed by our feline companions.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>clever,cat,door,opening,video,Jepara,Indonesia,surprise,talent,resourceful,ingenuity,amazement,owner,outside,learn,astonishment,heartwarming,intelligence,adaptability,feline</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Jepara</media:city>
                  <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>ID</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2578</guid>
                  <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 07:29:30 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2578.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2578.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Bathroom bliss: Indonesian cat's unique way to beat the heat</media:title>
                  <media:description>In Yogyakarta, Indonesia, a heartwarming video captured by @bagus_muhammad_ on March 28, 2023, showcases the adorable antics of his feline companion during a hot day. The short clip features his cat lying flat on its stomach in the cool confines of the bathroom, delightfully spreading its hind legs for ultimate relaxation. As temperatures rise, it seems this clever kitty has found its perfect oasis for beating the heat. With a contented expression on its face, it's evident that the bathroom has become the preferred spot for the cat to seek respite from the sweltering weather. </media:description>
                  <media:keywords>cat,bathroom,Indonesia,Yogyakarta,video,pet,feline,hot,heat,adorable,antics,relaxation,hind legs,oasis,cool,weather,comfort,pets,content,warmer days</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Yogyakarta</media:city>
                  <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>ID</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2577</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 08:17:01 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2577.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2577.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Adventurous Manda: a curious cat's high-rise escapades in Yogyakarta!</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a captivating moment caught on video by @a.youu_ on July 4, 2023, in Yogyakarta, Indonesia, a curious cat named Manda was spotted perched atop an unfinished building. The enigmatic feline appeared unsure of its surroundings, leaving viewers both amused and intrigued by its daring escapade. With a playful spirit, the author decided to record the charming scene, showcasing Manda's adventurous nature and uncertain demeanor as it surveyed the world from its lofty vantage point.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>cat,video,Yogyakarta,Indonesia,Manda,building,perched,curious,confused,fun,playful,adventurous,daring,charming,uncertain,climb,pet,antics,moment,heartwarming</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Yogyakarta</media:city>
                  <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>ID</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Tue, 4 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2573</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 08:15:12 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2573.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2573.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Adventurous boat dog: a joyful journey on the waters of Posadas, Argentina</media:title>
                  <media:description>In Posadas, Argentina, a heartwarming sight was captured by @fefu1408 on December 1, 2021. A video showcased a spirited dog perched confidently on the front of a speeding boat, appearing to relish every moment of the thrilling experience. As the author went rowing with a friend, they encountered this common occurrence of dogs joining the boating adventures. In this particular instance, the dog belonged to another boat that passed them by, showcasing the adventurous spirit and love for the water that these furry companions hold. </media:description>
                  <media:keywords>rowing,boat,dog,adventure,Posadas,Argentina,speed,waters,joyful,companions,video,water,front,perched,passing,friend,common,furry,capture,spirit</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Posadas</media:city>
                  <media:country>Argentina</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>AR</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Wed, 1 Dec 2021</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2572</guid>
                  <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 07:28:52 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2572.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2572.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Enchanting fur patterns: unique cat in Blitar delights in friendly affection</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a heartwarming scene captured on video by @polseksrengat on June 30, 2023, in Blitar, Indonesia, a cat with naturally polished fur became the center of attention among a group of friends. The cat sported a striking combination of white fur on its face and a mix of white and black fur on the rest of its body, making it truly unique. As the friends scratched the cat gently, it basked in their affectionate company, closing its eyes in contentment each time one of them touched its head. The endearing sight of this feline enjoying the camaraderie warmed the hearts of those who witnessed the adorable encounter, reminding us of the profound bond between humans and their feline companions.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>polished,fur,cat,white,black,unique,friends,affection,company,contentment,adorable,feline,bond,Indonesia,Blitar,video,captured,June30,2023,@polseksrengat</media:keywords>
                  <media:city> Blitar</media:city>
                  <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>ID</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2571</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 08:08:02 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2571.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2571.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Quirky Yeti: cat asserts ownership over owner's resting foot in hilarious video!</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a heartwarming yet amusing video captured by @dymova_brows on December 14, 2022, in Zaporozhye, Ukraine, a 7-year-old cat named Yeti showcases its unique character. The footage shows Yeti attempting to keep its owner's foot still under the blanket while playfully growling like a dog when met with resistance. The quirky feline's predilections include strolls on the balcony and relishing wet food, but it fiercely guards its delicious meals from fellow feline companions. The short video captures Yeti's endearing and assertive personality, providing a delightful glimpse into the fascinating world of this furry friend.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>cat,yeti,video,quirky,owner,foot,bed,blanket,growl,dog,character,Zaporozhye,Ukraine,balcony,wet food,delicious,unique,feline,playful,adorable</media:keywords>
                  <media:city> Zaporozhye</media:city>
                  <media:country>Ukraine</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>UA</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2569</guid>
                  <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 07:20:35 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2569.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2569.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Cat chaos: Minsk feline's hilarious morning escape from the mysterious carrier bag!</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a humorous yet chaotic scene captured by @vorobyov2021 on May 5, 2023, in Minsk, Belarus, a scared feline caused havoc as she ran around the house with a carrier bag caught on her back. The video showcases the frantic cat darting from room to room, desperately trying to escape the seemingly terrifying bag. According to the author, the unexpected morning commotion served as an amusing wake-up call, as the mischievous cat poked and prodded her way through the apartment in a comical attempt to be free from her unexpected accessory.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>cat,video,Minsk,Belarus,scared,carrier bag,back,running,banging,things,escape,hilarious,chaos,feline,apartment,wake-up,poke,capture,room,commotion</media:keywords>
                  <media:city> Minsk</media:city>
                  <media:country>Belarus</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>BY</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Fri, 5 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2566</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 07:53:24 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2566.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2566.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Catnap couture: adorable feline caught napping in boutique's pink mavin!</media:title>
                  <media:description>In the city of Borisov, Belarus, on July 16, 2023, a heartwarming scene unfolded in a second clothes boutique. Local resident @ugimaster stumbled upon a delightful sight as he entered the store - a contented cat fast asleep amidst the clothes. Its furry head was cozily nestled on a soft pink mavin, adding an extra touch of cuteness to the scene. The video captured by @ugimaster quickly went viral, spreading smiles and warming hearts across the internet.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>cat,sleeping,clothes,boutique,Borisov,Belarus,@ugimaster,video,peaceful,pink,mavin,adorable,feline,nap,city,viral,internet,heartwarming,cozy,cute</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Borisov</media:city>
                  <media:country>Belarus</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>BY</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2562</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 07:47:37 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2562.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2562.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Raccoon's Miron misadventures: a heartwarming birthday surprise!</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a heartwarming tale of misadventures, @raccoon_miron from St. Petersburg, Russia, captured a touching video while searching for her beloved raccoon pet, Miron on April 27, 2023. The furry troublemaker had managed to scatter her belongings all over the apartment on the eve of his birthday, leaving her in tears, fearing he had escaped through the window. However, to her relief, Miron was just being mischievous and had fallen asleep amidst her things. The emotional rollercoaster of worry and joy unfolded in the video.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>raccoon,miron,video,pet,birthday,surprise,misadventures,St. Petersburg,Russia,apartment,balcony,work,order,sobbing,window,smart,boy,asleep,things,love,joy.</media:keywords>
                  <media:city> St. Petersburg</media:city>
                  <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2558</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 07:43:53 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2558.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2558.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Record-breaking capture: the world's longest Burmese python defeated on US41</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a remarkable feat of courage and teamwork, a group of adventurers on US41 between Naples and Miami, USA, captured the world's longest Burmese python ever documented. The incredible event was documented in a video by @gladesboys on July 10, 2023. Braving the late-night encounter at 1 am, the author and his three inexperienced companions faced the massive serpent on the road. With nerves of steel, he expertly dodged the snake's strikes, finally managing to grasp its tail and secure the head. Despite the dangers, the skilled team managed the capture flawlessly, ensuring that no one was harmed during the process. </media:description>
                  <media:keywords>python,road,US41,Naples,Miami,USA,video,capture,longest,Burmese,record,encounter,hunters,tail,head,courageous,teamwork,adventure,wildlife,triumph,danger</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>US41 between Naples and Miami</media:city>
                  <media:country>United States</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>US</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2557</guid>
                  <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 14:58:10 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2557.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2557.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Massive moth invasion: swarms of flying creatures fill the night skies in Yelets, Russia</media:title>
                  <media:description>On the night of Monday, July 24, 2023, the city of Yelets in the Lipetsk region, Russia, experienced a bizarre phenomenon as drivers encountered a massive invasion of insects. Thousands of flying creatures, identified as moths, enveloped the road lights, creating "swarm clouds" that obstructed the path on the Karakum bridge. Disturbing footage recorded by a driver showcased the surreal scene, where the insects swarmed around vehicles, making navigation challenging. </media:description>
                  <media:keywords>insects,invasion,Yelets,Russia,night,Monday,July 24,Lipetsk,drivers,filmed,massive,flying,creatures,swarm,clouds,Karakum,bridge,moths,video,way,drove</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Yelets, Lipetsk region</media:city>
                  <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ODD</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2556</guid>
                  <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 14:56:15 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2556.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2556.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Silent expectations: a comical tale of leash mishaps and unspoken desires</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a heartwarming yet amusing video captured by @bentleyandfinnn on June 12, 2023, in Texas, USA, a dog's expressive response to an unexpected leash mishap left viewers in stitches. The dog, eagerly anticipating a walk, stood still as its owner accidentally dropped the leash. With a look of anticipation and confusion, the canine waited for the owner to pick it up and continue the outing, but to no avail. The silence spoke volumes as the dog's expressive eyes and hopeful demeanor conveyed its desires without a single bark. Eventually, the dog took matters into its paws and returned to the owner, as if to say, "Let's try this again, but get it right this time!" The video exemplified the unspoken bond between pets and their owners, evoking laughter and heartwarming feelings all at once.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>dog,leash,video,Texas,USA,cute,funny,owner,walk,expectation,confusion,expressive,eyes,paws,bond,outing,pet,laughter,heartwarming,silent,mishap</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Texas</media:city>
                  <media:country>United States</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>US</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2547</guid>
                  <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023 17:52:44 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2547.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2547.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Adorable new arrival: baby parrot dreams peacefully in loving hands</media:title>
                  <media:description>On June 8th, 2023, in Izmir, Turkey, a heartwarming video captured by @hknyilmaz35 showcased a newly hatched parrot in the gentle hands of its caretaker, Hakan. The tiny parrot, peacefully asleep, melted hearts with its undeniable cuteness. The short clip resonated with viewers worldwide, celebrating the beauty of new life and the bond between humans and animals.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>adorable,parrot,hatchling,video,Izmir,Turkey,hands,caretaker,asleep,cute,newlife,bond,humans,animals,heartwarming,tiny,love,peaceful,@hknyilmaz35,June8th2023</media:keywords>
                  <media:city> Izmir</media:city>
                  <media:country>Turkey</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>TR</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Thu, 8 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2546</guid>
                  <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023 18:03:14 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2546.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2546.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Raging cow causes chaos during Eid al-Adha in Belakang Padang, Indonesia</media:title>
                  <media:description>On June 29, 2023, in Belakang Padang, Kampung Baru, Indonesia, a dramatic incident unfolded during the celebration of Eid al-Adha. A video captured by @donieffendi98 showcased a cow running furiously through the streets just before its scheduled sacrifice. The animal went berserk, dashing into the houses of local residents, causing panic and chaos. Despite efforts to restrain it with a rope, the cow remained in a state of rage and lashed out by kicking a nearby parked motorcycle. The unexpected and intense encounter left the community startled, and the situation was eventually brought under control.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>rage,cow,sacrifice,berserk,houses,residents,panic,chaos,restrain,rope,motorcycle,intense,encounter,community,startled,control,video,Belakang Padang,Kampung Baru,Indonesia</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Belakang Padang, Kampung Baru</media:city>
                  <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>ID</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2543</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 07:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2543.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2543.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Unconventional cat and mouse chase: when the prey strikes back in Lviv, Ukraine!</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a comical scene captured by @bohdansereda on June 11, 2023, in Lviv, Ukraine, a cat found itself in an amusing predicament with a crafty mouse. The video showcased the mouse perched confidently on the cat's back, seemingly taunting the feline as it attempted to catch its elusive companion. Despite the mouse's daring trickery, the determined cat valiantly pursued the rodent, refusing to give up the chase. After a series of entertaining antics, the mouse's luck eventually ran out, and it tumbled from the cat's back, leading to a swift and triumphant pounce by the feline. </media:description>
                  <media:keywords>cat,mouse,lviv,ukraine,video,chase,trick,clever,funny,pursuit,adventure,pounce,whiskers,comical,scene,internet,sensation,playful,showdown,triumph,amusing</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Lviv</media:city>
                  <media:country>Ukraine</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>UA</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2534</guid>
                  <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 15:07:59 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2534.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2534.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Feathered frenzy: Loki the staffy takes on the seagull invasion in Hull, UK!</media:title>
                  <media:description>On June 3, 2023, in Hull, UK, @zaynetowe witnessed an amusing sight in her garden as her dog, Loki the Staffy, took charge against a swarm of seagulls. The video captured the moment when numerous seagulls invaded the garden, prompting Loki to dash into action. With unyielding determination, Loki fearlessly chased the seagulls away, leaving the garden free from the feathery invaders. It was a comical display of canine bravery, as the loyal pup swiftly returned to the safety of the house after successfully warding off the feathered intruders.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>garden,dog,Loki,staffy,seagulls,chase,video,Hull,UK,funny,brave,invasion,action,loyal,pup,feathered,intruders,June,@zaynetowe,house</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Hull, England </media:city>
                  <media:country>United Kingdom</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>GB</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sat, 3 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2529</guid>
                  <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 20:56:41 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2529.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2529.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Startling encounter: snake dangles and vanishes in Ho Chi Minh city home</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a harrowing incident captured on a home camera in Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam, a resident, @congdonghoainhon, had an unsettling surprise. On May 12, 2023, the camera alerted him to movement in his bedroom, and upon checking the footage, he was startled to see a snake dangling near the camera. Moments later, the snake fell out of sight, leaving him alarmed. Rushing back home, he searched his room diligently but found no trace of the elusive serpent. Speculating that it might have taken refuge inside the air conditioner, the resident remains on edge, unable to locate the reptile.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>snake,camera,bedroom,video,home,work,warn,movement,shocked,rummage,find,air conditioner,Vietnam,Ho Chi Minh City,resident,encounter,alert,elusive,reptile,tags</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Ho Chi Minh City</media:city>
                  <media:country>Vietnam</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>VN</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Fri, 12 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2528</guid>
                  <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 20:58:54 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2528.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2528.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Slippery shenanigans: Fatty the dog's hilarious underground parking adventure!</media:title>
                  <media:description>In Jiangxi province, China, on June 9th, 2023, a playful dog named Fatty found himself in a comical situation at the underground parking lot. His owner, Fatty, captured the moment on video as the excited canine ran towards her, only to slip on the wet floor. With a quick recovery, Fatty tried to hide his embarrassment by looking forward, creating a humorous and endearing scene. Thankfully, no harm was done, and Fatty's misadventures added a touch of laughter to an otherwise ordinary day at the parking lot.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>june 9th,2023,jiangxi province,china,fatty,dog,video,running,sliding,wet floor,underground parking,car,water,slip,embarrassment,owner,playfulness,comical,recovery,laughter,misadventure</media:keywords>
                  <media:city> Jiangxi province</media:city>
                  <media:country>China</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>CN</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Fri, 9 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2527</guid>
                  <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 21:01:29 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2527.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2527.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Charming canine shenanigans: dog delights in self-play on the couch!</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a heartwarming video captured by @mia.the.staffy on June 16, 2023, in Örebro, Sweden, a delightful canine showcased its unique form of entertainment. The dog Mia, which is a staffy breed, was seen playfully folding itself on the couch, engrossed in the amusing activity of nibbling at its own leg. The endearing display of self-play charmed viewers, highlighting the joyful and quirky nature of our beloved four-legged companions.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>playful,canine,video,couch,leg,nibbling,adorable,@mia.the.staffy,Sweden,Örebro,charming,self-play,entertaining,dog,folding,heartwarming,quirky,delightful,nature,beloved</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Örebro</media:city>
                  <media:country>Sweden</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>SE</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2524</guid>
                  <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 09:32:57 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2524.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2524.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                     </channel>
                  </rss>
                