<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
        xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
        xmlns:openSearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearchrss/1.0/"
        xmlns:dfpvideo="http://api.google.com/dfpvideo"
        xmlns:tms="http://data.tmsapi.com/v1.1"
        version="2.0">
         <channel>
           <title>ViralBear videos</title>
           <dfpvideo:version>2</dfpvideo:version><item>
              <media:title>Unlikely confrontation: tourist's dog faces fierce cat at Irganai reservoir</media:title>
              <media:description>In an unexpected turn of events at the picturesque Irganai reservoir in Dagestan, Russia, a tourist's leisurely day took a surprising twist when their four-legged companion faced off against a disgruntled cat. On June 11, 2023, @dag.travel captured a video showing the intense encounter. The cat lunged at the dog, prompting the owner to swiftly intervene, pulling the dog away and moving to a safer distance. Despite the distance, the persistent cat continued its pursuit, leading the dog's owner to carry their pet to avoid further confrontation. The serene outing turned into an unusual showdown, leaving both the onlookers and the tourists in awe of the unexpected clash between these unlikely adversaries.</media:description>
              <media:keywords>dog,cat,attack,Irganai,reservoir,Dagestan,Russia,tourist,owner,atmosphere,video,confront,surprising,encounter,lunge,persistent,pursuit,carry,onlookers,clash</media:keywords>
              <media:city>Dagestan</media:city>
              <media:country>Russia</media:country>
              <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
              <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
              <media:category>Animals</media:category>
              <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
              <media:filmingDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
              <guid>2503</guid>
              <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 19:17:00 GMT</pubDate>
              <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2503.jpg" />
              <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/reuters-videos/2503.mp4" />
              <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
              </item><item>
            <media:title>Rare waterspout sighted over Kama River near Perm, Russia due to unusual temperature anomaly</media:title>
            <media:description>On the evening of July 13th, 2023, residents near Cape Strelka in Perm, Russia, were amazed to witness a rare natural phenomenon - a waterspout over the Kama River. The unusual occurrence was attributed to the surface temperature of the water being several degrees higher than the air temperature, as reported by the GIS center of Perm State University. The sight of the swirling waterspout left onlookers in awe, as it gracefully danced over the river, a remarkable event rarely seen in the region.</media:description>
            <media:keywords>waterspout,kama,russia,cape strelka,perm,phenomenon,temperature,air,swirling,river,unusual,natural,evening,july 13th,2023,GIS center,state university,higher,surface,dancing</media:keywords>
            <media:city>Perm</media:city>
            <media:country>Russia</media:country>
            <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
           <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>      
            <media:category>Weather</media:category>
            <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
            <media:filmingDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
            <guid>2502</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 14:22:06 GMT</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2502.jpg" />
            <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/reuters-videos/2502.mp4" />
            <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
            </item><item>
            <media:title>Bra brawl: furry guardians turn fashion feud in Selangor, Malaysia!</media:title>
            <media:description>In a surprising and amusing spectacle captured by @rita_roslie in Selangor, Malaysia on June 28, 2023, two dogs were caught on camera engaging in a hilarious tug-of-war over a bra. The canines seemed to have stumbled upon the lingerie in question and were passionately tugging at each end, playfully bickering over their newfound treasure. As one dog clenched its teeth onto one side of the bra, the other dog stubbornly held onto the opposite end, creating a comical fashion feud. The author, the eyewitness, revealed that one of the dogs involved was her loyal garden guardian, but she was clueless about where they had discovered the bra.</media:description>
            <media:keywords>dogs,fighting,bra,tugofwar,hilarious,spectacle,Malaysia,Selangor,video,canines,fashion,feud,treasure,comical,viral,pets,quirky,antics,animals,guardians</media:keywords>
            <media:city>Selangor</media:city>
            <media:country>Malaysia</media:country>
            <media:regionCode>MY</media:regionCode>
           <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>      
            <media:category>Animals</media:category>
            <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
            <media:filmingDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
            <guid>2500</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 14:26:17 GMT</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2500.jpg" />
            <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/reuters-videos/2500.mp4" />
            <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
            </item><item>
            <media:title>Fierce yet gentle: Russian serval cat's playful encounter with watchful dog</media:title>
            <media:description>In a captivating video captured by @mainecoonnhaching on July 8th, 2023, in Dau Mot city, Binh Duong province, Vietnam, a serval cat imported from Russia displayed a striking mix of ferocity and tenderness. The video shows the cat enthusiastically chasing after an object thrown towards their glass door, revealing the curious dog outside. The cat runs straight to the door and, though fierce in appearance, slumps its head while retrieving the toy. The dog, kept outside to prevent accidents indoors, remains safe behind a fenced gate, thanks to careful guarding.</media:description>
            <media:keywords>cat,video,serval,Russia,fierce,gentle,dog,play,glass,door,chase,curious,outside,safe,fenced,gate,guarding,harmony,environment,adorable</media:keywords>
            <media:city>Dau Mot city, Binh Duong province</media:city>
            <media:country>Vietnam</media:country>
            <media:regionCode>VN</media:regionCode>
           <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>      
            <media:category>Animals</media:category>
            <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
            <media:filmingDate>Sat, 8 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
            <guid>2498</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 13:13:12 GMT</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2498.jpg" />
            <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/reuters-videos/2498.mp4" />
            <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
            </item><item>
            <media:title>How to quickly cross the river? Vietnamese surfer conquers new heights!</media:title>
            <media:description>Vietnamese surfer, @chuongfoil, made waves in Dien Chau district, Nghe An province, Vietnam, on April 23, 2023, with his exceptional hydrofoil surfing skills. After dedicating two years to rigorous training, he finally achieved success, gliding effortlessly on the river's surface. Overcoming initial struggles where he frequently sank, @chuongfoil's perseverance and determination paid off, allowing him to conquer the water's edge with finesse and mastery. </media:description>
            <media:keywords>surfing,hydrofoil,lake,Vietnam,@chuongfoil,adventure,water,skill,perseverance,success,training,mastery,waves,gliding,surfboard,journey,transformation,enthusiasm,determination,athlete</media:keywords>
            <media:city>Dien Chau district, Nghe An province</media:city>
            <media:country>Vietnam</media:country>
            <media:regionCode>VN</media:regionCode>
           <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>      
            <media:category>Sport</media:category>
            <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
            <media:filmingDate>Sun, 23 Apr 2023</media:filmingDate>
            <guid>2497</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 12:53:46 GMT</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2497.jpg" />
            <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/reuters-videos/2497.mp4" />
            <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
            </item><item>
            <media:title>Amusing cat drama unfolds: playful feline duo turns kitchen mishap into entertainment!</media:title>
            <media:description>In a heartwarming yet comical scene captured by @thanhtam8880 on June 14th, 2023, in Thanh Xuan district, Hanoi, Vietnam, two cats shared a playful moment in the kitchen. As one curious feline inadvertently stuck its tail between the cupboard door, its furry friend mistook the situation for a game and started playfully tugging at the trapped tail. While the incident might have seemed concerning at first, it quickly turned into a delightful display of camaraderie as the mischievous companion successfully freed its tail.</media:description>
            <media:keywords>cat,video,playful,kitchen,cupboard,tail,stuck,comical,companionship,feline,heartwarming,Hanoi,Thanh Xuan district,Vietnam,friends,entertaining,cooking,mishap,funny,moment</media:keywords>
            <media:city>Thanh Xuan district, Hanoi</media:city>
            <media:country>Vietnam</media:country>
            <media:regionCode>VN</media:regionCode>
           <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>      
            <media:category>Animals</media:category>
            <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
            <media:filmingDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
            <guid>2496</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 12:28:49 GMT</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2496.jpg" />
            <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/reuters-videos/2496.mp4" />
            <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
            </item><item>
            <media:title>Rail rampage: freight train mishap causes havoc at Matveevskaya Station in Moscow</media:title>
            <media:description>On July 18, 2023, at Moscow's Matveevskaya station in Russia, a freight train transporting rails experienced a serious accident. During transportation, one of the rails shifted and obstructed the train's path, causing extensive damage to everything in its way. The incident resulted in the destruction of the platform's pavilion and the damage of the driver's cab in an oncoming train. Fortunately, no injuries were reported among the people at the station. Despite the chaos caused by the runaway rail, there were no traffic delays along the route. </media:description>
            <media:keywords>rail,accident,freight,train,platform,Moscow,Russia,transportation,damage,pavilion,oncoming,driver's cab,mishap,knockdown,path,havoc,delay,people,repairs,footage</media:keywords>
            <media:city>Matveevskaya, Moscow </media:city>
            <media:country>Russia</media:country>
            <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
           <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>      
            <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
            <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
            <media:filmingDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
            <guid>2494</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 12:14:26 GMT</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2494.jpg" />
            <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/reuters-videos/2494.mp4" />
            <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
            </item><item>
              <media:title>Caught on camera: two boys' epic grad party adventure foiled by mom</media:title>
              <media:description>In a viral video capturing a memorable July 9th, 2023, night in New Jersey, USA, user @nverdesco_ shared an unforgettable moment when two boys' well-planned graduation party took an unexpected turn. The footage shows the boys caught red-handed by their mother after sneaking out to enjoy their long-awaited celebration. One of the boys explained that they had meticulously planned the event for an entire year, pooling their savings to make it a reality, fully aware that getting caught was a possibility. Despite their earnest attempts to explain, their mother remained firm, insisting they leave the party immediately.</media:description>
              <media:keywords>party,graduation,sneaking,caught,video,viral,New Jersey,USA,celebration,planned,savings,mother,determined,risks,social media,adventure,milestone,unforgettable,youthful,firm</media:keywords>
              <media:city>New Jersey</media:city>
              <media:country>United States</media:country>
              <media:regionCode>US</media:regionCode>
              <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
              <media:category>Fails and Funnies</media:category>
              <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
              <media:filmingDate>Sun, 9 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
              <guid>2492</guid>
              <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 09:38:49 GMT</pubDate>
              <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2492.jpg" />
              <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/reuters-videos/2492.mp4" />
              <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
              </item><item>
            <media:title>Emotional homecoming: a surprise puppy fulfilling two years of longing</media:title>
            <media:description>In a heartwarming video captured by @stuartthegoldenweenie on July 5th, 2023, in New York, USA, a girlfriend's dream finally came true after two years of daily pleas for a puppy. Living in a small 1-bedroom apartment, she would send her partner videos of golden wiener dogs, expressing her desire for one once they had enough space. Last month, they purchased a new house together, and seizing the opportunity to surprise her, he presented her with the puppy of her dreams. Overwhelmed with joy, the girlfriend can be seen lying on the floor, sobbing as she cradles the furry companion on her chest. A simple act of love and thoughtfulness turned a long-awaited wish into a reality, filling their new home with love and happiness.</media:description>
            <media:keywords>puppy,surprise,girlfriend,video,love,longing,dream,joy,house,home,new york,usa,golden weenie,sobbing,emotion,fulfillment,space,apartment,pet,happiness</media:keywords>
            <media:city>New York</media:city>
            <media:country>United States</media:country>
            <media:regionCode>US</media:regionCode>
           <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>      
            <media:category>Heartwarming</media:category>
            <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
            <media:filmingDate>Wed, 5 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
            <guid>2491</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 09:39:44 GMT</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2491.jpg" />
            <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/reuters-videos/2491.mp4" />
            <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
            </item><item>
              <media:title>Su-25 training flight ends in disaster: engine failure causes crash over sea of Azov, pilot survives ejection</media:title>
              <media:description>On July 17th, 2023, a Su-25 attack aircraft crashed near the coast of Yeysk, Krasnodar Territory, Russia, while conducting a training flight over the Sea of Azov. The preliminary investigation points to an engine failure as the cause of the incident. Disturbingly, the crash occurred in close proximity to people who were resting on the coast at the time. Fortunately, the pilot successfully ejected from the aircraft before the impact and was rescued by emergency services. Currently, specialists from the Ministry of Defense of the Russian Federation and other relevant agencies are on-site, investigating the accident.</media:description>
              <media:keywords>crash,su-25,yeysk,krasnodar territory,russia,engine failure,training flight,sea of azov,incident,emergency services,pilot,eject,rescuers,ministry of defense,special services,scene,coast,rest,investigation,accident</media:keywords>
              <media:city>Yeysk, Krasnodar Territory</media:city>
              <media:country>Russia</media:country>
              <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
              <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
              <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
              <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
              <media:filmingDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
              <guid>2490</guid>
              <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 09:40:33 GMT</pubDate>
              <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2490.jpg" />
              <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/reuters-videos/2490.mp4" />
              <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
              </item><item>
              <media:title>Su-25 aircraft crashes into sea of Azov during training flight in Yeysk, Russia, due to engine failure</media:title>
              <media:description>On July 17th, 2023, a Su-25 aircraft crashed into the Sea of Azov near Yeysk, Krasnodar Territory, Russia, during a training flight. The incident occurred around 15:00, and according to the press service of the Southern Military District, the preliminary cause of the crash was attributed to engine failure. Fortunately, there were no reported casualties, and specialists from the Ministry of Defense and special services are currently investigating the accident on-site.</media:description>
              <media:keywords>crash,aircraft,sea,training,Yeysk,Russia,engine failure,incident,casualties,specialists,Ministry of Defense,special services,investigation,coast,Su-25,Azov,preliminary cause,spot,press service,Southern Military District</media:keywords>
              <media:city>Yeysk, Krasnodar Territory</media:city>
              <media:country>Russia</media:country>
              <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
              <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
              <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
              <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
              <media:filmingDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
              <guid>2489</guid>
              <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 09:42:11 GMT</pubDate>
              <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2489.jpg" />
              <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/reuters-videos/2489.mp4" />
              <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
              </item><item>
              <media:title>Drunken man survives fall from fifth floor, saved by antenna in Georgievsk, Stavropol</media:title>
              <media:description>In a remarkable incident that occurred on July 5th, 2023, in Georgievsk, Stavropol Territory, a 56-year-old man, well-known to local rescuers for his troubled lifestyle, survived a fall from the fifth floor thanks to an antenna. The drunken man stumbled at an open window, plummeting to the ground, but miraculously caught his foot on an antenna at the third floor level. Rescuers arrived at the scene and carefully removed him from the antenna before providing necessary assistance. Despite serious leg injuries, the man's life was saved by the antenna, and he was hospitalized in stable condition, no longer in danger.</media:description>
              <media:keywords>drunken,man,survived,fall,antenna,Georgievsk,Stavropol,rescuers,incident,miraculous,hospitalization,stable,leg,injuries,intoxicated,neighbor,fifth floor,assistance,known,lifestyle</media:keywords>
              <media:city>Georgievsk, Stavropol</media:city>
              <media:country>Russia</media:country>
              <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
              <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
              <media:category>News</media:category>
              <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
              <media:filmingDate>Wed, 5 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
              <guid>2488</guid>
              <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 10:12:53 GMT</pubDate>
              <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2488.jpg" />
              <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/reuters-videos/2488.mp4" />
              <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
              </item><item>
              <media:title>Sanitary felling mishap: poplar collapses on residential building</media:title>
              <media:description>In the Tyukhtet region of Russia, an incident occurred on July 5th, 2023, during a sanitary felling operation. Workers cut down a poplar tree, but it unexpectedly collapsed onto a residential building that also housed a pharmacy and a shop. Fortunately, local authorities reported that the damage was minor, and the house was promptly repaired on the same day. According to the first deputy head of the Tyukhtetsky municipal district, Vladimir Napryushkin, the poplar tree only touched a part of the roof with one of its branches, causing damage to several sheets. However, no injuries were reported in the incident. The tree felling is a preventive measure taken in the region to remove old trees that pose potential dangers to people and buildings. No one was injured as a result of the incident.</media:description>
              <media:keywords>residential,building,pharmacy,shop,poplar,collapse,incident,Tyukhtet,Russia,workers,tree,damage,repaired,roof,pediment,felling,danger,authorities,minor,no injuries</media:keywords>
              <media:city>Tyukhtet</media:city>
              <media:country>Russia</media:country>
              <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
              <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
              <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
              <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
              <media:filmingDate>Wed, 5 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
              <guid>2487</guid>
              <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 12:43:55 GMT</pubDate>
              <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/b615cfb9-6dbd-42ac-968d-ea39c34fd49c.jpg" />
              <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/reuters-videos/328c1bda-bfc0-411d-9bc1-2d02eab6f369.mp4" />
              <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
              </item><item>
            <media:title>Conalie the playful puddle prancer: a horse's muddy adventure in Göthewitz, Germany</media:title>
            <media:description>In Göthewitz, Germany, a delightful sight was captured by @frizziarnold on April 11th, 2021. The video showcased a horse named Conalie engaging in a playful activity. With a lady on its back, Conalie joyfully tapped the mud with its front legs, creating an endearing scene. The horse had discovered a small puddle and decided to embrace its mischievous side, playfully walking through the dirty water. The heartwarming moment captured the essence of the horse's carefree spirit and brought smiles to viewers' faces.</media:description>
            <media:keywords>horse,mud,playful,video,Göthewitz,Germany,Conalie,tapping,front legs,lady,puddle,dirty water,joy,mischievous,carefree,smiles,playful spirit,@frizziarnold,April 11th,2021</media:keywords>
            <media:city>Göthewitz</media:city>
            <media:country>Germany</media:country>
            <media:regionCode>DE</media:regionCode>
           <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>      
            <media:category>Animals</media:category>
            <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
            <media:filmingDate>Sun, 11 Apr 2021</media:filmingDate>
            <guid>2485</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 09:36:53 GMT</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/9d681a58-9032-422d-bce9-5166eb06806b.jpg" />
            <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/reuters-videos/aaec3079-8fb3-40bc-8f1f-7ea085f84424.mp4" />
            <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
            </item><item>
            <media:title>Snake's surprise: when a reptile acts like a cat!</media:title>
            <media:description>In a surprising and adorable video captured by @children.of.loki on June 13th, 2023, in Texas, USA, a snake displayed remarkably cat-like behavior. The footage shows the snake slithering around the house until its owner scratches its back. Astonishingly, the reptile bends the area where it receives the scratch, seemingly relishing the affectionate gesture. Captioned as "My snake is a cat," this extraordinary behavior showcases the fascinating and unexpected similarities between these two vastly different creatures.
</media:description>
            <media:keywords>snake,reptile,pet,Texas,USA,video,cat-like,behavior,adorable,surprising,scratch,slithering,house,owner,affectionate,gesture,fascination,creature,similarities,captivating</media:keywords>
            <media:city>Texas</media:city>
            <media:country>United States</media:country>
            <media:regionCode>US</media:regionCode>
           <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>      
            <media:category>Animals</media:category>
            <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
            <media:filmingDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
            <guid>2484</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 09:35:26 GMT</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/dccfb477-e6cb-4f39-a2e9-be93aaab4eff.jpg" />
            <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/reuters-videos/12408cf2-ff18-4c12-b4b1-9a9cf41f8669.mp4" />
            <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
            </item><item>
            <media:title>Enchanting Serpukhov slumber: meet Jim, the bed-loving pet raccoon!</media:title>
            <media:description>In a heartwarming and endearing display of companionship, a captivating video emerged on June 2, 2023, from Serpukhov, Russia, showcasing the adorable bond between a pet raccoon and its owner. Shared by @enot_jim, the footage captured her furry friend, Jim, curled up cozily in bed. Jim, the affectionate pet raccoon, has won the hearts of netizens with his penchant for catching forty winks in the comfort of his owner's bed.</media:description>
            <media:keywords>sleeping,raccoon,pet,bed,Serpukhov,Russia,cute,video,Jim,adorable,bond,owner,cozy,heartwarming,furry,netizens,household,charming,relationship,companionship</media:keywords>
            <media:city>Serpukhov</media:city>
            <media:country>Russia</media:country>
            <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
           <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>      
            <media:category>Animals</media:category>
            <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
            <media:filmingDate>Fri, 2 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
            <guid>2483</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 09:34:32 GMT</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/acd9474c-3f02-437f-b297-9ab3fe3fa3cf.jpg" />
            <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/reuters-videos/268092ad-e3fd-4fca-af9b-710e6481bbaf.mp4" />
            <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
            </item><item>
            <media:title>Enchanting encounter: friendly dolphin delights swimmer at Suishohama Beach, Japan</media:title>
            <media:description>On July 17th, 2023, at Suishohama Beach in Mihama, Mikata District, Japan, a remarkable scene unfolded as a curious dolphin made a surprise appearance near the shore. @Ooo_MEN_ captured the heartwarming moment on video, showing the dolphin playfully interacting with a lone swimmer using a floater. The extraordinary encounter left beachgoers in awe as they witnessed the gentle marine creature approaching and engaging with the delighted individual. </media:description>
            <media:keywords>dolphin,beach,interaction,swimmer,floater,video,Japan,Mihama,Mikata District,Suishohama Beach,nature,wildlife,encounter,playful,surprise,curious,harmony,awe,enchanting,filmed</media:keywords>
            <media:city>Mihama, Mikata District</media:city>
            <media:country>Japan</media:country>
            <media:regionCode>JP</media:regionCode>
           <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>      
            <media:category>Animals</media:category>
            <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
            <media:filmingDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
            <guid>2481</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 10:25:14 GMT</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/401402ff-22eb-4a49-9a06-dfbde13add42.jpg" />
            <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/reuters-videos/b0ffcab6-0702-4724-b2bf-486cb4b58e13.mp4" />
            <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
            </item><item>
            <media:title>Whiskered surprise: playful cat in a cute box captivates Siheung City</media:title>
            <media:description>In Siheung City, Korea, a heartwarming incident occurred on June 3, 2023, as a video captured by @goarongggoo went viral. The clip featured a curious cat tucked away inside a cute box. The man behind the camera revealed that he was selling these delightful boxes when he stumbled upon the feline surprise. With a playful knock on the box resembling a door, he decided to unveil the mystery. Upon opening the box, a charming cat emerged. </media:description>
            <media:keywords>cat,box,video,cute,Siheung City,Korea,surprise,viral,@goarongggoo,June 3,2023,knock,door,feline,playful,charming,joy,wonder,internet,community,moment</media:keywords>
            <media:city>Siheung City</media:city>
            <media:country>South Korea</media:country>
            <media:regionCode>KR</media:regionCode>
           <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>      
            <media:category>Animals</media:category>
            <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
            <media:filmingDate>Sat, 3 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
            <guid>2480</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 09:31:32 GMT</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/71eed083-e8af-46f6-8c74-09a7128c2948.jpg" />
            <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/reuters-videos/2480.mp4" />
            <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
            </item><item>
            <media:title>Harv's chicken house harmony: cat and chickens live in paw-sitive coexistence!</media:title>
            <media:description>In a heartwarming display of unexpected camaraderie, a captivating video captured by @harvs.gamla.skola on July 3rd, 2023 from Harv, Sweden, showcased a remarkable scene in her chicken house. The footage revealed her feline companion perched gracefully on one of the chicken trays while the feathered inhabitants remained surprisingly calm and at ease in the presence of their newfound friend. Captioned with a touch of amusement, "I'm not even surprised anymore...," the video serves as a testament to the harmonious coexistence between the cat and the chickens. </media:description>
            <media:keywords>cat,chicken,harmony,coexistence,video,Sweden,Harv,pets,animals,friendship,unexpected,bond,companionship,feathers,tray,love,heartwarming,amusement,captivated,surprising,delightful</media:keywords>
            <media:city>Harv</media:city>
            <media:country>Sweden</media:country>
            <media:regionCode>SE</media:regionCode>
           <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>      
            <media:category>Animals</media:category>
            <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
            <media:filmingDate>Mon, 3 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
            <guid>2479</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 08:23:59 GMT</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/bad55bf2-197f-4722-8387-d12a5844b496.jpg" />
            <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/reuters-videos/305cce9e-1b1a-490d-93b8-6deed141c6de.mp4" />
            <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
            </item><item>
            <media:title>Resilient Weimaraner overcomes adversity: walking proudly with unlikely footwear amidst health challenges</media:title>
            <media:description>In a heartwarming moment captured by @ms_zwaal on May 20th, 2023, in Port Hueneme, California, USA, her Weimaraner, Dutch, showed incredible resilience and adaptability. While hanging out and watching TV, they heard a peculiar "clack, clack" sound and discovered Dutch walking around with a slipper on his hind leg. Unbothered by the unusual situation, Dutch showcased his indomitable spirit despite his fragile appearance. The video's caption revealed that Dutch is an old guy battling a tumor in his spleen and liver, reassuring viewers that he is well taken care of.</media:description>
            <media:keywords>resilient,weimaraner,dog,slipper,hind leg,unbothered,California,USA,video,TV,clack,sandal,fragile,old,tumor,spleen,liver,pet,companion,bond</media:keywords>
            <media:city>Port Hueneme, California</media:city>
            <media:country>United States</media:country>
            <media:regionCode>US</media:regionCode>
           <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>      
            <media:category>Animals</media:category>
            <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
            <media:filmingDate>Sat, 20 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
            <guid>2478</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 19:08:16 GMT</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/9bb30096-7336-40e4-99b4-8a3c5f4777c6.jpg" />
            <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/reuters-videos/55ea0281-f6b7-4285-b506-f2d184cab733.mp4" />
            <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
            </item><item>
            <media:title>Doggie oasis: Beha finds refreshing relief from the heat by the shore</media:title>
            <media:description>On June 17th, 2023, in Balashikha, Moscow, Russia, a heartwarming video captured the attention of many as @nemez_bexa shared a delightful moment with her dog. The scorching heat couldn't keep Beha away from cooling off in the water near the shore. In the short clip, the dog is seen seated in the water, content and relaxed. </media:description>
            <media:keywords>dog,water,shore,hot,Beha,play,video,Balashikha,Moscow,Russia,heat,pet,playful,refresh,summer,cool,socialmedia,cute,joy,happiness,retrieve</media:keywords>
            <media:city> Balashikha, Moscow</media:city>
            <media:country>Russia</media:country>
            <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
           <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>      
            <media:category>Animals</media:category>
            <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
            <media:filmingDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
            <guid>2477</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 18:48:43 GMT</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/ed8cd420-ed98-48df-9484-6be4d907eff5.jpg" />
            <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/reuters-videos/8d17f570-45ef-4163-9b03-1f4f7090277c.mp4" />
            <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
            </item><item>
            <media:title>Severe flooding wreaks havoc in Akita Prefecture, Japan</media:title>
            <media:description>As of July 15, 2023, Akita Prefecture, Japan, is facing ongoing disruptions due to severe flooding caused by heavy downpours. The Japan Meteorological Agency (JMA) has issued orange-level heavy rain and landslide warnings, along with yellow flood advisories across the region. The storms, accompanied by strong winds, lightning, hail, and potential tornadoes, have led to dangerous river levels and widespread transportation disruptions. Several cities and towns, including Akita, Daisen, Noshiro, Oga, Fujisato, Gojome, and Hachirogata, are under evacuation orders. The Babame and Uchikawa rivers have overflowed, causing significant flooding and damage to properties in affected areas. Tragically, one person has already lost their life due to the heavy rain. The Akita Shinkansen has been suspended between Morioka and Akita stations, further exacerbating the situation. @be5b48tgmailcom captured a video showing flooding in Akita station east exit rotary.</media:description>
            <media:keywords>flooding,akita,japan,weather,disruptions,heavyrain,landslides,warnings,evacuation,storms,strongwinds,lightning,hail,tornadoes,riveroverflow,transportation,propertydamage,poweroutages,meteorologicalagency,rainfall</media:keywords>
            <media:city>Akita Prefecture</media:city>
            <media:country>Japan</media:country>
            <media:regionCode>JP</media:regionCode>
           <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>      
            <media:category>Weather</media:category>
            <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
            <media:filmingDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
            <guid>2476</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 18:32:38 GMT</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/4e66ff04-2157-4f3d-89c2-7ca8f905ef47.jpg" />
            <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/reuters-videos/d5b71e0d-01dc-468f-9d42-33d3363f0fb7.mp4" />
            <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
            </item><item>
            <media:title>Mesmerizing aerial encounter: epic dust storm sweeps towards Phoenix, Arizona</media:title>
            <media:description>On July 17th, 2023, @philthatremains, while flying over Arizona, USA, managed to capture an incredible video of a massive dust storm heading towards Phoenix. The mesmerizing aerial footage showcased the sheer power and scale of the natural phenomenon as it engulfed the landscape. The video quickly gained attention on social media, leaving viewers in awe of the intense dust storm's raw force and impact on the region.</media:description>
            <media:keywords>arizona,usa,dust storm,video,capture,aerial,@philthatremains,flying,incredible,landscape,power,scale,phenomenon,social media,awe,intense,force,impact,region,weather</media:keywords>
            <media:city>Arizona</media:city>
            <media:country>United States</media:country>
            <media:regionCode>US</media:regionCode>
           <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>      
            <media:category>News</media:category>
            <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
            <media:filmingDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
            <guid>2475</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/408b4c20-59c2-4abf-a242-ab15055c3047.jpg" />
            <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/reuters-videos/6dd16b45-3b77-42c8-968e-eba5f206ac93.mp4" />
            <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
            </item><item>
            <media:title>Swan's protective standoff: a brave encounter with a curious canine</media:title>
            <media:description>In a remarkable incident captured by @semenova_lena on June 3rd, 2023, in Novorossiysk, Russia, a serene family of swans by the Sudzhuk Spit estuary encountered an unexpected visitor. As onlookers observed the graceful swans, a dog, seemingly unaccompanied by its owner, approached the water's edge. The situation took a tense turn when one of the swans began hissing in defense. The quick-thinking observers promptly intervened, safely removing the curious canine from the swan's perceived territory. </media:description>
            <media:keywords>swan,hissing,dog,family,water,shore,Novorossiysk,Sudzhuk Spit,Russia,video,captured,June 3rd,2023,estuary,protective,encounter,onlookers,curious,owner,wildlife,balance</media:keywords>
            <media:city>Novorossiysk</media:city>
            <media:country>Russia</media:country>
            <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
           <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>      
            <media:category>Animals</media:category>
            <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
            <media:filmingDate>Sat, 3 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
            <guid>2474</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 13:40:52 GMT</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/8fad0eb7-2eda-4538-a056-4b6cd5ffc87f.jpg" />
            <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/reuters-videos/535d4369-fa53-4783-be3c-6c274e91d64f.mp4" />
            <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
            </item><item>
            <media:title>Fear of the unknown: a son's dance with a glass floor in San Pedro Nuevo Leon</media:title>
            <media:description>In a heartwarming yet fearful moment captured by @osvaldawg on May 27th, 2023, in San Pedro Nuevo Leon, Mexico, a young boy was confronted with a see-through glass floor. Terrified of the unknown depths below, he hesitated to take a step, frozen in his fear. The boy's concerned father gently pushed him onto the glass, but the overwhelming anxiety caused the child to quickly retreat.</media:description>
            <media:keywords>afraid,glass,floor,fear,son,video,Mexico,San Pedro,hesitation,unknown,depths,anxiety,father,push,retreat,courage,face,step,capture,moment</media:keywords>
            <media:city>San Pedro Nuevo Leon</media:city>
            <media:country>Mexico</media:country>
            <media:regionCode>MX</media:regionCode>
           <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>      
            <media:category>Fails and Funnies</media:category>
            <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
            <media:filmingDate>Sat, 27 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
            <guid>2473</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 13:06:03 GMT</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/a3d8050a-f5d4-41e9-a51e-fb96d93acd3d.jpg" />
            <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/reuters-videos/53db4947-8538-4dce-b49d-8a9f1bc4ef08.mp4" />
            <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
            </item><item>
            <media:title>Near disaster at North Morowali's wooden bridge: motorbikes overload nearly causes collapse!</media:title>
            <media:description>On June 27th, 2023, a heart-stopping incident occurred in North Morowali, Indonesia, when a wooden bridge came close to collapsing under the weight of multiple motorbikes. The alarming scene was captured on video by @srcyayaaa, who witnessed the incident unfold. Instead of crossing the bridge one by one as recommended, the riders decided to pass together, causing an overwhelming strain on the aging structure. Miraculously, the bridge managed to hold on, preventing a potentially catastrophic accident. </media:description>
            <media:keywords>wooden,bridge,collapse,motorbike,weight,North Morowali,Indonesia,video,nearly,one by one,together,fall,repaired,incident,captured,@srcyayaaa,danger,structure,safety,guidelines</media:keywords>
            <media:city>North Morowali</media:city>
            <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
            <media:regionCode>ID</media:regionCode>
           <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>      
            <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
            <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
            <media:filmingDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
            <guid>2472</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 11:56:22 GMT</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/626d8c53-00bd-4110-afc2-335d637a3843.jpg" />
            <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/reuters-videos/0ee55b97-720f-4e2a-b385-a82766e1cc1d.mp4" />
            <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
            </item><item>
            <media:title>Amusing misunderstanding: clever Shih Tzu eagerly eats treats after playful vet pretense</media:title>
            <media:description>In a heartwarming and humorous video captured by @Fimmy_theshihtzu on May 31st, 2023, in Cavite, Philippines, a delightful Shih Tzu showcased its cleverness and sense of humor. The adorable pet initially refused to eat its treats, prompting the owner's dad to pretend to call the vet and humorously warn of an impending rear injection if the dog didn't eat. Surprisingly, the moment the word "injection" was mentioned, the furry companion quickly changed its mind and eagerly devoured the treats. Many viewers found the video entertaining, believing that the pet had genuinely understood the playful jest.</media:description>
            <media:keywords>adorable,shih tzu,pet,treats,funny,clever,video,Philippines,Cavite,eat,pretend,vet,injection,rear,amusement,understanding,heartwarming,owner,dad,humor</media:keywords>
            <media:city>Cavite</media:city>
            <media:country>Philippines</media:country>
            <media:regionCode>PH</media:regionCode>
           <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>      
            <media:category>Animals</media:category>
            <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
            <media:filmingDate>Wed, 31 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
            <guid>2471</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 12:50:58 GMT</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2471.jpg" />
            <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/reuters-videos/2471.mp4" />
            <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
            </item><item>
            <media:title>Secret snack: crafty courier caught on camera enjoying customer's pie in Yakutia</media:title>
            <media:description>In a surprising incident caught on camera on June 30th, 2023 in Yakutia, Russia, a daring courier decided to indulge in a customer's order, leaving onlookers stunned. The footage shows the crafty courier skillfully slicing the pie, ensuring his act remained unnoticed, as he devoured the treat with a small knife. With calculated precision, he closed the pie back up, seamlessly concealing any evidence of his secret snack, and continued on his delivery route. The video has sparked both amusement and disbelief.</media:description>
            <media:keywords>feast,courier,footage,eyewitnesses,yakutia,russia,pie,bike,motorbike,careful,crime,small knife,eating,delivery,secret,snack,indulgence,skillful,amusement,disbelief</media:keywords>
            <media:city>Yakutia</media:city>
            <media:country>Russia</media:country>
            <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
           <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>      
            <media:category>News</media:category>
            <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
            <media:filmingDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
            <guid>2470</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 11:06:16 GMT</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/a7ac6ccf-a978-41ad-b5d9-62de66fbfd80.jpg" />
            <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/reuters-videos/2470.mp4" />
            <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
            </item><item>
              <media:title>Teenage AVM scooter crash at intersection in Ust-Izhora, St. Petersburg: investigation underway</media:title>
              <media:description>In Ust-Izhora, St. Petersburg, Russia, on Thursday, June 29th, a collision occurred at the intersection of Pushkinskaya and Truda streets involving a teenager on an AVM scooter and a Nissan X-Treil driven by a 32-year-old woman. The young driver of the scooter failed to yield, resulting in the crash. Both the 16-year-old driver and their passenger sustained injuries and were taken to the hospital in moderate condition. The incident is currently under investigation to establish the exact circumstances of the accident.</media:description>
              <media:keywords>accident,scooter,Nissan,crash,intersection,Ust-Izhora,StPetersburg,Russia,teenager,AVM,give-way,injured,hospitalized,moderate,LenTV24,footage,investigation,circumstances,driver,passenger</media:keywords>
              <media:city> Ust-Izhora, St. Petersburg</media:city>
              <media:country>Russia</media:country>
              <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
              <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
              <media:category>Road accidents</media:category>
              <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
              <media:filmingDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
              <guid>2469</guid>
              <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 08:51:39 GMT</pubDate>
              <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/b29c594a-ed6e-410b-9258-195d1f1c3738.jpg" />
              <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/reuters-videos/7986b347-4abf-49de-b13c-67bf742c43e4.mp4" />
              <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
              </item><item>
              <media:title>Prompt metro staff rescue: dog's paw freed from escalator in Moscow metro</media:title>
              <media:description>In a recent incident on July 1st, 2023 at the Moscow metro, a dachshund's paw became trapped in the escalator during a transition between the Krasnopresnenskaya and Barrikadnaya stations. The metro staff acted promptly, switching off the escalator and coming to the aid of the distressed animal. The metro's press service confirmed that no serious injuries occurred and urged passengers to transport their pets in carriers or bags. The veterinary clinic attending to the dachshund reported that although a small tear was observed on the paw, there were no fractures or severe injuries. Assurances were given that the dog would fully recover from the ordeal.</media:description>
              <media:keywords>moscow,metro,dog,paw,escalator,incident,krasnopresnenskaya,barrikadnaya,staff,rescue,prompt,trapped,injury,passengers,carriers,bags,veterinary,clinic,fractures,recovery</media:keywords>
              <media:city>Moscow </media:city>
              <media:country>Russia</media:country>
              <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
              <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
              <media:category>Rescue</media:category>
              <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
              <media:filmingDate>Sat, 1 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
              <guid>2468</guid>
              <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 08:39:22 GMT</pubDate>
              <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/c9214d0a-84df-4aa5-9547-1575920469c3.jpg" />
              <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/reuters-videos/55b8ec28-73b8-46ae-8171-9bad5fe8f640.mp4" />
              <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
              </item><item>
              <media:title>Tragic clash in Nerekhta: intoxicated foreign car driver hits pedestrian girl and crashes into building</media:title>
              <media:description>A horrific incident occurred in Nerekhta, Kostroma region, Russia, as reported by the press service of the UGIBDD of the Ministry of Internal Affairs. On June 29th, 2023, a foreign car driver, under the influence of alcohol, recklessly crashed into a young girl before colliding into a residential building. Shocking video footage from CCTV cameras circulated on social media, capturing the car speeding towards the helpless victim. The impact was mitigated slightly by bushes, possibly saving the girl's life. Urgently hospitalized, she now fights for recovery, while the driver will be held accountable for his actions according to the law.</media:description>
              <media:keywords>accident,clash,nerekhta,kostroma,russia,foreign car,pedestrian,girl,building,video footage,cctv,social media,intoxicated,driver,hospitalization,bushes,speeding,accountable,law,tragic</media:keywords>
              <media:city>Nerekhta, Kostroma region</media:city>
              <media:country>Russia</media:country>
              <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
              <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
              <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
              <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
              <media:filmingDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
              <guid>2467</guid>
              <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 08:28:34 GMT</pubDate>
              <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/f50935ab-19a9-4134-9232-d6071d0d4327.jpg" />
              <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/reuters-videos/213fa37c-be89-441e-b4ff-ae7688f64e58.mp4" />
              <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
              </item><item>
            <media:title>Bowls of melody: young virtuoso creates enchanting music with chopsticks in Gansu Province, China</media:title>
            <media:description>On July 4th, 2023, in Gansu Province, West China, an extraordinary musical performance unfolded on the streets. @baldheadplayingbowlbrother, a talented traditional Chinese musician, captured a video of his young son showcasing his remarkable skills with chopsticks and bowls. The child played a mesmerizing piece of music entirely on his own, drawing in a captivated crowd of onlookers who were amazed by the young virtuoso's talent. Through the rhythmic tapping of the bowls with chopsticks, the boy effortlessly produced enchanting melodies that resonated throughout the street, earning him well-deserved praise and admiration from the audience. The heartwarming performance showcased the beauty of traditional Chinese music and left a lasting impression on all who were fortunate enough to witness it.</media:description>
            <media:keywords>talented,traditional,chinese,musician,chopsticks,bowls,music,performance,son,street,captivating,crowd,onlookers,virtuoso,rhythmic,melodies,enchanting,praise,audience,heartwarming</media:keywords>
            <media:city>Gansu Province</media:city>
            <media:country>China</media:country>
            <media:regionCode>CN</media:regionCode>
           <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>      
            <media:category>Heartwarming</media:category>
            <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
            <media:filmingDate>Tue, 4 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
            <guid>2466</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 08:11:20 GMT</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/6a307182-7dc3-4d9e-8dd3-08837c6543ca.jpg" />
            <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/reuters-videos/c4fd8b5f-47fa-467b-8f77-c17270932884.mp4" />
            <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
            </item><item>
            <media:title>Fearful furry friends: Ball the dog and a playful deer's zoo encounter in Beijing!</media:title>
            <media:description>In a heartwarming yet cautious encounter at a zoo in Beijing, China, a dog named Ball had a surprising interaction with a curious deer. The moment was captured on video by @todaythemoonisnotopen on July 3rd, 2023. As Ball sat inside the car, a deer approached, seemingly eager to engage in a kiss. However, the dog's apprehension was evident, and it quickly retreated back into the safety of the vehicle. Despite the brief interaction, the endearing exchange between the two animals left a lasting impression, highlighting the beauty of unexpected connections in the animal kingdom.</media:description>
            <media:keywords>playful,deer,dog,zoo,Beijing,China,encounter,video,July3rd,2023,curious,kiss,car,interaction,animals,connection,heartwarming,cautious,moment,captured</media:keywords>
            <media:city>Beijing</media:city>
            <media:country>China</media:country>
            <media:regionCode>CN</media:regionCode>
           <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>      
            <media:category>Animals</media:category>
            <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
            <media:filmingDate>Mon, 3 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
            <guid>2465</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 20:14:19 GMT</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/291686df-edaf-40a2-b29e-324e7310ae8e.jpg" />
            <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/reuters-videos/0aa16f8f-fcd5-478e-855b-65c0cc6eee1a.mp4" />
            <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
            </item><item>
            <media:title>Troublemaker Prince: the mischievous parrot's love for cupboards!</media:title>
            <media:description>In a charming video captured by @tamiaoveres in Vancouver, Canada, on November 15th, 2022, her mischievous parrot, Prince, found himself in a bit of a predicament after sneaking into a forbidden cabinet filled with delicate glass cups. As the author called out to her feathery companion, Prince seemed to revel in the adventure, hopping around and singing playfully. However, after a brief dance of mischief, the mischievous bird finally hopped back into author's arms. According to the amused owner, Prince's fascination with cupboards outweighed his interest in toys, making him an adorable troublemaker with a flair for exploring forbidden spaces.</media:description>
            <media:keywords>parrot,prince,video,Vancouver,Canada,cabinet,glass cups,mischief,forbidden,bird,arms,singing,dance,owner,fascination,toys,troublemaker,adorable,exploration,spaces</media:keywords>
            <media:city>Vancouver</media:city>
            <media:country>Canada</media:country>
            <media:regionCode>CA</media:regionCode>
           <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>      
            <media:category>Animals</media:category>
            <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
            <media:filmingDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2022</media:filmingDate>
            <guid>2464</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 19:57:10 GMT</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/1995213b-d46f-47c5-8db5-d1a01e5dc6f0.jpg" />
            <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/reuters-videos/bbb1d531-686d-4bbd-91af-70942a1796ae.mp4" />
            <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
            </item><item>
            <media:title>Disastrous auto repair mishap: Mercedes Benz plummets off forklift, front bumper lost!</media:title>
            <media:description>On July 1st, 2023, in Zhejiang province, China, @ObligationXingaoAutomobileMaintenance documented a shocking incident at their repair shop. A video captured the moment a damaged Mercedes Benz, which was being lifted off a tow truck using a forklift, tragically plummeted to the ground. The unfortunate incident resulted in the car's front bumper falling off, compounding the initial damage. The vehicle's owner had entrusted it to the shop for repairs, only to face an unexpected and costly setback.</media:description>
            <media:keywords>mercedes,benz,repair,shop,forklift,accident,tow,truck,bumper,damage,incident,china,zhejiang,province,automobile,maintenance,video,owner,mishap,investigation</media:keywords>
            <media:city> Zhejiang province</media:city>
            <media:country>China</media:country>
            <media:regionCode>CN</media:regionCode>
           <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>      
            <media:category>Fails and Funnies</media:category>
            <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
            <media:filmingDate>Sat, 1 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
            <guid>2463</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 19:31:50 GMT</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/d5e866e5-dda6-4e97-86bc-281fa1269e38.jpg" />
            <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/reuters-videos/cfb6a3e0-689e-4b01-b858-a78456a05117.mp4" />
            <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
            </item><item>
              <media:title>Heartwarming rescue: a father's swift response as baby takes a tumble in Quy Hoa Village, Vietnam</media:title>
              <media:description>In a heartwarming moment captured by @dungthiem on May 27th, 2023, in Quy Hoa Village, Vietnam, a baby's playful adventure took an unexpected turn. Seated on a stroller, the little one gleefully played with it until a sudden loss of balance caused the stroller to tip forward, making the baby fall. The scene unfolded in a flash, but the baby's caring father rushed to the rescue, swiftly picking him up and offering comforting words as tears flowed. The baby is fine.</media:description>
              <media:keywords>playful,baby,stroller,fall,balance,father,rush,rescue,comforting,tears,love,protection,parents,mishap,adorable,village,Vietnam,cute,family,parenting</media:keywords>
              <media:city>Quy Hoa Village, Yen Hoa Commune, Cam Xuyen District</media:city>
              <media:country>Vietnam</media:country>
              <media:regionCode>VN</media:regionCode>
              <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
              <media:category>Fails and Funnies</media:category>
              <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
              <media:filmingDate>Sat, 27 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
              <guid>2461</guid>
              <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 19:03:55 GMT</pubDate>
              <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/85e68d81-c06b-4e88-8e66-9cc0999d883c.jpg" />
              <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/reuters-videos/9db5c2da-14e3-42a7-b3cc-b2a1b11c897f.mp4" />
              <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
              </item><item>
              <media:title>Terrifying mishap: electric bike tumbles as tricycle's rope causes crash in Fujian Province, China</media:title>
              <media:description>In a startling incident captured on video by @-firstprizeontheway on February 24th, 2021, in Fujian province, Southeast China, an electric motorbike experienced a malfunction while driving. As it approached a crossing, a tricycle ahead of it had a hanging rope trailing behind. Suddenly, the rope entangled with the front wheel of the electric bike, causing the rider to lose balance and fall immediately. Fortunately, there were no reported injuries.</media:description>
              <media:keywords>electric,motorbike,malfunction,tricycle,rope,crash,video,Fujian,China,incident,crossing,entangled,rider,fall,danger,roads,balance,captured,southeast,no injuries</media:keywords>
              <media:city>Fujian province</media:city>
              <media:country>China</media:country>
              <media:regionCode>CN</media:regionCode>
              <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
              <media:category>Road accidents</media:category>
              <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
              <media:filmingDate>Wed, 24 Feb 2021</media:filmingDate>
              <guid>2460</guid>
              <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 14:40:16 GMT</pubDate>
              <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/bfa7daff-913c-403a-b5f7-022489eaf6a8.jpg" />
              <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/reuters-videos/134594c7-8706-4a92-b363-efc7ff63a6a0.mp4" />
              <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
              </item><item>
              <media:title>A serene stumble: when aesthetic dreams meet a slippery reality</media:title>
              <media:description>On July 9, 2023, in Malang city, Indonesia, a videographer known as @rikoclok_03 attempted to create an aesthetic video while walking on a wooden staircase surrounded by a lush green environment, holding a cup of his favorite drink. However, his intentions took an unexpected turn when the wet stairs caused him to tumble and fall. The man is fine.</media:description>
              <media:keywords>aesthetic,videographer,stairs,green,serene,environment,cup,drink,wet,tumble,fall,unexpected,mishap,life,pursuit,beauty,nature,unpredictable,reminder,video</media:keywords>
              <media:city>Malang city</media:city>
              <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
              <media:regionCode>ID</media:regionCode>
              <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
              <media:category>Fails and Funnies</media:category>
              <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
              <media:filmingDate>Sun, 9 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
              <guid>2459</guid>
              <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 14:20:14 GMT</pubDate>
              <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/28e4b2a9-2348-499f-b358-ab650cf0b358.jpg" />
              <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/reuters-videos/c086ef1c-a234-4962-8c26-3db0cefc8493.mp4" />
              <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
              </item><item>
            <media:title>Birthday cake ambush: raccoon Patrick's sweet greed unleashed!</media:title>
            <media:description>In a hilarious yet mischievous scene, @raccoon.patrick, on May 14th, 2023, in Dnipro, Ukraine, captured a video that showcased their raccoon, Patrick, in action. It was his birthday, and to celebrate, a delicious cake had been prepared for the guests. However, Patrick couldn't resist the temptation, and with nimble paws, he skillfully  began clawing at the cake with pure greed.</media:description>
            <media:keywords>cake,raccoon,Patrick,birthday,video,Dnipro,Ukraine,mischief,celebration,temptation,guests,clawing,nimble,cunning,playful,curiosity,appetite,funny,adorable,animals</media:keywords>
            <media:city>Dnipro</media:city>
            <media:country>Ukraine</media:country>
            <media:regionCode>UA</media:regionCode>
           <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>      
            <media:category>Animals</media:category>
            <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
            <media:filmingDate>Sun, 14 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
            <guid>2457</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 06:01:41 GMT</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/c93dd98d-7b83-4b15-83f4-e8c57bf3cdb6.jpg" />
            <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/reuters-videos/b08f04f3-c5f0-4257-a49b-ef727ffa435d.mp4" />
            <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
            </item><item>
            <media:title>Tenacious ferret's persistent pursuit: the wallet heist in Bytom, Poland</media:title>
            <media:description>In a quirky incident captured by @ferret_fred on May 20, 2023, in Bytom, Poland, a mischievous ferret showcased its determined nature. The video shows the furry little creature retrieving a wallet from the top of a counter. According to the author, her ferret has a penchant for collecting things under the bed, and that day, it stumbled upon her boyfriend's wallet. Despite her efforts to return the wallet to its original position, the persistent ferret insisted on stealing it repeatedly.</media:description>
            <media:keywords>ferret,pet,Poland,Bytom,video,wallet,theft,mischievous,determined,collect,under,bed,boyfriend,persistent,stubborn,amusing,cute,curious,animal,hunt</media:keywords>
            <media:city>Bytom</media:city>
            <media:country>Poland</media:country>
            <media:regionCode>PL</media:regionCode>
           <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>      
            <media:category>Animals</media:category>
            <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
            <media:filmingDate>Sat, 20 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
            <guid>2456</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 05:47:05 GMT</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/25bac6f5-44dc-4a56-b291-1806ab4753ac.jpg" />
            <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/reuters-videos/2e7b3ad0-8708-4523-87df-2eb32974bace.mp4" />
            <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
            </item><item>
              <media:title>Miraculous animal bond: minke whale saves ailing boar in Saint Petersburg region</media:title>
              <media:description>In a heartwarming incident captured on video by @PavelGlazkov in the Priozersky district of the Leningrad region, Russia on June 27th, 2023, a boar found itself in distress, struggling to stand on its feet. Its mother sensed the urgency and immediately took action, giving her ailing piglet a massage around the heart area with her sinewy heel. Despite her efforts, the baby showed no signs of life. However, a surprising turn of events unfolded as another minke whale rushed to the scene and took over the care. This compassionate whale diligently massaged the body of its sibling, and astonishingly, the piglet regained consciousness. Without hesitation, the piglet resumed eating, showcasing the remarkable bond between animals and their capacity for empathy and aid in the most unexpected circumstances.

Credit to: https://t.me/kazdoytvaripopare</media:description>
              <media:keywords>boar,mother,massage,illness,consciousness,minke whale,Russia,Priozersky district,Leningrad region,baby,sibling,empathy,help,video,trap,heart,feet,eating,distress,remarkable,bond.</media:keywords>
              <media:city>Priozersky district of the Saint Petersburg region</media:city>
              <media:country>Russia</media:country>
              <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
              <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
              <media:category>Animals</media:category>
              <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
              <media:filmingDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
              <guid>2455</guid>
              <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 05:38:05 GMT</pubDate>
              <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/c239ec24-bc12-4273-a7eb-f9c3314253d5.jpg" />
              <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/reuters-videos/56995e0f-a867-4806-b13d-4e49326eb659.mp4" />
              <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
              </item><item>
            <media:title>Torrential thunderstorm turns Krasnodar streets into rivers as tractor battles flooding</media:title>
            <media:description>On July 8, 2023, Krasnodar, Russia experienced a severe thunderstorm accompanied by heavy rainfall that lasted over an hour. The downpour resulted in extensive flooding on the streets, parking lots, and even the Mega shopping center in neighboring Yablonovsky. The floodwaters turned many roads into fast-flowing rivers, leading to traffic disruptions and paralysis in some areas. In an attempt to mitigate the flooding, a tractor was seen valiantly collecting water from the inundated streets and channeling it away from the affected areas. </media:description>
            <media:keywords>storm,floods,Krasnodar,Russia,thunder,downpour,streets,cars,parking lots,Mega shopping center,Yablonovsky,rivers,traffic,paralyzed,tractor,water,waves,afternoon,July 8,2023</media:keywords>
            <media:city>Krasnodar</media:city>
            <media:country>Russia</media:country>
            <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
           <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>      
            <media:category>News</media:category>
            <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
            <media:filmingDate>Sat, 8 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
            <guid>2454</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 05:12:52 GMT</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/636aab4b-dbef-4f15-895c-2d903e2cacac.jpg" />
            <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/reuters-videos/6c85a31c-4a48-4382-937e-2109fbb3d7fd.mp4" />
            <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
            </item><item>
            <media:title>Thrilling river adventure: brother's epic wakeboarding stunt delights all!</media:title>
            <media:description>In an adrenaline-pumping video captured by @mr_valerian in Salihorsk, Belarus, on July 2nd, 2023, his brother showcased an impressive wakeboarding stunt. Tied to a car with a rope, he skillfully water-skied on the river near the road, all while avoiding potential hazards like posts along the way. As the video unfolds, it becomes apparent that the cable came close to catching on the posts, but @mr_valerian cleverly controlled the situation from the car's backseat, ensuring a smooth and exhilarating ride for his brother. Laughter and excitement filled the air as the brother stood up on the wakeboard, showcasing his enjoyment throughout the daring feat. With precise execution and a touch of thrill, the video captivated viewers worldwide, leaving them in awe of the daring waterskiing adventure.</media:description>
            <media:keywords>wakeboarding,river,stunt,car,rope,Belarus,adventure,water,road,posts,thrilling,excitement,laughter,skill,control,ride,video,brother,enjoy,daring</media:keywords>
            <media:city>Salihorsk</media:city>
            <media:country>Belarus</media:country>
            <media:regionCode>BY</media:regionCode>
           <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>      
            <media:category>Cool</media:category>
            <media:exclusivity>exclusive</media:exclusivity>
            <media:filmingDate>Sun, 2 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
            <guid>2453</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 04:51:15 GMT</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/36984f91-3c1e-4780-acb8-beb6d6764df9.jpg" />
            <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/reuters-videos/a23e4a2f-5d5c-4dd3-ae13-912b62094aca.mp4" />
            <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
            </item><item>
            <media:title>Massive blaze strikes Changzhou food processing factory</media:title>
            <media:description>On June 28th, 2023, a massive fire broke out in a food processing factory in Changzhou, China, causing thick smoke to billow from the scene and the fire to rapidly expand. @ChangzhouXinbeiPhysicalChemistryTeacher captured this video footage of the raging inferno while passing by the area. The cause of the fire is still under investigation, but officials have confirmed that there were no casualties resulting from the incident.</media:description>
            <media:keywords>fire,factory,changzhou,china,smoke,blaze,video,footage,accident,investigation,officials,casualties,inferno,nearby,raging,food,processing,thick,billowing,expanding</media:keywords>
            <media:city>Changzhou</media:city>
            <media:country>China</media:country>
            <media:regionCode>CN</media:regionCode>
           <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>      
            <media:category>News</media:category>
            <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
            <media:filmingDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
            <guid>2452</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2023 09:09:19 GMT</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/ba2676b5-b683-4842-b9c2-b654355ffb33.jpg" />
            <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/reuters-videos/05bb536e-919f-488a-a17c-d25c85473fe2.mp4" />
            <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
            </item><item>
            <media:title>Unusual playtime: fearless dog entertains itself with cockroach in Batangas, Philippines</media:title>
            <media:description>In a peculiar video captured by @chiquito_boy on May 2nd, 2023, in Batangas, Philippines, his brave and vaccinated dog can be seen engaging in an unexpected playtime activity. The footage shows the dog fearlessly interacting with a cockroach, seemingly amused by the tiny creature. While some viewers might find the sight unusual, the author assures that his dog's health is protected.</media:description>
            <media:keywords>playtime,video,dog,cockroach,Batangas,Philippines,brave,vaccinated,amusing,unusual,interaction,socialmedia,attention,netizens,reactions,unconventional,pet,insect,entertainment,curious,playful</media:keywords>
            <media:city>Batangas</media:city>
            <media:country>Philippines</media:country>
            <media:regionCode>PH</media:regionCode>
           <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>      
            <media:category>Animals</media:category>
            <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
            <media:filmingDate>Tue, 2 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
            <guid>2451</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2023 08:44:58 GMT</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/3c4e48dd-e74c-4d27-9bb2-dd67a3c154aa.jpg" />
            <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/reuters-videos/111d4bb3-af31-4b4c-a464-a8df3323a0b7.mp4" />
            <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
            </item><item>
            <media:title>Tuapse's mop-wielding heroine: the savior of a flooded city</media:title>
            <media:description>In the flooded city of Tuapse, Russia, a remarkable woman with nothing but a mop in hand emerged as a local hero on July 12th, 2023. Fearlessly standing in the water, she took it upon herself to clear the storm drain from debris, preventing further flooding in the area. Social media was abuzz with admiration for her courageous act, and a video capturing her determined efforts quickly gained attention online. Many hailed her as the savior of the city, and the mop became a symbol of her selflessness and resilience in the face of adversity.</media:description>
            <media:keywords>tuapse,russia,woman,mop,storm drain,debris,flooding,local,hero,social media,admiration,video,savior,courageous,water,city,fearless,selflessness,resilience,adversity</media:keywords>
            <media:city> Tuapse</media:city>
            <media:country>Russia</media:country>
            <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
           <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>      
            <media:category>News</media:category>
            <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
            <media:filmingDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
            <guid>2450</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2023 16:31:17 GMT</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/9b1d4d58-31cc-4c4c-8acd-0a47379bd97a.jpg" />
            <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/reuters-videos/965dcd39-02c6-4585-8ba4-d262a4b11429.mp4" />
            <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
            </item><item>
            <media:title>Enthusiastic equine: the joyful journey of Tosha, the Bashkir breed Macintosh horse</media:title>
            <media:description>In a heartwarming video captured by @mashak_b on May 4th, 2023, in Lobnya, Moscow, Russia, we witness an endearing moment between a skilled equestrian and his beloved horse, Tosha. The footage shows the author standing on a wooden stool as Tosha, a magnificent Bashkir breed Macintosh horse, gallops towards him with boundless enthusiasm. As the author reveals, this video showcases one of Tosha's favorite exercises, where he is asked to "park" at the end of their class. The genuine connection between the rider and his horse is evident, portraying the sheer joy and fulfillment that comes from this beautiful bond between man and equine companion.</media:description>
            <media:keywords>horse,video,Bashkir,Macintosh,Tosha,equestrian,enthusiasm,Moscow,Russia,Lobnya,wooden,stool,student,exercise,park,connection,rider,gallop,bond,joy,fulfillment</media:keywords>
            <media:city>Lobnya, Moscow</media:city>
            <media:country>Russia</media:country>
            <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
           <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>      
            <media:category>Animals</media:category>
            <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
            <media:filmingDate>Thu, 4 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
            <guid>2449</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2023 16:13:46 GMT</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/4d478e9e-fbb6-4a65-a9ca-e981b78a2bd5.jpg" />
            <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/reuters-videos/79af3797-87e5-4c2e-89ec-15e744c2b66d.mp4" />
            <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
            </item><item>
              <media:title>Shocking gas stove explosion sends diners scrambling at restaurant</media:title>
              <media:description>The video, shared by @a2tuinho100991 on September 9th, 2022, showcases the alarming moment when the gas stove malfunctioned, creating a chaotic scene inside the restaurant. In a startling incident captured on video, a gas stove exploded on a table at A Đạt Hot Pot Restaurant in Tra Vinh Province, Vietnam. The explosion occurred while people were seated at the table, enjoying their meal. The intense blast caused the diners to disperse rapidly in panic, seeking safety. All people are fine.</media:description>
              <media:keywords>explosion,gas stove,table,restaurant,Vietnam,diners,video,panic,safety,malfunction,chaos,incident,traumatic,startling,alarming,captured,shared,moment,scattered,meal</media:keywords>
              <media:city>Chau Thanh District, Tra Vinh Province</media:city>
              <media:country>Vietnam</media:country>
              <media:regionCode>VN</media:regionCode>
              <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
              <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
              <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
              <media:filmingDate>Fri, 9 Sep 2022</media:filmingDate>
              <guid>2448</guid>
              <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jul 2023 19:22:10 GMT</pubDate>
              <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/d1b7672c-f517-4cb7-8e7c-9a3f718d6dbb.jpg" />
              <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/reuters-videos/db06829b-922b-4154-a386-8a4f37d50068.mp4" />
              <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
              </item><item>
            <media:title>Joyful moments: a bubble-filled performance by a talented young star</media:title>
            <media:description>In a heartwarming video captured by @artem_pedan on May 14th, 2023, in Moscow, Russia, a young boy's love for blowing bubbles and acting shines through. The short clip showcases the child's delightful playfulness as he combines both passions into one enchanting performance. With bubbles floating in the air around him, the young star takes center stage, bringing a sense of joy and wonder to viewers.</media:description>
            <media:keywords>bubbles,son,video,Moscow,Russia,play,actor,capture,joy,childhood,happiness,performance,enchanting,delightful,love,playful,moment,simplicity,pleasure,wonder</media:keywords>
            <media:city> Moscow</media:city>
            <media:country>Russia</media:country>
            <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
           <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>      
            <media:category>Heartwarming</media:category>
            <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
            <media:filmingDate>Sun, 14 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
            <guid>2447</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jul 2023 19:00:54 GMT</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/dcc591ad-6682-4db8-bfda-7de1054a8add.jpg" />
            <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/reuters-videos/54d9a1f4-e6af-4db4-9397-01c4fb07011d.mp4" />
            <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
            </item><item>
            <media:title>Devastating tornado strikes Barrhaven, Ottawa: homes damaged, power outages reported</media:title>
            <media:description>A powerful tornado struck the suburban area of Barrhaven in Ottawa, Canada, on July 13th, 2023, causing significant damage to homes and leaving a trail of destruction. A video captured by @TheShagtor showed the tornado trying to form near his house. David Sills, the executive director of the Northern Tornadoes Project, confirmed the tornado's occurrence, which hit approximately 25 kilometers south of downtown Ottawa. Reports indicated that around 125 homes in the affected area suffered various degrees of damage, ranging from roofs being torn off to broken windows and downed trees. Moreover, approximately 1,600 homes were left without power, with concerns of potential gas leaks due to the destruction. The impact of the tornado left residents in shock and authorities working diligently to restore normalcy and provide assistance to those affected by the incident.</media:description>
            <media:keywords>tornado,barrhaven,ottawa,canada,damage,homes,destruction,power outages,gas leaks,emergency,assistance,suburb,roofs,windows,trees,devastation,residents,authorities,recovery,Northern Tornadoes Project</media:keywords>
            <media:city>Barrhaven </media:city>
            <media:country>Canada</media:country>
            <media:regionCode>CA</media:regionCode>
           <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>      
            <media:category>News</media:category>
            <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
            <media:filmingDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
            <guid>2444</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jul 2023 12:35:11 GMT</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/eb78110f-e301-42a2-983f-0e3e94641f4f.jpg" />
            <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/reuters-videos/34c09519-3bae-4624-8eb7-a1df885390ac.mp4" />
            <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
            </item></channel>
           </rss>