<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
            <rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
            xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
            xmlns:openSearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearchrss/1.0/"
            xmlns:dfpvideo="http://api.google.com/dfpvideo"
            xmlns:tms="http://data.tmsapi.com/v1.1"
            version="2.0">
              <channel>
                <title>ViralBear videos</title>
                <dfpvideo:version>2</dfpvideo:version>
                  
                        <item>
                          <media:title>gf</media:title>
                          <media:description>gfd Credit to: fgd</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>g</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>gfd</media:city>
                          <media:country>American Samoa</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>AS</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>ODD</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Road accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>exclusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Wed, 8 Nov 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>3268</guid>
                          <pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 16:39:52 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear2.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/3268.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear2.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/3268.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 19:09:03 GMT</dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Motorbike accident in Zhejiang, China: nighttime tumble due to uneven road surface</media:title>
                          <media:description>In Zhejiang province, China, a motorbike accident was captured on video by @autobots on October 3, 2023. The incident occurred at night when the motorcyclist lost control and toppled on an uneven road surface. @autobots, who was driving home at the time, quickly stopped to check on the injured man. Fortunately, the motorcyclist only sustained minor trauma, and there was no imminent danger. The accident was attributed to the combination of the poor road conditions and reduced visibility typical of nighttime travel.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>night,accident,motorbike,Zhejiang,China,uneven road,trauma,@autobots,video,topple,safety,incident,driver,visibility,October 3,2023,man,no fluff,car,observation</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Zhejiang province</media:city>
                          <media:country>China</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>CN</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Road accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Tue, 3 Oct 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>3258</guid>
                          <pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2023 13:23:05 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/3258.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/3258.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Electric bike accident in Chongqing: woman loses control, falls into ditch, promptly aided</media:title>
                          <media:description>In a recent incident captured on camera by @DistrictMahei0902 on September 2, 2023, in Chongqing, southwest China, a woman on an electric bike lost control while approaching an intersection and fell into a nearby ditch. Startled by the sudden appearance of another motorbike in her path, the woman failed to make a turn, let out a scream, and ended up in the ditch near a house. Swiftly, bystanders in the area rushed to her aid, and she was subsequently taken to a nearby hospital for treatment. Fortunately, her injuries were minor, and she is expected to recover.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>accident,electric bike,Chongqing,China,video,woman,ditch,intersection,road,vehicle,fall,scream,aid,hospital,minor injuries,recovery,bystanders,incident,capture,September 2023</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Chongqing</media:city>
                          <media:country>China</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>CN</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Road accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Sat, 2 Sep 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>3230</guid>
                          <pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2023 05:22:07 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/3230.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/3230.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Motorcycle collision caught on camera in Chongqing, China</media:title>
                          <media:description>On August 10, 2023, in Chongqing, Southwest China, a harrowing incident was captured by @LaoLiu'smotorcycletraveldiary as he and his wife were driving home. While a vehicle was navigating a bend ahead of them, a motorcycle traveling from the opposite direction collided with it, sending the motorcycle careening towards their car. The video records the spine-chilling moment when @LaoLiu'swife's terrified screams filled the air as the motorcycle made impact with the front of their car. The motorcyclist is fine.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>accident,motorcycle,car,collision,video,Chongqing,China,incident,travel,journey,wife,screaming,impact,harrowing,unexpected,@LaoLiu'smotorcycletraveldiary,bend,front,stop,moment</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Chongqing</media:city>
                          <media:country>China</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>CN</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Road accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>3226</guid>
                          <pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2023 05:18:49 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/3226.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/3226.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Highway collision: parked car leads to accident in Guangdong, China</media:title>
                          <media:description>In an incident captured by a dash camera on August 25, 2023, in Guangdong province, China, a driver, known as @WaiteratZiyungeStore, found themselves in a harrowing situation when a white car suddenly appeared ahead in their lane. Despite slowing down, a collision with the parked car on the side was inevitable. @WaiteratZiyungeStore recounted that the car in front had struck the guard rail, forcing its occupants to evacuate. However, crucial safety precautions such as warning signs and activated flashers and lights were neglected, rendering the parked car nearly invisible and leading to the unfortunate accident.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>collision,dashcam,incident,highway,Guangdong,China,accident,warning,lights,safety,parked car,visibility,evacuation,driver,white car,guard rail,unexpected,hazard,traffic,negligence</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Guangdong province</media:city>
                          <media:country>China</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>CN</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Road accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Fri, 25 Aug 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>3218</guid>
                          <pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 14:39:52 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/3218.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/3218.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Drunk Mercedes driver causes 7-car pileup in Tyumen city center</media:title>
                          <media:description>In a shocking incident on August 21, 2023, in Tyumen, Russia, a drunk Mercedes driver triggered a chaotic chain of events, resulting in a massive seven-car pileup in the heart of the city. The incident unfolded around noon, near Sovetskaya Street's 124th house, when the intoxicated driver of a Mercedes ML350 collided with a Lexus, Renault, Datsun, Toyota, and two Mitsubishi vehicles. Disturbing footage captured the Mercedes ramming into multiple cars, alternately moving forward and reversing. The reckless collision left the Mercedes driver injured, leaving a trail of destruction on one of Tyumen's central streets.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>accident,drunk,Mercedes,Tyumen,Russia,collision,chaos,cars,Sovetskaya,street,pileup,Lexus,Renault,Datsun,Toyota,Mitsubishi,driver,injuries,central,footage</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Tyumen</media:city>
                          <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Accidents,Road accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>3154</guid>
                          <pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2023 14:24:46 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/3154.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/3154.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 03:14:41 GMT</dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Teenagers deliberately hit child on bicycle in Dagestan, driver detained</media:title>
                          <media:description>In a shocking incident in the Dagestan village of Agachaul, Russia, on September 22, 2023, two teenagers driving a Zhiguli car intentionally struck a boy who was riding his bicycle on the street. The young men believed that the child had obstructed their path and decided to take revenge. Surveillance cameras captured the disturbing scene, showing the Lada car catching up to the boy on the bicycle, then reversing to deliberately hit him. Hours later, the victim's relatives located the perpetrators and set their car on fire. The regional Ministry of Internal Affairs confirmed the deliberate nature of the attack and detained the driver, who turned out to be a 16-year-old teenager. Investigations are ongoing to establish the full circumstances of this harrowing incident.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>teenagers,incident,Dagestan,Russia,village,Agachaul,bicycle,hit,revenge,surveillance,video,car,deliberate,detain,driver,child,shocked,relatives,investigation,authorities</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Dagestan</media:city>
                          <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Road accidents,News</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>3122</guid>
                          <pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 19:07:39 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/3122.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/3122.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Moscow resident's reckless tire burnout nearly engulfs car in flames</media:title>
                          <media:description>On September 24, 2023, in Moscow, Russia, a shocking video surfaced showing a car engulfed in flames as its owner engaged in a conversation with a group of individuals while parked. The incident began with ominous plumes of smoke billowing from the vehicle's rear, quickly followed by roaring flames. Instead of evacuating the scene, the car's owner astonishingly decided to reverse the vehicle and drive away, all while the rear end of the car was ablaze. What initially appeared to be a daredevil tire-burning spectacle by a Moscow resident, designed to impress friends, nearly resulted in the complete destruction of his own car, aptly named Podem. Fortunately, the situation was brought under control by the prompt intervention of the Ministry of Emergency Situations.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>car,flames,video,Moscow,Russia,incident,smoke,reckless,owner,conversation,emergency,situation,tire,friends,resident,rear,reverse,burnout,Ministry,Podem</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Moscow</media:city>
                          <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Road accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>3119</guid>
                          <pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 19:05:20 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/3119.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/3119.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Terrifying moment: Fuso truck's uncontrolled roll-off on Bukittinggi highway</media:title>
                          <media:description>A dramatic incident unfolded on September 15, 2023, along the Bukittinggi highway in the Badukuang New area of Lembah Anai, X Koto District, Tanah Datar Regency, Indonesia. A Fuso truck and driven by Ismanto, aged 40, from Padang, suffered a brake malfunction while en route from Padang Panjang to Padang. The truck careened into a roadside wall before colliding with a Toyota Avanza, driven by Indra, aged 57, from Limapuluh cities. Following the impact, the Fuso truck came to a halt on the left lane of the road, and its engine was turned off. Fortunately, there were no casualties, although the truck driver sustained minor injuries. The incident was captured on video by @septianiniii, showing the truck's uncontrolled movement leading to its roll-off. Both vehicles involved sustained damage as a result of the accident. </media:description>
                          <media:keywords>accident,truck,video,Bukittinggi,highway,Indonesia,Fuso,crash,driver,Toyota,Avanza,collision,brakes,damage,injuries,Padang,Panjang,Lembah,Anai,traffic</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>X koto District, Tanah Datar Regency</media:city>
                          <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>ID</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Road accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>exclusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>3067</guid>
                          <pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2023 09:28:38 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/3067.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/3067.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>10-year-old girl hit by car while crossing street at controlled pedestrian crossing in Krasnoyarsk, Russia</media:title>
                          <media:description>On the evening of August 13, 2023, a tragic incident unfolded on Krasnodarskaya Street in Krasnoyarsk, Russia, as a 10-year-old girl was struck by a Toyota car. Surveillance footage revealed that the young girl had been attempting to cross the road at a controlled pedestrian crossing, although the specific traffic light signal remains unspecified. Tragically, the impact of the collision sent the girl flying several meters, leading to her hospitalization. The driver, a 36-year-old individual, was captured on the surveillance camera. Authorities from the traffic police department are currently investigating the circumstances surrounding this unfortunate incident.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>accident,girl,car,crossing,street,Krasnoyarsk,Russia,surveillance,footage,hospitalization,driver,investigation,tragic,incident,pedestrian,traffic,controlled,evening,impact,circumstances</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Krasnoyarsk</media:city>
                          <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Road accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>3043</guid>
                          <pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2023 09:41:26 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/3043.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/3043.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Near miss: pedestrian narrowly escapes truck collision in Krasnoyarsk, Russia</media:title>
                          <media:description>In a heart-stopping incident near Krasnoyarsk, Russia, on September 11, 2023, a pedestrian narrowly escaped a catastrophic collision with a multi-ton truck. The harrowing moment was captured on video as the truck careened off the road, hurtling towards the pedestrian at high speed. Miraculously, the pedestrian managed to evade the oncoming disaster just in the nick of time. The truck, however, plowed through a fence and tumbled into a ditch, severing a power line and overturning in the process. The video footage shows the truck's cab detaching from the rest of the vehicle as it veered off the road. The fate of the truck's driver remains uncertain. </media:description>
                          <media:keywords>miracle,pedestrian,truck,collision,Krasnoyarsk,Russia,accident,near miss,escape,video,dramatic,danger,road,power line,overturn,witness,shocking,lucky,survival,uncertainty</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Krasnoyarsk</media:city>
                          <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Road accidents,News</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>3037</guid>
                          <pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2023 12:25:37 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/3037.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/3037.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Motorcycle rider's risky gamble leads to collision with car on Hanoi's La Thanh road</media:title>
                          <media:description>In a startling dash cam footage captured by @ducanhdo6991 on August 7, 2023, on La Thanh Road in Hanoi, Vietnam, a motorcycle rider with a passenger learned a harsh lesson in road safety. Ignoring an oncoming car, the rider proceeded to cross the road, seemingly assuming that the larger vehicle would yield. Unfortunately, their assumption proved costly as the car collided with the motorcycle, causing the riders to tumble onto the road. The people is fine.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>collision,road,motorcycle,car,accident,safety,risk,assumption,dashcam,video,incident,Hanoi,Vietnam,riders,passengers,traffic,consequences,reminder,caution,awareness</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Dong Da District, Hanoi</media:city>
                          <media:country>Vietnam</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>VN</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Road accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Mon, 7 Aug 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>3030</guid>
                          <pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2023 09:10:08 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/3030.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/3030.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Miraculous escape: two survive terrifying car crash in Pavlovsky Posad</media:title>
                          <media:description>In a harrowing incident on the evening of August 20, 2023, Pavlovsky Posad, Russia, witnessed a serious accident that left bystanders in awe of the miraculous outcome. The accident occurred on Kirova Street, number 19, when the driver of a foreign car lost control while navigating a turn, leading to the vehicle overturning. Eyewitnesses reported a terrifying scene as the driver was ejected through the windshield due to the force of the impact. Surveillance footage captured the car careening at high speed, striking a curb, and landing upside down on the road. Fortunately, the fate seemed to smile upon all those involved, as there were no other vehicles or pedestrians in the vicinity at the time. Concerned passers-by rushed to the scene and, remarkably, found that none of the individuals in the car had sustained serious injuries.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>accident,pavlovsky posad,russia,car,crash,eyewitnesses,driver,control,turn,overturn,impact,pavement,speed,curb,roadway,fortunate,bystanders,help,motorists,injuries</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Pavlovsky Posad</media:city>
                          <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Road accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>3010</guid>
                          <pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2023 08:17:14 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/3010.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/3010.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Shocking hit-and-run incident: police officer attacked by fleeing van</media:title>
                          <media:description>In a startling incident that unfolded on the evening of September 3, 2023, in the Kovrovsky district of Russia, a shocking video capturing the moment of a brazen attack on a police officer has emerged on social media. The footage reveals a blue van forcefully ramming into a police officer who was standing near a patrol car, before speeding away from the scene. The Kovrov police have declined to provide any immediate comments on the audacious crime. However, the Investigative Committee for the Vladimir region swiftly initiated a criminal case for the use of violence dangerous to life or health against a government official. The alleged driver of the GAZelle involved in the incident is reported to be a 39-year-old Kovrov resident, and an intensive investigation is currently underway to apprehend the perpetrator and bring them to justice.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>police,incident,Russia,attack,video,criminal,ramming,Kovrov,officer,assault,investigation,social,media,shocking,van,flee,government,dangerous,life,health</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Kovrovsky district</media:city>
                          <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>News,Road accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Sun, 3 Sep 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>2954</guid>
                          <pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 11:58:28 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2954.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2954.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Chaotic journey: van passenger tumbles amidst treacherous roads</media:title>
                          <media:description>In a remarkable yet concerning incident captured on July 11, 2023, by @kristin_laolii, a video surfaced from Hunogoa Village in the Nias Regency of North Sumatra, Indonesia. The footage depicts a perilous journey as a van navigates severely damaged roads, causing a dramatic sequence of events. Amidst a group of seated men in the back of the van, the bumpy terrain proves to be a formidable challenge. As the van maneuvers its way along the  route, one unfortunate passenger is jolted out and tumbles to the ground. The incident not only sheds light on the daunting road conditions that persist in the region, causing congestion and difficulties for all kinds of vehicles, but also serves as a vivid reminder of the risks and hardships faced by those traveling through these treacherous pathways.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>bumpy,village,incident,van,roads,journey,passenger,video,Nias,Sumatra,Indonesia,congestion,damaged,challenge,treacherous,travel,route,jolted,hardships,terrain</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Hunogoa Village, Nias Regency, North Sumatra</media:city>
                          <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>ID</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Road accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>exclusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>2834</guid>
                          <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 10:34:57 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2834.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2834.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Child hit by a car in Tver: surveillance footage captures the accident in Brusilovo microdistrict</media:title>
                          <media:description>In a distressing incident on the evening of August 22, 2023, a child was struck by a foreign car in the Brusilovo microdistrict of Tver, Russia. The accident occurred near house number 33 on Osnabrückskaya Street, where a Volkswagen Polo collided with a young girl. The heart-wrenching moment was captured by surveillance cameras, revealing the driver's car navigating through the parking lot when the child suddenly emerged from behind parked vehicles, crossing paths with the moving vehicle. Swift action was taken as an ambulance rushed to the scene promptly. The injured child was immediately transported to the Tver Children's Clinical Hospital for medical attention. </media:description>
                          <media:keywords>accident,child,car,Tver,Russia,Brusilovo,microdistrict,Volkswagen,Polo,surveillance,footage,parking,ambulance,hospital,injured,girl,residential,caution,vigilance,pedestrians</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Brusilovo microdistrict</media:city>
                          <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Road accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>2833</guid>
                          <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 12:36:54 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2833.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2833.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Miraculous escape: four-year-old girl survives after being hit by car in Tavda, Russia</media:title>
                          <media:description>In a heart-stopping incident on July 30, 2023, in Tavda, Russia, a four-year-old girl narrowly escaped a potentially tragic accident after being hit by a KIA RIO car. The young child had been engrossed in picking apples along the roadside, a mere 70 meters away from her home. Unaware of the approaching danger, she suddenly darted across the road without checking for oncoming vehicles. The driver of the car, who recounted the harrowing event, recounted his desperate attempts to avoid the collision, turning the steering wheel and slamming the brakes. Despite his efforts, the impact was inevitable. Fortunately, the girl emerged with minor abrasions, and following a thorough medical examination, she was deemed fit to return home. </media:description>
                          <media:keywords>apples,accident,Tavda,Russia,KIA RIO,child,roadside,escape,abrasions,examination,doctors,driver,collision,Ministry of Internal Affairs,miraculous,survival,vigilance,road safety,incident,afternoon</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Tavda</media:city>
                          <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Road accidents,News</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>2787</guid>
                          <pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2023 09:28:01 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2787.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2787.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Pedestrian collision in Novosibirsk: heroic first aid after impact and controversial driver reaction</media:title>
                          <media:description>In an unsettling incident on July 26, 2023, in Novosibirsk, Russia, a pedestrian's reckless attempt to cross the road ended in a powerful collision that left him unconscious and injured. Ignoring the oncoming traffic, the pedestrian dashed across the road without caution, only to be struck by a vehicle coming from the opposite direction. The impact sent him flying, and he crashed into a parked car along the roadside. Swift action from his companion prevented further harm, as the friend promptly dragged the injured pedestrian to the sidewalk and administered initial first aid. However, tensions escalated as the driver of the vehicle that was hit expressed indignation over the incident. The injured pedestrian was subsequently rushed to the hospital, his current condition remaining uncertain. </media:description>
                          <media:keywords>collision,pedestrian,injuries,reckless,road,traffic,vehicle,impact,flying,parked car,companion,first aid,tension,hospital,driver,indignation,caution,risks,negligence</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Novosibirsk</media:city>
                          <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Road accidents,News</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>2776</guid>
                          <pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2023 13:40:50 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2776.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2776.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Motorcyclist injured in Volgograd collision after running red light</media:title>
                          <media:description>On July 26, 2023, in the Krasnoarmeisky district of Volgograd, Russia, a motorcyclist sustained injuries following a collision at the intersection of Lazorevaya and Kuibyshev streets. The accident took place around 12:10 am when the motorcyclist proceeded through the intersection against a red traffic light, resulting in a collision with a Kia car. According to the Main Directorate of the Ministry of Internal Affairs for the Volgograd Region, the injured motorcyclist was promptly transported to a local hospital for medical treatment. </media:description>
                          <media:keywords>accident,motorcyclist,injured,collision,intersection,traffic light,Kia car,Volgograd,Russia,Krasnoarmeisky district,Lazorevaya,Kuibyshev streets,hospital,injuries,red light,road safety,Ministry of Internal Affairs,regulations,traffic,incident</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Volgograd</media:city>
                          <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Road accidents,News</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>2767</guid>
                          <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 11:30:41 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2767.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2767.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Shocking dashcam footage captures motorcycle collision with pedestrian in Shanxi Province</media:title>
                          <media:description>In a startling incident captured by @TrafficSafetyeveryday's dashboard camera on June 1, 2023, in Shanxi Province, China, a pedestrian narrowly escaped serious injury as he was struck by a speeding motorcycle while crossing an intersection. The video footage shows the man attempting to cross near the parked vehicle when a motorbike from the opposite direction suddenly accelerates, colliding with him. Although the impact left the man slightly injured, the incident serves as a reminder of the importance of road safety and cautious driving.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>accident,intersection,pedestrian,motorcycle,collision,dashcam,video,incident,speeding,injury,road,safety,crossing,parked car,footage,impact,caution,reminder,China,Shanxi</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Shanxi Province </media:city>
                          <media:country>China</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>CN</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Road accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Thu, 1 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>2707</guid>
                          <pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 09:42:56 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2707.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2707.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Caught on camera: unmasking guilt - a tale of a Zhejiang car accident</media:title>
                          <media:description>On a seemingly routine evening drive home on May 22, 2023, in Zhejiang Province, China, the driver unwittingly became a witness to a dramatic car accident. As he navigated the streets after a day's work, he turned left onto a side street, passing through an intersection. Abruptly, his attention was drawn to a car on the right that misjudged its turn, resulting in a forceful collision with a small truck ahead and subsequently careening into a nearby tree. Reacting swiftly, the author sounded his horn in a futile attempt to alert the car's driver. What followed was a clash of perspectives, as the driver initially refused culpability. It wasn't until traffic authorities arrived, scrutinized the author's recorded video evidence, and meticulously reconstructed the sequence of events that the truth emerged. </media:description>
                          <media:keywords>accident,witness,video,collision,intersection,driver,responsibility,traffic,rules,evidence,technology,dispute,authority,perspective,vehicle,tree,evening,Zhejiang,China</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Zhejiang Province </media:city>
                          <media:country>China</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>CN</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Road accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Mon, 22 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>2705</guid>
                          <pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 09:39:30 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2705.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2705.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Miraculous escape: child unhurt as Lada Xray collides with bicycle and Subaru in Yekaterinburg</media:title>
                          <media:description>In a heart-stopping incident on July 13, 2023, in Yekaterinburg, Russia, a young boy on a bicycle narrowly escaped serious harm after being struck by a "Lada Xray" car. The accident occurred when the child unexpectedly entered the roadway of a residential passage. The collision mangled he bike, and the child tumbled to the pavement. However, by some stroke of luck, the child emerged from the ordeal without any injuries. Following the initial collision, the "Lada Xray" then careened into a parked Subaru, causing additional damage. Surprisingly, despite the severity of the accident, the city traffic police revealed that no one had reported the incident to them. Authorities are urging witnesses to come forward to assist with their investigation into the unsettling incident.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>bicycle,accident,Yekaterinburg,Russia,Lada Xray,boy,roadway,yard,passage,collision,Subaru,traffic,police,injury,bike,pavement,luck,witnesses,investigation,damage</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Yekaterinburg</media:city>
                          <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Road accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>2634</guid>
                          <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 07:56:33 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2634.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2634.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Traffic police car collides with child in Bataysk, Russia: investigation underway</media:title>
                          <media:description>In an unfortunate incident on July 11, 2023, in Bataysk, Russia, a young boy was involved in a collision with a traffic police patrol car on Slavy Street, 7. The incident was caught on video by residents of the house and shared on social media. The footage shows the child being knocked down but managing to get back up and limping in shock towards the entrance of the house. Surprisingly, the inspector driving the patrol car did not approach the child after the accident but instead returned to the driver's seat. The Main Directorate of the Ministry of Internal Affairs of Russia for the Rostov Region stated that the child, born in 2014, suddenly ran out onto the road due to parked vehicles. An investigation into the circumstances surrounding the incident is currently underway.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>accident,bataysk,russia,boy,traffic,police,patrol,car,video,social,media,collision,pedestrian,investigation,shock,limping,entrance,inspector,parked,vehicles</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Bataysk</media:city>
                          <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Road accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>2628</guid>
                          <pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 14:02:51 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2628.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2628.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Reckless white SUV causes collision with street light: violation of traffic rules in Jiangxi Province, China</media:title>
                          <media:description>In Jiangxi Province, China, a recent traffic incident captured on video by @Jiangxitrafficpolice has brought attention to the dangers of reckless driving. On June 15, 2023, a driver was maneuvering their vehicle along a normal route when disaster struck. As they passed an uphill section, a white SUV suddenly appeared, overtaking on the hill and violating traffic regulations. The video shows the desperate attempt of the driver to avoid the SUV, but tragically, they collided with a street light post instead. The footage clearly highlights the white SUV's failure to adhere to road rules as the main cause of the accident. As a result, no one was hurt.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>accident,video,traffic,jiangxi,china,collision,streetlight,SUV,overtaking,hill,regulations,responsible,driving,safety,road,incident,reckless,footage,violation,driver</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Jiangxi</media:city>
                          <media:country>China</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>CN</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Road accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>2625</guid>
                          <pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 13:59:40 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2625.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2625.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Unusual collision in Jiangsu: scooters smile and carry on despite impact at crossing</media:title>
                          <media:description>In a peculiar incident captured by @trafficsafetyeveryday in Jiangsu Province, China, on July 24, 2023, two motorists collided in front of a moving car at a crossing area. The collision involved a woman driving an electric scooter and a delivery rider, both also on electric scooters. Surprisingly, despite the impact, the two parties showed an unexpected reaction. Instead of anger and frustration, they exchanged smiles after checking for injuries and continued on their way. The scene left the author intrigued, leading them to save the video. The incident serves as a unique reminder of how even in the midst of accidents, a moment of understanding and positivity can arise on the roads.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>collision,motorists,Jiangsu,China,video,crossing,traffic lights,electric bicycles,delivery rider,interesting,smile,accident,understanding,positivity,roads,@trafficsafetyeveryday,July 24,2023,intriguing,motorists,movement</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Jiangsu</media:city>
                          <media:country>China</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>CN</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Road accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>2624</guid>
                          <pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 13:57:46 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2624.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2624.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Friend's car narrowly avoids major collision with large truck on rural road in Heilongjiang Province</media:title>
                          <media:description>In a heart-stopping incident captured by @trafficsafetyeveryday on July 20, 2023, in Heilongjiang Province, China, a group of friends experienced a harrowing moment while driving to the countryside. As they were passing through a rural road, their friend's car, positioned in front of the author's vehicle, collided with the body of a large truck. The tense situation unfolded when the truck abruptly slammed on its brakes, causing the vehicle to lose control and veer towards the back of the truck. Fortunately, luck was on their side as the collision was not as severe as it could have been, considering it occurred just as they were nearly past each other. No harm done.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>accident,traffic,safety,video,friends,car,truck,collision,countryside,rural,road,Heilongjiang,China,brake,control,closecall,tense,vigilance,luck,reminder</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Heilongjiang Province</media:city>
                          <media:country>China</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>CN</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Road accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>2623</guid>
                          <pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 13:55:37 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2623.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2623.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Teenage AVM scooter crash at intersection in Ust-Izhora, St. Petersburg: investigation underway</media:title>
                          <media:description>In Ust-Izhora, St. Petersburg, Russia, on Thursday, June 29th, a collision occurred at the intersection of Pushkinskaya and Truda streets involving a teenager on an AVM scooter and a Nissan X-Treil driven by a 32-year-old woman. The young driver of the scooter failed to yield, resulting in the crash. Both the 16-year-old driver and their passenger sustained injuries and were taken to the hospital in moderate condition. The incident is currently under investigation to establish the exact circumstances of the accident.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>accident,scooter,Nissan,crash,intersection,Ust-Izhora,StPetersburg,Russia,teenager,AVM,give-way,injured,hospitalized,moderate,LenTV24,footage,investigation,circumstances,driver,passenger</media:keywords>
                          <media:city> Ust-Izhora, St. Petersburg</media:city>
                          <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Road accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>2469</guid>
                          <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/b29c594a-ed6e-410b-9258-195d1f1c3738.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/56a84566-7776-482c-8306-c2d628df9b0f.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Terrifying mishap: electric bike tumbles as tricycle's rope causes crash in Fujian Province, China</media:title>
                          <media:description>In a startling incident captured on video by @-firstprizeontheway on February 24th, 2021, in Fujian province, Southeast China, an electric motorbike experienced a malfunction while driving. As it approached a crossing, a tricycle ahead of it had a hanging rope trailing behind. Suddenly, the rope entangled with the front wheel of the electric bike, causing the rider to lose balance and fall immediately. Fortunately, there were no reported injuries.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>electric,motorbike,malfunction,tricycle,rope,crash,video,Fujian,China,incident,crossing,entangled,rider,fall,danger,roads,balance,captured,southeast,no injuries</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Fujian province</media:city>
                          <media:country>China</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>CN</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Road accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Wed, 24 Feb 2021</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>2460</guid>
                          <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/bfa7daff-913c-403a-b5f7-022489eaf6a8.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/99d13db4-ce82-4971-b19b-9f6c5bf826a5.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Caught on camera: motorcyclist launches violent attack on driver in Orenburg collision</media:title>
                          <media:description>In a shocking incident captured by surveillance cameras on Br. Khusainov Street in Orenburg, Russia, on 8th June, 2023 a heated confrontation between a motorcyclist and a driver unfolded after a collision involving their vehicles. The footage reveals that the driver of a Lada car had accidentally bumped into one of the motorcycles, prompting him to step out of his vehicle to address the situation. However, within seconds, another motorcyclist launched a vicious attack on the driver, escalating the situation into a violent altercation.

Despite the intervention attempts of other motorists present at the scene, their efforts to separate the two individuals proved futile, and the confrontation continued to escalate. The other motorists left the motorcyclist and the driver to their own devices. They later stopped fighting on their own.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>fight,surveillance,cameras,motorcyclist,driver,collision,Lada,attack,confrontation,altercation,violence,intervention,motorists,onlookers,dispersal,investigation,incident,dangers,calm,justice</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Orenburg</media:city>
                          <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Road accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Thu, 8 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>2232</guid>
                          <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 16:50:37 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/ad328bc5-13a6-445c-abce-5e39217bc3c9.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2232.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Tram derailment in Barnaul: tram collides with a car</media:title>
                          <media:description>In a recent incident in Barnaul, Russia, a tram derailed and crashed into a foreign car, according to the regional traffic police. The accident took place on June 5th, 2023, at approximately 15:15 on Chelyuskintsev Street near house number 119b. As the tram veered off its tracks, it collided with a Toyota, causing significant damage to the vehicles involved.

Fortunately, no one was injured in the accident. However, the collision resulted in temporary roadblocks as the damaged car obstructed traffic. Authorities swiftly responded to the scene to ensure the safety of all individuals involved and to restore the flow of vehicles on the affected roadway.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>tram,derailment,collision,foreign car,Barnaul,Russia,Chelyuskintsev Street,accident,traffic police,no injuries,temporary,roadway,Toyota,derailed,crash,damaged,investigation,authorities,safety,obstruction</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Barnaul</media:city>
                          <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Road accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Mon, 5 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>2222</guid>
                          <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 21:06:34 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/f5069885-9c88-44cc-bbb4-357836f22adc.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2222.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>17-year-old cyclist injured in collision with car in Aldan, Russia: accident under investigation</media:title>
                          <media:description>A 17-year-old boy was hospitalized after a car and bicycle collided on June 1st, 2023 in Aldan, Russia. The incident occurred when the young cyclist, traveling at high speed down a slope, veered into the oncoming lane and collided with a foreign car, a "Mitsubishi Lancer," driven by a 37-year-old individual. The entire accident was captured on video, clearly showing the moment of impact as the cyclist crashed into the car's hood and was propelled over it. Both the driver and the cyclist were found to be sober at the time of the accident. Currently, authorities from the State Traffic Inspectorate of the Ministry of Internal Affairs for Yakutia are conducting an investigation into the incident.

The injured teenager was immediately transported to the trauma department for medical care. The press service of the State Traffic Inspectorate confirmed that the young boy's condition required hospitalization. </media:description>
                          <media:keywords>accident,car,bicycle,injured,hospitalized,trauma,department,press,service,traffic,inspectorate,ministry,internal,affairs,Yakutia,minor,cyclist,collision,video,investigation</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Aldan</media:city>
                          <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Road accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Thu, 1 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>2217</guid>
                          <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 07:57:19 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/a06c1a17-2a96-4ed8-a3e0-02b1d7671a9d.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/1f1d4194-9579-4202-a7b1-be0687d3197b.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Miraculous escape: elderly couple narrowly avoids injury as tree collapses on tricycle amid traffic jam</media:title>
                          <media:description>In a heart-stopping moment captured on camera on 13th May, 2023, an elderly couple narrowly escaped injury when a tree unexpectedly fell on their tricycle in Shandong, East China. The incident occurred amidst a minor traffic jam, as the couple cautiously drove along the edge of the road. However, their peaceful ride took a sudden turn when a tree on the roadside came crashing down, landing directly on their tricycle.

Fortunately, luck was on their side as both the elderly man and woman emerged from the incident unharmed. Although shaken by the startling turn of events, they were able to walk away without any major injuries. </media:description>
                          <media:keywords>accident,tricycle,elderly couple,traffic jam,tree,incident,shaken,lucky,escape,China,Shandong,video,road,roadside,unexpected,danger,safety,vigilance,congestion,hazard</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Shandong</media:city>
                          <media:country>China</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>CN</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Road accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Sat, 13 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>2196</guid>
                          <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 18:46:54 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/7669ca10-2362-47fc-8e36-8029b2ca535f.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2c6d4bdd-af1d-450c-9335-49612a569dff.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Unforgettable tumble: an unexpected motorbike mishap in Henan Province</media:title>
                          <media:description>In a surprising turn of events captured on camera in Henan Province, central China, a man's motorbike ride took an unexpected tumble. The footage, shot by @love on the 26th of May, 2023, reveals the man confidently boarding the motorbike with another man who is the rider. However, just a few yards into their journey, the man who boarded the motorbike falls off the moving vehicle.

The man rolls on the ground eventually coming to a halt. Despite the dramatic fall, the man manages to stand up afterward. The extent of his injuries remains unknown, leaving viewers in suspense as to whether he sustained any harm from the incident.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>man,motorbike,fall,tumble,Henan Province,China,footage,captured,ride,unexpected,journey,control,skid,roll,suspense,injuries,adventure,caution,thrill-seekers</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Henan Province</media:city>
                          <media:country>China</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>CN</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Road accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Fri, 26 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>2152</guid>
                          <pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 18:17:02 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/f64d7aed-f1aa-4605-9b4f-ef3a9eba3946.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/396692ad-08a2-40eb-ad2f-fdacc06b8e4f.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Truck crashes into car on Shanghai highway, miraculous escape for occupants</media:title>
                          <media:description>In a heart-stopping incident captured on camera by @trafficsafetyeveryday, a truck collided with a small car on a highway in Shanghai, China, on the 12th of May, 2023. The video reveals a harrowing moment as the author, who was driving at the time, noticed a line of vehicles ahead and instinctively slowed down. Out of nowhere, a truck veering uncontrollably from the left suddenly crashed into the car in front, causing a devastating impact. Miraculously, all occupants involved in the collision emerged unscathed, escaping what could have been a tragic outcome.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>truck,car,collision,highway,Shanghai,China,video,accident,near miss,safety,traffic,vehicles,balance,unscathed,vigilant,unpredictable,defensive driving,investigation,road,motorists</media:keywords>
                          <media:city> Shanghai</media:city>
                          <media:country>China</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>CN</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Road accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Fri, 12 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>2132</guid>
                          <pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 07:18:21 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/bbb62799-7460-4f9c-8b7f-b603bbc10c30.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/067b6970-2a04-4641-bd58-e47712dbc721.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Mercedes crashes into underground passage in Chelyabinsk, Russia</media:title>
                          <media:description>In a shocking incident in Chelyabinsk, Russia, a Mercedes-Benz car with passengers crashed into an underground pedestrian crossing, causing significant damage on 13th May, 2023. The incident took place on Pobeda Avenue near the heat engineering institute. Disturbing videos of the crash have been circulating on social media, capturing the moment the foreign car plowed into the underpass at full speed, resulting in the flattening of the car's hood.

According to the Chelyabinsk traffic police, the accident left three individuals injured. The driver, a 25-year-old male, along with two passengers aged 20 and 23, were inside the Mercedes at the time of the crash. The impact was so powerful that all occupants were ejected from the vehicle upon collision. The exact details leading to the accident are currently under investigation by the authorities to establish a comprehensive understanding of the circumstances.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>accident,chelyabinsk,russia,mercedes,underground,passage,pedestrian,crossing,video,social media,damage,injuries,investigation,driver,passengers,collision,concern,road safety,authorities,responsibility</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Chelyabinsk</media:city>
                          <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Road accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Sat, 13 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>2126</guid>
                          <pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2023 06:38:35 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2126.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2126.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Tourist negligence exposed: risky motorbike maneuver caught on camera in Ubud, Bali</media:title>
                          <media:description>In a video captured by @Setya_pranatha02 on April 24, 2023, in the picturesque town of Ubud, Bali, Indonesia, a motorbike rider's reckless maneuver caught the attention of onlookers and highlighted the issue of tourist negligence when it comes to renting motorbikes.

The video begins with the motorbike rider carrying a passenger in front of the author as they had stopped by the side of the road. A packed car blocked their path, and the rider attempted to navigate his way past it. However, what followed was a series of wavering movements as the rider struggled to regain control of the bike after getting back on the road. Eventually, they disappeared from sight, leaving behind a scene that raised concerns among witnesses.

</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>motorbike,rider,passenger,negligence,tourists,rental,Ubud,Bali,Indonesia,video,captured,road,maneuver,packed car,onlookers,risks,accidents,behavior,safety,helmets</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Ubud, Bali</media:city>
                          <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>ID</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Road accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Fri, 24 Mar 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>2070</guid>
                          <pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2023 04:13:28 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2070.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2070.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Risky motorbike stunt goes wrong: rider escapes with minor injuries</media:title>
                          <media:description>In a heart-stopping moment captured on video by @bayudhenger7 on 22nd October 2022, a group of friends in Blora, Central Java, Indonesia, found themselves in a dangerous situation when an attempt at a daring motorbike stunt took an unexpected turn.

One individual decided to push the limits by riding on the rear tire while raising the front wheel, a maneuver known for its high level of difficulty and risk. Little did they know that this stunt would soon go awry.

As the rider attempted to maintain balance, disaster struck. With the front wheel raised, their leg made contact with the road surface, resulting in a terrifying drag. Realizing the danger, the rider quickly released the motorbike, allowing it to continue moving forward uncontrollably. The driver is fine.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>motorbike,stunt,risk,danger,video,friends,adrenaline,balance,drag,release,uncontrollable,puddle,scratch,skill,experience,safety,gear,supervision,boundaries,responsibility</media:keywords>
                          <media:city> Blora, Central Java</media:city>
                          <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>ID</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Road accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Sat, 22 Oct 2022</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>2057</guid>
                          <pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2023 04:13:28 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2057.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2057.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Patient escapes moving ambulance in Komsomolsk-on-Amur while being transported for injuries from a fight</media:title>
                          <media:description>In a bizarre incident in Komsomolsk-on-Amur, Russia, on 4th of May, 2023 a patient escaped from a moving ambulance while being transported for injuries sustained in a fight. According to local reports, the incident was captured on camera by a car driving behind the ambulance.

The video footage shows the ambulance slowing down at an intersection, and suddenly the back door opens, and a young man falls out of the vehicle onto the pavement. After hesitantly getting to his feet, the man hurriedly starts running away, while the ambulance drives off without noticing the escapee.

The patient, who was wounded in the neck during the fight, had been called in for medical attention by the police. However, he managed to escape from the ambulance while still in transit to the hospital.

Local media reports indicate that the police are searching for the fugitive, who is still at large. </media:description>
                          <media:keywords>ambulance,escape,patient,fight,injuries,Komsomolsk-on-Amur,Russia,police,fugitive,safety,protocols,emergency,medical,services,incident,video,footage,search,public,concern</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Komsomolsk-on-Amur</media:city>
                          <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Road accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Thu, 4 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>2013</guid>
                          <pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 18:21:46 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2013.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2013.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Miraculous survival: car and motorcycle collision in Voronezh leaves passengers unscathed</media:title>
                          <media:description>A dramatic car and motorcycle collision occurred in the Russian city of Voronezh on May 1st, 2023. Despite the severity of the crash, both the motorcyclist and their passenger survived.

The incident was captured on video and quickly circulated on social media. The footage showed the car and motorcycle speeding down Taneyev Street and Yaroslavskaya Street, respectively, before colliding at the intersection.

The impact of the collision sent the motorcyclist hurtling through the air, while their passenger was flung to the side. Thankfully, passers-by rushed to the scene to help the injured parties. The driver of the car also stopped and appeared to offer assistance.

Despite the violent nature of the accident, both the motorcyclist and their passenger managed to escape without serious injuries. In fact, the motorcycle passenger immediately got to their feet and helped their driver, demonstrating remarkable resilience and bravery in the face of danger.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>accident,collision,Voronezh,Russia,car,motorcycle,video,social media,high speed,intersection,injuries,survival,passengers,passers-by,help,driver,Taneyev,Yaroslavskaya,lucky,incident</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Voronezh</media:city>
                          <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Road accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Mon, 1 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>2002</guid>
                          <pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2023 06:38:35 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2002.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2002.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Truck carrying paint products overturns and explodes in Uzbekistan</media:title>
                          <media:description>On April 6th, 2023, a truck carrying paint products overturned and exploded while driving in Uzbekistan. The incident occurred during the day on the 259th kilometer of the international highway Tashkent - Osh, on the Kamchik pass. The truck had been speeding while descending from the pass when it overturned and exploded. The products from the semi-trailer spilled onto the asphalt and instantly caught fire.

At around 11:10 am, as a result of the collision, the truck caught fire and hit three other cars. Fire and rescue squads from the Ministry of Emergency Situations arrived at the scene of the accident and extinguished the fire within 25 minutes. During the extinguishing process, one side of the pass was temporarily closed.


According to preliminary information, six people were injured as a result of the accident and were hospitalized in the nearest medical facility. After the fire was completely extinguished, it was discovered that the driver of the truck had died in the cabin.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>Uzbekistan,truck,paint,products,overturns,explodes,international,highway,Tashkent,Osh,Kamchik,pass,collision,fire,rescue,squads</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>-</media:city>
                          <media:country>Uzbekistan</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>UZ</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Road accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Thu, 6 Apr 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>1938</guid>
                          <pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2023 06:38:35 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/1938.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/1938.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Incredible escape: car in Dagestan survives rockslide thanks to driver's quick thinking</media:title>
                          <media:description>In Dagestan, a car carrying passengers narrowly escaped a potentially fatal accident when it was caught in a rockslide on April 7th, 2023. The incident occurred when the car was travelling on a road and rocks began to tumble down the mountain, burying the roadway in a cloud of dust and debris.

The driver of the car acted quickly, realizing that the only way out was to reverse the vehicle. With a bit of ingenuity and skill, the driver managed to back the car out of the rubble before it was completely buried. Although the extent of the damage to the vehicle is unclear, the important thing is that everyone inside the car survived unscathed.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>Dagestan,car,rockslide,passengers,escape,quick thinking,driver,reversing,rubble,unpredictable,environment,lifesaving,decision,forward,damage,unscathed,mountain,debris,roadway,ingenuity</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>-</media:city>
                          <media:country>Dagestan</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>undefined</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>undefined</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Road accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Fri, 7 Apr 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>1870</guid>
                          <pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2023 06:38:35 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/1870.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/1870.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Miraculous escape: woman narrowly avoids cars in Saint Petersburg accident</media:title>
                          <media:description>In the afternoon of March 17th, 2023, the bustling city of Saint Petersburg, Russia, was shaken by a serious car accident at one of its busiest intersections. The incident was caught on video surveillance cameras, which recorded two cars colliding and sending debris flying across the street. However, what was even more shocking than the accident itself was the fact that a woman was caught on camera narrowly avoiding being hit by the flying cars.

The woman in question has since been dubbed the "most fearless woman in the Saint Petersburg region" by local media outlets. In the video footage, she can be seen calmly walking towards the intersection, unaware of the impending danger. As the cars collide and spin out of control, she suddenly stops in her tracks, and just in the nick of time, she manages to dart out of the way of the flying debris.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>Saint Petersburg,Russia,car accident,video surveillance,fearless woman,lucky escape,intersection</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Saint Petersburg</media:city>
                          <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>undefined</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>undefined</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Road accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>1756</guid>
                          <pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 18:21:46 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/1756.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/1756.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>An eight-year-old boy dies in a tragic motorcycle accident in London</media:title>
                          <media:description>Tragedy struck in Plumstead, London, on February 19, 2023, as an eight-year-old boy lost his life in a motorcycle accident. The incident took place on a pedestrian crossing on Plumstead Road, close to the junction with Lenton Street in Woolwich.

Three people, including the young boy, a 10-year-old boy, and a man in his 40s, were crossing the road when they were hit by a motorcycle. The 10-year-old boy and the man are in life-threatening conditions and have been rushed to the hospital for treatment. The family of the deceased boy has been informed and is being supported by specialist officers.

The rider of the motorcycle, a 20-year-old man, was also taken to the hospital, and his condition has been assessed as not life-threatening. The Met, the London Ambulance Service, and the Air Ambulance all came to help with the accident, and investigations into what happened are still going on. Road closures are still in place, and police have reported that no arrests have been made so far.

James Delamare, who filmed the numerous police cars at the scene. The footage shows the gravity of the accident and the response of emergency services.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>motorcycle,crash,boy,dies,accident,pedestrian,life-threatening,hospital,treatment,street,no arrest,hit,London,police</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Plumstead</media:city>
                          <media:country>London</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>undefined</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>undefined</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Road accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>1629</guid>
                          <pubDate>Invalid Date</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1629.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1629.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>A racing event in Indonesia takes an unexpected turn as a man is struck by a motorcycle</media:title>
                          <media:description>Bandung, Indonesia, was the site of a racing event on December 29, 2022, that had a surprising and unfortunate twist. @mochilyas164__ was there to film the excitement, but what he captured on video was a shocking incident that has since gone viral.

As the race was in full swing, a person who was apparently unaware that it had started suddenly appeared on the track, running across it. The individual was not paying attention and failed to notice the speeding race motorcycle, which resulted in a collision. The impact caused the person to stumble and fall to the ground.

The person in the video was lucky to have escaped with only minor injuries and was not seriously injured. The man sustained only a few abrasions as a result of the impact.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>race,event,Indonesia,motorcycle,collision,track,accident,injuries,lucky,abrasions,unaware</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Bandung</media:city>
                          <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>undefined</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>undefined</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Road accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Invalid date</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>1610</guid>
                          <pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2023 04:13:28 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1610.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1610.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>An ice block flying off a truck injures a 3-year-old in a road accident in Russia</media:title>
                          <media:description>Kostroma, Russia, witnessed a shocking road accident on January 7, 2023, when a video of the incident was published and went viral on the Internet. The video was recorded by a participant in the accident, who was driving along the Kostroma-Sharya-Kirov-Perm highway in the Kadyisky district. The driver reported that an ice block flew off the roof of an oncoming truck at high speed, breaking the glass of his car and injuring his 3-year-old daughter, who was in the back seat.

The regional traffic police department is investigating the matter and is reviewing recordings from video cameras in the area. The truck that was allegedly responsible for the accident has disappeared, and it is suspected that the driver may not have even been aware of the incident. The traffic police are conducting an audit to classify the incident and identify the perpetrators.

The good news is that the young girl was seated in a child car seat in the rear passenger seat of the Toyota and was properly fastened, which prevented a more tragic outcome. The traffic police emphasized the importance of following traffic laws and regulations to ensure the safety of all road users. This includes ensuring that any heavy loads on vehicles are properly secured to prevent objects from falling off and endangering other road users.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>ice block,truck,road accident,Russia,investigation,young girl,car seat,safety,traffic laws,driver,vehicle,Toyota</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Kostroma</media:city>
                          <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>undefined</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>undefined</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Road accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Sat, 7 Jan 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>1608</guid>
                          <pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2023 06:38:35 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1608.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1608.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>An incident of a passenger car colliding with a tractor in Belarus</media:title>
                          <media:description>An accident involving a passenger car and a tractor took place in the afternoon of February 3, 2023, in Novolukoml, Belarus. The incident was captured by a surveillance camera and is currently being investigated by the traffic police.

According to inspectors, the 47-year-old driver of a Chery was attempting to pass a Belarus tractor at a designated intersection when the car collided with the tractor and flipped over. The cause of the accident is currently being investigated, however, it has been reported that the driver of the passenger car was trying to overtake the tractor at the time of the crash.

Fortunately, the traffic police have reported that the driver of the passenger car was wearing a seat belt at the time of the accident and was not injured in the crash. The driver of the tractor was also unharmed.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>Accident,Passenger car,Tractor,Collision,Surveillance,Investigation,Overtaking,Seat belt,Unharmed,flipped,Belarus</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Novolukoml</media:city>
                          <media:country>Belarus</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>undefined</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>undefined</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Road accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Fri, 3 Feb 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>1584</guid>
                          <pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2023 06:38:35 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1584.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1584.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>An unaware truck driver dragged the car for about 150 meters</media:title>
                          <media:description>On February 3, 2023, an accident took place in Kostroma, Russia, at an intersection near the Philharmonic, involving a heavy truck and a car. A video of the accident was shared on social media, showing the truck dragging the car for a distance of about 150 meters.

The city traffic police say that the woman driving the Peugeot was leaving a parking lot and trying to change lanes when she drove into the Volvo truck's blind spot. The truck driver, who was on his way towards Ivan Susanin Street, was unaware of the car and continued to drive, dragging it through the intersection.

The accident came to a halt only when another motorist honked at the truck driver, who then realized what had happened. Fortunately, no one was injured in the accident. The press service of the city traffic police is investigating the incident to determine the exact cause and to ensure such incidents are prevented in the future.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>truck,car,drag,accident,intersection,driver,unaware,injury,meter,parking,Russia</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Kostroma</media:city>
                          <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>undefined</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>undefined</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Road accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Fri, 3 Feb 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>1578</guid>
                          <pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2023 06:38:35 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1578.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1578.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>A man riding a motorcycle crashed and tumbled on the hump</media:title>
                          <media:description>On November 9, 2020, in Wonosobo, Java, Indonesia, a man had a close call while trying out a motorcycle. The incident was captured by @alim_096, who was recording his friend as he rode the motorcycle. The ride started off smoothly, with the man doing a great job controlling the bike. However, things took a turn for the worse when he encountered a hump on a farm. The man crashed into the hump and fell in a funny way.

Thankfully, despite the fall, the man was not seriously injured. This is a reminder that even the most experienced riders can have mishaps, and it's important to always wear proper safety gear while riding a motorcycle.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>motorcycle,man,hump,tumbled,incident,crash,funny,injury,reminder,safety,friends</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Wonosobo, Java</media:city>
                          <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>undefined</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>undefined</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Road accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Mon, 9 Nov 2020</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>1575</guid>
                          <pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2023 04:13:28 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1575.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1575.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>A man's motorcycle stunt goes wrong in Malaysia</media:title>
                          <media:description>Penang, Malaysia, witnessed an exciting yet nerve-wracking moment on December 27, 2022. @_alif.fti captured a video of his friend showcasing his motorcycle stunts. The video shows the friend executing a series of impressive tricks on his motorcycle. He flawlessly performed one stunt after another.

However, the excitement took a turn for the worse when the rider attempted another trick. The motorcycle crashed, and the rider fell to the ground. Alif held their breath as they watched the incident unfold.

Thankfully, the rider was fine and only sustained minor injuries. The accident shows how dangerous these kinds of stunts can be and how important it is to always put safety before show.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>motorcycle,stunts,trick,crash,fall,injury,road,accident,safety,dangerous,Malaysia</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Penang</media:city>
                          <media:country>Malaysia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>undefined</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>undefined</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Road accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Invalid date</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>1566</guid>
                          <pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 18:21:46 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1566.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1566.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Two Motorcycle Racers Bravely Battle Injury and Cold After Falling Through Ice in Russia</media:title>
                          <media:description>On 30 January 2023, a dramatic scene took place in the Kanash region of Russia. Two motorcycle racers, who were training together, fell through the ice on a frozen river. The incident was caught on camera by one of the racers and later posted on his YouTube channel (@MXLive21).

One of the racers was driving his motorcycle on the frozen river when the ice gave way, causing his motorcycle to go under the water. However, he managed to stay afloat on the ice. Seeing his comrade fall, the second racer went in after him to help.

Unfortunately, both racers were injured in the incident. The first racer suffered a broken collarbone, while the second racer sustained a shoulder injury. In addition, they both caught a cold due to being in the cold water. The racers managed to retrieve their equipment, but their motorcycles suffered a water hammer, causing damage to the engines.

Despite the challenges they faced, the racers showed bravery and determination in their rescue efforts. The incident serves as a reminder of the dangers of extreme sports and the importance of taking necessary precautions.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>motorcycle,racer,brave,fall,crack,ice,frozen,river,injured,extreme sports,Russia</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Kanash</media:city>
                          <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>undefined</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>undefined</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Road accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Thu, 2 Feb 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>1548</guid>
                          <pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 18:21:46 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1548.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1548.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Motorcycle riders fall into a paddy field of mud</media:title>
                          <media:description>On January 14, 2023, a video surfaced on social media of an incident that took place in Sukorejo Kendal, Central Java, Indonesia. The video, recorded by @hendrawan_adji, shows three individuals riding a motorcycle together. Unfortunately, due to an apparent lack of caution, the individuals fell backwards off their motorcycle into a paddy field filled with mud.

Thankfully, despite the fall, the individuals involved in the incident are reported to be fine. This incident serves as a reminder of the importance of safety when operating a motorcycle. It is crucial for riders to always wear protective gear, such as helmets, and to be aware of their surroundings at all times. Additionally, it is important for riders to understand the limitations of their vehicle and not take unnecessary risks.

The paddy field is the main source of livelihood for the local farmers in Sukorejo Kendal, Central Java. The farmers have to work hard to maintain it. This incident not only damages the paddy field but also puts the lives of the riders in danger. It's important to be careful when riding in rural areas and to respect the local community.

Injuries resulting from motorcycle accidents can be severe and even fatal. It is crucial for riders to prioritize safety and to always practice caution while operating their vehicles. We are glad to hear that the individuals involved in this incident are safe, and we hope that they learn from this experience to be more careful and aware when riding in the future.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>motorcycle,rider,fall,paddy field,mud,incident,fine,vehicle,injuries,Indonesia</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Sukorejo Kendal</media:city>
                          <media:country>Central Java, Indonesia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>undefined</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>undefined</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Road accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Sat, 14 Jan 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>1534</guid>
                          <pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2023 04:13:28 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1534.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1534.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>The truck driver fell asleep and crashed into parked cars.</media:title>
                          <media:description>During Orenburg's snow night, the truck rushed down the road, colliding with parked cars before coming to a halt. Based on sources, police officers found that the truck driver fell asleep while driving and damaged nine cars. 

One of the citizens who live in this area commented on social media that the accident served as a kind of "alarm clock" because it occurred in the early morning of the third of January. For car owners, the new year did not start very well. Many people believe the driver was drunk or tired from working night shifts. The driver is fine.
</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>accident,crash,car,truck,sleep,snow,road,police,New Year</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Orenburg</media:city>
                          <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>undefined</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>undefined</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Road accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Tue, 3 Jan 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>1471</guid>
                          <pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 18:21:46 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/942f5395-d51f-4d5f-bcc3-8ff436362723.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1471.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>A group of people used tank as sleds and dressed as Santa.</media:title>
                          <media:description>A group of people dressed as Santa Claus use a tank as a sled to cross the narrow street of Angarrack village in west Cornwall, England, The tank causes damage to the car, blocks access to the decorated streets, and causes traffic. Another source says that one of the Santas tries to argue and is positively too drunk, while the driver argues with the traffic warden over being let into the village. There is no evidence that the driver has been drinking.

Credit to: @ian_jepson</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>Santa,tank,road,incident,sled,drunk,traffic,street,United Kingdom</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>-</media:city>
                          <media:country> England, United Kingdom</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>undefined</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>undefined</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Road accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Invalid date</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>1457</guid>
                          <pubDate>Invalid Date</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1457.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1457.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>A motorcycle starts a massive fire on the side of the road!</media:title>
                          <media:description>The Author said: "Suddenly the motor caught fire, and we tried to stop it using the fire extinguisher."

Credit to: ZEE Moto</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>motorcycle,fire,road,accidents,extinguisher,sudden,Philippines</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Nueva Ecija</media:city>
                          <media:country>Philippines</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>undefined</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>undefined</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Road accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Tue, 2 Aug 2022</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>1451</guid>
                          <pubDate>Invalid Date</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1451.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1451.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>The driver of the car miraculously did not hit the girl with the bicycle!</media:title>
                          <media:description>A girl on a bicycle almost got hit by a car in Bryansk on Flotskaya Street. The driver miraculously managed to notice the danger and slow down.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>accident,car,luck,road,driver,girl,bike,bicycle</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Bryansk</media:city>
                          <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>undefined</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>undefined</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Road accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2022</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>1443</guid>
                          <pubDate>Invalid Date</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1443.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1443.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>The train driver miraculously stopped the train inches from the stuck truck!</media:title>
                          <media:description>In the city of Dmitrov, Moscow Region, a truck got stuck at a railway crossing right in front of an approaching train. It happened at night, but the train driver managed to react and stop the train a few centimeters from KamAZ.
The footage shows that a red light is on at the crossing, a bell is ringing announcing the approach of a train, and its driver is signaling a truck stuck on the tracks. As a result of the incident, no one was injured.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>accident,car,train,railway,road,russia,truck,luck</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Dmitrov</media:city>
                          <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>undefined</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>undefined</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Road accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Invalid date</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>1441</guid>
                          <pubDate>Invalid Date</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1441.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1441.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>A man lights up a gas tank with a lighter in Voronezh</media:title>
                          <media:description>A curious case of the destruction of their own car occurred in Voronezh. While refueling at one of the stations, the minivan driver, for some unknown reason, decided to light up the fuel tank with a lighter. Gasoline fumes ignited predictably, and flames quickly engulfed the rear of the vehicle. The man quickly pulled the gun out of the tank, but the footage from the scene shows that the gun itself continues to burn.

What caused the strange act is unknown. There is also no information about whether the unfortunate driver could put out his minivan.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>accident,car,petrol,russia,voronezh,vehicle,fire,refueling,fail</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Voronezh</media:city>
                          <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>undefined</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>undefined</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Road accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Invalid date</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>1431</guid>
                          <pubDate>Invalid Date</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1431.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1431.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>High speed motorbike riding crash on a tree!</media:title>
                          <media:description>The Author said: "My friend is testing the circuit. He was five turns in and looked tired from the first corner. Like in Superball, I recorded it, and he lost control of the motor. He is ok!" 

Credit to: Fahmi Faisal</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>motorbike,crash,tree,speed,superball,circuit,tired,Indonesia</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Bandung</media:city>
                          <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>undefined</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>undefined</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Road accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Sat, 1 Oct 2022</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>1413</guid>
                          <pubDate>Invalid Date</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1413.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1413.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Unexpected motorcycle accident slip crash in Indonesia!</media:title>
                          <media:description>The Author said: "I recorded my friend's while we were driving. They slid and crashed as we turned onto the road. As a result of the incident, my friend suffered minor injuries."

Credit to: @ar.royyan.a</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>accidents,slip,crash,Indonesia,driving,road,friend,suffered,injuries</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Tomang</media:city>
                          <media:country>West Jakarta, Indonesia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>undefined</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>undefined</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Road accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Sat, 17 Oct 2020</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>1363</guid>
                          <pubDate>Invalid Date</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1363.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1363.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Unsuccessful parking of a man, as a result of which he flew into the forest!</media:title>
                          <media:description>An elderly man, when parking, decided to park the car a little better than it was, as a result, he flew into the forest. The young man offered to help him, to which he refused. He ended up hitting a couple of cars, broke the sandbox, and crashed his car. According to him, the car jammed after washing.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>car,fail,crash,parking,forest,russia,road</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Saynsk</media:city>
                          <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>undefined</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>undefined</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Road accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2022</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>1334</guid>
                          <pubDate>Invalid Date</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1334.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1334.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>The man was almost crushed by an SUV at a car competition in Russia!</media:title>
                          <media:description>30 October 2022, Barnaul, Russia

It is known that the victim was the navigator of the SUV. During the competition, his pilot was in the mud, and he came out to help him. However, the cars continued to move, and one of them crushed the man. Eyewitnesses managed to prevent the hit in time and stopped the competition. According to the audience, the navigator is fine. He stood up on his own and stepped aside.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>man,crush,car,SUV,accident,competition,russia</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Barnaul</media:city>
                          <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>undefined</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>undefined</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Road accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2022</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>1277</guid>
                          <pubDate>Invalid Date</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/274b4fa1-43ec-4dfd-a3b8-c99934a43f37.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/b49fa38c-9383-4549-b2ed-83ac90696432.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Two drivers fought in the middle of the road in Russia!</media:title>
                          <media:description>16 November 2022, Voronezh, Russia
After the accident, two drivers left the cars and started a fight in the middle of the roadway. The footage shows two colliding foreign cars. The men, judging by the video, fought for a long time - one of them managed to fall in the middle of the roadway. All this time they interfered with traffic, passing motorists signaled to rowdy men. People asked them to disperse, as a traffic jam formed because of them.
Credit to: @Anatoly Biryukov</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>drivers,fight,road,Russia,accident,cars,men,traffic</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Voronezh</media:city>
                          <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>undefined</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>undefined</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Road accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2022</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>1276</guid>
                          <pubDate>Invalid Date</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/2f8a1895-77fd-4d4f-90ce-e1e85e2b4b4a.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/3554716d-6ab4-413f-96b7-8d118b1023e9.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>In Bashkiria, a driver knocked down an 11-year-old schoolboy who escaped with only bruises</media:title>
                          <media:description>14 November 2022, Uchaly, Russia

The driver knocked down an 11-year-old student at a pedestrian crossing in Uchaly.

The boy jumped out onto the road - right under the sign he was demolished by a car. The child rolled over in the air and flew several meters, but, fortunately, received only a bruise. The police started checking.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>fail,accident,road accident,child,schoolboy</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Uchaly</media:city>
                          <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>undefined</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>undefined</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Road accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2022</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>1257</guid>
                          <pubDate>Invalid Date</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/fff4b2e3-a24d-48b8-8c2b-95feb4f10229.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1bb9752c-f457-4dde-9cdd-5fcf4093b4c8.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>In the village of Russia, a truck demolished the porch of a grocery store!</media:title>
                          <media:description>17 October 2022, Stroitelej, Russia
The truck pulled up to the store. But the driver did not calculate the dimensions and hit the porch with the edge of the booth. It just collapsed. At that moment, a store employee was standing on the porch. She miraculously survived, at the last moment she managed to run into the store. 
No violations were found with the truck driver, everything is in order with the documents, the man was sober.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>village,Russia,truck,accident,porch,store,road,building</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Stroitelej</media:city>
                          <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>undefined</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>undefined</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Road accidents</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2022</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>1219</guid>
                          <pubDate>Invalid Date</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/d4ebe8d3-cd6e-4fbb-b598-038df697f1e1.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/9f14bb6d-c02b-463e-9b8f-664acc601b4d.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                         </channel>
                      </rss>
                    