<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
            <rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
            xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
            xmlns:openSearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearchrss/1.0/"
            xmlns:dfpvideo="http://api.google.com/dfpvideo"
            xmlns:tms="http://data.tmsapi.com/v1.1"
            version="2.0">
              <channel>
                <title>ViralBear videos</title>
                <dfpvideo:version>2</dfpvideo:version>
                  
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Rescue mission: dog saved from war-torn neighborhood in Orikhiv, Ukraine</media:title>
                          <media:description>In a heartwarming act of compassion amidst the ongoing conflict between Ukraine and Russia, @ludenskyi embarked on a rescue mission in the war-torn neighborhood of Orikhiv, Zaporizhia Oblast, Ukraine. Their mission was to save a black Labrador retriever that had been abandoned by neighbors who had been forced to leave their home due to the devastation caused by shelling. The Labrador had found refuge with a couple named Natalia and her husband, who cared for not only the abandoned dog but also other animals in the neighborhood. On September 30, 2023, @ludenskyi and the rescue team arrived to find half of the couple's house destroyed by a recent shell, with Natalia and her husband in the hospital. They made the courageous decision to rescue the Labrador and pledged to return for the other dogs in the neighborhood once conditions allowed. The rescued dog will find temporary shelter in Khmelnytskyi until its owners can regain stability.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>rescue,dog,Ukraine,conflict,compassion,Orikhiv,neighborhood,Labrador,abandoned,neighbors,shelter,kindness,mission,courage,devastation,shell,hospital,temporary,stability,resilience</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Orikhiv</media:city>
                          <media:country>Ukraine</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>UA</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Animals,Rescue,News</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>3185</guid>
                          <pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2023 17:45:49 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/3185.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/3185.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 04:27:05 GMT</dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Skydiving instructor rescues spinning student in dramatic free fall</media:title>
                          <media:description>In a heart-pounding moment captured on video on July 28, 2023, in Kemerovo, Russia, a skilled skydiving instructor, @anti.bloger, came to the rescue of a struggling student in mid-air. The student had leaped out of an aircraft for a thrilling free fall experience but found themselves in a perilous situation, spiraling uncontrollably with no parachute deployment in sight. Without hesitation, the instructor, who was closely following the student, took swift action and assisted in deploying the parachute, ensuring a safe and dramatic landing for the student.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>skydiving,rescue,instructor,student,freefall,adrenaline,heroism,video,Kemerovo,Russia,parachute,dramatic,courage,safety,thrill,expert,moment,spiraling,landing,assistance</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Kemerovo</media:city>
                          <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Rescue</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>exclusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>3144</guid>
                          <pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2023 05:11:57 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/3144.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/3144.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Child rescued from door lock mishap: a happy ending in Klaten, Indonesia</media:title>
                          <media:description>On September 19, 2023, in Klaten, Jawa Tengah, Indonesia, a child named Arvin found himself in a sticky situation when his curiosity got the best of him. Captured on video by @purplegirl13, young Arvin had managed to get his index finger stuck in a door lock while his mother scolded him for his misadventure. The tense moment was diffused when a quick-thinking rescuer applied cooking oil to the finger, allowing it to slip free from the lock. Despite the scolding, Arvin's relief and happiness were palpable after the successful rescue.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>child,rescue,mishap,video,door,lock,Klaten,Indonesia,curiosity,mother,scolding,relief,happiness,cooking oil,incident,parental guidance,Arvin,finger,stuck,@purplegirl13</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Klaten, Jawa Tengah</media:city>
                          <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>ID</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Rescue</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>exclusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>3143</guid>
                          <pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2023 07:25:22 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/3143.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/3143.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Seal escapes killer whales by climbing onto yacht in Avacha Bay, Kamchatka</media:title>
                          <media:description>In a remarkable wildlife encounter on September 6, 2023, in Kamchatka, Russia, captured by @Maxim Gaevoy, a seal found itself in a life-or-death situation as it attempted to evade a group of killer whales in Avacha Bay. The chase unfolded as several killer whales relentlessly pursued the seal, cornering it against the starboard side of the yacht. Quick-thinking crew members intervened, encouraging the distressed seal to climb onto the yacht's swimming platform for refuge. Once the seal was safe, the vessel wasted no time and accelerated away from the pursuing whales, ensuring the seal's survival. </media:description>
                          <media:keywords>seal,yacht,kamchatka,russia,killer whales,avacha bay,rescue,wildlife,encounter,maxim gaevoy,survival,ocean,adventure,dramatic,escape,marine,crew,nature,chase,refuge</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Avacha Bay, Kamchatka</media:city>
                          <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Animals,Rescue</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Wed, 6 Sep 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>3097</guid>
                          <pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2023 17:17:41 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/3097.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/3097.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Heroic rescue: man saves dog amid Ukraine-Russia conflict</media:title>
                          <media:description>In a harrowing video captured by @ludenskyi on September 18, 2023, in Orikhiv, Ukraine, a man was seen heroically rescuing a dog from the midst of the Ukraine-Russia conflict. The man, whose home had been personally struck by enemy shells, risked his life to evacuate the frightened dog from the war-torn area. Holding the dog by its collar, he explained the dire situation, stating that the area was subjected to daily attacks. The rescued dog is now undergoing rehabilitation in Dnipro before finding its way to a shelter in Khmelnytskyi, where efforts will be made to secure a new loving family for the fortunate canine.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>rescue,conflict,heroism,dog,Ukraine,Russia,evacuation,Orikhiv,shelter,rehabilitation,kindness,compassion,humanity,video,man,brave,survival,hope,compassion,solidarity</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Orikhiv</media:city>
                          <media:country>Ukraine</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>UA</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Rescue,News</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>3087</guid>
                          <pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2023 11:56:43 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/3087.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/3087.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Rescue mission: cat with plastic bag on its head evades help in Salatiga City</media:title>
                          <media:description>In a recent incident in Salatiga City, Central Java, Indonesia, a concerned citizen, @teransimalem09, captured a video on July 9, 2023 that has stirred emotions online. The footage shows a cat with its head trapped inside a plastic bag, struggling to navigate its surroundings. Eager to assist the distressed feline, @teransimalem09 attempted to approach it, but the cat's impaired vision caused it to flee in fear. Undeterred, the individual persevered, calling out to the cat as they followed it in an effort to provide the much-needed help.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>cat,plasticbag,rescue,Salatiga,Indonesia,video,help,concern,citizen,feline,distressed,vision,fear,waste,disposal,animal,companion,emotion,online,incident</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Salatiga City, Central Java</media:city>
                          <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>ID</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Animals,Rescue</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>exclusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Sun, 9 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>3085</guid>
                          <pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2023 11:36:17 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/3085.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/3085.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>A man rescues squirrel from Khimki Reservoir</media:title>
                          <media:description>In a heartwarming display of compassion and quick thinking, a kind-hearted passerby in Moscow, Russia, came to the rescue of a stranded squirrel in the Khimki Reservoir on July 4, 2023. Upon spotting the distressed creature struggling in the water, the man wasted no time in fashioning an impromptu ladder from a nearby branch, offering the stranded squirrel a lifeline to safety. Although the brave little rodent initially had some difficulty scaling the makeshift ladder, perseverance paid off as it finally found its footing and climbed to safety. With a gentle hand, the man lowered the squirrel to solid ground, ensuring its safe return to the wild.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>squirrel,rescue,Moscow,Russia,kindness,compassion,hero,pond,branch,water,animal,passerby,Khimki Reservoir,wildlife,stranded,safety,ladder,swimming,bravery,heartwarming.</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Moscow</media:city>
                          <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Rescue</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Tue, 4 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>3078</guid>
                          <pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 11:58:04 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/3078.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/3078.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Rescue mission: swallow freed from tight window space in Gomel, Belarus</media:title>
                          <media:description>In Gomel, Belarus, on June 1, 2023, @Kirill captured a video of a swallow trapped between two windows. Acting swiftly and carefully, he rescued the bird by using a cloth to prevent scratches and gently pushing it upwards until its wings were free. Kirill provided reassurance throughout the process, and the swallow was successfully saved, unharmed, and eventually flew away.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>bird,rescue,window,Gomel,Belarus,video,swallow,trapped,help,wings,balcony,ventilation,claws,careful,reassurance,free,saved,unharmed,Kirill,June</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Gomel</media:city>
                          <media:country>Belarus</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>BY</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Rescue</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>exclusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Thu, 1 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>3074</guid>
                          <pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 07:18:35 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/3074.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/3074.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Brave vacationers rescue entangled shark in Primorsky Territory, Russia</media:title>
                          <media:description>On September 16, 2023, in the Primorsky Territory of Russia, quick-thinking vacationers came to the rescue of an entangled Pacific herring shark in Triozerye Bay. Although these sharks are typically non-threatening to humans, they can become trapped in nets or obstacles, posing a danger to themselves. Displaying remarkable courage and compassion, the vacationers used their paddleboards to approach the distressed shark and successfully free it from the entanglement. After the rescue, they captured a memorable moment as video footage alongside the shark before releasing it back into the sea. </media:description>
                          <media:keywords>shark,rescue,vacationers,Primorsky,compassion,paddleboards,entanglement,courage,Triozerye,herring,predator,selfie,marine,ecosystem,balance,ocean,Russia,nets,release,danger</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Primorsky Territory</media:city>
                          <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Rescue</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>3066</guid>
                          <pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2023 09:35:44 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/3066.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/3066.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Rescuers save five-year-old trapped in washing machine in Kazan, Russia</media:title>
                          <media:description>On September 11, 2023, in Kazan, Russia, a dramatic incident unfolded when an emergency call to the number 112 reported that a five-year-old boy had become trapped inside a washing machine within one of the city's apartments. Swift action was taken as rescuers promptly arrived at the scene. The video footage of the rescue operation revealed the child's lower body wedged within the machine. With remarkable skill and dedication, the rescuers successfully extricated the young boy from his perilous predicament. The child was swiftly handed over to emergency medical personnel for evaluation and care.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>rescue,child,washing machine,Kazan,Russia,emergency,responders,incident,video,trapped,apartment,heroic,teamwork,swift,assistance,safety,medical,professionalism,dramatic,successful</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Kazan</media:city>
                          <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>News,Rescue</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>3053</guid>
                          <pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2023 14:54:46 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/3053.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/3053.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Heroic rescue: Dagestan electrical worker saves cat stuck on power pole</media:title>
                          <media:description>In a heartwarming incident in Dagestan, Russia, on September 10, 2023, an employee of the Levashinsky district electrical networks performed a daring rescue. A cat had found itself stranded atop a power line support pole, unable or unwilling to make its way down. Devoid of the feline's natural climbing abilities, the man utilized a specialized tool known as fitter's claws to carefully retrieve the distressed cat. He then called for assistance from his colleagues, who arrived with a piece of cloth to hold the cat as it made its way down. With a gentle release from the pole, the cat descended to safety, unharmed.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>rescue,cat,power line,pole,Dagestan,Russia,electrical worker,fitter's claws,colleagues,assistance,heartwarming,incident,stranded,specialized tool,distressed,safety,unharmed,daring,September 10,Levashinsky district</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Dagestan</media:city>
                          <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Animals,Heartwarming,Rescue</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Sun, 10 Sep 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>3024</guid>
                          <pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2023 13:38:58 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/3024.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/3024.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Heroic rescue efforts amidst phosphorus mines: saving 'Malysh' the dog in Chasiv Yar, Ukraine</media:title>
                          <media:description>In Chasiv Yar, Donetsk region, Ukraine, a heartwarming rescue mission unfolded as a group of individuals attempted to evacuate a dog named "Malysh" from an abandoned homestead. The video was captured by @ludenskyi on April 1, 2023. As they settled outside with the canine, a series of white objects began falling from the sky, later identified as phosphorous mines. Thankfully, the dog was safely hidden in a cage. However later, as they approached a tow car, an illuminating mine landed perilously close. With quick thinking and a stroke of luck, the mine detonated in mid-air, sparing the car from destruction. The rescue team proceeded to reposition the vehicle and successfully retrieved the dog, but not without witnessing several more mine landings nearby, causing small fires. </media:description>
                          <media:keywords>rescue,dog,homestead,Ukraine,phosphorus,mine,evacuation,courage,danger,video,lucky,car,fire,mission,sky,illuminating,Chasiv Yar,Donetsk,Malysh,April</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Chasiv Yar, Donetsk region</media:city>
                          <media:country>Ukraine</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>UA</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>News,Rescue</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Sat, 1 Apr 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>2918</guid>
                          <pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2023 09:52:27 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2918.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2918.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Unfortunate swimmer saved from canal by passers-by using metal fence</media:title>
                          <media:description>In a recent incident on August 9, 2023, in St. Petersburg, Russia, an unlucky individual found themselves in a perilous situation after an ill-advised swim in the Obvodny Canal. Underestimating the effects of alcohol combined with the scorching heat, the man lost control of his body while hanging onto a ring on the canal wall. Alerted by observant bystanders, rescuers were summoned to the scene. Recognizing the urgency of the situation, quick-thinking pedestrians orchestrated a daring rescue using a section of metal fence. With combined efforts, they successfully maneuvered the makeshift contraption into the water, safely retrieving the stranded swimmer. </media:description>
                          <media:keywords>canal,swimmer,rescue,alcohol,heat,incident,St. Petersburg,Russia,fence,water,ring,bystanders,bystanders,observers,community,crisis,body,forces,land,unfortunate,organized</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>St. Petersburg</media:city>
                          <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>News,Rescue</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Wed, 9 Aug 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>2872</guid>
                          <pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2023 19:52:38 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2872.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2872.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Rescuer's heartwarming discovery: mother dog and puppies found amidst ruins in Dnipro, Ukraine</media:title>
                          <media:description>In a heartwarming display of compassion, @pitbull911maliok captured a touching moment on August 24, 2023, in Dnipro, Ukraine. The video showcases her discovery of a mother dog and her adorable litter of puppies nestled amidst the remains of a dilapidated building near the train tracks. The abandoned location held a special significance for the rescuer, as it was where she had previously found and saved a puppy with broken paws, which was later sent to a new loving family in England. The video captures the puppies' joyful barks and wagging tails as @pitbull911maliok pats them affectionately, underscoring the power of resilience and care in the face of adversity.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>puppies,rescue,compassion,discovery,abandoned,building,debris,joy,barking,mother,heartwarming,Dnipro,Ukraine,@pitbull911maliok,video,love,family,train tracks,happiness,puppies</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Dnipro</media:city>
                          <media:country>Ukraine</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>UA</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Animals,Rescue,Heartwarming</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>2852</guid>
                          <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 10:31:08 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2852.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2852.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Swift and skillful rescue: Tasikmalaya firefighters save child with tin can stuck on head</media:title>
                          <media:description>In a remarkable display of quick thinking and expertise, the Tasikmalaya City Fire Department located in Indonesia, successfully rescued a young child named Muhammad Gabriel, whose head became trapped in a tin can. The incident, captured in a video by @damkar_kota_tasikmalaya113 on July 30, 2023, unfolded as the worried parents sought help from the firefighters. Demonstrating their proficiency, the firefighters delicately executed the rescue operation, using a method that involved placing a metal spoon to shield the child's head while cutting the can. Water was continuously poured to cool the area during the process, ensuring the child's safety. Within a mere 10 minutes, the operation was triumphantly completed, highlighting the efficient and skilled response of the Tasikmalaya City Fire Department in averting a potentially hazardous situation.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>rescue,child,tin can,firefighters,expertise,parents,swift,skilled,operation,video,Tasikmalaya,head,can cutting,water,safety,efficient,hazardous,successful,quick,department</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Tasikmalaya</media:city>
                          <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>ID</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Rescue</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>2838</guid>
                          <pubDate>Fri, 25 Aug 2023 14:03:12 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2838.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2838.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Heroic police investigator saves drowning child: a tale of courage and quick thinking in Astana pool</media:title>
                          <media:description>In a heart-stopping incident on August 7, 2023, at a poolside in Astana, Kazakhstan, a sharp-eyed child's timely observation proved to be a lifesaver. Spotting a young boy submerged in the water, the child wasted no time and promptly alerted the lifeguard on duty. Swift action followed as the lifeguard pulled the unresponsive child from the pool, but the situation remained dire as he wasn't breathing. A ray of hope emerged when a vacationer, later identified as Nazym Sharipova, an investigator from the Yesil district police department, rushed to administer life-saving cardiopulmonary resuscitation (CPR). With practiced precision, Sharipova's skillful efforts successfully revived the child. As fate would have it, this guardian angel was a dedicated police officer enjoying a leisurely day by the pool with her family. The arriving medical professionals commended the swift and effective first aid administered by Sharipova, ultimately ensuring the young boy's recovery.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>child,boy,water,lifeguard,victim,pool,breathing,vacationer,woman,CPR,policeman,investigator,health,danger,hero,courage,quick thinking,Astana,Kazakhstan,incident</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Astana</media:city>
                          <media:country>Kazakhstan</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>KZ</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>News,Rescue</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Mon, 7 Aug 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>2832</guid>
                          <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 12:38:43 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2832.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2832.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Miraculous rescue: brave bystanders save toddler dangling from 7th floor balcony in Chita</media:title>
                          <media:description>In a heart-stopping incident on August 3, 2023, in Chita, Russia, quick-thinking bystanders managed to avert a tragedy as they witnessed a three-year-old child perilously hanging from a seventh-floor balcony. Eyewitnesses captured the heart-pounding moment on camera, showing the child gripping onto the balcony's edge with both hands and precariously balancing with their feet on a small ledge below. The height of the protective fence seemed insurmountable for the child's small stature, raising questions about how they ended up in such a dangerous situation. Startled residents of the building banded together, hastily deploying blankets to cushion a potential fall. Fortunately, before the authorities arrived, the child was safely brought back into the apartment. The incident led to the authorities apprehending the 22-year-old parents, who also had another four-year-old child, revealing a troubled family dynamic marked by dysfunction and frequent altercations, as reported by concerned neighbors.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>balcony,toddler,rescue,Chita,Russia,incident,eyewitnesses,danger,courage,bystanders,footage,height,fence,family,dysfunction,police,apartment,parents,neighbors,screaming</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Chita</media:city>
                          <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>News,Rescue</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Thu, 3 Aug 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>2831</guid>
                          <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 07:35:09 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2831.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2831.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Dramatic rescue: quick response saves little girl on ledge of 9th floor in Kaspiysk</media:title>
                          <media:description>In a heart-stopping incident on August 14, 2023, in Kaspiysk, Russia, a young girl was rescued from a precarious situation on the 9th-floor ledge of a building on Khalilov Street. The city administration received an urgent alert through the "112" system at 05:08 local time, indicating that a child was perilously seated on an air conditioner outside the window. Alarmed tourists were the first to notice the child and raised the alarm. Promptly responding to the call, local law enforcement arrived, alongside concerned residents who formed two groups – one attempting to open the apartment door without startling the child, and the other positioned beneath the window with a protective blanket. With no adults present in the apartment, authorities worked diligently to gain access, eventually succeeding. The tense situation resolved as an older girl within the apartment bravely opened the door to the awaiting police, reuniting the siblings and averting a potential tragedy.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>rescue,incident,girl,ledge,window,apartment,parents,tourists,alert,air conditioner,police,response,tense,situation,access,siblings,bravery,reunite,danger,tragedy</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Kaspiysk</media:city>
                          <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>News,Rescue</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>2830</guid>
                          <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 07:34:11 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2830.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2830.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Heroic fishermen rescue family of five beluga whales stranded in Kamchatka's Tigilsky district</media:title>
                          <media:description>On August 14, 2023, in the breathtaking landscapes of Kamchatka's Tigilsky district in Russia, an inspiring tale of humanity and nature unfolded as a family of five beluga whales faced a perilous plight. Minister of Natural Resources for the region, Alexei Kumarkov, confirmed the heartening rescue operation that saw local fishermen rally together to save these marine giants. The Sokol family artel members, namely Andrei Korolev, Vladimir Kochelaevsky, Sergey Umkev, and Ashot Ustyan, discovered four mature beluga whales and a youthful cub stranded on the shores of the Sea of Okhotsk. Their diligent efforts to hydrate the creatures persisted for hours until the tide, a natural savior, returned, and the whales were at last free to rejoin their aquatic realm. The touching scene, documented in a video, showcased the whales side by side, emitting poignant sounds and even shedding what resembled tears. Beluga whales, belonging to the narwhal family within the cetacean order, captivate with their journey from dark blue infancy to the pristine white of adulthood by the age of five.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>rescue,beluga whales,fishermen,Kamchatka,Russia,Tigilsky district,nature,compassion,humanity,stranded,Sea of Okhotsk,Sokol family artel,marine,giants,effort,tide,touching,video,narwhal family,cetacean,journey</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Kamchatka</media:city>
                          <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Animals,Rescue,Heartwarming</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>2763</guid>
                          <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 11:35:23 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2763.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2763.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Rescuing little adventurer: a silent cry heard in West Jakarta</media:title>
                          <media:description>In a poignant scene captured by @justintewaulu on July 25, 2023, in West Jakarta, Indonesia, a child's adventurous spirit led to a moment of distress. The video shows a young child, his foot trapped in a trench near his house while attempting to pluck a leaf from a tree. Struggling silently, the child's tearful expression spoke volumes, though no sound could be heard. Fortunately, a concerned woman, presumably a family member, swiftly came to his aid, lifting him from the trench and providing comfort. </media:description>
                          <media:keywords>child,trench,distress,adventure,silent cry,leaf,tree,Jakarta,Indonesia,video,family,member,rescue,tearful,moment,curiosity,comfort,loved ones,aid,capture</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>West Jakarta</media:city>
                          <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>ID</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Rescue,Fails and Funnies</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>2704</guid>
                          <pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 09:34:30 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2704.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2704.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Goat rescued after getting caught on electrical wires while being transported in Dagestan, Russia</media:title>
                          <media:description>In a heartwarming incident in the village of Kutih, Dagestan, Russia, a goat was saved from a perilous situation after it got entangled in electrical wires while being transported by truck. The incident, which occurred on July 31, 2023, was captured on video and later surfaced online, capturing the attention of netizens worldwide. According to a representative of the administration of the Charodinsky district, the unfortunate incident was a result of the truck's height being incompatible with the low-hanging wires in the area. Thankfully, concerned individuals came to the goat's rescue promptly. The animal was apparently being transported from the Levashinsky district to the Charodinsky district for sale. </media:description>
                          <media:keywords>goat,rescued,incident,video,online,Dagestan,Russia,truck,electrical,wires,village,Kutih,administration,Charodinsky,district,height,low,hanging,animals,transportation</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Dagestan</media:city>
                          <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Rescue</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>2640</guid>
                          <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 09:34:11 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2640.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2640.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Trapped in flames: dramatic rescue of residents from Almaty apartment fire</media:title>
                          <media:description>In a devastating incident that shook Almaty, Kazakhstan, on August 1, 2023, an apartment on the fifth floor of a multi-storey building in the Akkent microdistrict caught fire. As panic spread among the residents, they resorted to desperate measures to escape the raging flames. In a heart-wrenching scene, parents threw their children out of windows in a bid to save them before jumping themselves. The heroic efforts of firefighters from the Ministry of Emergency Situations, however, proved crucial as they arrived within six minutes and swiftly initiated rescue operations. Braving the intense heat and danger, the firefighters skillfully used ladders to evacuate at least 290 people from the high-rise inferno, preventing further loss of life and mitigating the catastrophe's impact. The cause of the fire remains unknown, leaving the community to mourn the tragedy and reckon with the scars left behind.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>fire,almaty,kazakhstan,afternoon,apartment,fifth floor,multi-storey,blaze,evacuation,panic,children,rescue,firefighters,emergency,inferno,tragedy,heroic,ladders,community,impact</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Almaty</media:city>
                          <media:country>Kazakhstan</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>KZ</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Rescue</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Tue, 1 Aug 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>2633</guid>
                          <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 08:07:52 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2633.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2633.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Miraculous rescue: cat safely recovered from perilous heights in Minsk</media:title>
                          <media:description>In a heartwarming incident in Minsk, Belarus, on July 19, 2023, a vigilant passerby, @victory_shh, captured a remarkable moment when a cat's life was saved from a precarious situation. The cat found itself in a perilous predicament, clinging onto a window pane on the outside of a story building. Curiosity piqued when the author noticed the presence of the Ministry of Emergencies' vehicle nearby. Upon approaching the scene, they witnessed the heartening sight of a rescue operation in progress. The skilled emergency responders swiftly rescued the cat after it appeared to fall and secured the frightened feline, bringing it to safety. Thankfully, the rescue was successful, and the cat was handed over to a man, presumably its owner.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>rescue,cat,building,Minsk,Belarus,window,emergency,passerby,video,heartwarming,precarious,Ministry,height,safe,owner,compassion,celebration,online,courage,grateful</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Minsk</media:city>
                          <media:country>Belarus</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>BY</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Rescue</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>2576</guid>
                          <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 08:16:28 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2576.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2576.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Prompt metro staff rescue: dog's paw freed from escalator in Moscow metro</media:title>
                          <media:description>In a recent incident on July 1st, 2023 at the Moscow metro, a dachshund's paw became trapped in the escalator during a transition between the Krasnopresnenskaya and Barrikadnaya stations. The metro staff acted promptly, switching off the escalator and coming to the aid of the distressed animal. The metro's press service confirmed that no serious injuries occurred and urged passengers to transport their pets in carriers or bags. The veterinary clinic attending to the dachshund reported that although a small tear was observed on the paw, there were no fractures or severe injuries. Assurances were given that the dog would fully recover from the ordeal.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>moscow,metro,dog,paw,escalator,incident,krasnopresnenskaya,barrikadnaya,staff,rescue,prompt,trapped,injury,passengers,carriers,bags,veterinary,clinic,fractures,recovery</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Moscow </media:city>
                          <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Rescue</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Sat, 1 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>2468</guid>
                          <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/c9214d0a-84df-4aa5-9547-1575920469c3.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/ad527678-5001-4b76-a1fb-adb738b146d6.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Stupino resident bravely rescues trapped 14-year-old girl from burning car</media:title>
                          <media:description>A courageous resident of Stupino, Moscow, Russia, has become a local hero after rescuing a 14-year-old girl from a burning car. The incident unfolded on 7th June, 2023 on Tchaikovsky Street, where the car had mysteriously been locked with the young girl trapped inside. Acting swiftly, Yudaev Aleksey Sergeevich sprang into action, quickly assessing the situation and locating a nearby brick. With mere seconds on the clock, he shattered the car's rear window, allowing him to reach inside and free the frightened teenager.

Authorities later revealed that the girl had been left inside the locked car by her father, though the reasons behind his actions remain unknown. Thanks to the heroic actions of her relative, disaster was averted. The quick thinking and bravery displayed by Yudaev Aleksey Sergeevich undoubtedly saved the young girl's life.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>rescue,hero,Stupino,Moscow,Russia,bravery,car,burning,girl,locked,relative,danger,quick,action,courage,community,vigilance,crisis,selfless,honor</media:keywords>
                          <media:city> Stupino, Moscow</media:city>
                          <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Rescue</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Wed, 7 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>2229</guid>
                          <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 16:54:33 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/6fa0e9ac-f454-4ce2-8412-c2de8ed3f17b.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/ebe2b5d1-68fd-440f-af38-251f331c9540.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Trapped in art: dramatic rescue as man stuck in Edmonton's Talus Dome Sculpture</media:title>
                          <media:description>In a bizarre incident on April 10th, 2023, a man found himself trapped inside a unique piece of public art in Edmonton, Alberta, Canada. The sculpture in question was the Talus Dome, composed of large silver spheres. @cwks, an ultra runner who happened to be nearby, documented the incident on his phone and got a closer look at the trapped individual. The man inside the structure was reported to be in a state of panic, resembling a mouse trapped in a bucket.

Edmonton firefighters swiftly responded to the scene around 8:30 p.m. that evening. The stranded man was stuck within the mound of polished stainless steel balls with no apparent means of escape. Schwindt, intrigued by the commotion, approached the firefighters and inquired about the situation. Upon learning that it was indeed a person trapped inside, he began capturing the unfolding events on his phone. Observing the trapped man's distress, Schwindt likened the scene to witnessing a panicked creature in confinement.

The rescue operation unfolded as the firefighters diligently worked to extricate the trapped individual from the Talus Dome sculpture. With their expertise, they managed to free the man from his confining predicament. Following his rescue, the man was subsequently arrested, though specific details regarding the reasons for his detainment were not disclosed.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>trapped,art,sculpture,spheres,Edmonton,Alberta,Canada,firefighters,commotion,rescue,incident,silver,stainless steel,panic,documentation,surreal,arrest,public,unusual,bizarre,curiosity</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Edmonton, Alberta</media:city>
                          <media:country>Canada</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>CA</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>ODD</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Rescue</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>2213</guid>
                          <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 16:31:48 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/25e2b5a2-53e6-4b1e-a80e-666ea7a16b80.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/75eb58c8-5837-4022-a5fe-59f19d2ea886.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Unlikely luck: rescuers save kitten trapped in metal pipe</media:title>
                          <media:description>In a heartwarming incident captured by @phillyfoodgirl, a small kitten found itself trapped in a precarious situation inside a metal pipe in Philadelphia, USA. The video, shared on May 27, 2023, showcased the intense moments of the rescue operation. The desperate cries of the distressed kitten echoed through the pipe until the skilled rescuers stepped in.

With a sense of urgency, the rescuers skillfully cut through the pipe, allowing the tiny feline to come into view. The sight of the kitten, sitting at the bottom of the pipe, tugged at the heartstrings of all who witnessed the video. As one of the rescuers gently retrieved the scared kitten, it was evident that luck had been on their side. The caption accompanying the video, "I can't believe the cat distribution system finally picked us," highlighted the overwhelming relief and gratitude for the successful rescue.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>rescue,kitten,trapped,metal pipe,Philadelphia,video,meowing,cut,view,removed,luck,cat,distribution,system,captured,small,bottom,grateful,compassion,grateful,heartwarming</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Philadelphia</media:city>
                          <media:country>United States</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>US</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Rescue</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Sat, 27 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>2189</guid>
                          <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 20:48:22 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/6952e581-e893-4c15-bc8a-d39682373d6b.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/da54c29a-a3c7-4907-b48c-0be28632363a.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Dramatic rescue: girl saved from 15th floor window ledge by heroic rescuers in Kursk</media:title>
                          <media:description>In a heart-stopping incident on 31st May, 2023 in Kursk, Russia, a young girl's life hung in the balance as she sat precariously on the window ledge of a 15th-floor apartment. Swift action from the emergency services and a heroic rescue operation prevented a tragedy from unfolding. The Ministry of Emergency Situations received a distress call, prompting firefighters, psychologists, police, and paramedics to rush to the scene. After four intense hours of negotiation, the girl slipped and fell, but quick reflexes from the rescuers saved her from a fatal plunge. Gripping her hands as she dangled perilously, they managed to secure her on a lower floor before eventually dragging her back to safety. This unprecedented operation, carried out by dedicated firefighters and rescuers, concluded in a matter of tense minutes, leaving those involved with a renewed appreciation for life and the bravery required to protect it.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>rescue,girl,window,ledge,firefighters,psychologists,police,paramedics,emergency,negotiation,fall,perilous,reflexes,safety,unprecedented,operation,tense,minutes,life,bravery</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Kursk</media:city>
                          <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Rescue</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Wed, 31 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>2171</guid>
                          <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 09:57:19 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/261b04eb-d801-4da0-9995-fc919ddb094c.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/60f5103e-12bf-4709-bf0c-22c1b8998387.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Heroic rescue: man saves stranded calf from torrential floods in Dagestan</media:title>
                          <media:description>In a heartwarming incident amidst the devastating heavy rains that recently struck Dagestan, Russia, a small calf found itself in a life-threatening situation as it fell into the raging Sulak River on 31st May, 2023. Fortunately, an alert eyewitness noticed the struggling animal and quickly sprung into action to save it from the treacherous currents.

The footage portrays the calf desperately fighting against the turbulent waters, occasionally being submerged as it tumbled downstream. The person behind the camera, recognizing the dire situation, made a courageous decision to intervene and ensure the calf's safety. With swift and determined actions, the rescuer covered the shivering animal with a blanket, providing warmth and comfort. The rescuer's care extended further as they even delicately wiped the calf's nose with a napkin.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>rains,mudflows,bridges,destruction,calf,Sulak River,eyewitness,rescue,video,views,frames,current,animal,blanket,warmth,barbecue,nose,napkin,compassion,bond</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Dagestan</media:city>
                          <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Rescue</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Wed, 31 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>2168</guid>
                          <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 18:13:19 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/3eb40c47-be95-482b-8acf-356d1bd8e14a.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2168.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Heroic dog leads owners to emaciated bear cub in Irkutsk</media:title>
                          <media:description>In a heartwarming incident in Irkutsk, Russia, on 29th May, 2023, a courageous dog led its owners to a pitiful sight—an emaciated bear cub struggling for survival. The specialists from the Irkutsk Zoo were on a routine trip to the forest when their loyal "nanny dog," named Elsa, unexpectedly encountered the distressed forest dweller. This remarkable discovery left the team astonished yet determined to rescue the bear cub from its dire condition. Lyudmila Ivushkina captured the video footage of the rescue.

According to Lyudmila Ivushkina, the director of the zoo gallery, the bear cub, believed to be a female, had been separated from her mother, likely due to hunters who had taken her life. Abandoned and alone, the cub's frail condition left her with only a day to live without intervention. Typically weighing around 15 kilograms at this age, the foundling weighed a mere 3.5 kilograms. Thankfully, the bear cub is now safe and receiving care at the "House of Nature," with plans underway to provide her a new home within the zoo.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>bear,cub,dog,rescue,emaciated,Irkutsk,forest,specialists,zoo,trip,unexpected,nanny,owner,hunters,critical,condition,weight,home,heartwarming,bond</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Irkutsk</media:city>
                          <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Rescue</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Mon, 29 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>2142</guid>
                          <pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 13:19:16 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/605d3a10-4950-4eb6-9c8e-ff9d29c3f298.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/8201a8e4-7205-4184-9265-8fe078d6d93a.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Rescuing orphaned bear cub: a new addition to the mini shelter in Altai, Russia</media:title>
                          <media:description>The department of protection of the reserve received a call from one of the camp sites (near the village of Artybash, Turochaksky district of the Altai Republic), in which they said that for two days now a bear cub has been sitting on a tree on their territory.

Probably, his mother died and the bear cub came by itself, or one of the cubs was beaten off from an inexperienced bear by a dog and driven into a tree. One way or another, but there was no chance to find a mother in the immediate vicinity of the village of Artybash or to survive independently - the baby sat on a tree without food and water for several days, looking down in fear from a high cedar.

Employees of the Altai Reserve had to make a decision, act as quickly as possible and urgently leave for an operation to rescue the bear cub.

Catching even a small bear cub is not an easy task, because the new ward of the shelter, despite its small size, is a real wild beast with an impressive arsenal of claws and teeth, fiercely clinging to a tree and life. Thanks to the clear and well-coordinated actions of the state inspectors of the Altai Reserve, Igor Svetloyar and Ivan Kungurov, the bear cub was removed from the tree as quickly and accurately as possible and was safe. Immediately, on an emergency basis, an enclosure was prepared for the new ward, in which the cubs had been preparing for release into the wild for three years.

What's in store for this little frightened woolly ball, barely 4 months old, in the future? The main task of the reserve is not just to raise cubs to a certain age (and this is a difficult daily work), but also to do everything so that the output is not a pet, but a wild animal. The staff of the reserve note that this bear cub has every chance - the time of contact with a person was minimal. For cubs, escaping in trees is a natural reaction, since the main danger, in addition to humans and dogs, is their own relatives. Credit to: @Roman Vorobyov</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>Rescue,Orphaned,Bear cubs,Mini shelter,Altai,Russia,Credit,Roman Vorobyov,Altai Reserve,May holidays,Tourist base,Tree,Mother,Dogs,Staff,Operation,Cub,Enclosure,Future,Taiga,Wildlife,bear</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Altai</media:city>
                          <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Rescue</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Fri, 12 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>2111</guid>
                          <pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 18:21:46 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2111.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2111.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Duckling rescue operation in Moscow: four little ones safely reunited with parents</media:title>
                          <media:description>In a heartwarming incident in Moscow, Russia, four ducklings were rescued from a perilous situation in the southern part of the city on 19th May, 2023. According to the press service of the department for civil defense, emergency situations, and fire safety, the ducklings had fallen into a three-meter deep hole in a park opposite house number 17 on Serpukhovskaya Val Street. Thanks to the quick response of rescuers, the ducklings were successfully saved from the hole and reunited with their adult duck parents.

To retrieve the stranded ducklings, the rescuers devised a clever plan. They utilized a watering tractor that happened to be passing by and filled the hole with water. The rising water level provided a lifeline for the distressed ducklings, allowing them to float safely to the surface. The skillful execution of this technique ensured the successful rescue of all four ducklings.

Following the rescue operation, the firefighters handed over the precious ducklings to their concerned parents, the adult ducks.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>rescue,ducklings,hole,Moscow,Russia,south,park,Serpukhovskaya Val Street,firefighters,watering tractor,water,surface,reunited,parents,emergency,responders,volunteers,animals,safety,heartwarming</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Moscow </media:city>
                          <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Rescue</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Fri, 19 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>2101</guid>
                          <pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 13:43:14 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2101.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2101.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Local guard's heroic efforts save stranded dolphin at Recreio Beach</media:title>
                          <media:description>In a heartwarming display of courage and compassion, a local guard at Recreio Beach in Rio de Janeiro, Brazil, came to the rescue of a stranded dolphin. The incredible incident was captured on video by @Recreionosso on May 8th, 2023, and has since been shared widely, spreading hope and inspiring many.

The video begins with the distressing sight of a dolphin washed ashore, just inches away from the water's edge. Though still in the water, the dolphin was clearly could not swim back to safety on its own. It desperately needed assistance to survive. The local guard, recognizing the urgency of the situation, sprang into action without hesitation.

With a firm grip on the dolphin's tail, the guard quickly made his way towards the ocean, determined to lead the struggling mammal to deeper waters. However, the relentless waves proved to be a formidable opponent, repeatedly pushing the dolphin back to shallow waters. 

Finally, after a prolonged struggle, a powerful wave crashed onto the shore, sweeping the dolphin back into the ocean's embrace. It was a triumphant moment as the dolphin resurfaced and gracefully dove into the deep blue sea, free at last. Cheers erupted from onlookers as they witnessed the successful rescue unfold before their eyes.
</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>dolphin,rescue,beach,guard,stranded,waves,ocean,water,shallow,deep,courageous,compassion,hope,inspire,video,community,environment,biodiversity,marine,unity</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Recreio, Rio de Janeiro</media:city>
                          <media:country>Brazil</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>BR</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Rescue</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Mon, 8 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>2076</guid>
                          <pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 18:28:02 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2076.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2076.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Miraculous rescue: dog saved from oil-soaked peril in Birobidzhan</media:title>
                          <media:description>In a heart-wrenching incident that took place in Birobidzhan, Russia on the 10th of May 2023, a dog was rescued from a death trap. The poor creature had spent more than a day in a puddle of fuel oil and was barely alive when rescuers found it.

It was only by chance that the dog was spotted by a passerby who heard a weak whine coming from a nearby swamp. On closer inspection, the person discovered the dog with only half of its muzzle above the surface of the black, sticky oil.

The rescuers were alerted immediately, and they sprang into action, realizing the dog was in grave danger. After several attempts, they managed to reach the dog and begin the complex and risky operation of freeing it from the thick, viscous oil.

It took nearly an hour of careful work, but the rescuers managed to extricate the dog from its perilous situation. They were amazed that the animal had managed to survive for so long in such a toxic environment, and they immediately transported it to a veterinary hospital for emergency treatment.
</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>rescue,dog,death trap,fuel oil,whine,muzzle,swamp,operation,saved,puddle,complex,hour,precarious,chance,passerby,peril,viscous,toxic,recovery,grateful</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Birobidzhan</media:city>
                          <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Rescue</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Wed, 10 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>2064</guid>
                          <pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 18:21:46 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2064.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2064.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Rescue adventure: saving abandoned dog 'Muffy' and giving him a second chance at life</media:title>
                          <media:description>Laura Chapman, a resident of Hempstead, Texas, was driving to her family ranch on 30th March, 2023 when she spotted something fluffy in the grass. As she got closer, she realized it was an abandoned dog that was in dire need of help. The dog was filthy, matted, and limping, and it was evident that it had been left there to fend for itself.

Without wasting any time, Laura sprang into action and booked an emergency appointment with the vet. Upon examination, it was discovered that the dog had fleas, a torn ACL, and was estimated to be around three years old. The vet prescribed antibiotics to help the dog heal, and they also gave him a good shave. She shared the video on her social media handle @lauralashbrow.

Laura and her sister then set out to find the dog's owners. They spoke to locals around the area where the dog was found and had him scanned for a microchip, but unfortunately, they were unable to locate his previous owners. The area where the dog was found was known to be a common dumping ground for dogs, and there was another dog that had been abandoned close to where they found Muffy.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>rescue,adventure,abandoned,dog,Texas,vet,flea,ACL,microchip,owners,family,ranch,compassion,kindness,second chance,furry,matted,limping,adoption,heartwarming</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Hempstead, Texas</media:city>
                          <media:country>United States</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>US</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Rescue</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>2003</guid>
                          <pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2023 11:06:30 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2003.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2003.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Lucky man survives near-death experience in Rostov Region River</media:title>
                          <media:description>
In a shocking incident that took place on the outskirts of the village of Belaya Kalitva in the Rostov region, Russia, a man almost drowned in a river near a destroyed dam. The incident occurred on April 25, 2023, and eyewitnesses were quick to call for help.

The man was reportedly crossing the remains of the dam that was built back in Soviet times for a power plant that was never built. The destroyed dam still attracts citizens as it provides a means to cross the river. However, in some places, it requires crossing waist-deep water.

When the man reached a particularly deep section of the river, he began to choke on water and quickly started to drown. The eyewitnesses believed that he would not survive and called for the rescue team. The rescuers arrived promptly and pulled the man out of the water.

Despite the severity of the situation, the man survived, leaving the local residents amazed and grateful that he made it.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>river,dam,near-drowning,rescue,Rostov,Belaya Kalitva,infrastructure,safety,caution,Soviet,power plant,eyewitnesses,grateful,lucky,survivor,awareness,maintenance,danger,bridge,incident</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Rostov region  </media:city>
                          <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Rescue</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>1968</guid>
                          <pubDate>Sat, 29 Apr 2023 15:36:46 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/1968.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/1968.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Adventurous raccoon takes unusual route on Novokuznetsk bus, reunited with owner after overexposure</media:title>
                          <media:description>An exotic animal caused quite a stir at a bus stop in Novokuznetsk, Russia, as a raccoon was spotted attempting to board a bus. The incident occurred on April 20, 2023 but footage of the animal's antics only surfaced a week later, captivating viewers on social media.

Eyewitnesses reported that the raccoon appeared at the Tomusinskaya bus stop in the Novobaydayevsky microdistrict of Novokuznetsk. In the video, the raccoon is first seen trying to board a PiteAvto bus, only to be prevented from doing so. Undeterred, the raccoon then makes its way to a nearby work bus, where it successfully gains entry.

While some bystanders found the raccoon's behavior amusing, others expressed concern for its safety. After being taken away for overexposure, the raccoon's owner was eventually located.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>raccoon,bus,Novokuznetsk,Russia,exotic,animal,driver,work,overexposure,owner,pets,danger,welfare,habitat,environment,protection,law,illegal,social media</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Novokuznetsk</media:city>
                          <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Rescue</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>1962</guid>
                          <pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 18:21:46 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/1962.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/1962.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Unconventional rescue: man uses chainsaw to save cat stuck in tree branch in Krasnodar</media:title>
                          <media:description>A video of an extraordinary cat rescue in Krasnodar, Russia has gone viral on social media. The footage shows a cat stuck on a high tree branch, seemingly unable to descend on its own. Fortunately, a brave man with a chainsaw came to the rescue and managed to save the feline.

The video, which was filmed on Wednesday afternoon, April 26, shows the man climbing up the tree with a chainsaw. He carefully made his way towards the cat, who appeared to be frightened and hesitant to move. The man eventually reached the branch on which the cat was sitting and cut it down with his chainsaw. The branch fell to the ground along with the cat, who scampered away without any apparent injuries.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>cat,rescue,Krasnodar,Russia,chainsaw,bravery,compassion,kindness,animals,community,social media,video,viral,tree,branch,safety,precautions,gratitude,admiration,rescue</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Krasnodar </media:city>
                          <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>ODD</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Rescue</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>1956</guid>
                          <pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 18:21:46 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/1956.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/1956.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Rescuing a sloth: Claudia Pereira's heroic act on a Brazilian road</media:title>
                          <media:description>In a heartwarming act of kindness, Claudia Pereira rescued a sloth in the middle of a road in Coqueiro Seco, Alagoas, Brazil. The incident occurred on the 11th of February, 2023 and was captured on video by @claudiapereira2020, which has since gone viral on social media.

In the video, Pereira can be seen approaching the sloth, which was lying on the tarmac road without moving. She carefully takes the sloth by its back and carries it to some vegetation cover alongside the road. The sloth, seemingly grateful for the help, starts moving once placed on the vegetation.

Sloths are known for their slow movement and their inability to move quickly, which often puts them in harm's way. Pereira's quick thinking and compassionate actions saved the sloth from a potentially dangerous situation. Credit to: @claudiapereira2020</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>sloth,rescue,kindness,compassion,Brazil,road,danger,vegetation,gratitude,heroism,viral,video,social media,wildlife,protection,Alagoas,Coqueiro Seco,slow,vulnerable,grateful</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Coqueiro Seco, Alagoas</media:city>
                          <media:country>Brazil</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>BR</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Rescue</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Sat, 11 Feb 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>1951</guid>
                          <pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 18:21:46 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/1951.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/1951.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Petersburg man bravely rescues drowning dog in Serebryany Pond Park</media:title>
                          <media:description>In a heartwarming display of bravery and kindness, a man in St. Petersburg rescued a dog from drowning in a local park on Friday, April 14. The incident occurred in the Serebryany Pond park, a popular spot in the Vyborgsky district of the city.

The rescue was caught on video and quickly circulated on social media, with many people praising the man for his heroism. In the footage, the man can be seen diving into the water to save the dog, who was struggling to stay afloat. He quickly grabbed the animal and brought it to the shore, where it was reunited with its grateful owner.

Locals in the area have affectionately nicknamed the park "Serebka," and it is a well-known spot for walking dogs and enjoying the outdoors.

The man's bravery and quick thinking likely saved the dog's life, and his actions have earned him praise and admiration from the community. The video of the rescue has been shared widely on social media, with many people expressing their gratitude to the man for his selfless act. Credit to: @Ольга</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>st. petersburg,russia,dog,rescue,pond,park,serebryany,hero,bravery,kindness,video,social media,community,pet,swimming,water,outdoors,gratitude,selfless,act</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>St. Petersburg</media:city>
                          <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>undefined</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>undefined</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Rescue</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>1921</guid>
                          <pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 18:21:46 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/1921.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/1921.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Man rescued from deep pit at construction site in Yakutia, Russia</media:title>
                          <media:description>In the early evening hours of April 18th, 2023, a man fell into a deep pit at a construction site in Yakutia, Russia. The guard on duty was doing his night rounds when he stumbled into the hole, which was deep enough to make it impossible for him to climb out on his own.

Upon receiving the distress call, a team of rescuers from the Ministry of Emergency Situations in the Republic of Sakha (Yakutia) arrived at the site. They quickly assessed the situation and began to formulate a plan to rescue the victim.

The pit was 12 to 15 meters deep, which meant that the rescuers had to use climbing equipment to reach the victim. One of the rescuers descended into the pit, carefully navigating the narrow space to reach the victim. Once he was close enough, he tied a safety harness around the victim and secured it to himself, ensuring that the victim would not fall further.

The other rescuer then carefully guided the two men up to the surface, using a system of pulleys and ropes to ensure their safety. The operation was tense and delicate, with the slightest mistake potentially causing the harness to come loose, putting both men at risk.

Fortunately, the rescue was successful, and the victim was handed over to the waiting medical team.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>construction,site,pit,accident,rescue,Yakutia,Russia,emergency,team,climbing,equipment,guard,night,rounds,deep,hole,safety,harness,medical,hospital</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Yakutia</media:city>
                          <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>undefined</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>undefined</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Rescue</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Tue, 18 Apr 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>1920</guid>
                          <pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 18:21:46 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/1920.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/1920.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Miraculous rescue: kitten freed from car engine after being trapped with injured paw</media:title>
                          <media:description>In a heartwarming incident that occurred in Moscow, Russia, on 10th March, 2023, a group of rescuers successfully extracted a trapped kitten from a car engine. The tiny feline had been stuck in the engine valve and was unable to free itself.

The distressed meows of the kitten were heard by the car's owner, who quickly called for assistance. The specialists arrived promptly and worked tirelessly to free the trapped animal. After a few moments of intense effort, the rescuers were able to remove the kitten from the engine and get it to safety.

Once the kitten was removed, it was immediately taken to a veterinary clinic for a full examination. The examination revealed that the kitten had suffered a serious injury to its paw joint due to its extended period of entrapment. However, the veterinarians expressed optimism that the kitten would make a full recovery with proper medical attention.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>rescue,kitten,car,engine,meow,owner,specialists,veterinarians,valve,paw,damage,video,brave,dedication,hardwork,empathy,kindness,compassion,furryfriends,safety</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Moscow</media:city>
                          <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>undefined</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>undefined</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Rescue</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>1889</guid>
                          <pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 18:21:46 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/1889.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/1889.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Fishermen save elk from bear attack in Far East Russia</media:title>
                          <media:description>In a heart-stopping moment captured on video by a group of fishermen on 11th April, 2023 in Far East, Russia, an elk was rescued from a bear attack.

The incident occurred as the elk was running along a mountain river with a bear in hot pursuit along the shore. The fishermen, who were in the area at the time, noticed the chase and immediately sprang into action.

Realizing the danger, the fishermen began shouting loudly at the bear, hoping to scare it away from the elk. Fortunately, their plan worked and the bear ran off in the opposite direction, allowing the moose to escape unharmed.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>far east,russia,fishermen,elk,bear,chase,mountain river,video,shout,predator,scare,escape,wildlife,conservation,protection,bravery,social media,encounter,natural world,responsibility</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Far East</media:city>
                          <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>undefined</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>undefined</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Rescue</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>1876</guid>
                          <pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 18:21:46 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/1876.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/1876.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Stray dog found by the river and taken home by kind-hearted individual</media:title>
                          <media:description>On April 4th, 2023, @osiel_ivan_malagon a resident of a small town near the river, found a stray dog near the shore. According to the author, the dog looked dilapidated and disoriented, as if it had been hit by a car or suffered some other kind of trauma. @osiel_ivan_malagon, who is known in the community for his love of animals, decided to take the dog home and provide it with shelter, food, and water, as there were no open vet services in the area at the time.

The dog seemed to have no identification or collar. The author suspected that the dog might have been abandoned or lost for a long time, as it was thin, dirty, and had some cuts and bruises on its body. The man has started to care for it as his own pet and promises to give updates on the well-being of the dog. Credit to: @osiel_ivan_malagon</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>dog rescue,animal welfare,kindness,compassion,stray dog,community support,pet adoption,veterinary care,animal shelter,injury recovery,pet ownership,abandoned pets,animal rescue,riverbank,first-aid,nurturing,animal love,social media,heartwarming,responsible ownership</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Springfield</media:city>
                          <media:country>USA</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>undefined</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>undefined</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Rescue</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Tue, 4 Apr 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>1864</guid>
                          <pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2023 11:06:30 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/1864.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/1864.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Police in St. Petersburg save man attempting to jump off roof</media:title>
                          <media:description>In a heart-stopping scene in St. Petersburg, police officers managed to save a young man who was on the brink of jumping off the roof of a building on Chernyakhovskogo Street on April 10, 2023.

The incident was brought to the attention of the authorities by concerned residents in the area who spotted the man hanging precariously off the edge of the building's roof. A police patrol was immediately dispatched to the scene, which included Deputy Head of Public Order Protection at the Main Directorate of the Ministry of Internal Affairs for the Central District of St. Petersburg, Police Major Denis Sorokin, and Police Lieutenant Alexander Gres, who was part of the mobile unit.

Upon arrival, the officers quickly sprang into action, running across the roof to reach the man. They first attempted to talk him down, urging him not to go through with the fatal act. When that didn't work, they resorted to physically grabbing him and pulling him back from the edge.

In a video of the incident, Lieutenant Gres can be heard saying, "Give me your hand, brother. My name is Sanya, let me help you. Put down the knife, throw it away. Come on, get up, my friend. Come on, Serega."

Thankfully, the officers were able to successfully pull the man back from the edge and secure him in handcuffs. He was then taken into custody and handed over to paramedics for medical evaluation.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>St. Petersburg,police,save,man,jump,roof,Chernyakhovskogo,patrol,deputy,public,order,protection,mobile,unit,talk,physical,grab,handcuffs,paramedics,bravery,rescue</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Saint Petersburg</media:city>
                          <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>undefined</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>undefined</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Rescue</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>1834</guid>
                          <pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 18:21:46 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/1834.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/1834.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Teenagers rescued from drifting ice floe in Orenburg, Russia</media:title>
                          <media:description>Three teenagers in Orenburg, Russia were rescued from a drifting ice floe on March 24, 2023, thanks to the efforts of emergency responders.

The boys had been walking on thin ice when they found themselves in the middle of the Ural River, unable to make their way back to the shore. The Main Directorate of the Ministry of Emergency Situations of Russia for the Orenburg Region, the 2nd fire and rescue unit, the State Inspectorate for Small Vessels, and the Emergency and Rescue Service of the Orenburg Region all responded to the emergency call.

The rescue operation was successful and the ice floe, along with the teenagers, was washed ashore near the railway bridge. The Ministry of Emergency Situations reported that the teenagers were able to get to shore on their own and were unharmed.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>Orenburg,Russia,teenagers,ice floe,Ural River,rescue,emergency responders,thin ice,caution,outdoor safety</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Orenburg</media:city>
                          <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>undefined</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>undefined</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Rescue</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Fri, 24 Mar 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>1761</guid>
                          <pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 18:21:46 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/1761.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/1761.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Dramatic Rescue Caught on Camera in Moscow's Losiny Ostrov Park</media:title>
                          <media:description>In a heartwarming tale of rescue and survival, a team of dedicated rescuers in Moscow, Russia, came to the aid of an elk that had fallen through the ice in the Losiny Ostrov park.

Eyewitnesses were quick to spot the struggling animal and immediately called for help. The rescuers arrived on the scene, equipped with the tools and expertise necessary to rescue the animal.

After cutting a path through the ice, the rescuers worked tirelessly to pull the elk to safety. Using a rope, they were able to carefully guide the animal out of the icy water and onto solid ground. The team of rescuers had saved the animal's life, and in the process, they had given him a name - Yegorka.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>Moscow,Russia,Rescuers,Elk,Ice,Losiny Ostrov park,Yegorka,Eyewitnesses,Rope,Survival</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Moscow</media:city>
                          <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>undefined</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>undefined</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Rescue</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Mon, 20 Mar 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>1742</guid>
                          <pubDate>Thu, 06 Apr 2023 09:28:34 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/1742.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/1742.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>A remarkable rescue: the UK ISAR team made a tunnel route that saved lives in Turkey</media:title>
                          <media:description>In times of crisis, it takes the best of humanity to step up and help those in need. On the morning of February 11, 2023, the UK International Search and Rescue (ISAR) team proved just that. Responding to a call for help in Antakya, Turkey, they quickly sprung into action to rescue casualties trapped under rubble. What sets this rescue apart, however, is the remarkable tunnel route they created to reach the trapped individuals.

Malcolm Russell, who was a member of the UK ISAR team, made an amazing video of the rescue effort. The video shows how hard the rescue workers had to work to get through the rubble and debris to get to the people who needed help.

As they worked together, digging with their bare hands and using shovels and other equipment to create a passage through the rubble. As the tunnel progresses, the team discovers one of the casualties trapped beneath the rubble. The video shows a man, covered in dust and debris, lying on his back. The team quickly assesses his condition, and they work diligently to free him from the rubble.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>UK ISAR Team,Rescue,Tunnel,Route,Turkey,Rubble,Casualties,Trapped,Help,Action,Debris,Condition</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Antakya</media:city>
                          <media:country>Turkey</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>undefined</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>undefined</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Rescue</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Sat, 11 Feb 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>1614</guid>
                          <pubDate>Invalid Date</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1614.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1614.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>An infant who had been stuck under rubble for 139 hours was saved by rescuers in Turkey</media:title>
                          <media:description>In a heartbreaking scenario that lasted nearly six days, rescue teams in Hatay, Turkey, successfully rescued a 7-month-old baby from the rubble on February 11, 2023. The rescue operation had been underway since the baby was reported missing and trapped in the rubble, following a disaster that left the city in a state of chaos.

The search for the missing baby was a joint effort between the local authorities, volunteers, and emergency responders. The rescue teams worked tirelessly, putting in round-the-clock efforts to locate the baby and get her to safety. Despite the difficulties posed by the treacherous conditions of the rubble, the rescue teams did not give up. They used advanced technology and equipment to dig through the debris, listening closely for any sounds that could indicate the baby's location.

Finally, after 139 hours of intense searching and digging, the rescue teams heard the faint cries of the baby. They quickly worked to free her from the rubble and bring her to safety. The video of the rescue was captured by @kocaelibld and has since been widely shared on social media, garnering widespread praise and admiration for the rescue teams.

The baby was rushed to a nearby hospital, where she received medical attention and was declared to be in stable condition. The news of the baby's rescue was met with relief and joy by the local community, which had been praying and hoping for a positive outcome. The rescue teams were hailed as heroes, with many taking to social media to express their gratitude and thanks.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>Rescue,Turkey,Infant,Rubble,Search,Joint effort,Hospital,Hero,Praise,Earthquake,Dig,Baby,Disaster</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Hatay</media:city>
                          <media:country>Turkey</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>undefined</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>undefined</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Rescue</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Sat, 11 Feb 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>1599</guid>
                          <pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 18:21:46 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1599.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1599.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                         </channel>
                      </rss>
                    