<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
        xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
        xmlns:openSearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearchrss/1.0/"
        xmlns:dfpvideo="http://api.google.com/dfpvideo"
        xmlns:tms="http://data.tmsapi.com/v1.1"
        version="2.0">
         <channel>
           <title>ViralBear videos</title>
           <dfpvideo:version>2</dfpvideo:version><item>
             <media:title>Hailstorm halts play: Coors Field transformed into winter wonderland as Rockies await Dodgers</media:title>
             <media:description>On June 29th, 2023, Coors Field in Denver, Colorado, USA, experienced a severe hailstorm that interrupted the preparations for the Colorado Rockies' game against the Los Angeles Dodgers. 
 @KelsWingert captured a video of hail pouring into the press box, with thick hail covering the field and seats. Despite the challenging weather conditions, the forecast looked promising for game time. Coors Field workers were seen diligently filling buckets with the mixture of water and hail that blocked the dugout doors to the home clubhouse. Colorado Rockies catcher Elias Diaz even took an adventurous dive into the small hail on the field. As the storm subsided, the stadium transformed into a temporary winter wonderland as everyone awaited the resumption of the game at 6 p.m.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>hailstorm,Coors Field,Denver,Colorado,USA,weather,severe,thunderstorm,hail,press box,game,forecast,field,seats,workers,buckets,clubhouse,Rockies,Dodgers,dive,winter wonderland</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Denver, Colorado</media:city>
             <media:country>United States</media:country>
             <media:regionCode>US</media:regionCode>
            <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>      
             <media:category>Weather</media:category>
             <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
             <media:filmingDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2345</guid>
             <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 10:18:46 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/0a43c7aa-7d0f-4e52-acba-9f56426fa81c.jpg" />
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/a411fda8-3b34-4d53-ac5e-c94ecfe8ada2.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Ashes chaos: environmental activists disrupt play at Lord's Cricket Ground"</media:title>
             <media:description>During the second Ashes cricket test between England and Australia at Lord's cricket ground in London, UK, on June 28th, 2023, chaos ensued when two protesters from the environmental group "Just Stop Oil" stormed onto the field. The activists attempted to spread orange powder on the pitch but were quickly thwarted by players from both teams. England's wicketkeeper, Jonny Bairstow, took down one protester and carried them approximately 50 meters before handing them over to security who carried hi away as captured by  @chaguejones. Meanwhile, Australia's David Warner and England's captain, Ben Stokes, managed to corral the other protester. Play was disrupted for a brief period before the situation was brought under control.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>protest,cricket,disruption,activism,Ashes,Lord's,London,UK,environmental,oil,powder,players,security,chaos,field,activists,England,Australia,tackle,intervention,corral</media:keywords>
             <media:city>London</media:city>
             <media:country>United Kingdom</media:country>
             <media:regionCode>GB</media:regionCode>
             <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
             <media:category>News</media:category>
             <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
             <media:filmingDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2344</guid>
             <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 09:05:02 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/b6e902ad-ff80-442c-85c7-db6f58da537e.jpg" />
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/024bbab6-0971-4624-8fc7-ad04302cbd1f.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Sea Paradise Festival ignites Quy Nhon City: spectacular fireworks draw crowds and cause traffic on Reunification Day</media:title>
             <media:description>Quy Nhon City Center in Binh Dinh province, Vietnam, came alive on April 30th, 2022, as the Sea Paradise Festival unfolded with a mesmerizing display of fireworks as captured by @tksdo.04. The occasion was none other than Reunification Day, attracting throngs of people who eagerly gathered in the streets to witness the spectacular event. However, the surge in attendance resulted in overcrowding, leading to significant traffic jams throughout the city. Despite the challenges posed by the congestion, the people were eager to witness the celebration.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>fireworks,celebration,Reunification Day,festival,Quy Nhon,Binh Dinh,Vietnam,crowds,gathering,city center,traffic,chaos,overcrowding,mesmerizing,atmosphere,unity,joy,night sky,enchanting,spectacle</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Quy Nhon City </media:city>
             <media:country>Vietnam</media:country>
             <media:regionCode>VN</media:regionCode>
            <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>      
             <media:category>News</media:category>
             <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
             <media:filmingDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2022</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2342</guid>
             <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 19:20:30 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/8e4c248b-db47-490d-be6a-a88123de073a.jpg" />
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/adb3d819-afc2-4fc9-a2eb-1cc7434498e6.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Unusual sunbathing buddy: large lizard pet enjoys window peeping in Bandung, Indonesia</media:title>
             <media:description>A remarkable video captured by @reptilergabut on June 16, 2023, in Bandung, Indonesia, showcases a peculiar sight—a large lizard-like reptile peeping on a window. Surprisingly, the author claims that this reptile is their pet. The footage, recorded at their home while sunbathing, has left viewers astonished and curious of the unusual sunbathing buddy. </media:description>
             <media:keywords>reptile,lizard,pet,video,window,Bandung,Indonesia,sunbathing,captured,peeping,home,astonishing,curious,encounter,mysterious,unusual,footage,remarkable,tags,small</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Bandung</media:city>
             <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
             <media:regionCode>ID</media:regionCode>
            <media:categoryCode>ODD</media:categoryCode>      
             <media:category>Animals</media:category>
             <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
             <media:filmingDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2341</guid>
             <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 18:52:51 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/e28bf0d0-15a0-4377-a117-a74c5898d350.jpg" />
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/f6db2590-ef96-444a-bd6d-58605cb0eccf.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Laughing off ignored warnings: unforgettable chair tumble in East Kutai, Indonesia</media:title>
             <media:description>In a video captured by @ayufebrinaaaa on April 5th, 2023, from East Kutai, Indonesia, an unexpected chair mishap takes center stage. Despite repeatedly warning others about the chair's instability, the author was met with indifference and ignored. However, her prophetic words came true when she attempted to sit down, only to find herself falling hilariously. Despite the unexpected tumble, the author maintains a lighthearted spirit and continues to find amusement in the incident.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>chair,fall,video,home camera,warning,ignored,laughter,mishap,East Kutai,Indonesia,amusement,lighthearted,incident,hilarious,sitting,captured,complained,shared,@ayufebrinaaaa,April 5th</media:keywords>
             <media:city>East Kutai</media:city>
             <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
             <media:regionCode>ID</media:regionCode>
             <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
             <media:category>Fails and Funnies</media:category>
             <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
             <media:filmingDate>Wed, 5 Apr 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2340</guid>
             <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 18:27:07 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/b0335fb4-69df-4e17-a294-1c77d2de977e.jpg" />
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/5399cd66-d126-4c17-84fe-43dc61df0b2e.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Protests erupt in Sarcelles after teen's death: French police officer investigated for voluntary homicide</media:title>
             <media:description>Sarcelles, France - The streets of Sarcelles were engulfed in chaos and flames in the early hours of June 29th, 2023, as protestors took to the streets to express their anger over the killing of a 17-year-old boy by a French police officer. The incident, which occurred during a routine traffic stop in the Paris suburb of Nanterre, has ignited widespread unrest across the country. The officer responsible for the shooting has now been placed under formal investigation for voluntary homicide. As videos and images circulated on social media, capturing the intensity of the protests, one user with the handle @laviedunrv shared a video showing several cars engulfed in flames, accompanied by the caption, "it's us or them! The fight continues 95/92." President Emmanuel Macron hastily convened a crisis meeting with senior ministers in an attempt to address public anger, while protestors planned a tribute march to honor the young victim.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>protests,sarcelles,france,video,cars,fire,2:30am,fight,95/92,riots,police,killing,investigation,voluntary homicide,anger,tribute march,teenager,social media,crisis,inequality,unrest</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Sarcelles</media:city>
             <media:country>France</media:country>
             <media:regionCode>FR</media:regionCode>
             <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
             <media:category>News</media:category>
             <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
             <media:filmingDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2339</guid>
             <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 18:09:30 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/99e7b798-0e74-4e8c-ae1d-c9688f818a76.jpg" />
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/bf8c97e0-f918-45df-94bd-f2651cbe280c.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Startling workshop blast caught on camera!</media:title>
             <media:description>In a shocking incident captured on camera, a workshop in Nghe An province, Vietnam became the site of a sudden explosion. On March 17th, 2023, @nghenhanmockhoanghethuat, the owner of the workshop, was engrossed in his work on the opposite side of the room. Out of nowhere, an item he had plugged in on the table erupted in a violent explosion. As it turned out later, the battery exploded. Reacting swiftly, @nghenhanmockhoanghethuat cautiously made his way towards the switch and swiftly unplugged it, bringing an end to the dangerous situation. </media:description>
             <media:keywords>explosion,workshop,video,Nghe An province,Vietnam,@nghenhanmockhoanghethuat,March 17th,2023,danger,unplugged,table,incident,owner,camera,hazard,workspace,vigilant,responsive,shocking,small letters,tags</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Nghe An province</media:city>
             <media:country>Vietnam</media:country>
             <media:regionCode>VN</media:regionCode>
            <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>      
             <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
             <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
             <media:filmingDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2338</guid>
             <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 13:45:18 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/c42a4150-8f42-48bd-a75c-4d00c710f395.jpg" />
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/55e77597-13a8-4dc8-8b02-e2209ce35604.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>First steps by the shore: a father's love and a daughter's beach adventure</media:title>
             <media:description>In a heartwarming scene captured by @muoimuoi0306 on October 1st, 2021, at Vung Tau beach in Vietnam, a father and his just over one-year-old daughter shared a special moment. It was the little girl's first time at the beach, and her father gently carried her towards the shoreline. With a mix of excitement and trepidation, he set her down on the sand, allowing her to take her first steps on her own. However, as the waves rolled in, a sudden tide caught her off guard, causing her to stumble. But her father was there in an instant, scooping her up in his protective arms. From that point on, they continued their beach adventure together, with the father cradling his daughter as they enjoyed the rhythmic embrace of the tides. It was a beautiful display of a father's love and a precious memory that will surely be cherished for years to come.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>beach,family,father,daughter,love,milestone,joy,parenting,bonding,waves,tide,sand,first steps,adventure,Vung Tau,Vietnam,precious,memories,embrace,video</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Vung Tau</media:city>
             <media:country>Vietnam</media:country>
             <media:regionCode>VN</media:regionCode>
            <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>      
             <media:category>Heartwarming</media:category>
             <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
             <media:filmingDate>Fri, 1 Oct 2021</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2337</guid>
             <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 13:30:56 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/d614ddfe-a23b-4297-a7b0-6d546159f537.jpg" />
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/9bda8956-6224-4b9f-92a4-e9d6bc5f38ba.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Firework chaos erupts: rioters target Fresnes Prison entrance, sparking alarm and confusion near Paris</media:title>
             <media:description>Rioters unleashed mayhem at the entrance of Fresnes prison, located near Paris, France as captured in a video by @SuperR_pigeon on June 29th, 2023. The footage showcased the intense moment when the penitentiary center was bombarded with fireworks, setting off a piercing siren that spread confusion throughout the vicinity. The riot, marked by its brazen act of targeting the prison, highlighted the escalating unrest in the area following the shooting of a 17 year-old by the police. </media:description>
             <media:keywords>riots,fresnes,prison,fireworks,video,chaos,siren,confusion,entrance,Paris,protest,teenager,killing,cars,fire,Nanterre,unrest,authorities,residents,safety</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Fresnes</media:city>
             <media:country>France</media:country>
             <media:regionCode>FR</media:regionCode>
             <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
             <media:category>News</media:category>
             <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
             <media:filmingDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2336</guid>
             <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 12:57:37 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/c6d7de16-4a17-4e86-b229-80ffdbadd5f1.jpg" />
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/7e55249d-8b79-488f-a53d-594de96291ba.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Motherly cat takes kitten on a house adventure, returns it safely to siblings</media:title>
             <media:description>In a heartwarming scene captured by @izanzzz_ in Sleman, Yogyakarta, Indonesia on June 1st, 2023, a remarkable display of motherly instincts unfolded. A video showcased a cat, presumed to be the mother, carefully picking up a kitten and embarking on a gentle journey around the entire house. Initially, it seemed as though the mother was relocating her offspring, but to everyone's surprise, she returned the tiny feline to its original spot. The remarkable cat walked purposefully with the kitten in tow, ensuring its safety, before reuniting it with its siblings.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>cat,kitten,video,motherly,instincts,journey,house,tour,reunion,feline,bond,care,protection,love,animals,pets,adorable,heartwarming,Sleman,Yogyakarta</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Sleman, Yogyakarta</media:city>
             <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
             <media:regionCode>ID</media:regionCode>
            <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>      
             <media:category>Animals</media:category>
             <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
             <media:filmingDate>Thu, 1 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2335</guid>
             <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 12:29:13 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/58e91622-56f1-4cd0-9d5b-de5ed4f1001a.jpg" />
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/e404a538-53ca-47ae-9be2-2434d465e19b.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Barking heroes: dogs unite against bear to protect puppies in Yakutia</media:title>
             <media:description>In an extraordinary turn of events in Yakutia, Russia, a horrifying yet remarkable scene unfolded beneath the windows of a private house on June 20th, 2023. A hungry bear, viewing defenseless puppies as easy prey, underestimated the power of unity among a pack of dogs. In a valiant effort to safeguard their young, the dogs devised a strategy to distract the formidable predator, allowing the vulnerable pups to seek refuge. With the operator capturing the intense spectacle on camera, this astonishing display of canine heroism resulted in a heart-pounding and action-packed video, showcasing the unwavering bravery of these barking heroes.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>horror,film,dogs,puppies,Yakutia,Russia,pack,predator,bear,strategy,unity,refuge,operator,action,bravery,heroism,video,spectacle,intense,barking</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Yakutia</media:city>
             <media:country>Russia</media:country>
             <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
             <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
             <media:category>Animals</media:category>
             <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
             <media:filmingDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2334</guid>
             <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 11:55:45 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/8074409f-c8ec-4d7a-a67e-8920193d9367.jpg" />
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/f4429a68-7828-483b-abbb-ad45e79bbf31.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Michigan's skyline vanishes: Detroit engulfed in smoke as Canadian wildfires blanket the region</media:title>
             <media:description>Detroit, Michigan, USA - A video captured by @Michigameman313 on June 27th, 2023, reveals a disquieting sight as Michigan becomes shrouded in dense smoke originating from the ongoing wildfires in Canada. With the wildfires raging for several months now, more than a third of the US population, stretching from the Midwest to the East Coast, finds themselves under air quality alerts due to the pervasive reach of the Canadian wildfire smoke. The skyline of Detroit disappears behind a haze, casting an eerie atmosphere over the city as the impacts of the wildfires make their presence felt across the region.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>smoke,video,Detroit,Michigan,Canada,wildfires,air quality,alerts,Midwest,East Coast,USA,sight,shrouded,haze,skyline,eerie,atmosphere,impacts,region</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Detroit, Michigan </media:city>
             <media:country>United States</media:country>
             <media:regionCode>US</media:regionCode>
            <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>      
             <media:category>News</media:category>
             <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
             <media:filmingDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2333</guid>
             <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 11:49:32 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/462bf183-d2c6-405d-9566-0b611444c92d.jpg" />
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/f91c84a9-efc3-4579-b07a-49e02a604201.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Unforgettable graduation moment as boy mistakes canvas for Wall and takes a tumble</media:title>
             <media:description>In a heartwarming yet amusing incident captured on video on June 17th, 2023 during a school children's graduation ceremony in Sidoarjo, Indonesia, two kids stole the spotlight unintentionally. The footage, courtesy of @azizahzindy, shows a boy and a girl holding hands as they make their way across the stage. However, in an unexpected turn of events, the boy leaned onto what he thought was a solid wall—a hanging canvas board—but to his surprise, it gave way, resulting in a comical tumble. </media:description>
             <media:keywords>kids,graduation,ceremony,video,mishap,school,children,boy,girl,holding hands,canvas board,fall,funny,accident,Sidoarjo,Indonesia,laughter,unexpected,joyous,lightheartedness</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Sidoarjo</media:city>
             <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
             <media:regionCode>ID</media:regionCode>
             <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
             <media:category>Fails and Funnies</media:category>
             <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
             <media:filmingDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2332</guid>
             <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 19:21:19 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/600dbfd0-2813-4430-b6ca-6838a009cc1a.jpg" />
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/0ce1539d-23e5-48fb-a679-0e6fd87af308.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Unfazed foodie: dining through floodwaters in Johor Bahru</media:title>
             <media:description>In a remarkable display of nonchalance, a local resident in Johor Bahru, Malaysia, captured a video that showcased an open restaurant engulfed in floodwaters. The footage, recorded by @bobieeee991 on May 3rd, 2023, revealed diners calmly continuing their meal as water flowed on the road and even under their tables. Undeterred by the unexpected turn of events, the author and his friend carried on eating, as the flooding subsided shortly after it began.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>flooding,open restaurant,video,eating,flood waters,road,table,Malaysia,Johor Bahru,nonchalance,diners,meal,water,unexpected,resilience,adaptability,nature,intervention,harm,surreal</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Johor Bahru</media:city>
             <media:country>Malaysia</media:country>
             <media:regionCode>MY</media:regionCode>
            <media:categoryCode>ODD</media:categoryCode>      
             <media:category>Weather</media:category>
             <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
             <media:filmingDate>Wed, 3 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2331</guid>
             <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 18:38:03 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/b2b66ff8-ca26-4043-a462-aed24f22d0e4.jpg" />
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/4bf813c1-ec59-4270-969d-518bc41f5733.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Rescuing hope: a compassionate encounter with an abandoned dog in Los Angeles</media:title>
             <media:description>In a touching encounter in Los Angeles, California, USA @tiana_thebuglady stumbled upon an abandoned dog while walking through a neighborhood on June 24th, 2023. The emaciated dog approached her, standing on its hind legs, seeking comfort and sustenance. Touched by its plight, the author quickly fetched food and water from a nearby restaurant and returned to the dog. Devouring the meal and drinking eagerly, the dog's hunger and thirst were momentarily quelled. The author stayed with the dog, showering it with affection and promising to seek further help despite facing challenges in contacting animal services. </media:description>
             <media:keywords>abandoned,dog,kind,compassion,nourishment,emaciated,neighborhood,Los Angeles,food,water,restaurant,grateful,canine,comfort,affection,challenges,animal services,assistance,commitment,well-being</media:keywords>
             <media:city> Los Angeles, California</media:city>
             <media:country>United States</media:country>
             <media:regionCode>US</media:regionCode>
             <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
             <media:category>Rescue</media:category>
             <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
             <media:filmingDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2330</guid>
             <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 18:21:59 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/940507b3-f19d-464d-aad8-21069501fda7.jpg" />
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/e662af1e-da40-4b9e-bdab-ba41ed396356.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Adventures of Morty: the mischievous pancake bandit</media:title>
             <media:description>In a humorous video captured by @nas_sam on June 6th, 2020 in St. Petersburg, Russia, her mischievous feline companion named Morty, inspired by the popular show Rick and Morty, attempted to steal some pancakes from the table. Despite the owner's attempts to discourage this behavior, the cunning cat proved to be a persistent food thief. Fast forward to the present day in Uzbekistan, Morty's thieving antics continue, with no signs of stopping.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>kitten,stealing,food,table,wean,failed,Uzbekistan,Morty,Rick and Morty,three years old,video,captured,pancakes,cat,mischievous,thief,antics,household,humor,exasperation</media:keywords>
             <media:city>St. Petersburg</media:city>
             <media:country>Russia</media:country>
             <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
            <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>      
             <media:category>Animals</media:category>
             <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
             <media:filmingDate>Sat, 6 Jun 2020</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2329</guid>
             <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 17:57:32 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2dcb8344-5395-4202-8aef-9b0541cd617b.jpg" />
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/83aa1a18-073e-45db-9154-b09c05a255dd.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Playful pursuit: Sasuke the dog's hilarious chase with a clever crow</media:title>
             <media:description>In a delightful scene captured by @sasuke_2017.0808 on June 14th, 2023, in Tokyo, Japan, a video showcased the amusing encounter between a persistent dog named Sasuke and a clever black crow. The canine's excitement was sparked as it spotted the crow perched on the balcony. However, instead of flying away, the mischievous bird continuously relocated to different parts of the balcony, keeping Sasuke in a constant pursuit. The author, found great amusement in witnessing this comical interaction between his dog and the crafty crow, creating a moment filled with laughter and joy.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>dog,crow,chase,balcony,Tokyo,Japan,video,Sasuke,amusement,laughter,pets,animals,funny,entertaining,playful,clever,mischievous,owner,encounter,joy</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Tokyo </media:city>
             <media:country>Japan</media:country>
             <media:regionCode>JP</media:regionCode>
            <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>      
             <media:category>Animals</media:category>
             <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
             <media:filmingDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2328</guid>
             <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 17:36:10 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/7c1bad1f-9d05-4c66-bca4-754b7fa5d8d5.jpg" />
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/77ce2601-f34d-4050-a660-13c350ae6a0b.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Captivating lightning illuminates Fredericksburg's night sky, creating a dazzling display</media:title>
             <media:description>In a captivating video captured by @thegavinwhite24 on June 26th, 2023, in Fredericksburg, Virginia, USA, the night sky was momentarily transformed into a breathtaking spectacle. As the author drove through the darkness, a bolt of bright streak lightning shattered the tranquility, illuminating the surroundings with an intensity that rivaled daylight. Lasting a mere five seconds, this incredible display left the author in awe, capturing the attention of viewers worldwide. </media:description>
             <media:keywords>lightning,night,Fredericksburg,Virginia,USA,video,driving,bright,streak,sky,day,moment,captivating,intense,power,awe,wonder,nature,raw,spectacle</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Fredericksburg, Virginia</media:city>
             <media:country>United States</media:country>
             <media:regionCode>US</media:regionCode>
            <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>      
             <media:category>Weather</media:category>
             <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
             <media:filmingDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2327</guid>
             <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 08:21:00 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/04c6f5a9-23cf-4cdc-94cd-25f934369613.jpg" />
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/3a12df32-fd41-4f1c-b6e9-e320859c7403.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>A woman is very lucky at a pedestrian crossing in Omsk, Russia</media:title>
             <media:description>In a heart-stopping incident in Omsk, Russia, a pedestrian's life was spared by a stroke of luck. On June 15th, 2023, a reckless driver failed to notice the woman as he sped towards the pedestrian crossing. Just a few meters away, the driver abruptly hit the brakes, narrowly avoiding a catastrophic collision. The vehicle skidded to a halt, teetering on the brink of overturning, while the shaken woman looked on in disbelief. The incident has ignited calls for the installation of speed bumps in front of the crossing, in the hope that such measures might deter future reckless drivers and safeguard pedestrians from similar encounters.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>reckless,driver,pedestrian,high speed,slowing down,speed bumps,safety,guardian angel,video,woman,narrow escape,emergency brakes,overturn,incident,Omsk,Russia,MSCh 9,crossing,collision,vigilance</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Omsk</media:city>
             <media:country>Russia</media:country>
             <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
            <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>      
             <media:category>News</media:category>
             <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
             <media:filmingDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2326</guid>
             <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 08:10:46 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/ec700293-9ba9-4c39-a645-15e4a1198db0.jpg" />
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/e704584b-34fb-4611-9550-ae2ff4de109b.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Chasing the elements: spectacular double rainbow enchants Ontario's skies</media:title>
             <media:description>On June 26th, 2023, storm chaser @craigdunmore stumbled upon a mesmerizing sight near Staples, Ontario, Canada. Capturing the moment on video, he excitedly shared the footage of a double rainbow stretching across the sky. The day had already been filled with thrilling experiences, including a probable funnel and captivating cloud formations. However, it was this vivid display of nature's artistry that left the author in awe. With his chase day now complete, the enchanting double rainbow served as a breathtaking finale to an unforgettable adventure.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>rainbow,chase,storm,Ontario,Canada,video,beauty,clouds,mesmerizing,nature,artistry,enchanting,breathtaking,adventure,weather,double,vivid,finale,awesome,funnel</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Staples, Ontario</media:city>
             <media:country>Canada</media:country>
             <media:regionCode>CA</media:regionCode>
            <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>      
             <media:category>Weather</media:category>
             <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
             <media:filmingDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2325</guid>
             <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 07:57:14 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/580bdf7c-66d2-4e23-aad4-e01d2ada3d79.jpg" />
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2edc6cd6-bf93-4e0e-a0a9-1a1df9cda32b.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Unauthorized helicopter landing at gas station in Altai</media:title>
             <media:description>The Gorno-Altai transport prosecutor's office has launched an investigation into an incident involving a helicopter in the Aktash village of the Altai Republic, Russia. Eyewitnesses captured footage of a Robinson helicopter landing at a gas stationon June 9th, 2023, raising concerns about safety. The pilot's departure from the site was marked by a perilous maneuver near power lines. The West Siberian Transport Prosecutor's Office revealed that the landing and takeoff had taken place without the necessary authorization from the aviation department. As the audit unfolds, there is a possibility of a criminal case being initiated.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>helicopter,incident,investigation,Altai,Russia,gas station,eyewitnesses,footage,safety,pilot,departure,power lines,unauthorized,landing,takeoff,transport prosecutor's office,audit,criminal case,Aktash village,West Siberian</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Altai</media:city>
             <media:country>Russia</media:country>
             <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
            <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>      
             <media:category>News</media:category>
             <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
             <media:filmingDate>Fri, 9 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2324</guid>
             <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 20:36:42 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/815d1424-308e-4441-96dd-ab80a7270e1c.jpg" />
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/75804d0a-1020-4301-931a-df0cd10df364.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Man sets neighbor on fire with flamethrower, wounds woman with harpoon in Primorye, Russia</media:title>
             <media:description>A shocking incident unfolded in the Primorye region of Russia on June 26th, 2023, as a man ignited his neighbor with a flamethrower and grievously injured a woman with a harpoon. The disturbing events took place in the village of Trudovoy, Vladivostok urban district, during an investigation into electricity theft. Apparently provoked by the excavation of an electrical cable, one resident became enraged and resorted to menacing his neighbors with a homemade flamethrower. When a courageous neighbor attempted to disarm him, he was tragically engulfed in flames. Adding to the horror, the assailant managed to harm a woman with a harpoon before medical assistance could arrive.

Authorities swiftly responded to the incident, with the Primorsky Territory Prosecutor's Office confirming the initiation of a criminal case for attempted murder. Both the victims and the perpetrator were immediately admitted to a medical facility to receive necessary treatment. The gravity of the situation became evident as it was revealed that the neighbor who had been set on fire suffered extensive burns covering 60% of his body. The investigation into this distressing case has been placed under careful scrutiny, ensuring that justice is served for the victims involved.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>fire,flamethrower,harpoon,incident,Primorye,Russia,neighbor,attack,homemade,Vladivostok,theft,electricity,excavation,enraged,menace,injury,criminal case,medical assistance,burns,investigation</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Primorye</media:city>
             <media:country>Russia</media:country>
             <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
             <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
             <media:category>News</media:category>
             <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
             <media:filmingDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2323</guid>
             <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 20:13:45 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/b4fcf64b-e600-41b5-9ee0-c561384db999.jpg" />
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/e119c440-3a8a-4bcb-8196-2ddd24d66bcc.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Adorable surprise: little Valentina's birthday dance with cat melts hearts worldwide!</media:title>
             <media:description>In a heartwarming moment captured on camera, a small girl named Valentina stole the internet's heart as she danced with a cat at her mom's birthday party in Lancaster, Texas, USA. The adorable video, filmed by @rockysoto74 on  October 1, 2022 and shared on TikTok, showcased Valentina holding the cat by its fore legs, as if they were hugging, while dancing to her sister's favorite song. Little did the author know that the innocent video would go viral overnight, garnering immense love and attention from people around the world. Despite being an unintended surprise, Valentina's delightful dance with her feline friend resonated with viewers, spreading joy and warmth in a single, heartfelt moment.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>dance,cat,girl,viral,heartwarming,birthday,party,Texas,USA,video,TikTok,hug,favorite,song,surprise,love,attention,joy,warmth,moment</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Lancaster, Texas</media:city>
             <media:country>United States</media:country>
             <media:regionCode>US</media:regionCode>
            <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>      
             <media:category>Heartwarming</media:category>
             <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
             <media:filmingDate>Sat, 1 Oct 2022</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2322</guid>
             <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 19:48:19 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/69e155e9-a4fb-49de-b050-19fed0a49fbd.jpg" />
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/af8b06eb-b934-44a6-ae4b-543d06426ff2.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Rostov-on-Don zoo evacuates animals as fire engulfs building</media:title>
             <media:description>A devastating fire erupted at the Rostov-on-Don Zoo in Russia on June 26, 2023 resulting in the evacuation of all animals. The blaze originated in one of the zoo's buildings and quickly spread across an area spanning 300 square meters. Thankfully, no injuries were reported. However, extinguishing the fire proved to be a challenging task due to the presence of a power cable passing through the affected area. To combat the flames, 17 firefighting vehicles and a team of 48 individuals were mobilized by the Ministry of Emergency Situations. </media:description>
             <media:keywords>fire,evacuation,animals,Rostov-on-Don,Russia,Ministry of Emergency Situations,buildings,injured,rank,equipment,people,extinguishing,zoo,power cable,spread,area,challenging,blaze,vehicles,impact</media:keywords>
             <media:city> Rostov-on-Don</media:city>
             <media:country>Russia</media:country>
             <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
             <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
             <media:category>News</media:category>
             <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
             <media:filmingDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2321</guid>
             <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 12:50:06 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2ca802c0-23a6-4ba3-8ef2-6bc5fcc84b4a.jpg" />
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/c51ecb98-7de3-401f-8182-023d24143405.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Terrifying blaze engulfs Ajman One Tower 02 in UAE's Ajman City</media:title>
             <media:description>In the early evening hours of June 26, 2023, a massive fire erupted in Tower 02 of the Ajman One residential complex in Ajman, United Arab Emirates. A video captured by @Ali_Abdulla99 shows the building's corner engulfed in flames, with debris falling to the ground as emergency services rush to the scene. The fire, which quickly grew in intensity, was eventually brought under control after hours of relentless efforts. Fortunately, there are no casualties.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>fire,high-rise,residential,complex,Ajman,UAE,disaster,emergency,flames,video,footage,incident,authorities,panic,debris,inferno,firefighters,catastrophe,safety,evacuation</media:keywords>
             <media:city> Ajman City</media:city>
             <media:country>United Arab Emirates</media:country>
             <media:regionCode>AE</media:regionCode>
            <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>      
             <media:category>News</media:category>
             <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
             <media:filmingDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2320</guid>
             <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 12:43:00 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/eda64977-01ef-4c9e-a84e-cc55fe4142f7.jpg" />
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/731d0c1e-b814-483c-83bb-aa3d32326b18.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Enigmatic glitter: mysterious shiny object spotted hovering above Las Vegas</media:title>
             <media:description>On the night of June 21, 2023, a baffling spectacle unfolded in the skies over Las Vegas, captivating the attention of local residents. A video captured by @Big7media in Henderson, Nevada , USA, showcased a shimmering object, gleaming brightly amidst the darkness. The intriguing footage left viewers puzzled, prompting the photographer to seek answers. With a simple yet captivating caption, "Can anyone tell me what this was tonight over Las Vegas?" The mysterious shiny object, its origin and purpose shrouded in uncertainty, continues to fuel speculation and intrigue among those who witnessed this extraordinary event.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>las vegas,shiny object,mystery,night sky,video,speculation,intrigue,unidentified,flying object,celestial,phenomenon,social media,capture,enigmatic,radiant,puzzle,origin,captivating,speculation,curious</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Henderson, Nevada</media:city>
             <media:country>United States</media:country>
             <media:regionCode>US</media:regionCode>
             <media:categoryCode>ODD</media:categoryCode>
             <media:category>News</media:category>
             <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
             <media:filmingDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2319</guid>
             <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 12:18:15 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/1da1717a-cf07-4218-b324-07e19472557b.jpg" />
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/98927475-352d-4cca-9cf2-29de63987c3e.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Vibrant victory: Sporting CP handball team shakes up Portuguese Cup celebration bus!</media:title>
             <media:description>The Sporting CP handball team triumphed in the Portuguese Cup, and their exuberant celebration on a bus en route to the airport became a sight to behold. Captured in a video by @sportingcp.adeptos on June 12, 2023, in Santa Cruz, Madeira, Portugal, the victorious players' jubilation caused the entire bus to shake. The shaking was so intense that it jolted those seated inside, resulting in contagious laughter. The team's contagious joy and the unexpected bus tremors perfectly encapsulated the spirit of their Portuguese Cup victory.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>sporting,cp,handball,team,celebration,bus,portuguese cup,victory,video,shaking,laughter,santa cruz,madeira,portugal,triumph,exuberant,players,passengers,joy,tremors</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Santa Cruz, Madeira</media:city>
             <media:country>Portugal</media:country>
             <media:regionCode>PT</media:regionCode>
            <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>      
             <media:category>Sport</media:category>
             <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
             <media:filmingDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2318</guid>
             <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 05:25:19 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2318.jpg" />
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2318.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Mischievous mac n' cheese muncher: wombat breaks into camper's tent in Melbourne!</media:title>
             <media:description>In a surprising turn of events, a video captured by @charliefowlvr on June 24, 2023, in Melbourne, Australia, shows a cheeky wombat making its way into a camper's tent. The mischievous creature apparently had a craving for mac n' cheese, as it had chewed its way through the tent to get a taste of the cheesy delight. In the footage, the wombat's head can be seen peeking inside the tent, while its body remains outside. This unexpected encounter highlights the resourcefulness and determination of Australia's native wildlife, even when it comes to satisfying their unusual appetites.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>wombat,tent,Melbourne,Australia,video,mac n cheese,chewed,wildlife,encounter,curious,mischief,resourcefulness,appetites,unexpected,capture,cheeky,craving,taste,camper,head</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Melbourne</media:city>
             <media:country>Australia</media:country>
             <media:regionCode>AU</media:regionCode>
            <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>      
             <media:category>Animals</media:category>
             <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
             <media:filmingDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2317</guid>
             <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 05:00:05 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/25ed8c77-d811-4f5d-983f-d624ee57c5a3.jpg" />
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/c3722437-b69d-4adc-a6e4-971a6ab6d62f.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Rescuer's heartbreak: stranded dogs expose alarming animal dumping crisis in Texas</media:title>
             <media:description>In a heart-wrenching incident caught on camera by @regil2022 on April 30, 2023, in Conroe, Texas, USA, the grim reality of animal dumping was vividly revealed. While returning from taking her son to school, the author stumbled upon two dogs in distress on a secluded backroad. One of the canines was tragically chained to a tree, with a severely injured neck, while the other wandered aimlessly on the nearby road. The author, a dedicated animal rescuer for almost three years, documented the scene, shedding light on the rampant issue of animal abandonment in Texas. </media:description>
             <media:keywords>animal,dumping,texas,usa,dogs,stranded,chained,tree,injured,rescue,backroad,crisis,video,awareness,compassion,abandonment,protection,heroic,heartbreaking,documentary</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Conroe, Texas</media:city>
             <media:country>United States</media:country>
             <media:regionCode>US</media:regionCode>
             <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
             <media:category>Rescue</media:category>
             <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
             <media:filmingDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2316</guid>
             <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 04:42:00 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/e5606bef-f174-4f2f-8cbc-8b45b7dbb47f.jpg" />
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/32411880-f062-42ec-b5df-1b28c9af7d5f.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Captivating canine concert: witness the enchanting howl of a Weimaraner!</media:title>
             <media:description>In a charming display of canine vocal prowess, a Weimaraner in La Crosse, Wisconsin, USA, has captivated the internet with its melodious howl. Shared by @mizj3n on May 21st, 2023, a video captured the precious moment as the Weimaraner let out a soulful cry from the comforts of its home. The caption accompanying the footage reads, " You ever seen a Weimaraner howl?... Now you have." The enchanting video quickly garnered attention, drawing viewers into the captivating world of this elegant breed.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>weimaraner,dog,howl,video,La Crosse,Wisconsin,USA,mizj3n,captivating,enchanting,melodious,soulful,internet,moment,precious,caption,attention,breed,elegant,haunting,heartwarming</media:keywords>
             <media:city>La Crosse, Wisconsin</media:city>
             <media:country>United States</media:country>
             <media:regionCode>US</media:regionCode>
            <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>      
             <media:category>Animals</media:category>
             <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
             <media:filmingDate>Sun, 21 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2314</guid>
             <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 18:54:29 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/b26d2ddf-bb9e-472c-b048-66136fed54d7.jpg" />
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/af7d812c-a21e-4821-9de5-238246397706.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Close call: worker's near-death slip on wet floor caught on camera</media:title>
             <media:description>A heart-stopping moment was caught on camera as a worker in Saint-Jérôme, Quebec, Canada narrowly escaped a potentially fatal accident. In a video captured by @karellevarin on June 21st, 2023 the worker can be seen carrying plates of food from the kitchen when she suddenly slips on a wet floor. The dramatic footage shows her nearly losing her balance, but miraculously manages to regain control just in time.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>worker,slip,wet floor,CCTV,video,near-death,accident,Saint-Jérôme,Quebec,Canada,kitchen,food,plates,balance,danger,workplace,safety,reminder,incident,footage,control</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Saint-Jérôme, Quebec</media:city>
             <media:country>Canada</media:country>
             <media:regionCode>CA</media:regionCode>
             <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
             <media:category>Fails and Funnies</media:category>
             <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
             <media:filmingDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2313</guid>
             <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 18:20:32 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/1868592e-0e3b-481e-b907-7e8a72627749.jpg" />
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/eb6fb124-9aed-46e4-a6ab-e55766663bfa.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Furry fun in Moscow: Ares and Axel delight in toy tent playtime!</media:title>
             <media:description>German Spitz breeder, @black_night_pom, based in Moscow, Russia, shared an adorable video on June 17th, 2023. The clip showcased two-month-old puppies, Ares and Axel, who have been reserved and will soon be named Amur and Umka by their excited new owners. The breeder captured the heartwarming moment as the playful pups frolicked inside a toy tent, showcasing their youthful energy and boundless enthusiasm. It's a joy for any owner to witness their beloved furry companions grow and thrive, and this delightful video perfectly captures the pure delight and happiness of these precious German Spitz puppies.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>puppies,breeder,German Spitz,Moscow,Russia,video,reservation,Ares,Axel,Amur,Umka,owners,baby,grow,captured,dogs,playing,toy tent,happy,dogs</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Moscow </media:city>
             <media:country>Russia</media:country>
             <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
            <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>      
             <media:category>Animals</media:category>
             <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
             <media:filmingDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2312</guid>
             <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 18:00:24 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/5a5481d2-74a2-465c-beb5-c92627599d01.jpg" />
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2312.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Explosive chaos: massive fireworks mishap on Simferopol Highway sends shockwaves</media:title>
             <media:description>A disastrous incident unfolded on the night of June 23, 2023, as chaos erupted on the Simferopol highway (M-2) between Podolsk and the village of Aleksandrovka in the Moscow region, Russia. The calamity originated when a trailer, laden with pyrotechnics, detached from a truck traveling towards Moscow. The jolting caused by the explosive cargo potentially triggered the detonation, although the exact cause remains uncertain.

At approximately 23:45, the trailer became unhinged at the 42nd kilometer mark of the Simferopol highway, leading to a fiery accident. The driver, sensing trouble, swiftly maneuvered to the roadside and hastily abandoned the cab. For the next half an hour, a dazzling yet perilous fireworks display unfolded, with volleys detonating around the burning wreckage. Astonishingly, despite the reverberations being heard within a five-kilometer radius, no other vehicles were harmed. The prompt response from the fire department managed to quell the open flames by 00:34. Thankfully, the proximity of the incident to the surrounding forest, coupled with the region's prolonged drought, did not ignite a potentially catastrophic forest fire. By morning, the remnants of the trailer and cab were carefully dismantled and removed from the road, ensuring minimal disruption to traffic.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>trailer,accident,fire,pyrotechnics,detonation,emergency,truck,explosion,highway,fireworks,performance,cab,volleys,sound,surprise,burning,forest,drought,remains,traffic</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Moscow region</media:city>
             <media:country>Russia</media:country>
             <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
            <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>      
             <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
             <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
             <media:filmingDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2311</guid>
             <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 17:35:05 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/7b626fae-d959-4613-bcba-ddc0ae1af6f0.jpg" />
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2a154364-32cb-45de-a866-abd706da10bb.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Indiana's terrifying encounter: Door Dasher captures heart-stopping tornado on video</media:title>
             <media:description>On 26th June, 2023 in Indiana, USA, a Door Dasher named @SlickReynolds found himself in the midst of a horrifying encounter with nature's fury. As he went about his delivery duties, an approaching tornado caught his attention. With awe and trepidation, he recorded the swirling monstrosity descending from the ominous clouds. The video, although unable to fully convey the true magnitude of the spectacle, captured the imminent danger he faced. The violent tornado, responsible for the loss of one life, wreaked havoc as it touched down in Martin County and Johnson County. This devastating event unfolded just a day after powerful storms ravaged a significant portion of the country, leaving a trail of destruction and claiming the lives of at least three individuals.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>tornado,indiana,usa,video,capture,swirling,clouds,door dash,danger,havoc,storms,devastation,tragedy,martin county,johnson county,weather,northeast,mid-atlantic,death,destruction</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Indiana</media:city>
             <media:country>United States</media:country>
             <media:regionCode>US</media:regionCode>
             <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
             <media:category>Weather</media:category>
             <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
             <media:filmingDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2310</guid>
             <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 17:16:19 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/318b4d77-7ff2-4f70-82f2-f11fef01a3c6.jpg" />
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/cf4ce304-8499-4278-8765-e482ffac4936.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Unforeseen wardrobe mishap: sister's skirt drops mid-performance, caught on camera!</media:title>
             <media:description>In an unexpected turn of events at a school event in Kediri, Indonesia, a video captured by @risazizah on June 15, 2023, showcased a girl's skirt falling during a performance. What made this incident even more surprising was the fact that the girl in question was none other than the sister of the author herself. As a teacher at the same school, the author had recorded the entire event, unaware that her sister would be the one experiencing a wardrobe malfunction. Fortunately, the girl had worn black leggings underneath, ensuring that she was not left completely exposed. </media:description>
             <media:keywords>school,event,video,skirt,fall,performance,sister,unexpected,captured,incident,leggings,permission,teacher,wardrobe,malfunction,exposure,Kediri,Indonesia,viral,twist</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Kediri</media:city>
             <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
             <media:regionCode>ID</media:regionCode>
            <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>      
             <media:category>Fails and Funnies</media:category>
             <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
             <media:filmingDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2309</guid>
             <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 04:38:26 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/6977856a-62b4-4474-965f-1cf394fdc86e.jpg" />
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/ef49dfa7-fc7f-455d-97ee-a38b00918596.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Unforgettable bachelorette fun: hilarious raft tumble at beer olympics afterparty!</media:title>
             <media:description>In a memorable bachelorette party celebration in Collingwood, Ontario, Canada, a group of friends found themselves in fits of laughter and screams after a day of Beer Olympics. The jovial atmosphere was captured on video by @jordan.ash.t on May 24, 2023. The highlight of the day came when one of the friends ingeniously hopped onto a wooden raft by lying flat on her stomach and clutching onto its sides. As the raft tilted to one side, her companions couldn't maintain their balance, plunging into the water with a symphony of shrieks. Luckily, everyone emerged unscathed, floating near the raft on the serene water body. It was an unforgettable moment of joy and camaraderie, capturing the essence of an epic bachelorette celebration. </media:description>
             <media:keywords>beer,olympics,bachelorette,party,friends,video,wooden raft,hilarious,tumble,water,screams,serene,Canada,Collingwood,Ontario,fun,adventure,capture,memories,laughter</media:keywords>
             <media:city> Collingwood, Ontario</media:city>
             <media:country>Canada</media:country>
             <media:regionCode>CA</media:regionCode>
            <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>      
             <media:category>Fails and Funnies</media:category>
             <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
             <media:filmingDate>Wed, 24 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2308</guid>
             <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 04:22:19 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/94d1f8d6-7067-4cc0-8e05-be1f07e40423.jpg" />
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/c1097b14-f72a-4eee-bd0d-cf143bd60c70.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Jumping for veggies: Muffy the 6-month-old cat's playful vegetable adventure!</media:title>
             <media:description>In a charming video captured by @olga.fedorova1974 on March 31, 2023 in Saint Petersburg, Russia, her mischievous 6-month-old cat, Muffy, takes center stage. The adorable feline can be seen energetically playing with pieces of vegetables scattered on the floor. Standing on her hind legs, Muffy jumps and pounces with delight, displaying her agile moves. In the background, the author's laughter adds an infectious joy to the scene, capturing a heartwarming moment of feline playfulness.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>cat,video,vegetable,play,Muffy,Saint Petersburg,Russia,cute,playful,jumping,hind legs,laughter,adorable,agile,mischievous,floor,joy,feline,pet,entertainment</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Saint Petersburg</media:city>
             <media:country>Russia</media:country>
             <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
            <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>      
             <media:category>Animals</media:category>
             <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
             <media:filmingDate>Fri, 31 Mar 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2307</guid>
             <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 04:04:56 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/b9089e09-0f03-4bcb-98c6-53c01f4e366b.jpg" />
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/4319bcb7-a70b-4aa1-89d9-d01e83299779.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Three-year-old girl's saga seed nose dilemma resolved through determined efforts</media:title>
             <media:description>In a moment of panic, a three-year-old girl found herself with a saga seed lodged in her nose, causing her mother to seek immediate assistance. The incident, captured by @mabecca4 on June 19th, 2023, in Jakarta, Indonesia, showcased the family's desperate attempts to remove the seed. Despite initial failed efforts using tweezers, the astute observation of the toddler's slowed dinner consumption led to the discovery of the foreign object. Eventually, through careful and determined manual extraction, the saga seed was successfully removed, bringing relief to the distressed family.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>panic,toddler,saga seed,nose,video,Jakarta,Indonesia,mother,tweezers,failed,observation,dinner,rice,slow,removal,hand,girl,captured,relieved,attempts</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Jakarta</media:city>
             <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
             <media:regionCode>ID</media:regionCode>
             <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
             <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
             <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
             <media:filmingDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2306</guid>
             <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 03:47:59 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/736a6678-612c-4b25-9f22-5a13744361a9.jpg" />
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/943e75ba-7839-4e90-9da2-e07a076f1fbe.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Adorable canine captain: fishing adventure awaits with patient pooch in Glendale!</media:title>
             <media:description>In a heartwarming scene captured by @bully_zeppelin on June 5, 2023, in Glendale, Arizona, USA, a video shows a dog sporting a sun hat while patiently waiting in a small boat on the riverbank. The dog's eager anticipation is evident as it awaits its human companion for a fishing trip. The adorable canine captain sits with an air of composure, ready to embark on an exciting adventure.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>dog,boat,riverbank,sun hat,fishing,Glendale,Arizona,USA,video,adorable,canine,captain,patience,waiting,companionship,outdoor,adventure,bond,pet,fishing trip,joy</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Glendale, Arizona</media:city>
             <media:country>United States</media:country>
             <media:regionCode>US</media:regionCode>
            <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>      
             <media:category>Animals</media:category>
             <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
             <media:filmingDate>Mon, 5 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2305</guid>
             <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 03:27:20 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/d8cc7378-501f-413f-abb8-6b5d4d864413.jpg" />
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/b9a49555-630c-432b-ab14-92abce8a8db5.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Funny mishap: toddler gets drink in her eyes, dad can't stop laughing!</media:title>
             <media:description>In a heartwarming yet hilarious moment captured on video, a father from St. George, Utah, USA, found himself in a comical mishap while fixing a drink for his young daughter. The footage, shared by @callmedivajustice on May 16, 2023, shows the dad playfully asking his daughter if she wanted to try the drink after vigorously shaking it in a drinking bottle. However, things took an unexpected turn as he opened the lid for his daughter, causing the drink to gush out from the straw and enter the toddler's eyes. Despite the momentary surprise, the brave little girl reassured her dad that she was okay. Unable to contain his laughter, the dad's amusement at the situation was evident.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>video,father,daughter,drink,mishap,laughter,St. George,Utah,USA,toddler,eyes,funny,captured,moment,shake,bottle,gushing,okay,comical,amusement,family</media:keywords>
             <media:city>St. George, Utah</media:city>
             <media:country>United States</media:country>
             <media:regionCode>US</media:regionCode>
            <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>      
             <media:category>Fails and Funnies</media:category>
             <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
             <media:filmingDate>Tue, 16 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2304</guid>
             <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 03:07:34 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/64fb124a-800a-4c01-9b11-9cd61d7dcca3.jpg" />
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/dd66a7b4-3eee-4b89-9a04-3d82ce60d72a.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Fatal AN-24 Aircraft crash near Kantemirovka village in Voronezh region</media:title>
             <media:description>An AN-24 aircraft crashed near the village of Kantemirovka in the Voronezh region of Russia on June 24th, 2023, resulting in at least three fatalities. The incident occurred amidst an ongoing counter-terrorism operation led by the Russian Armed Forces in the region. Governor Alexander Gusev dismissed reports of military equipment movements as unreliable, while also revealing the closure of over 300 kilometers of the M-4 Don highway in the affected area. </media:description>
             <media:keywords>crash,aircraft,Voronezh,Russia,Kantemirovka,fatalities,counter-terrorism,operation,Russian Armed Forces,governor,Alexander Gusev,unreliable,data,military equipment,region,M-4 Don highway,investigations,cause,authorities,management</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Voronezh</media:city>
             <media:country>Russia</media:country>
             <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
             <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
             <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
             <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
             <media:filmingDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2303</guid>
             <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jun 2023 19:22:30 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/34c0760a-2bb4-426e-82ed-9e9458b9636a.jpg" />
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2303.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Highways dug up in Lipetsk Region as Wagner PMC advances towards Moscow</media:title>
             <media:description>In a startling development, a video has surfaced depicting excavators digging up a major highway in the Lipetsk region of Russia on June 24, 2023. This incident has taken place in an area that reportedly houses one of the columns belonging to the notorious Wagner Private Military Company (PMC). Led by Yevgeny Prigozhin, the founder of the organization, the mercenaries are believed to be staging a rebellion against the Russian military leadership and are allegedly heading towards Moscow.

Filmed on the border of the Dobrovsky and Chaplyginsky districts, specifically on the highway leading to Chaplygin, the video has caused significant concern among local residents. Further reports suggest that additional roads in the Chaplygin area have also been subjected to similar excavation. One resident expressed their frustration saying, "I am standing in front of the Chaplyginsky district - in short, everything, we can no longer drive through. I don't know how to go home."</media:description>
             <media:keywords>excavators,highway,Lipetsk,Russia,rebellion,Wagner PMC,mercenaries,Moscow,video,Chaplygin,Dobrovsky,district,Ryazan,border,digging,chaos,tension,residents,roads,security</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Lipetsk</media:city>
             <media:country>Russia</media:country>
             <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
             <media:categoryCode>CWP</media:categoryCode>
             <media:category>News</media:category>
             <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
             <media:filmingDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2302</guid>
             <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jun 2023 09:32:09 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/ff9745a6-b904-4577-a16d-f35c97c9569e.jpg" />
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/b7b7f59e-cbb9-4797-9f93-bfb02c8e4860.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Rostov on high alert as military equipment and camouflaged personnel appear near Southern Military District headquarters</media:title>
             <media:description>Rostov, Russia - Tensions rise as heavy equipment and armed personnel have been spotted near the headquarters of the Southern Military District in Rostov. On the morning of June 24th, 2023, an array of vehicles, accompanied by individuals dressed in camouflage uniforms and carrying weapons, appeared at 43 Budyonnovsky Avenue. The sudden presence of military forces has prompted a change in traffic patterns, causing disruptions in the city center.

In response to the developments, law enforcement officers in the Rostov region have been placed on high alert since the night of June 24th. The borders with the self-proclaimed Donetsk People's Republic (DNR) and Luhansk People's Republic (LNR) have been closed, indicating a potential escalation of tensions in the region. Vasily Golubev, the governor of the Don region, has urged residents to remain at home whenever possible and advised against unnecessary travel to the city center. While transportation services continue to operate normally, certain areas within the city center are subject to cordons due to the presence of military equipment.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>rostov,russia,equipment,headquarters,southern military district,heavy,cars,budyonnovsky avenue,morning,june 24th,camouflage,weapons,cordon,traffic,law enforcement,enhanced service,borders,dnr,lnr,governor,home.</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Rostov</media:city>
             <media:country>Russia</media:country>
             <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
             <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
             <media:category>News</media:category>
             <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
             <media:filmingDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2301</guid>
             <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 15:44:02 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/8d280782-9a1d-4359-a809-9cadeff2f546.jpg" />
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/25a2842a-e6dd-49c9-9a98-a0d2baf69318.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Ka-52 military helicopter evades rocket strike in Voronezh: heat traps save the day</media:title>
             <media:description>In a startling incident captured by eyewitnesses in Voronezh, Russia on June 24, 2023, a Ka-52 military helicopter successfully evaded an attempted rocket strike. The gripping footage reveals the heart-stopping moment when a rocket was fired towards the helicopter. However, the skilled crew aboard the Ka-52 quickly deployed heat traps, effectively diverting the projectile away from its intended target. The rocket detonated harmlessly at a safe distance, averting potential disaster. </media:description>
             <media:keywords>helicopter,attack,Voronezh,Russia,eyewitnesses,footage,rocket,strike,Ka-52,military,heat traps,diversion,explosion,danger,defense,training,capabilities,crew,safeguarding,region</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Voronezh</media:city>
             <media:country>Russia</media:country>
             <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
             <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
             <media:category>News</media:category>
             <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
             <media:filmingDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2300</guid>
             <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 14:07:26 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/73faf492-b487-4941-aba2-61b65d65a207.jpg" />
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/74bbe99c-f81e-4399-9981-b0834288f6d4.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title> Projectile hits Voronezh residential complex's parking lot, endangering nearby residents</media:title>
             <media:description>In a shocking incident, a projectile landed within the premises of the Ozerki residential complex in Voronezh, Russia, on  24th June, 2023 causing panic among residents and endangering lives. The projectile, believed to be a shell, struck the parking lot where several people were present at the time. 
 The exact origin and nature of the projectile remain unknown, leaving residents anxious about their safety. </media:description>
             <media:keywords>residential,complex,Voronezh,Russia,projectile,shell,parking,people,panic,endanger,lives,Ozerki,incident,alarm,shelter,authorities,investigation,safety,security,measures</media:keywords>
             <media:city> Voronezh</media:city>
             <media:country>Russia</media:country>
             <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
             <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
             <media:category>News</media:category>
             <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
             <media:filmingDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2299</guid>
             <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 13:45:45 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/a39a9d7f-6abb-436e-92a1-4d8f0b662432.jpg" />
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/b2c41924-af4d-4ac1-a251-2280e4761bd1.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Explosion at Voronezh oil depot: helicopter incident sparks fear amidst Prigozhin's rebellion case</media:title>
             <media:description>An alarming incident unfolded in Voronezh, Russia, as eyewitnesses captured a chilling video of an explosion at an oil depot on June 24, 2023. The footage revealed the presence of a helicopter near the facility just moments before the eruption occurred. In the background, a terrified child, who recorded the scene, can be heard screaming to their mother about the frightening spectacle they witnessed.

This unsettling event took place against the backdrop of an ongoing investigation into an armed rebellion allegedly organized by Yevgeny Prigozhin, the owner of the Wagner private military company (PMC), stationed in the neighboring Rostov region. The Voronezh region shares a border with Rostov, heightening concerns about potential connections between the explosion and the rebel forces. Russian President Vladimir Putin, while addressing the nation, denounced the rebels as traitors and vowed to deliver inevitable punishment upon them.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>explosion,oil depot,helicopter,eyewitnesses,video,Voronezh,Russia,fear,child,mother,Wagner PMC,armed rebellion,Yevgeny Prigozhin,criminal case,traitors,punishment,borders,Rostov,investigation,unsettling</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Voronezh</media:city>
             <media:country>Russia</media:country>
             <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
             <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
             <media:category>News</media:category>
             <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
             <media:filmingDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2298</guid>
             <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 13:25:11 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/282fdc6e-1105-4d6a-83e9-f2f68fb5a8b0.jpg" />
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/bee882f3-38a6-482c-b10d-1da3006e9cdb.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Attempted armed rebellion shakes Rostov-on-Don: Wagner PMC militants block key locations and cause chaos</media:title>
             <media:description>In a shocking turn of events, the city of Rostov-on-Don in Russia was plunged into chaos as a convoy of military equipment rolled through its streets on the night of June 24, 2023. The armed rebellion attempt, led by fighters from the notorious Wagner Private Military Company (PMC) allegedly linked to businessman Yevgeny Prigozhin, targeted key locations including Budyonnovsky Prospekt and the pedestrian passage along Pushkinskaya Street, where the headquarters of the Southern Military District is situated. Eyewitnesses reported the presence of individuals in military attire without any identification marks near important government buildings, such as the Ministry of Internal Affairs, the Federal Security Service, and the city administration, raising concerns among authorities and residents alike. As a precautionary measure, authorities advised residents to stay indoors and avoid panic.

The repercussions of this uprising extended beyond the city limits, causing significant disruptions to transportation systems. The M-4 Don highway witnessed restricted traffic, resulting in a massive traffic jam that stretched for several kilometers. Motorists were urged by Rosavtodor to seek alternative routes, while pedestrians faced challenges accessing essential services, such as water, due to the need to walk to nearby shops. Moreover, the northern passage to Rostov-on-Don and roads leading to the administrative borders with the self-proclaimed Luhansk People's Republic (LPR) and Donetsk People's Republic (DPR) were blocked, further complicating the situation. </media:description>
             <media:keywords>armed,rebellion,Rostov,Russia,military,equipment,convoy,Wagner PMC,Prigozhin,blockade,chaos,identification,marks,authorities,residents,panic,traffic,disruption,pedestrians,water,investigation</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Rostov</media:city>
             <media:country>Russia</media:country>
             <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
             <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
             <media:category>News</media:category>
             <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
             <media:filmingDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2297</guid>
             <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 13:13:15 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/e9ed0429-3e26-49b9-8b6f-ac77beeb59ab.jpg" />
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/706b23b1-0f29-46b2-b8f7-d9b8a4669e25.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Security tensions rise in Rostov-on-Don as military equipment surrounds key government buildings</media:title>
             <media:description>In a concerning turn of events, Rostov-on-Don, Russia, witnessed a significant display of military presence on the morning of June 24th, 2023. Footage captured from the heart of the city revealed a scene dominated by individuals clad in camouflage attire and tanks, their gun barrels ominously directed towards the headquarters of the Southern Military District. Startlingly, this cordoning off extended to other vital establishments, including the Ministry of Internal Affairs, the Federal Security Service, and the city administration. Earlier social media videos had also surfaced, suggesting the entry of unidentified equipment, raising further questions about the situation.

Despite the gravity of the military's maneuvers, the civilian population appeared somewhat unperturbed, with bystanders observed closely monitoring the movements of the military personnel and machinery. </media:description>
             <media:keywords>military,equipment,cordon,headquarters,Southern Military District,Rostov-on-Don,Russia,footage,camouflage,tanks,barrels,aimed,Ministry of Internal Affairs,Federal Security Service,city administration,social networks,entry,civilian population,concern,movement,surveillance</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Rostov-on-Don</media:city>
             <media:country>Russia</media:country>
             <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
             <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
             <media:category>News</media:category>
             <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
             <media:filmingDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2295</guid>
             <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 12:43:09 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/8a6f083f-700b-4d17-98d8-0eda04aa462a.jpg" />
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/7e100ab8-388b-45b8-8e7a-52902580240d.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Tensions rise as military equipment cordons off southern military district headquarters in Rostov-on-Don</media:title>
             <media:description>Rostov-on-Don, Russia - On the morning of June 24rd, 2023 the headquarters of the Southern Military District in Rostov-on-Don found itself cordoned off by military equipment. Startling footage published on social media captured people in camouflage alongside tanks, their barrels ominously directed towards the district's headquarters. The video revealed that not only the military district's headquarters but also the head office of the Ministry of Internal Affairs, the Federal Security Service, and the city administration were all subjected to the cordon.

Earlier circulating videos on social media showcased a diverse array of equipment entering the city, some of which appeared unrelated to the Russian Armed Forces. Intriguingly, despite the presence of the military and the high-stakes situation, the civilian population seemed relatively unperturbed. Many were observed closely monitoring the movements of the military personnel, suggesting a curious atmosphere surrounding the events unfolding in Rostov-on-Don.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>military,equipment,cordon,headquarters,Southern Military District,Rostov-on-Don,footage,camouflage,tanks,barrels,portal,Ministry of Internal Affairs,Federal Security Service,city,administration,social networks,entry,civilian population,concern,movement</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Rostov-on-Don</media:city>
             <media:country>Russia</media:country>
             <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
             <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
             <media:category>News</media:category>
             <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
             <media:filmingDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2294</guid>
             <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 09:49:14 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/92989cc4-e87d-4e55-b32e-dd9e6874853b.jpg" />
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/fa8dee0b-b625-411a-8684-4525cbb524e6.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Flying swan's graceful mishap: a slippery perch over Stockholm's river</media:title>
             <media:description>On 10th June, 2023 in Stockholm, Sweden, @williamruyter had a chance encounter with a remarkable sight—a majestic swan gracefully soaring through the air above a lushly vegetated river. In a captivating video captured by the author, the swan attempted to alight on a colossal pipe that spun across the river, but fate had other plans. As the swan landed, its elegant wings momentarily lost balance, causing a slip. Despite the unexpected tumble, the author says that the swan emerged unscathed from the slip. </media:description>
             <media:keywords>stockholm,sweden,video,flying,swan,river,vegetation,growth,perch,pipe,slip,mishap,nature,encounter,majestic,balance,beauty,capture,moment,graceful</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Stockholm</media:city>
             <media:country>Sweden</media:country>
             <media:regionCode>SE</media:regionCode>
             <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
             <media:category>Animals</media:category>
             <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
             <media:filmingDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2293</guid>
             <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 19:56:09 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/4e14ba7b-522b-409f-a507-9dfa1d24ac43.jpg" />
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/ea83f35e-ea9e-4380-be02-d7a5c750312e.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item></channel>
           </rss>