<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
        <rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
        xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
        xmlns:openSearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearchrss/1.0/"
        xmlns:dfpvideo="http://api.google.com/dfpvideo"
        xmlns:tms="http://data.tmsapi.com/v1.1"
        version="2.0">
          <channel>
            <title>ViralBear videos</title>
            <dfpvideo:version>2</dfpvideo:version>
              
                    <item>
                      <media:title>Rescued stray 'Mickey' shakes his booty: heartwarming dance of joy in Marikina City</media:title>
                      <media:description>In a heartwarming display of pure joy, a dog named Mickey stole the spotlight in Marikina City, Philippines. A video captured by @hazidapadap on May 5, 2023, showcased Mickey's exuberant dance as his owner sang a happy tune. The infectious energy was palpable as the rescued stray wiggled and shook his body from side to side, celebrating the return of his beloved human. </media:description>
                      <media:keywords>dog,dance,joy,video,Mickey,Marikina,Philippines,happy,stray,owner,adopted,shake,booty,excitement,love,bond,companionship,heartwarming,celebrate,return</media:keywords>
                      <media:city>Marikina city</media:city>
                      <media:country>Philippines</media:country>
                      <media:regionCode>PH</media:regionCode>
                      <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                      <media:category>Animals,Heartwarming</media:category>
                      <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                      <media:filmingDate>Fri, 5 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
                      <guid>2803</guid>
                      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 08:08:01 GMT</pubDate>
                      <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2803.jpg" />
                      <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2803.mp4" />
                      <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                      </item>
                    
                    <item>
                      <media:title>Soldier's birthday celebration amidst conflict: moments of unity in Kharkiv's defense</media:title>
                      <media:description>Amidst the tense backdrop of the ongoing conflict between Ukraine and Russia, a heartwarming scene unfolded in Male Vesele, Kharkiv Oblast, Ukraine. A video captured by @tyson000003 on August 13, 2023, showcased soldiers celebrating a fellow comrade's birthday. The footage depicts a soldier carefully carrying a birthday cake from underground trenches, emerging onto the surface where makeshift tables were adorned with refreshments. As the soldier made his way to the group, laughter and camaraderie filled the air. The birthday celebrant blew out the candle on the cake, only for the cake bearer to playfully smash a bit of it onto his face, drawing jovial reactions.</media:description>
                      <media:keywords>soldiers,celebration,birthday,camaraderie,unity,conflict,Ukraine,Russia,video,trenches,refreshments,tables,laughter,moment,resilience,human,connections,adversity,Kharkiv,Male Vesele</media:keywords>
                      <media:city>Male Vesele, Kharkiv Oblast</media:city>
                      <media:country>Ukraine</media:country>
                      <media:regionCode>UA</media:regionCode>
                      <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                      <media:category>News,Heartwarming</media:category>
                      <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                      <media:filmingDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2023</media:filmingDate>
                      <guid>2802</guid>
                      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 09:06:59 GMT</pubDate>
                      <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2802.jpg" />
                      <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2802.mp4" />
                      <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                      </item>
                    
                    <item>
                      <media:title>Harmonious sunset serenade: a charming evening of music and love in Lviv's town square</media:title>
                      <media:description>On the enchanting evening of August 5, 2023 in Lviv, Ukraine, the bustling market square near the town hall became a stage for an unexpected yet heartwarming spectacle. Amidst a gathering crowd, a couple took to their balcony, igniting a musical moment that would linger in the memories of those fortunate enough to witness it. Captured by @reenatoochkaa, the video showcases a delightful scene of affection and artistry. As the sun set, casting a warm glow over the square, the couple's rendition of a melodious tune filled the air. With a cherry tree as their backdrop, the girl's beautiful voice resonated through the atmosphere, captivating the listeners who had gathered below. Strangers transformed into an impromptu audience, united by the magic of music and the embrace of the evening's serenity. </media:description>
                      <media:keywords>sunset,music,love,balcony,couple,Lviv,Ukraine,town square,market,atmosphere,serenade,harmony,cherry tree,enchanting,affection,artistry,memories,witnesses,audience,magic</media:keywords>
                      <media:city>Lviv</media:city>
                      <media:country>Ukraine</media:country>
                      <media:regionCode>UA</media:regionCode>
                      <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                      <media:category>Cool,Heartwarming</media:category>
                      <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                      <media:filmingDate>Sat, 5 Aug 2023</media:filmingDate>
                      <guid>2791</guid>
                      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2023 09:35:23 GMT</pubDate>
                      <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2791.jpg" />
                      <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2791.mp4" />
                      <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                      </item>
                    
                    <item>
                      <media:title>Musical bonding: father-son duet creates heartwarming twinkle twinkle symphony</media:title>
                      <media:description>In a touching moment captured by @Gia and Ven Acoustics on August 11, 2023, in Guihulngan City, Negros Oriental, Philippines, a heartwarming video emerged of young Gibson, at just 1 year and 7 months old, showcasing his budding musical talents. The video features Gibson singing "Twinkle Twinkle Little Star" alongside his father's guitar strumming, infusing the classic melody with his own endearing gibberish lyrics. The father-son duo created a captivating musical bond, allowing Gibson to effortlessly craft his own lyrical expressions that harmoniously melded with the rhythm of the guitar. This enchanting display of musical connection sheds light on Gibson's early passion for music and his ability to engage with it creatively at such a tender age.</media:description>
                      <media:keywords>music,bonding,toddler,guitar,duet,family,creativity,melody,harmony,video,father,son,lyrics,love,twinkle,Philippines,acoustic,moment,expressions,connection</media:keywords>
                      <media:city>Guihulngan City, Negros Oriental</media:city>
                      <media:country>Philippines</media:country>
                      <media:regionCode>PH</media:regionCode>
                      <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                      <media:category>Cool,Heartwarming</media:category>
                      <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                      <media:filmingDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023</media:filmingDate>
                      <guid>2789</guid>
                      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2023 09:18:28 GMT</pubDate>
                      <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2789.jpg" />
                      <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2789.mp4" />
                      <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                      </item>
                    
                    <item>
                      <media:title>Fierce feeding frenzy: street cat's growls guard its precious meal in Aktau, Kazakhstan</media:title>
                      <media:description>In a heartwarming scene captured by @prohor.tv on July 30, 2023, in Aktau, Kazakhstan, a compassionate encounter unfolded as a street cat enjoyed a meal. The video showcased the feline's determination to safeguard its food from other hungry strays, emitting low growls to fend them off. While the video focused on the protective street cat, the paw of another hopeful cat occasionally made daring attempts to share in the feast. Although @prohor.tv remained unseen in the footage, his gesture of kindness was evident as he gently patted the cat's head after providing nourishment. </media:description>
                      <media:keywords>feeding,street cat,video,growling,Kazakhstan,Aktau,compassion,hungry,strays,paw,food,kindness,interaction,stray cats,footage,gesture,nourishment,challenges,vulnerable,heartwarming</media:keywords>
                      <media:city>Aktau</media:city>
                      <media:country>Kazakhstan</media:country>
                      <media:regionCode>KZ</media:regionCode>
                      <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                      <media:category>Animals,Heartwarming</media:category>
                      <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                      <media:filmingDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                      <guid>2782</guid>
                      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2023 09:41:12 GMT</pubDate>
                      <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2782.jpg" />
                      <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2782.mp4" />
                      <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                      </item>
                    
                    <item>
                      <media:title>Joyful adventures: baby's playful mattress sandwich delights in new home</media:title>
                      <media:description>In a heartwarming scene captured by @ebyrslan on July 26, 2023, in Ipoh, Malaysia, a small child finds delight in the simplest of circumstances. Having recently moved into a new home, the child was discovered lying between two mattresses, a serene smile adorning their face instead of the expected tears. With the family gathered around, the child, nestled snugly between a queen and a single mattress on the floor, exuded an air of contentment. As the camera rolled, the child's father beckoned for the recording to commence, immortalizing this charming moment. </media:description>
                      <media:keywords>smile,baby,mattresses,new home,joy,Malaysia,Ipoh,family,contentment,father,recording,innocence,wonder,childhood,moving,happiness,playful,memories,simple,delightful</media:keywords>
                      <media:city>Ipoh</media:city>
                      <media:country>Malaysia</media:country>
                      <media:regionCode>MY</media:regionCode>
                      <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                      <media:category>Heartwarming</media:category>
                      <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                      <media:filmingDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                      <guid>2773</guid>
                      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 10:28:20 GMT</pubDate>
                      <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2773.jpg" />
                      <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2773.mp4" />
                      <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                      </item>
                    
                    <item>
                      <media:title>Heroic fishermen rescue family of five beluga whales stranded in Kamchatka's Tigilsky district</media:title>
                      <media:description>On August 14, 2023, in the breathtaking landscapes of Kamchatka's Tigilsky district in Russia, an inspiring tale of humanity and nature unfolded as a family of five beluga whales faced a perilous plight. Minister of Natural Resources for the region, Alexei Kumarkov, confirmed the heartening rescue operation that saw local fishermen rally together to save these marine giants. The Sokol family artel members, namely Andrei Korolev, Vladimir Kochelaevsky, Sergey Umkev, and Ashot Ustyan, discovered four mature beluga whales and a youthful cub stranded on the shores of the Sea of Okhotsk. Their diligent efforts to hydrate the creatures persisted for hours until the tide, a natural savior, returned, and the whales were at last free to rejoin their aquatic realm. The touching scene, documented in a video, showcased the whales side by side, emitting poignant sounds and even shedding what resembled tears. Beluga whales, belonging to the narwhal family within the cetacean order, captivate with their journey from dark blue infancy to the pristine white of adulthood by the age of five.</media:description>
                      <media:keywords>rescue,beluga whales,fishermen,Kamchatka,Russia,Tigilsky district,nature,compassion,humanity,stranded,Sea of Okhotsk,Sokol family artel,marine,giants,effort,tide,touching,video,narwhal family,cetacean,journey</media:keywords>
                      <media:city>Kamchatka</media:city>
                      <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                      <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                      <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                      <media:category>Animals,Rescue,Heartwarming</media:category>
                      <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                      <media:filmingDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023</media:filmingDate>
                      <guid>2763</guid>
                      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 11:35:23 GMT</pubDate>
                      <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2763.jpg" />
                      <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2763.mp4" />
                      <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                      </item>
                    
                    <item>
                      <media:title>Drenched dedication: dogs' rainy day stroll at Frew Park</media:title>
                      <media:description>In a heartwarming display of dedication, a recent video captured by @sosdogsaustralia on August 3, 2023, showcased a group of dogs and their guides navigating a sudden rain shower at Frew Park in Paddington, Brisbane, Australia. The unexpected rain caught the canine companions off-guard during their stroll, prompting the guides to swiftly lead them back. Despite the downpour, the guides exhibited unwavering commitment as they skillfully managed multiple dogs on leashes, briskly navigating the wet pathways. The video, captioned with "Definition of dedication!…go team SOS Dogs," highlights the remarkable bond between the guides and their furry charges as they braved the elements together.</media:description>
                      <media:keywords>rain,guides,dogs,stroll,dedication,Frew Park,Brisbane,Australia,@sosdogsaustralia,video,leash,wet,pathways,bond,elements,teamwork,companions,briskly,unexpected,pawprints,unity</media:keywords>
                      <media:city>Brisbane </media:city>
                      <media:country>Australia</media:country>
                      <media:regionCode>AU</media:regionCode>
                      <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                      <media:category>Animals,Heartwarming</media:category>
                      <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                      <media:filmingDate>Thu, 3 Aug 2023</media:filmingDate>
                      <guid>2760</guid>
                      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 11:40:30 GMT</pubDate>
                      <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2760.jpg" />
                      <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2760.mp4" />
                      <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                      </item>
                    
                    <item>
                      <media:title>From frontlines to family: a heartwarming homecoming in Far East, Russia</media:title>
                      <media:description>In a heartwarming scene captured on video in the Far East, Russia on July 12, 2023, a Russian soldier made his triumphant return home from the frontlines of the Russia-Ukraine conflict. Clutching a bouquet of flowers in his hands, he was met with tears of joy and embraces from his eagerly awaiting family members. His wife's sobbing embrace was soon joined by his mother's, as the simple day transformed into a jubilant celebration for this resilient family. The touching reunion served as a poignant reminder of the deep emotions and sacrifices that soldiers and their families endure during times of conflict.</media:description>
                      <media:keywords>soldier,homecoming,family,Russia,frontlines,conflict,Ukraine,video,flowers,tears,joy,embrace,celebration,reunion,resilience,emotions,sacrifices,war,Far East,sobbing</media:keywords>
                      <media:city>Far East </media:city>
                      <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                      <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                      <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                      <media:category>Heartwarming</media:category>
                      <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                      <media:filmingDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                      <guid>2750</guid>
                      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 10:23:44 GMT</pubDate>
                      <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2750.jpg" />
                      <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2750.mp4" />
                      <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                      </item>
                    
                    <item>
                      <media:title>Reilly's joyful water ballet: a canine's aquatic adventure</media:title>
                      <media:description>In a heartwarming scene captured on July 13, 2023, at Dowagiac, Michigan, USA, a video shared by @holland_meh showcased a remarkable display of canine enthusiasm. Their dog, Reilly, was caught on camera rushing into the water at the family lake house, standing on her hind legs, and playfully tapping the water's surface with her front paws. The video exemplified Reilly's unbridled love for the water, as she reveled in the opportunity to swim and fetch with boundless energy. @holland_meh explained that Reilly's eagerness to dive in was insatiable, often taking off before her owner could even fetch the bumper. The endearing footage portrayed a dog's pure joy in nature's embrace, embodying the essence of carefree playfulness and a deep connection to the water.</media:description>
                      <media:keywords>dog,water,Michigan,Reilly,lake,swimming,fetch,joy,canine,nature,play,family,happiness,video,paws,enthusiasm,adventure,bond,summer,pet</media:keywords>
                      <media:city>Dowagiac, Michigan </media:city>
                      <media:country>United States</media:country>
                      <media:regionCode>US</media:regionCode>
                      <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                      <media:category>Animals,Heartwarming</media:category>
                      <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                      <media:filmingDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                      <guid>2741</guid>
                      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 10:20:36 GMT</pubDate>
                      <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2741.jpg" />
                      <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2741.mp4" />
                      <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                      </item>
                    
                    <item>
                      <media:title>Joyful celebration: a heartwarming birthday serenade for Bududuts, the resilient furbaby</media:title>
                      <media:description>In a heartwarming display of love and resilience, @bulonchufurbabies from Antipolo City, Philippines, shared a touching video on April 30, 2023, capturing the celebration of her beloved dog Bududuts' 2nd birthday. Despite the challenges life might have thrown their way, the duo found a way to make the occasion special, showering Bududuts, affectionately known as Duts, with affection. The video shows Duts being serenaded with a rendition of "Happy Birthday," which he clearly enjoyed. As the camera pans, we see a table adorned with a spread fit for a canine king – a sumptuous feast of chicken and rice, with a chicken standing in for a birthday cake. </media:description>
                      <media:keywords>dog,birthday,celebration,love,resilience,video,singing,Antipolo City,Philippines,Bududuts,Duts,beloved,affection,serenade,chicken,rice,bond,furry,companions,cherished</media:keywords>
                      <media:city>Antipolo City </media:city>
                      <media:country>Philippines</media:country>
                      <media:regionCode>PH</media:regionCode>
                      <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                      <media:category>Animals,Heartwarming</media:category>
                      <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                      <media:filmingDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2023</media:filmingDate>
                      <guid>2739</guid>
                      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 07:53:20 GMT</pubDate>
                      <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2739.jpg" />
                      <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2739.mp4" />
                      <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                      </item>
                    
                    <item>
                      <media:title>Resilience amidst conflict: evacuation of a Ukrainian family from the frontline village of Druzhby</media:title>
                      <media:description>In the midst of the ongoing Ukraine-Russia conflict, a poignant scene unfolds in the village of Druzhby, Ukraine. Captured on June 8, 2023, by @alexbutukr, a heartrending video depicts a family's courageous evacuation from the relentless shelling of their frontline home. The family's decision to leave was guided by the concern for their safety, and volunteers played a crucial role in assisting and convincing them to evacuate. Against the backdrop of turmoil, this footage stands as a testament to the resilience and unity exhibited by both the affected families and the compassionate volunteers striving to ensure their well-being.</media:description>
                      <media:keywords>conflict,evacuation,frontline,shelling,Ukraine,Russia,village,family,safety,volunteers,compassion,unity,turmoil,resilience,video,Druzhby,ongoing,captured,June 8,2023</media:keywords>
                      <media:city>Druzhby </media:city>
                      <media:country>Ukraine</media:country>
                      <media:regionCode>UA</media:regionCode>
                      <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                      <media:category>Heartwarming</media:category>
                      <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                      <media:filmingDate>Thu, 8 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
                      <guid>2737</guid>
                      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 07:40:29 GMT</pubDate>
                      <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2737.jpg" />
                      <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2737.mp4" />
                      <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                      </item>
                    
                    <item>
                      <media:title>Ray of hope: lighting up lives amidst conflict in Ukraine's Druzhby village</media:title>
                      <media:description>In the midst of the ongoing Ukraine-Russia conflict, a poignant moment was captured by @alexbutukr on June 8, 2023, in the village of Druzhby, Ukraine. The video showcases an act of compassion and resilience as aid reaches a 94-year-old man enduring the constant shelling by Russian forces. The aid, in the form of lighting equipment, aims to provide a semblance of normalcy in the elderly man's life, illuminating his surroundings despite the challenging circumstances. The footage captures a soldier's gesture of mounting the light device and patiently demonstrating its operation to the elderly resident. This powerful scene highlights the enduring spirit of individuals amid adversity, offering a ray of hope in the midst of turmoil.</media:description>
                      <media:keywords>elderly,conflict,aid,lighting,resilience,Ukraine,Russia,village,shelling,compassion,video,soldier,equipment,Druzhby,94 years,hope,adversity,normalcy,spirit,illumination</media:keywords>
                      <media:city>Druzhby </media:city>
                      <media:country>Ukraine</media:country>
                      <media:regionCode>UA</media:regionCode>
                      <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                      <media:category>Heartwarming</media:category>
                      <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                      <media:filmingDate>Thu, 8 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
                      <guid>2736</guid>
                      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 07:41:46 GMT</pubDate>
                      <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2736.jpg" />
                      <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2736.mp4" />
                      <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                      </item>
                    
                    <item>
                      <media:title>Reunion amidst conflict: a Ukrainian soldier's homecoming after 8 months on the frontline</media:title>
                      <media:description>In the midst of an ongoing conflict between Russia and Ukraine that has stretched on for over a year, a heartfelt scene emerged in Kharkiv, Ukraine. Captured by @drossell_live on July 29, 2023, the video depicts a moment of profound joy as a Ukrainian soldier returns home after eight grueling months on the frontline. The soldier, who had been actively defending Ukraine within an assault brigade stationed near Bakhmut, finally reunited with his parents in Kharkiv for a fleeting 24-hour visit. The emotional embrace between the soldier and his mother serves as a poignant reminder of the sacrifices made by individuals on the frontlines and the enduring strength of familial bonds amidst the trials of conflict.</media:description>
                      <media:keywords>conflict,reunion,soldier,frontline,Ukraine,Russia,aggression,video,emotion,parents,Kharkiv,defense,assault,Bakhmut,joy,sacrifice,bonds,visit,poignant,trials</media:keywords>
                      <media:city>Kharkiv </media:city>
                      <media:country>Ukraine</media:country>
                      <media:regionCode>UA</media:regionCode>
                      <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                      <media:category>Heartwarming</media:category>
                      <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                      <media:filmingDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                      <guid>2735</guid>
                      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 07:50:37 GMT</pubDate>
                      <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2735.jpg" />
                      <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2735.mp4" />
                      <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                      </item>
                    
                    <item>
                      <media:title>Vacuum delight: Luke Skywalker's purrfect massage session in Moscow!</media:title>
                      <media:description>In a charming scene that unfolded on July 6, 2023, in Moscow, Russia, @sky_super_cat documented a delightful moment between their 6-year-old feline companion, Luke Skywalker, and an unexpected source of joy - a vacuum cleaner. The heartwarming video captures Luke Skywalker reclining comfortably on his back atop the vacuum, savoring a serene stomach rub administered by a caring lady. With evident contentment, he expertly shifts his attention to a nearby shoe, using it as a conduit for a gentle head rub while continuing to receive soothing strokes along his back. The author shared that Luke's affinity for the vacuum cleaner is undeniable, as he enthusiastically gravitates toward its sound, establishing a heartwarming bond between a feline friend and an unconventional household item.</media:description>
                      <media:keywords>vacuum,cat,Luke Skywalker,rub,Moscow,Russia,video,affection,joy,back,stomach,shoe,lady,sound,bond,feline,companion,unexpected,household,moment</media:keywords>
                      <media:city>Moscow</media:city>
                      <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                      <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                      <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                      <media:category>Animals,Heartwarming</media:category>
                      <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                      <media:filmingDate>Thu, 6 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                      <guid>2727</guid>
                      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 07:54:21 GMT</pubDate>
                      <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2727.jpg" />
                      <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2727.mp4" />
                      <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                      </item>
                    
                    <item>
                      <media:title>London adventures: cycling through the capital with deaf Norwegian forest cat, Sigrid</media:title>
                      <media:description>In a delightful display of companionship, @skintension from London, UK, took to the bustling streets on his bike accompanied by his loyal Norwegian Forest Cat, Sigrid, on July 30, 2023. With Sigrid securely fastened to his chest using a harness, the duo fearlessly navigated the city's roads, showcasing an unbreakable bond. Despite Sigrid's deafness, the intrepid feline seemed undeterred by the urban commotion, her forward-facing perch affording her a unique perspective of the city's sights. The author affectionately mentioned, "Sigrid is very spoilt; she wouldn't make it outdoors. She doesn't care about cars; she would just walk out in the road." This heartwarming partnership serves as a testament to the extraordinary lengths one can go to ensure a beloved pet's happiness and safety, all while exploring the vibrant metropolis of London.</media:description>
                      <media:keywords>bike,cat,London,UK,cycling,companionship,Norwegian Forest Cat,Sigrid,harness,deaf,urban,streets,roads,bond,feline,outdoors,cars,spoilt,city,sights</media:keywords>
                      <media:city>London </media:city>
                      <media:country>United Kingdom</media:country>
                      <media:regionCode>GB</media:regionCode>
                      <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                      <media:category>Animals,Cool,Heartwarming</media:category>
                      <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                      <media:filmingDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                      <guid>2721</guid>
                      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 08:10:56 GMT</pubDate>
                      <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2721.jpg" />
                      <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2721.mp4" />
                      <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                      </item>
                    
                    <item>
                      <media:title>Energetic youth and resourceful grandmother: unconventional football match on Kyiv's streets</media:title>
                      <media:description>In an endearing and lively scene captured on April 15, 2023, along Kyiv's Khreschatyk street in Ukraine, an unexpected and heartwarming game of football unfolded between generations. The video, attributed to @sergey_black_12, showcased the spirited interaction between a spry young man and a determined grandmother. Evidently unmatched in terms of agility, the young man effortlessly dribbled the ball, while the grandmother, undeterred by the odds, ingeniously wielded her walking stick as a makeshift foot to join in the fun. With an unyielding spirit, she attempted to kick the ball away from her opponent, resulting in a delightful and spirited exchange that brought smiles to onlookers. Despite not reclaiming the ball, the grandmother's tenacity painted a heartwarming picture of intergenerational bonding and the universal joy of play.</media:description>
                      <media:keywords>energetic,agile,heartwarming,intergenerational,spirited,bonding,joy,football,grandmother,young man,Kyiv,Khreschatyk street,Ukraine,playful,unconventional,determined,onlookers,video,capture,scene</media:keywords>
                      <media:city> Kyiv </media:city>
                      <media:country>Ukraine</media:country>
                      <media:regionCode>UA</media:regionCode>
                      <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                      <media:category>Cool,Heartwarming</media:category>
                      <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                      <media:filmingDate>Sat, 15 Apr 2023</media:filmingDate>
                      <guid>2703</guid>
                      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 09:33:37 GMT</pubDate>
                      <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2703.jpg" />
                      <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2703.mp4" />
                      <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                      </item>
                    
                    <item>
                      <media:title>Soldier's tender touch: Ukrainian troop cares for homeless kitten amidst conflict's chaos</media:title>
                      <media:description>Amidst the turmoil of the ongoing conflict between Ukraine and Russia, a heartwarming scene has emerged, showcasing the compassion and humanity that can thrive even in the midst of adversity. Ukrainian soldier @igrande7, on July 2, 2023, captured a poignant moment on camera in the Kharkiv district of Ukraine. After a fierce battle, the soldiers stumbled upon a homeless kitten and, moved by empathy, decided to provide both shelter and care. In a touching video, one of the soldiers is seen delicately cleaning the kitten's eyes with cotton swabs, a gesture of tenderness that stands in stark contrast to the harsh realities of war. </media:description>
                      <media:keywords>compassion,soldier,kindness,kitten,ukraine,conflict,rescue,empathy,video,cotton,swabs,heartwarming,battle,humanity,homeless,tenderness,wounded,adversity,realities,vulnerable</media:keywords>
                      <media:city>Kharkiv district</media:city>
                      <media:country>Ukraine</media:country>
                      <media:regionCode>UA</media:regionCode>
                      <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                      <media:category>Animals,Heartwarming</media:category>
                      <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                      <media:filmingDate>Sun, 2 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                      <guid>2700</guid>
                      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2023 14:07:51 GMT</pubDate>
                      <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2700.jpg" />
                      <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2700.mp4" />
                      <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                      </item>
                    
                    <item>
                      <media:title>Cortnee Vine's winning penalty ignites joyous celebration at Cathy Freeman Park as Matildas secure semi-finals spot in Women's World Cup</media:title>
                      <media:description>In a historic moment for Australian sports, Cathy Freeman Park outside Stadium Australia in Sydney Olympic Park witnessed a jubilant eruption of cheers and celebration as the national women's soccer team, the Matildas, clinched a dramatic victory over France in the Quarter Finals of the FIFA Women’s World Cup™ on August 12, 2023. Captured by @accorstadium, the atmosphere was electrifying as fans gathered to support their team, who ultimately emerged triumphant in a nail-biting penalty shootout. The winning penalty, skillfully converted by Cortnee Vine, sent the Matildas into the Semi-Finals of the tournament, marking a memorable 'Where were you moment' in Australian sporting history. With the park echoing with chants of victory and national pride, the scene symbolized the passion and dedication of both the team and its fervent supporters. The Matildas' remarkable journey continues as they prepare to face their next challenge with unwavering enthusiasm.</media:description>
                      <media:keywords>celebration,victory,soccer,Matildas,fans,history,moment,Quarter Finals,France,shootout,Sydney,Olympic Park,excitement,passion,pride,triumph,Semi-Finals,tournament,Cathy Freeman Park,Cortnee Vine</media:keywords>
                      <media:city>Sydney </media:city>
                      <media:country>Australia</media:country>
                      <media:regionCode>AU</media:regionCode>
                      <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                      <media:category>News,Sport,Heartwarming</media:category>
                      <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                      <media:filmingDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023</media:filmingDate>
                      <guid>2699</guid>
                      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2023 09:32:38 GMT</pubDate>
                      <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2699.jpg" />
                      <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2699.mp4" />
                      <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                      </item>
                    
                    <item>
                      <media:title>Uniting hearts: delivering hope and clean water to Nikopol amidst conflict</media:title>
                      <media:description>In a heartwarming display of international solidarity, an inspiring video captured by @anov_vlog on July 10, 2023, in Nova Kakhovka, Ukraine, showcased dedicated individuals from a humanitarian organization diligently packaging vital aid. Collaborating with Canadian and Ukrainian partners, the team worked tirelessly to assemble much-needed supplies destined for the conflict-affected city of Nikopol. Ravaged by the ongoing strife between Ukraine and Russia, Nikopol has found a beacon of hope in this organization's unwavering support. Among their life-saving contributions, the organization has been instrumental in providing essential water filtration systems to the beleaguered city, ensuring access to clean and safe drinking water. </media:description>
                      <media:keywords>hope,unity,compassion,aid,conflict,resilience,water,partnership,Nikopol,Ukraine,Canada,organization,video,packaging,humanitarian,city,support,filtration,impact,teamwork</media:keywords>
                      <media:city>Nova Kakhovka</media:city>
                      <media:country>Ukraine</media:country>
                      <media:regionCode>UA</media:regionCode>
                      <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                      <media:category>Heartwarming</media:category>
                      <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                      <media:filmingDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                      <guid>2691</guid>
                      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 13:44:55 GMT</pubDate>
                      <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2691.jpg" />
                      <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2691.mp4" />
                      <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                      </item>
                    
                    <item>
                      <media:title>Respite and reconnection: soldiers' heartwarming bond with a kitten in Donetsk, Ukraine</media:title>
                      <media:description>Amidst the harrowing backdrop of the ongoing conflict between Ukraine and Russia, a touching moment of humanity and camaraderie emerged as captured by @mrtoha827 on August 4, 2023, in Donetsk, Ukraine. In the video, battle-worn soldiers find solace in the company of a newfound feline friend. The soldiers, having returned from the frontlines, discovered a tiny kitten, and their exhaustion momentarily gave way to pure delight. Using a simple twig, they engaged in a heartwarming play, coaxing the kitten to climb onto one of the soldiers. This brief interlude served as a poignant reminder that even in the midst of turmoil, the bonds of compassion and shared experiences have the power to transcend the harsh realities of conflict.</media:description>
                      <media:keywords>harrowing,conflict,Ukraine,Russia,touching moment,humanity,camaraderie,@mrtoha827,Donetsk,video,soldiers,solace,company,feline friend,battle-worn,frontlines,tiny kitten,exhaustion,pure delight,twig,heartwarming play,climb,interlude,poignant reminder,turmoil,bonds,compassion,shared experiences,power,transcend</media:keywords>
                      <media:city> Donetsk </media:city>
                      <media:country>Ukraine</media:country>
                      <media:regionCode>UA</media:regionCode>
                      <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                      <media:category>Animals,Heartwarming</media:category>
                      <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                      <media:filmingDate>Fri, 4 Aug 2023</media:filmingDate>
                      <guid>2683</guid>
                      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 08:54:41 GMT</pubDate>
                      <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2683.jpg" />
                      <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2683.mp4" />
                      <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                      </item>
                    
                    <item>
                      <media:title>Enchanting moments: little boy joins the Yangko Dance, spreading joy in Heilongjiang Province, China</media:title>
                      <media:description>In the heartwarming province of Heilongjiang, China, a captivating scene unfolded during a traditional Yangko Dance activity. Local resident @happy captured a delightful moment on July 9, 2023, as a little boy couldn't resist joining the dancers while watching the mesmerizing performance. The Yangko Dance, renowned in northern China, saw its spirit come alive as the young boy wholeheartedly embraced the rhythmic moves, adding his own touch of innocence and joy to the age-old tradition. The video shared by the author quickly went viral, spreading smiles and warmth across social media platforms, reminding us all of the universal language of dance and the pure happiness it brings.</media:description>
                      <media:keywords>happy,dance,yangko,china,heilongjiang,traditional,boy,video,viral,community,performance,northern,joy,heartwarming,moment,captivating,innocence,socialmedia,tradition,smiles</media:keywords>
                      <media:city>Heilongjiang province</media:city>
                      <media:country>China</media:country>
                      <media:regionCode>CN</media:regionCode>
                      <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                      <media:category>Heartwarming</media:category>
                      <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                      <media:filmingDate>Sun, 9 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                      <guid>2639</guid>
                      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 08:10:17 GMT</pubDate>
                      <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2639.jpg" />
                      <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2639.mp4" />
                      <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                      </item>
                    
                    <item>
                      <media:title>Swaddle buddies: heartwarming video shows cat and baby bonding in Ciamis, Indonesia</media:title>
                      <media:description>In a heartwarming display of unlikely companionship, a video captured by @sheisseu malikeymouse on July 22, 2023, in Ciamis, Indonesia, has taken the internet by storm. The footage shows a swaddled baby peacefully lying next to a swaddled cat, with the feline seemingly unfazed by the tiny human's presence. According to the account owner, the cat has a penchant for disturbing the child, prompting the clever idea of swaddling them both together. </media:description>
                      <media:keywords>swaddle,baby,cat,companionship,bond,video,Indonesia,Ciamis,heartwarming,pets,harmony,unexpected,love,animals,internet,admiration,unique,clever,touching,footage</media:keywords>
                      <media:city>Ciamis</media:city>
                      <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
                      <media:regionCode>ID</media:regionCode>
                      <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                      <media:category>Heartwarming</media:category>
                      <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                      <media:filmingDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                      <guid>2611</guid>
                      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 08:15:55 GMT</pubDate>
                      <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2611.jpg" />
                      <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2611.mp4" />
                      <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                      </item>
                    
                    <item>
                      <media:title>Love blossoms at a birthday party: tender smiles of a toddler</media:title>
                      <media:description>In a heartwarming moment captured by @ayreeeshh_ on March 12, 2023, at a birthday party in Las Piñas, Manila, Philippines, a two-year-old boy named Drei melted hearts as he looked tenderly at a little girl named Aliah. The usually quiet and well-behaved toddler seemed to be smitten with Aliah, flashing sweet smiles and even raising his eyebrows at her, giving the impression of a young love in the making. Drei's mother shared the adorable video, describing how her son became seemingly interested in Aliah, and it quickly became a viral sensation, spreading joy and warmth across the internet. This endearing encounter serves as a reminder of the innocent and pure connections that can blossom even among the youngest of hearts.</media:description>
                      <media:keywords>love,toddler,birthday,party,smiles,tender,falling,in,young,children,innocence,adorable,viral,internet,connections,heartwarming,Manila,Philippines,Aliah,Drei,@ayreeeshh_</media:keywords>
                      <media:city>Las Piñas, Manila</media:city>
                      <media:country>Philippines</media:country>
                      <media:regionCode>PH</media:regionCode>
                      <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                      <media:category>Heartwarming</media:category>
                      <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                      <media:filmingDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2023</media:filmingDate>
                      <guid>2592</guid>
                      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 10:51:48 GMT</pubDate>
                      <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2592.jpg" />
                      <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2592.mp4" />
                      <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                      </item>
                    
                    <item>
                      <media:title>Fast-pass to thrills: a wild ride at Disneyland!</media:title>
                      <media:description>In a heartwarming yet adrenaline-pumping moment at Disneyland, California, USA, a father's attempt to reassure his daughter during a roller coaster ride took an unexpected turn. Captured by @enrique7kcg on July 9, 2023, the video shows the duo enjoying the thrilling experience, but with a hilarious twist. As they embarked on the coaster adventure, the father promised his daughter that they would take it slow, only to find the roller coaster had other plans. Despite his reassurances, the ride took off at high speed, resulting in his daughter's excited yet terrified screams. Sharing the video on social media, @enrique7kcg humorously captioned it as "I got a fast-pass to hell for this one." The heartwarming father-daughter moment, coupled with the roller coaster's unexpected speed, made it a cherished memory for both, an unforgettable day of family fun at the magical land of Disneyland.</media:description>
                      <media:keywords>roller coaster,disneyland,california,usa,father,daughter,ride,fast-pass,thrill,adventure,hilarious,social media,caption,screams,family,fun,magical,amusement park,memory,excitement</media:keywords>
                      <media:city> California</media:city>
                      <media:country>United States</media:country>
                      <media:regionCode>US</media:regionCode>
                      <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                      <media:category>Heartwarming</media:category>
                      <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                      <media:filmingDate>Sun, 9 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                      <guid>2584</guid>
                      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 08:24:03 GMT</pubDate>
                      <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2584.jpg" />
                      <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2584.mp4" />
                      <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                      </item>
                    
                    <item>
                      <media:title>Emotional dilemma: heartwarming video shows child's tears turn into joy when offered money</media:title>
                      <media:description>In a touching video captured by @yhangespela on June 2, 2023, in San Mateo, Rizal, Philippines, a young child's conflicting emotions towards money were showcased. The footage depicted the child initially crying but quickly becoming quiet and even expressing a desire for more when presented with money. The heartwarming scene left viewers pondering the complexities of children's perceptions of money and the diverse range of emotions it can evoke in young minds.</media:description>
                      <media:keywords>crying,money,child,emotions,video,touching,Philippines,San Mateo,young,tears,joy,desire,perception,mother,quiet,conflicting,heartwarming,captured,presented,note</media:keywords>
                      <media:city>San Mateo, Rizal</media:city>
                      <media:country>Philippines</media:country>
                      <media:regionCode>PH</media:regionCode>
                      <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                      <media:category>Heartwarming</media:category>
                      <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                      <media:filmingDate>Fri, 2 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
                      <guid>2568</guid>
                      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 07:55:27 GMT</pubDate>
                      <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2568.jpg" />
                      <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2568.mp4" />
                      <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                      </item>
                    
                    <item>
                      <media:title>Resilience amidst adversity: heartwarming acts of kindness in the midst of conflict</media:title>
                      <media:description>In the midst of an ongoing conflict between Russia and Ukraine, a heartwarming video captured by @sneg0111 on April 7, 2023, in Zaporozhye, Ukraine, showcased the unwavering spirit of the Ukrainian people. The footage depicted a woman and her dog walking home after grocery shopping in the midst of a blackout caused by shelling on infrastructure, including the thermal power plant. Despite the challenging circumstances, the woman ingeniously used her dog's help to carry the groceries with its mouth, highlighting the resourcefulness and unity of the community. In times of crisis, the residents of Ukraine rallied together, extending their compassion and support to one another, regardless of whether it was a person or a furry companion. This heartwarming act of kindness serves as a reminder of the resilience displayed by ordinary individuals in extraordinary times.</media:description>
                      <media:keywords>resilience,conflict,video,woman,dog,grocery,shopping,blackout,infrastructure,unity,community,crisis,kindness,support,compassion,Russia,Ukraine,Zaporozhye,touching,heartwarming</media:keywords>
                      <media:city>Zaporozhye</media:city>
                      <media:country>Ukraine</media:country>
                      <media:regionCode>UA</media:regionCode>
                      <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                      <media:category>Heartwarming</media:category>
                      <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                      <media:filmingDate>Fri, 7 Apr 2023</media:filmingDate>
                      <guid>2561</guid>
                      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 07:46:09 GMT</pubDate>
                      <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2561.jpg" />
                      <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2561.mp4" />
                      <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                      </item>
                    
                    <item>
                      <media:title>Ageless bonds: heartwarming dinner with grandma and her furry companion</media:title>
                      <media:description>In a touching video captured by @wolfchava on June 1, 2023, in Sums, Ukraine, viewers witnessed a heartwarming scene at a family dinner. The video showcased an 86-year-old grandmother sharing a meal with her wolf companion named Chavez. As the elderly woman sat at the table, the dog playfully approached, seemingly asking for some of the delicious food. This endearing moment beautifully highlighted the special bond between generations and the love shared within this standard family setting.</media:description>
                      <media:keywords>grandmother,dinner,family,bond,love,ageless,heartwarming,video,Ukraine,Sums,@wolfchava,June,2023,table,meal,companion,touching,generations,standard,wolf</media:keywords>
                      <media:city>Sumy</media:city>
                      <media:country>Ukraine</media:country>
                      <media:regionCode>UA</media:regionCode>
                      <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                      <media:category>Heartwarming</media:category>
                      <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                      <media:filmingDate>Thu, 1 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
                      <guid>2526</guid>
                      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 15:09:50 GMT</pubDate>
                      <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2526.jpg" />
                      <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2526.mp4" />
                      <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                      </item>
                    
                    <item>
                      <media:title>Love in a tray: a mother parrot's care for her little ones in Izmir, Turkey</media:title>
                      <media:description>In a heartwarming scene captured on July 11th, 2023, in Izmir, Turkey, @hknyilmaz35 shared a touching video featuring a devoted mother parrot and her adorable young ones. The video showcases the loving care provided by Hakan, a parrot breeder, to a yellow parrot and her recently hatched chicks. As the camera rolls, the affectionate mother can be seen nurturing her little ones in a tray, chirping tender words of love and protection. Hakan's expertise in parrot breeding shines through as he highlights the fascinating distinction between the girls and one boy among the brood. This heartening display of maternal love and expert care reminds us of the remarkable bonds that exist in the animal kingdom, leaving viewers touched and captivated by the beautiful scene.</media:description>
                      <media:keywords>parrot,young ones,tray,Izmir,Turkey,video,love,mother,chirping,breeding,Hakan,yellow,care,girls,boy,affectionate,maternal,expert,bonds,animal</media:keywords>
                      <media:city>Izmir</media:city>
                      <media:country>Turkey</media:country>
                      <media:regionCode>TR</media:regionCode>
                      <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                      <media:category>Heartwarming</media:category>
                      <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                      <media:filmingDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                      <guid>2523</guid>
                      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 21:06:46 GMT</pubDate>
                      <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2523.jpg" />
                      <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2523.mp4" />
                      <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                      </item>
                    
                    <item>
                      <media:title>Purr-fect dance duo: heartwarming moment with Sonya in Ulan-Ude, Buryatia, Russia</media:title>
                      <media:description>In a heartwarming video captured on June 14th, 2023, in Ulan-Ude, Buryatia, Russia, a cat named Sonya and her owner, @turbo_psih, shared a special dance together. The tender moment was beautifully captured as @turbo_psih held Sonya in his arms, while she gently placed her paw on his cheek. The undeniable bond between the two shone through as they swayed to the rhythm, creating a touching display of love and companionship.</media:description>
                      <media:keywords>dancing,cat,Sonya,Ulan-Ude,Buryatia,Russia,pet,owner,love,bond,video,viral,heartwarming,companionship,tender,moment,paw,cheeks,@turbo_psih,connection,swaying</media:keywords>
                      <media:city>Ulan-Ude, Buryatia</media:city>
                      <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                      <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                      <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                      <media:category>Heartwarming</media:category>
                      <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                      <media:filmingDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
                      <guid>2501</guid>
                      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 08:19:08 GMT</pubDate>
                      <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2501.jpg" />
                      <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2501.mp4" />
                      <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                      </item>
                    
                    <item>
                      <media:title>Emotional homecoming: a surprise puppy fulfilling two years of longing</media:title>
                      <media:description>In a heartwarming video captured by @stuartthegoldenweenie on July 5th, 2023, in New York, USA, a girlfriend's dream finally came true after two years of daily pleas for a puppy. Living in a small 1-bedroom apartment, she would send her partner videos of golden wiener dogs, expressing her desire for one once they had enough space. Last month, they purchased a new house together, and seizing the opportunity to surprise her, he presented her with the puppy of her dreams. Overwhelmed with joy, the girlfriend can be seen lying on the floor, sobbing as she cradles the furry companion on her chest. A simple act of love and thoughtfulness turned a long-awaited wish into a reality, filling their new home with love and happiness.</media:description>
                      <media:keywords>puppy,surprise,girlfriend,video,love,longing,dream,joy,house,home,new york,usa,golden weenie,sobbing,emotion,fulfillment,space,apartment,pet,happiness</media:keywords>
                      <media:city>New York</media:city>
                      <media:country>United States</media:country>
                      <media:regionCode>US</media:regionCode>
                      <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                      <media:category>Heartwarming</media:category>
                      <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                      <media:filmingDate>Wed, 5 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                      <guid>2491</guid>
                      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 09:39:44 GMT</pubDate>
                      <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2491.jpg" />
                      <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2491.mp4" />
                      <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                      </item>
                    
                    <item>
                      <media:title>Bowls of melody: young virtuoso creates enchanting music with chopsticks in Gansu Province, China</media:title>
                      <media:description>On July 4th, 2023, in Gansu Province, West China, an extraordinary musical performance unfolded on the streets. @baldheadplayingbowlbrother, a talented traditional Chinese musician, captured a video of his young son showcasing his remarkable skills with chopsticks and bowls. The child played a mesmerizing piece of music entirely on his own, drawing in a captivated crowd of onlookers who were amazed by the young virtuoso's talent. Through the rhythmic tapping of the bowls with chopsticks, the boy effortlessly produced enchanting melodies that resonated throughout the street, earning him well-deserved praise and admiration from the audience. The heartwarming performance showcased the beauty of traditional Chinese music and left a lasting impression on all who were fortunate enough to witness it.</media:description>
                      <media:keywords>talented,traditional,chinese,musician,chopsticks,bowls,music,performance,son,street,captivating,crowd,onlookers,virtuoso,rhythmic,melodies,enchanting,praise,audience,heartwarming</media:keywords>
                      <media:city>Gansu Province</media:city>
                      <media:country>China</media:country>
                      <media:regionCode>CN</media:regionCode>
                      <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                      <media:category>Heartwarming</media:category>
                      <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                      <media:filmingDate>Tue, 4 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                      <guid>2466</guid>
                      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
                      <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/6a307182-7dc3-4d9e-8dd3-08837c6543ca.jpg" />
                      <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/178481ee-cd37-46ed-a70a-aa4944b23c89.mp4" />
                      <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                      </item>
                    
                    <item>
                      <media:title>Joyful moments: a bubble-filled performance by a talented young star</media:title>
                      <media:description>In a heartwarming video captured by @artem_pedan on May 14th, 2023, in Moscow, Russia, a young boy's love for blowing bubbles and acting shines through. The short clip showcases the child's delightful playfulness as he combines both passions into one enchanting performance. With bubbles floating in the air around him, the young star takes center stage, bringing a sense of joy and wonder to viewers.</media:description>
                      <media:keywords>bubbles,son,video,Moscow,Russia,play,actor,capture,joy,childhood,happiness,performance,enchanting,delightful,love,playful,moment,simplicity,pleasure,wonder</media:keywords>
                      <media:city> Moscow</media:city>
                      <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                      <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                      <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                      <media:category>Heartwarming</media:category>
                      <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                      <media:filmingDate>Sun, 14 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
                      <guid>2447</guid>
                      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
                      <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/dcc591ad-6682-4db8-bfda-7de1054a8add.jpg" />
                      <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/58bdb59b-d4ae-44fd-aae3-128b4cb9b5ba.mp4" />
                      <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                      </item>
                    
                    <item>
                      <media:title>Allan Children's Ministries: bringing hope to vulnerable children in Uganda</media:title>
                      <media:description>A video of Ugandan orphans lined up to be served food has gone viral, raising awareness for Allan Children's Ministries, a charity organization that is working to provide for over 150 children in Kampala, Uganda. the video was captured by @allan_children_ministries on 29th of June 2023.

The video was posted on social media by Allan Kato, the founder and creator of Allan Children's Ministries. Kato explains that the organization was formed in November 2017. Allan Children's Ministries raises funds to provide food, clothes, school tuition, medication bills, monthly rent bills, and other basic needs to children in Uganda. Kato is grateful for the support that Allan Children's Ministries has received. </media:description>
                      <media:keywords>orphan,children,charity,hope,healing,christ,food,clothes,school,tuition,medication,rent,bill,donate,volunteer,spread,word,ugandan,viral</media:keywords>
                      <media:city>Kampala</media:city>
                      <media:country>Uganda</media:country>
                      <media:regionCode>UG</media:regionCode>
                      <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                      <media:category>Heartwarming</media:category>
                      <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                      <media:filmingDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
                      <guid>2413</guid>
                      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
                      <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/dee2ece2-f82f-49bb-b330-291d8531226c.jpg" />
                      <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/0cb7cfce-5b0f-42fe-836d-e18c2b6a1a04.mp4" />
                      <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                      </item>
                    
                    <item>
                      <media:title>Adorable mishap: little helper's cat-feeding adventure takes an unexpected turn</media:title>
                      <media:description>In a heartwarming yet comical incident captured on video, a little girl's attempt to feed her family cat turned into a delightful mess. The footage, shared by @i_am_inna on April 1, 2021, from Moscow, Russia, shows the young girl opening a bag of cat food with great determination. However, her enthusiasm got the best of her, and she accidentally spilled the entire contents onto the floor. Undeterred, the cat wasted no time and started enjoying the impromptu feast while the girl valiantly tried to collect the spilled food. Despite the unexpected turn of events, the child remained composed and focused, showcasing a surprising maturity beyond her years. </media:description>
                      <media:keywords>cat,feeding,video,daughter,spilled,floor,playing,food,hands,collect,return,captured,adult,silence,rustling,packaging,fuss,serious,equanimity,adorable</media:keywords>
                      <media:city>Moscow</media:city>
                      <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                      <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                      <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                      <media:category>Heartwarming</media:category>
                      <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                      <media:filmingDate>Thu, 1 Apr 2021</media:filmingDate>
                      <guid>2404</guid>
                      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
                      <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/ebb16482-3807-4bb2-a41b-4bfaf611516b.jpg" />
                      <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/253619d1-cd95-45a1-937d-c8b374b37c5b.mp4" />
                      <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                      </item>
                    
                    <item>
                      <media:title>Balloons, cake, and joy: little Alice celebrates her third birthday</media:title>
                      <media:description>Naberezhnyye Chelny, Russia - In a heartwarming video captured by @alisatyt on June 10th, 2023, a little girl named Alice stole the spotlight on her third birthday. With colorful balloons playfully tied to her two ponytails, Alice stood beside a table adorned with a cake displaying the number three. Her name gracefully arched across the top of the cake. With anticipation in her eyes, Alice leaned forward and blew out the solitary candle that adorned the side of the cake. It was a precious moment of celebration and pure childhood joy.</media:description>
                      <media:keywords>balloons,cake,birthday,celebration,three,ponytails,candles,joy,video,girl,Alice,Naberezhnyye Chelny,Russia,June 10th,2023,captured,table,name,blowing,three</media:keywords>
                      <media:city>Naberezhnyye Chelny</media:city>
                      <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                      <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                      <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                      <media:category>Heartwarming</media:category>
                      <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                      <media:filmingDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
                      <guid>2399</guid>
                      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
                      <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/feccff5b-ec5d-409b-a61d-3d53aa4f9293.jpg" />
                      <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2399.mp4" />
                      <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                      </item>
                    
                    <item>
                      <media:title>The making of a young star: infant Markolilit's promising acting debut</media:title>
                      <media:description>In a heartwarming video captured by @markadan on June 11th, 2022 in Silang, Cavite, Philippines, his infant son Markolilit steals the spotlight as he effortlessly executes various acting commands. At less than six months old, Markolilit shows remarkable potential as he follows his father's instructions with adorable enthusiasm. With each gesture and expression, it's clear that this little one is a natural performer in the making. The video serves as a glimpse into the early stages of what could be a promising acting career for the talented infant.</media:description>
                      <media:keywords>infant,actor,video,Mark,command,Silang,Cavite,Philippines,talent,potential,performer,cute,adorable,young,debut,promising,father,son,capturing,acting</media:keywords>
                      <media:city>Silang, Cavite</media:city>
                      <media:country>Philippines</media:country>
                      <media:regionCode>PH</media:regionCode>
                      <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                      <media:category>Heartwarming</media:category>
                      <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                      <media:filmingDate>Sat, 11 Jun 2022</media:filmingDate>
                      <guid>2395</guid>
                      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
                      <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/669860f5-4082-451e-b668-32d8529d3769.jpg" />
                      <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/56c1285a-8461-4962-b136-5842ffe5bb4e.mp4" />
                      <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                      </item>
                    
                    <item>
                      <media:title>Unbreakable bond: dog becomes toddler's playful guardian in heartwarming video</media:title>
                      <media:description>In a heartwarming video captured by @its.bleecker.boy.time on May 11th, 2023, a dog in the West Village of New York City showcased its remarkable instinct and unwavering devotion to its toddler companion. The adorable footage revealed the dog diligently following the young boy through a house corridor until a stumble sent the little one tumbling onto his stomach. Seizing the opportunity to play, the dog gently bit onto the boy's shoe and proceeded to tug him along the carpet, eliciting joyous laughter from the delighted child. </media:description>
                      <media:keywords>dog,toddler,playtime,bond,companionship,West Village,New York,USA,video,corridor,stumble,fall,shoe,carpet,laughter,joy,love,animals,pets,heartwarming</media:keywords>
                      <media:city>West Village, New York</media:city>
                      <media:country>United States</media:country>
                      <media:regionCode>US</media:regionCode>
                      <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                      <media:category>Heartwarming</media:category>
                      <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                      <media:filmingDate>Thu, 11 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
                      <guid>2370</guid>
                      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
                      <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/3fa5c23f-a7c5-4b05-9548-e651b879a2bf.jpg" />
                      <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/8233eaec-ac96-4a32-916f-43c685ce3927.mp4" />
                      <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                      </item>
                    
                    <item>
                      <media:title>Adorable surprise: little Valentina's birthday dance with cat melts hearts worldwide!</media:title>
                      <media:description>In a heartwarming moment captured on camera, a small girl named Valentina stole the internet's heart as she danced with a cat at her mom's birthday party in Lancaster, Texas, USA. The adorable video, filmed by @rockysoto74 on  October 1, 2022 and shared on TikTok, showcased Valentina holding the cat by its fore legs, as if they were hugging, while dancing to her sister's favorite song. Little did the author know that the innocent video would go viral overnight, garnering immense love and attention from people around the world. Despite being an unintended surprise, Valentina's delightful dance with her feline friend resonated with viewers, spreading joy and warmth in a single, heartfelt moment.</media:description>
                      <media:keywords>dance,cat,girl,viral,heartwarming,birthday,party,Texas,USA,video,TikTok,hug,favorite,song,surprise,love,attention,joy,warmth,moment</media:keywords>
                      <media:city>Lancaster, Texas</media:city>
                      <media:country>United States</media:country>
                      <media:regionCode>US</media:regionCode>
                      <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                      <media:category>Heartwarming</media:category>
                      <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                      <media:filmingDate>Sat, 1 Oct 2022</media:filmingDate>
                      <guid>2322</guid>
                      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 07:45:47 GMT</pubDate>
                      <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/69e155e9-a4fb-49de-b050-19fed0a49fbd.jpg" />
                      <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/af8b06eb-b934-44a6-ae4b-543d06426ff2.mp4" />
                      <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                      </item>
                    
                    <item>
                      <media:title>Emotional reunion: military mother surprises daughter at graduation, leaving hearts touched</media:title>
                      <media:description>In a heartwarming incident that touched the hearts of many, a military mother made a surprise visit to attend her daughter's graduation ceremony in Sobolevo, Kamchatka, Russia on June 24, 2023. The touching video capturing the emotional reunion between the mother and her daughter Kira quickly gained popularity on social networks, spreading far beyond the peninsula. The heartfelt moment depicted the sacrifice and dedication of a military parent, who, despite being separated by duty, managed to create a lasting memory with her daughter before returning to the frontlines. </media:description>
                      <media:keywords>graduation,military,mother,daughter,surprise,reunion,sacrifice,dedication,Kamchatka,Sobolevo,video,popular,social networks,touching,ceremony,front,love,resilience,memory,heartfelt</media:keywords>
                      <media:city>Sobolevo, Kamchatka</media:city>
                      <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                      <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                      <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                      <media:category>Heartwarming</media:category>
                      <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                      <media:filmingDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
                      <guid>2359</guid>
                      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
                      <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/a920f456-aad8-487c-af70-8095e6ee9791.jpg" />
                      <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2359.mp4" />
                      <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                      </item>
                    
                    <item>
                      <media:title>Adorable twins nap in car-like walkers: hilarious video goes vral</media:title>
                      <media:description>In a heartwarming and humorous moment captured by @jaylabrenay on June 24th, 2023, in St. Louis, Missouri, USA, her twin babies were found peacefully asleep in their car-like walkers. The twins were in their own walkers designed to resemble miniature automobiles. In the viral video, one of the babies dozed off while resting on the toy steering wheel, while the other slumbered in an amusing backwards position. With the caption "milk gone bad while driving home, these babies are hilarious," the endearing footage has gained widespread attention, spreading smiles and laughter across social media platforms.</media:description>
                      <media:keywords>twins,carwalkers,sleep,StLouis,Missouri,USA,hilarious,video,babies,milk,bad,driving,home,adorable,laughter,socialmedia,viral,caption,funny,siblings,cute</media:keywords>
                      <media:city> St. Louis, Missouri</media:city>
                      <media:country>United States</media:country>
                      <media:regionCode>US</media:regionCode>
                      <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                      <media:category>Heartwarming</media:category>
                      <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                      <media:filmingDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
                      <guid>2366</guid>
                      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
                      <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/cf26ec26-37e1-4d36-9204-09657b3a0405.jpg" />
                      <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/59fa5f64-0add-4492-8450-6ca57537d097.mp4" />
                      <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                      </item>
                    
                    <item>
                      <media:title>First steps by the shore: a father's love and a daughter's beach adventure</media:title>
                      <media:description>In a heartwarming scene captured by @muoimuoi0306 on October 1st, 2021, at Vung Tau beach in Vietnam, a father and his just over one-year-old daughter shared a special moment. It was the little girl's first time at the beach, and her father gently carried her towards the shoreline. With a mix of excitement and trepidation, he set her down on the sand, allowing her to take her first steps on her own. However, as the waves rolled in, a sudden tide caught her off guard, causing her to stumble. But her father was there in an instant, scooping her up in his protective arms. From that point on, they continued their beach adventure together, with the father cradling his daughter as they enjoyed the rhythmic embrace of the tides. It was a beautiful display of a father's love and a precious memory that will surely be cherished for years to come.</media:description>
                      <media:keywords>beach,family,father,daughter,love,milestone,joy,parenting,bonding,waves,tide,sand,first steps,adventure,Vung Tau,Vietnam,precious,memories,embrace,video</media:keywords>
                      <media:city>Vung Tau</media:city>
                      <media:country>Vietnam</media:country>
                      <media:regionCode>VN</media:regionCode>
                      <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                      <media:category>Heartwarming</media:category>
                      <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                      <media:filmingDate>Fri, 1 Oct 2021</media:filmingDate>
                      <guid>2337</guid>
                      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 16:15:05 GMT</pubDate>
                      <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/d614ddfe-a23b-4297-a7b0-6d546159f537.jpg" />
                      <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/9bda8956-6224-4b9f-92a4-e9d6bc5f38ba.mp4" />
                      <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                      </item>
                    
                    <item>
                      <media:title>Jogging joy: California runner embraces playful sidewalk game</media:title>
                      <media:description>A video captured by @raisedonrice on June 4th, 2023, in California, USA, showcases a heartwarming moment of spontaneity and joy. While jogging along a pavement path, a man discovered a children's box game drawn on the ground. Without hesitation, he turned back, leaped over the boxes with a playful spirit, and seamlessly resumed his jog. This inspiring act reminds us all to embrace the childlike wonder and find moments of delight in our everyday routines.</media:description>
                      <media:keywords>jogger,pavement,path,children's game,boxes,spontaneous,joy,California,USA,video,captured,joy,playfulness,agility,creativity,inspiration,lightheartedness,detour,happiness,wonder</media:keywords>
                      <media:city>California</media:city>
                      <media:country>United States</media:country>
                      <media:regionCode>US</media:regionCode>
                      <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                      <media:category>Heartwarming</media:category>
                      <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                      <media:filmingDate>Sun, 4 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
                      <guid>2236</guid>
                      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 19:46:06 GMT</pubDate>
                      <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/96a816b1-fa40-47eb-8d71-f975469d3dc0.jpg" />
                      <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/b03375d5-778a-4acb-84fd-3639bf02b84e.mp4" />
                      <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                      </item>
                    
                    <item>
                      <media:title>Dancing yellow jackets: South African firefighters bring unity and rhythm to Edmonton's wildfire battle</media:title>
                      <media:description>In a heartwarming display of solidarity and unity, a group of 200 firefighters from the renowned South African organization, Working on Fire, landed in Edmonton, Canada, on June 4, 2023, to lend their expertise in battling the raging fires. The arrival of this dedicated team was captured on video by @wo_fire and the footage has taken the internet by storm, quickly going viral. The remarkable scene shows a wave of yellow-clad firefighters dancing and singing in perfect harmony, creating an atmosphere of resilience and determination.

Their infectious energy and synchronized movements not only serve as a testament to their camaraderie but also highlight the power of music and dance in fostering unity amidst adversity.

As they join forces with local firefighters, the South African team's unwavering spirit and expertise promise to make a significant impact in combatting the wildfires that have plagued the region.</media:description>
                      <media:keywords>firefighters,unity,solidarity,Edmonton,Canada,South Africa,Working on Fire,arrival,video,viral,dancing,singing,yellow jackets,wildfire,battle,resilience,determination,camaraderie,hope,support,impact</media:keywords>
                      <media:city>Edmonton</media:city>
                      <media:country>Canada</media:country>
                      <media:regionCode>CA</media:regionCode>
                      <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                      <media:category>Heartwarming</media:category>
                      <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                      <media:filmingDate>Sun, 4 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
                      <guid>2240</guid>
                      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2023 17:19:07 GMT</pubDate>
                      <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/6ed62ca7-4cbc-49c6-98c3-e724646b4370.jpg" />
                      <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/5a6b69eb-5cf3-4d6d-8d23-f4640de34754.mp4" />
                      <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                      </item>
                    
                    <item>
                      <media:title>Baby's tears turn to smiles: the miraculous phone solution</media:title>
                      <media:description>In a heartwarming moment captured by @yenlinh536 in Thuận An town, Bình Dương Province, Vietnam on April 6th, 2023, their baby girl's tears turned into smiles with a simple glance at herself on a phone screen. The adorable video showcased the power of self-recognition as the little one, in the midst of her tears, caught a glimpse of her reflection and immediately transformed her expressions. The magical encounter left viewers in awe, reminding us of the innate joy and wonder children can find in their own image. </media:description>
                      <media:keywords>adorable,baby,crying,smiling,video,reflection,self-recognition,innocence,joy,wonder,tears,phone,screen,glimpse,transformation,power,perception,simple,moment,smiles</media:keywords>
                      <media:city>Thuận An town, Bình Dương Province</media:city>
                      <media:country>Vietnam</media:country>
                      <media:regionCode>VN</media:regionCode>
                      <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                      <media:category>Heartwarming</media:category>
                      <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                      <media:filmingDate>Thu, 6 Apr 2023</media:filmingDate>
                      <guid>2264</guid>
                      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 11:18:57 GMT</pubDate>
                      <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/8d87963c-8ccc-4963-826a-6cc7ed3b0eae.jpg" />
                      <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/7d8a2fff-1368-485e-9556-656b5b25affd.mp4" />
                      <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                      </item>
                    
                    <item>
                      <media:title>Innocence and assertiveness: a little girl stands up for herself in school</media:title>
                      <media:description>In a heartwarming video captured by @lola_and_aria on 23rd May, 2023, a mother from Greenville, South Carolina, USA, her daughter, Aria, showcased both innocence and assertiveness as she recounted an incident at school. The young girl passionately explained how another student, who happened to be German, attempted to put their hands in her food, a behavior she found inappropriate. Unfazed, she confidently confronted the student, smirking and warning them not to repeat such actions.

Despite her mother's attempts to explain that it was not appropriate to respond in that manner, determined Aria remained stubborn, insisting that she had the right to stand up for herself. Her adorable demeanor and unwavering belief in her actions captured the hearts of viewers. </media:description>
                      <media:keywords>adorable,innocence,assertiveness,school,incident,video,daughter,Greenville,South Carolina,USA,German,food,inappropriate,stubborn,explanation,mother,hands,smirk,warning,self-advocacy</media:keywords>
                      <media:city>Greenville, South Carolina</media:city>
                      <media:country>United States</media:country>
                      <media:regionCode>US</media:regionCode>
                      <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                      <media:category>Heartwarming</media:category>
                      <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                      <media:filmingDate>Tue, 23 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
                      <guid>2255</guid>
                      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 20:14:58 GMT</pubDate>
                      <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/0871ce1d-48e3-4256-ba4c-7eebe4f627d1.jpg" />
                      <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/4742d174-51c0-4c9e-9f9f-805720b46f47.mp4" />
                      <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                      </item>
                    
                    <item>
                      <media:title>Startled success: Texas toddler's surprising reaction to mother's cheerful congratulation</media:title>
                      <media:description>In a heartwarming moment captured on video, a toddler in Texas, USA, showcased his impressive hand-eye coordination while playing with a wooden cube and a ball. The video, shared by @camillesmiith on May 22, 2023, depicts the toddler successfully throwing the ball through the hole in the cube. As soon as he achieved this feat, his mother congratulated him. However, the suddenness of her voice startled the little one, creating an adorable reaction.</media:description>
                      <media:keywords>wooden cube,ball,toddler,Texas,USA,video,playing,achievement,hand-eye coordination,surprise,startle,moment,joy,parenting,innocence,development,milestone,support,determination,encouragement,happiness</media:keywords>
                      <media:city>Texas</media:city>
                      <media:country>United States</media:country>
                      <media:regionCode>US</media:regionCode>
                      <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                      <media:category>Heartwarming</media:category>
                      <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                      <media:filmingDate>Mon, 22 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
                      <guid>2241</guid>
                      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 19:54:49 GMT</pubDate>
                      <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/7daa08c1-3e23-4848-8704-7e72260a37d1.jpg" />
                      <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/e7a1bb2f-2742-471a-864b-c595d1658455.mp4" />
                      <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                      </item>
                    
                    <item>
                      <media:title>Children's kindness shines as they help fallen green doll rise again</media:title>
                      <media:description>In a heartwarming incident captured on video, a person dressed as a green doll with a tail took a tumble and found themselves unable to get back on their feet. The incident, which occurred on April 2nd, 2023, in Baling, Kedah, Malaysia, attracted the attention of three compassionate children who rushed to lend a helping hand.

The video, filmed by @masyitahosman, shows the person inside the green doll struggling to regain their balance. With each attempt, they seemed to face further difficulties. However, their struggle did not go unnoticed. Three children, whose names remain unknown, quickly approached the fallen doll. With a remarkable display of empathy and kindness, they joined forces and worked together to lift the doll back onto its feet.</media:description>
                      <media:keywords>green,doll,tail,fallen,struggle,feet,children,help,kindness,compassion,video,captured,Baling,Kedah,Malaysia,forces,heartwarming,empathy,selfless,connection</media:keywords>
                      <media:city>Baling, Kedah</media:city>
                      <media:country>Malaysia</media:country>
                      <media:regionCode>MY</media:regionCode>
                      <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                      <media:category>Heartwarming</media:category>
                      <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                      <media:filmingDate>Sun, 2 Apr 2023</media:filmingDate>
                      <guid>2250</guid>
                      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 20:11:47 GMT</pubDate>
                      <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/7c0e8c45-a4d6-4c56-8857-c4bf68842c3e.jpg" />
                      <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/e20f8d86-4d40-426c-86df-7691d27b8b69.mp4" />
                      <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                      </item>
                    
                    <item>
                      <media:title>Adorable toddler's hilarious twist: moldy bun served at playtime store!</media:title>
                      <media:description>In a heartwarming moment captured by @kyliecgray in Barrie, Ontario, Canada, her young son embarked on his first imaginative play as a storekeeper on  May 28th, 2023. Little did she expect the unexpected twist that awaited her when she placed an order for a cheeseburger and fries. Instead of the anticipated treat, the adorable toddler handed her a random moldy bun With a mischievous smile. 

</media:description>
                      <media:keywords>store,toddler,playtime,moldy,bun,cheeseburger,fries,imagination,Barrie,Ontario,Canada,laughter,adorable,video,creativity,surprise,make-believe,joy,memory,chuckle</media:keywords>
                      <media:city>Barrie, Ontario</media:city>
                      <media:country>Canada</media:country>
                      <media:regionCode>CA</media:regionCode>
                      <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                      <media:category>Heartwarming</media:category>
                      <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                      <media:filmingDate>Sun, 28 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
                      <guid>2208</guid>
                      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 09:24:02 GMT</pubDate>
                      <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/74e45764-8058-48c8-99f0-aa3219399bb3.jpg" />
                      <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/1b78bd31-48ac-40be-9379-a974ec5ddc87.mp4" />
                      <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                      </item>
                    
                    <item>
                      <media:title>Sibling love: a heartwarming journey of a big brother and his little sister</media:title>
                      <media:description>In a heartwarming video captured by @yolandjimmy, a family in Padang, Indonesia, celebrated the arrival of their youngest member on 1st November 2022. The video showcased the beautiful bond between a 13-month-old boy and his newborn sister, with the boy eagerly embracing his new role as a big brother.

In the footage, the boy's excitement was palpable as he showered his sister with affection. He playfully kissed her face and gently touched her tiny ears, displaying his adoration for the little bundle of joy. However, in a moment of youthful exuberance, he accidentally hit her on the face. Fortunately, the mother reassured viewers that the baby was unharmed. </media:description>
                      <media:keywords>baby,siblings,love,bond,joy,excitement,affection,newborn,brother,sister,video,adorable,playfulness,kisses,face,youngest,family,Padang,Indonesia,heartwarming</media:keywords>
                      <media:city> Padang</media:city>
                      <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
                      <media:regionCode>ID</media:regionCode>
                      <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                      <media:category>Heartwarming</media:category>
                      <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                      <media:filmingDate>Tue, 1 Nov 2022</media:filmingDate>
                      <guid>2199</guid>
                      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 09:12:20 GMT</pubDate>
                      <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/55917b90-cc8d-4b2d-a2ac-4aa8a0338c64.jpg" />
                      <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/b033e7de-830b-45f9-96a5-e53ccd072a08.mp4" />
                      <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                      </item>
                    
                    <item>
                      <media:title>Bamboo bliss: adorable panda finds unusual dining style in Guangzhou!</media:title>
                      <media:description>In a heartwarming scene captured by @Panda'sSlowLife, a renowned panda video photographer, a panda in Guangzhou, South China, was spotted enjoying a delightful meal of bamboo shoots while lying on its back. The adorable moment, captured on the 23rd of May, 2023, showcases the unique dining style of this furry creature.

The author, who specializes in filming the lives of pandas, was drawn to the panda's living area that afternoon. The sight of the panda munching on bamboo in such a charming manner was simply irresistible. With his camera ready, he filmed this captivating video, highlighting the sheer cuteness of the panda as it relished its meal while reclining on its back.</media:description>
                      <media:keywords>panda,bamboo,shoots,video,photographer,Guangzhou,South China,cute,adorable,filming,living area,afternoon,munching,charming,reclining,endearing,surprising,gentle,giants,captivating</media:keywords>
                      <media:city> Guangzhou</media:city>
                      <media:country>China</media:country>
                      <media:regionCode>CN</media:regionCode>
                      <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                      <media:category>Heartwarming</media:category>
                      <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                      <media:filmingDate>Tue, 23 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
                      <guid>2153</guid>
                      <pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 18:16:24 GMT</pubDate>
                      <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/6b7feb5b-eb6f-4bc8-b753-a0ac40717eac.jpg" />
                      <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/7f9c0da6-4841-4ba1-a35c-8837f5218066.mp4" />
                      <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                      </item>
                    
                    <item>
                      <media:title>Father's love triumphs: heartwarming reconciliation with daughter over safety concerns</media:title>
                      <media:description>In a heartwarming incident captured on video in Kendari City, South East Sulawesi, Indonesia, a concerned father was seen persuading his young daughter against crossing a busy road alone. The video, taken by user @gorogo_14 on May 23, 2023, showcases a tender moment between the father and his determined little girl. Despite her eagerness to explore a place filled with enchanting lights across the road, her father rightfully forbade her, emphasizing the potential dangers. Frustrated by his refusal, the girl refused to communicate with her father and turned away whenever he attempted to engage her face to face.

The video demonstrates the father's unwavering commitment to his daughter's safety. He patiently engages with her, explaining the risks involved in crossing the road independently. His persistence pays off as the young girl eventually agrees to converse with him. Overwhelmed by her father's love, she embraces him tightly, signaling their reconciliation. With their bond reaffirmed, the father scoops her up into his arms and they walk away together.</media:description>
                      <media:keywords>father,daughter,road,safety,video,love,communication,parenting,concern,reconciliation,hug,persuasion,refusal,danger,trust,bonding,guidance,lights,capture,emotions</media:keywords>
                      <media:city>Kendari City, South East Sulawesi</media:city>
                      <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
                      <media:regionCode>ID</media:regionCode>
                      <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                      <media:category>Heartwarming</media:category>
                      <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                      <media:filmingDate>Tue, 23 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
                      <guid>2157</guid>
                      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 07:39:22 GMT</pubDate>
                      <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/6042ac19-2173-4619-a4e3-6886625dcbbe.jpg" />
                      <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/ad8c6c94-02d8-4121-9532-4a436b86ecc1.mp4" />
                      <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                      </item>
                    
                    <item>
                      <media:title>Carabao ride: two wheel commute amazes social media on first day of school!</media:title>
                      <media:description>In a heartwarming and eco-friendly twist, the first day of school at Irawan Elementary School in San Vicente, Palawan, Philippines, captured the attention of social media users around the world. A video, shot by @IngridGenena on August 22, 2022, showcased six elementary school children being fetched by an unconventional mode of transportation—a carabao. The sight of these young students riding a cart pulled by the gentle beast left viewers in awe and admiration.</media:description>
                      <media:keywords>heartwarming,eco-friendly,carabao,school,children,video,first day,San Vicente,Palawan,Philippines,Irawan Elementary,social media,amazed,two wheel drive,gas saver,alternative,cultural heritage,sustainable living,innovative,commuting</media:keywords>
                      <media:city>San Vicente, Palawan</media:city>
                      <media:country>Philippines</media:country>
                      <media:regionCode>PH</media:regionCode>
                      <media:categoryCode>ODD</media:categoryCode>
                      <media:category>Heartwarming</media:category>
                      <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                      <media:filmingDate>Mon, 22 Aug 2022</media:filmingDate>
                      <guid>2094</guid>
                      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2023 11:56:17 GMT</pubDate>
                      <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2094.jpg" />
                      <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2094.mp4" />
                      <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                      </item>
                    
                    <item>
                      <media:title>Rescuer's heart on Fire: fireman proposes to girl on balcony in Birsk, Russia</media:title>
                      <media:description>In a heartwarming gesture, a senior inspector of the Birsk Interdistrict Department of Supervisory Activities and Preventive Work, Nikita Slobodchikov, climbed a ladder to the seventh floor of an apartment building to propose to his girlfriend on her balcony.

The incident took place in Birsk on 5th May 2023, a city in the Republic of Bashkortostan, Russia. Slobodchikov, who is also a rescuer, arrived at the location on a fire truck with a ladder and climbed to his girlfriend's balcony with a bouquet of flowers.

In a video the young woman can be seen appearing on the balcony, surprised and emotional at the sight of her boyfriend on a ladder with flowers in hand.

Slobodchikov then makes a heartfelt proposal, saying, "I have a fire in my heart, and I don't want to put it out. I have one question: will you become my wife?" His girlfriend can be heard saying yes. 

The video has since gone viral, with many people applauding Slobodchikov's romantic gesture.</media:description>
                      <media:keywords>rescuer,proposal,balcony,Birsk,Russia,fireman,flowers,love,engagement,surprise,courage,romance,heroic,viral,happiness,celebration,unity,hope,heartwarming,joy</media:keywords>
                      <media:city>Birsk</media:city>
                      <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                      <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                      <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                      <media:category>Heartwarming</media:category>
                      <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                      <media:filmingDate>Fri, 5 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
                      <guid>2059</guid>
                      <pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 11:24:41 GMT</pubDate>
                      <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2059.jpg" />
                      <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2059.mp4" />
                      <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                      </item>
                    
                    <item>
                      <media:title>Playful imagination: Sasha's serenade with the spray bottle</media:title>
                      <media:description>In the bustling city of Kyiv, Ukraine, a heartwarming scene unfolded on 9th March, 2023. @andrexlg, a proud parent, captured an adorable moment featuring his son Sasha, who was below the age of five. Sasha, armed with a spray bottle, embarked on a playful adventure with an indoor plant.

Though no water was actually sprayed, the sounds of sprinkling filled the air as Sasha gleefully circled the tree, creating a magical world of his own. This endearing display of imagination and innocence reminds us of the simple joys that children bring into our lives.</media:description>
                      <media:keywords>spray,water,plant,imagination,playtime,children,innocence,sounds,fantasy,creativity,development,parenthood,joy,pride,capture,Kyiv,Ukraine,play,childhood,moments</media:keywords>
                      <media:city>Kyiv</media:city>
                      <media:country>Ukraine</media:country>
                      <media:regionCode>UA</media:regionCode>
                      <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                      <media:category>Heartwarming</media:category>
                      <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                      <media:filmingDate>Thu, 9 Mar 2023</media:filmingDate>
                      <guid>2053</guid>
                      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2023 11:40:07 GMT</pubDate>
                      <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2053.jpg" />
                      <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2053.mp4" />
                      <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                      </item>
                    
                    <item>
                      <media:title>Father's gaming session lulls daughter to sleep with headphones on</media:title>
                      <media:description>In today's fast-paced world, it's often difficult to find moments of peace and quiet. However, a heartwarming video captured in Pavlodar, Kazakhstan, on 27th April, 2023 by @bessmertnayakris showcases a rare moment of serenity that many parents can relate to.

In the video, we see a father sitting at his computer, engrossed in a gaming session. Meanwhile, his young daughter is sitting on his lap, wearing a pair of headphones. At first, she seems alert and interested in what her father is doing. But as time goes by, the soothing sound of the game and her father's calming presence begin to have their effect. The little girl starts to falling asleep with the headphones still on her ears.</media:description>
                      <media:keywords>father,daughter,gaming,headphones,serenity,bonding,family,love,peaceful,moment,tenderness,care,security,comfort,relaxation,home,Kazakhstan,video,amusing,touching</media:keywords>
                      <media:city>Pavlodar</media:city>
                      <media:country>Kazakhstan</media:country>
                      <media:regionCode>KZ</media:regionCode>
                      <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                      <media:category>Heartwarming</media:category>
                      <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                      <media:filmingDate>Mon, 27 Mar 2023</media:filmingDate>
                      <guid>2022</guid>
                      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2023 11:40:07 GMT</pubDate>
                      <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2022.jpg" />
                      <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2022.mp4" />
                      <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                      </item>
                    
                    <item>
                      <media:title>The joy of Kindness: a simple act of consideration leads to a heartwarming encounter</media:title>
                      <media:description>Kindness is a powerful force that can bring happiness and joy to both the giver and the receiver. It can take many forms, from a simple smile to a grand gesture. But it is often the small acts of kindness that have the biggest impact. One such act of kindness took place in Odessa, Ukraine, on 29th of April, when a man named @metbackk turned off his engine to avoid disturbing a father and his child in a stroller.

The author and his friend had come to Odessa from Kyiv to ride and relax. As they were searching for a particular location, @metbackk noticed a father approaching with a stroller. Without hesitation, he turned off his engine to avoid making noise that might disturb the child. Although it was a small act, it had a big impact on the father.

The father was touched by his consideration and kindness. He expressed his gratitude for the simple act. In that moment, the author and the father formed a connection based on mutual respect and appreciation.</media:description>
                      <media:keywords>kindness,consideration,connection,gratitude,respect,appreciation,relationships,well-being,happiness,joy,impact,smallact,difference,socialconnections,purpose,meaning,fastpaced,opportunity,simpleact,power</media:keywords>
                      <media:city>Odessa</media:city>
                      <media:country>Ukraine</media:country>
                      <media:regionCode>UA</media:regionCode>
                      <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                      <media:category>Heartwarming</media:category>
                      <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                      <media:filmingDate>Sat, 29 Apr 2023</media:filmingDate>
                      <guid>2041</guid>
                      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2023 11:40:07 GMT</pubDate>
                      <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2041.jpg" />
                      <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2041.mp4" />
                      <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                      </item>
                    
                    <item>
                      <media:title>Easter egg fun with Arseniy: a toddler's joyful egg-tapping adventure</media:title>
                      <media:description>Easter is a special time of year, where families all around the world come together to celebrate the holiday. For @mari.sunsova and her family, Easter is a cherished occasion where they can enjoy spending time together and create new memories. She captured one of these special moments on film, which she shared with her loved ones and later uploaded to social media.

The video shows her two-year-old son, Arseniy, breaking Easter eggs by tapping them on the table. The excitement on Arseniy's face is palpable, as he eagerly waits for his mother to give him another egg to crack. She explains that the family had spent the day before painting the eggs, making the experience even more special for her son.</media:description>
                      <media:keywords>easter,family,celebration,toddler,joy,memories,eggs,painting,love,traditions,social media,sharing,happiness,video,record,archive,childhood,fun,excitement,simplicity</media:keywords>
                      <media:city>Perm</media:city>
                      <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                      <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                      <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                      <media:category>Heartwarming</media:category>
                      <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                      <media:filmingDate>Sun, 16 Apr 2023</media:filmingDate>
                      <guid>1964</guid>
                      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2023 11:06:30 GMT</pubDate>
                      <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/1964.jpg" />
                      <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/1964.mp4" />
                      <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                      </item>
                    
                    <item>
                      <media:title>Sailor's bacon heist from mom's plate </media:title>
                      <media:description>In March 16th, 2023, a video captured by a mother in Payson, Utah, USA went viral on social media. The video features her toddler daughter, Sailor, who is almost two years old, standing on a chair beside her as she eats breakfast. The mother, @lala.kenn, was filming Sailor dancing when suddenly she notices the little one reaching over to grab a piece of bacon from her plate. Sailor quickly snatches the bacon and scurries away, giving her mom a cheeky smile and a sideways glance.

The video is heartwarming and hilarious at the same time. It shows the pure joy and innocence of a child who is just learning about the world around her. Sailor's bacon heist shows her curious and mischievous side. Credit to: @lala.kenn</media:description>
                      <media:keywords>toddler,bacon,theft,dance,funny,heist,mischief,innocence,joy,curiosity,video,viral,social media,cute,funny,heartwarming,family,parenting,love,happiness</media:keywords>
                      <media:city>Payson, Utah</media:city>
                      <media:country>United States</media:country>
                      <media:regionCode>US</media:regionCode>
                      <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                      <media:category>Heartwarming</media:category>
                      <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                      <media:filmingDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2023</media:filmingDate>
                      <guid>1928</guid>
                      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2023 11:06:30 GMT</pubDate>
                      <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear2.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/1928.jpg" />
                      <media:content url="https://viralbear2.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/1928.mp4" />
                      <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                      </item>
                    
                    <item>
                      <media:title>Street cat stands on hind legs and begs for food at Istanbul restaurant | Heartwarming moment caught on camera</media:title>
                      <media:description>A street cat in Istanbul, Turkey has captured the hearts of people all over the internet after a video was shared by @hakanalagozfilm on February 19, 2023. The author of the video stated, "This cat knows its business. I took this video when I saw these sweet states of the cat who wanted to eat in a restaurant in Istanbul Balat. I expected the video to be watched, but I didn’t expect it to get so much attention."

In the video, the adorable cat can be seen standing on its hind legs and asking for food through the window of a restaurant. The cook kindly gives the cat a treat, and the cat is visibly happy with its meal. The cat's charm and sweet demeanor have garnered it a lot of attention on social media.</media:description>
                      <media:keywords>Istanbul,Turkey,street cat,restaurant,video,viral,social media,kindness,compassion,animals</media:keywords>
                      <media:city>Istanbul</media:city>
                      <media:country>Turkey</media:country>
                      <media:regionCode>undefined</media:regionCode>
                      <media:categoryCode>undefined</media:categoryCode>
                      <media:category>Heartwarming</media:category>
                      <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                      <media:filmingDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2023</media:filmingDate>
                      <guid>1762</guid>
                      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2023 11:06:30 GMT</pubDate>
                      <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/1762.jpg" />
                      <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/1762.mp4" />
                      <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                      </item>
                    
                    <item>
                      <media:title>Sleepy little biker boy: a funny moment in Bandung, West Java</media:title>
                      <media:description>In the bustling city of Bandung, West Java, a small boy was caught in a hilarious moment that left bystanders laughing and smiling. The boy, who appeared to be no more than five or six years old, had leaned on a motorbike parked in front of a shop and sleepy, seemingly oblivious to the commotion around him.

As people passed by and noticed the sleepy child, their initial surprise quickly turned into amusement. A small crowd gathered, chuckling at the sight of the boy slumped against the motorbike. It was clear that he was exhausted, and needed sleep. Credit to: @obelt27</media:description>
                      <media:keywords>Bandung West Java,Sleepy boy,Motorbike nap,Hilarious moment,Innocence,Simple pleasures,Unexpected beauty,Heartwarming,Social media viral,Rest and relaxation</media:keywords>
                      <media:city>Bandung</media:city>
                      <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
                      <media:regionCode>undefined</media:regionCode>
                      <media:categoryCode>undefined</media:categoryCode>
                      <media:category>Heartwarming</media:category>
                      <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                      <media:filmingDate>Wed, 8 Mar 2023</media:filmingDate>
                      <guid>1835</guid>
                      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2023 12:00:55 GMT</pubDate>
                      <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/1835.jpg" />
                      <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/1835.mp4" />
                      <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                      </item>
                    
                    <item>
                      <media:title>Newlyweds take the plunge: bungee jumping at Sky Park Sochi</media:title>
                      <media:description>Sky Park Sochi, Russia - In a thrilling display of bravery and adventure, newlyweds took the plunge and bungee jumped off a towering platform at the Sky Park Sochi on March 13th, 2023. The heart-racing video captured the couple as they prepared for the daring feat with the support of cheering crowds.

The scene at Sky Park Sochi was electric as spectators gathered around to watch the brave couple take on the challenge. With cameras flashing and the sound of whoops and cheers echoing through the air, the atmosphere was nothing short of exhilarating.

Donning their bungee gear and taking in the stunning views from atop the platform, the newlyweds appeared both excited and nervous as they prepared to take the leap of faith.

But with the support of the cheering crowds, the couple summoned the courage to take the plunge. As they jumped off the platform, their screams of excitement echoed through the air, adding to the thrill of the moment.</media:description>
                      <media:keywords>newlyweds,bungee,courage,support,cheers,adrenaline,excitement,platform,thrill,adventure,bravery,spectators,cameras,stunning views,leap of faith,screams,safety,applause,congratulations,human connection</media:keywords>
                      <media:city>Sochi</media:city>
                      <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                      <media:regionCode>undefined</media:regionCode>
                      <media:categoryCode>undefined</media:categoryCode>
                      <media:category>Heartwarming</media:category>
                      <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                      <media:filmingDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2023</media:filmingDate>
                      <guid>1877</guid>
                      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2023 14:23:49 GMT</pubDate>
                      <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/1877.jpg" />
                      <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/1877.mp4" />
                      <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                      </item>
                    
                    <item>
                      <media:title>Mom and child and suddenly the baby took his first steps</media:title>
                      <media:description>A video of a mother and 1year old child has gone viral on social media. In the video, the mother is seen getting ready for the day while her child is dressed in a festive outfit. She decides to take a video of them together, but her son is not interested and tries to run away from her. However, he forgets that he cannot walk yet and ends up taking his first steps on camera.

The video was taken on December 7th, 2022 in Volkhov, Russia and has since been shared widely on social media platforms. It is a heartwarming reminder of the joys of parenthood.

Credit to: @yana__denisovna</media:description>
                      <media:keywords>mother,child,viral,social media,festive outfit,video,first steps,Volkhov,Russia</media:keywords>
                      <media:city>Volkhov</media:city>
                      <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                      <media:regionCode>undefined</media:regionCode>
                      <media:categoryCode>undefined</media:categoryCode>
                      <media:category>Heartwarming</media:category>
                      <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                      <media:filmingDate>Wed, 7 Dec 2022</media:filmingDate>
                      <guid>1797</guid>
                      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2023 11:40:07 GMT</pubDate>
                      <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/1797.jpg" />
                      <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/1797.mp4" />
                      <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                      </item>
                    
                    <item>
                      <media:title>Adorable Baby Shaffiya can't stop smiling while playing with Dad in Kuala Lumpur!</media:title>
                      <media:description>On January 19th, 2023, in the Damansara district of Kuala Lumpur, a heartwarming moment between a father and his child was captured on video by @captainshaf8. The video features a baby girl named Shaffiya, who was lying on the floor while her father buttoned up her clothes. In the video, the baby's eyes were covered by clothes, but when her father uncovered them, Shaffiya couldn't stop smiling.

The video shows the bond between a father and his child and the joy that comes with spending time together. The way the father interacts with his child in the video is heartwarming, and it's clear that the baby feels safe and loved in her father's arms.</media:description>
                      <media:keywords>father,child,video,Damansara,Kuala Lumpur,smile,adorable,bond,social media,positive feedback</media:keywords>
                      <media:city>Damansara</media:city>
                      <media:country>Kuala Lumpur</media:country>
                      <media:regionCode>undefined</media:regionCode>
                      <media:categoryCode>undefined</media:categoryCode>
                      <media:category>Heartwarming</media:category>
                      <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                      <media:filmingDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023</media:filmingDate>
                      <guid>1748</guid>
                      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2023 11:34:18 GMT</pubDate>
                      <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/1748.jpg" />
                      <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/1748.mp4" />
                      <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                      </item>
                    
                    <item>
                      <media:title>Heartwarming Moment as Sick Dog Daisy Greets Father in USA </media:title>
                      <media:description>In a heartwarming moment captured filmed on 8 January 2023 by Tiktok user @anxious.dog.mom, a sick dog named Daisy is seen greeting her father despite facing some health difficulties. The video, which has been making rounds on social media, has garnered widespread attention and praise for its touching depiction of the bond between humans and their furry companions.

Daisy, who resides in the United States, is shown in the video excitedly wagging her tail and jumping up to greet her "dada" every night when he returns home. Despite her illness, Daisy is clearly overjoyed to see her father, and the moment is a testament to the unbreakable bond that can form between pets and their owners.</media:description>
                      <media:keywords>dog,Father,Health difficulties,Heartwarming moment,USA,Bond,Greeting,Social media</media:keywords>
                      <media:city>-</media:city>
                      <media:country>USA</media:country>
                      <media:regionCode>undefined</media:regionCode>
                      <media:categoryCode>undefined</media:categoryCode>
                      <media:category>Heartwarming</media:category>
                      <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                      <media:filmingDate>Sun, 8 Jan 2023</media:filmingDate>
                      <guid>1707</guid>
                      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2023 11:06:30 GMT</pubDate>
                      <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1707.jpg" />
                      <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1707.mp4" />
                      <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                      </item>
                    
                    <item>
                      <media:title>A heartwarming scene of grandchildren and pets sleeping together</media:title>
                      <media:description>On January 8, 2023, @7777.pv had the pleasure of hosting her grandchildren for a visit at her home in Pavlodar, Kazakhstan. As she checked on them during their nap, she couldn't help but notice the peaceful scene in front of her: her grandchildren snuggled up with her beloved pets.

Olga is the proud owner of four furry companions. Two older cats were adopted from a shelter, starting with just one kitten. As time passed, Olga and her family couldn't resist adding more feline friends to their household. She named her cat Senior Klaus, Middle Benjamin, and Junior Tyson, and her dog Archie.

Overwhelmed with the cuteness of the moment, Olga decided to capture it on video, as the sight of her grandchildren peacefully sleeping alongside her pets was too beautiful not to share. The quiet and peaceful atmosphere in the room was a reminder of the joy and love that pets bring into our lives.

It's clear that Olga's pets are not only beloved members of her family but also bring happiness and comfort to her grandchildren during their visits. Pets have a unique ability to create a sense of warmth and security, making any home feel like a sanctuary.</media:description>
                      <media:keywords>grandchildren,pets,animals,sleep,cats,dog,peaceful,shelter,cute,comfort,hosting</media:keywords>
                      <media:city>Pavlodar</media:city>
                      <media:country>Kazakhstan</media:country>
                      <media:regionCode>undefined</media:regionCode>
                      <media:categoryCode>undefined</media:categoryCode>
                      <media:category>Heartwarming</media:category>
                      <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                      <media:filmingDate>Sun, 8 Jan 2023</media:filmingDate>
                      <guid>1541</guid>
                      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2023 13:13:50 GMT</pubDate>
                      <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1541.jpg" />
                      <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1541.mp4" />
                      <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                      </item>
                    
                    <item>
                      <media:title>Touching video! The teacher took care of the student's child while she was taking the exam</media:title>
                      <media:description>24 September 2022, Catbalogan, Philippines
The author: "My classmate bring her 5 month old babie because according to her their is no one who will take care of the baby that time. Eventually our professor saw her carying the baby in her left arm while answering. And he ask the mother if he could carry the baby until the mother finished the exam so that she also can focus on it ."
Credit to: @ezzapermaci</media:description>
                      <media:keywords>teacher,student,touching,care,baby,child,exam,mother</media:keywords>
                      <media:city>Catbalogan</media:city>
                      <media:country>Philippines</media:country>
                      <media:regionCode>undefined</media:regionCode>
                      <media:categoryCode>undefined</media:categoryCode>
                      <media:category>Heartwarming</media:category>
                      <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                      <media:filmingDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2022</media:filmingDate>
                      <guid>1314</guid>
                      <pubDate>Invalid Date</pubDate>
                      <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1314.jpg" />
                      <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1314.mp4" />
                      <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                      </item>
                    
                    <item>
                      <media:title>Man makes broom using recycled plastic bottles.</media:title>
                      <media:description>The Author said: "I am a street sweeper, and in my spare time, I make brooms using recycled plastic bottles. I am an alcoholic and separated from my husband. I decided to go to a rehabilitation clinic. Now I am free from alcoholism and make brooms using machines for recycling used plastic bottles.

My dream is to have a recycling center here in Paraíba, I have been using bottles for seven years, and we have removed 10 tons of bottles from the environment. I have the first recycled broom factory to use 100% clean and renewable energy."

Credit to: Giorggio gari ecológico</media:description>
                      <media:keywords>recycled,plastic,bottles,broom,alcoholic,environment,Brazil</media:keywords>
                      <media:city>Paraíba</media:city>
                      <media:country>Brazil</media:country>
                      <media:regionCode>undefined</media:regionCode>
                      <media:categoryCode>undefined</media:categoryCode>
                      <media:category>Heartwarming</media:category>
                      <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                      <media:filmingDate>Invalid date</media:filmingDate>
                      <guid>1393</guid>
                      <pubDate>Invalid Date</pubDate>
                      <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1393.jpg" />
                      <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1393.mp4" />
                      <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                      </item>
                    
                    <item>
                      <media:title>Boy's sweet reaction to father dressed in Spider-Man costume!</media:title>
                      <media:description>27 October 2022, Breinigsville, PA, USA
The author said: "Our 2 and a half year old son has loved anything involving marvel since he was about 7 months old or so. He favors the hulk, iron man, and of course Spiderman! I’ve personally been a Spider-Man fan since I was about 10 and his dad has gotten into all marvel films since we’ve been together. We watch the movies as a couple at home and Leo, our son, was captivated the moment he first saw one! His dad went to the store one day and came home with a Spider-Man mask full on expecting Leo to know it was daddy, to our surprise he lit up with excitement and embraced spidey sharing his home! I will add a couple photos from trick or treat where daddy dressed up as Spider-Man and Leo as Hulk, to which Leo was thrilled."
Credit to: @emmie_rei</media:description>
                      <media:keywords>boy,baby,reaction,father,dad,Spider-Man,marvel,cute</media:keywords>
                      <media:city>Breinigsville</media:city>
                      <media:country>USA</media:country>
                      <media:regionCode>undefined</media:regionCode>
                      <media:categoryCode>undefined</media:categoryCode>
                      <media:category>Heartwarming</media:category>
                      <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                      <media:filmingDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022</media:filmingDate>
                      <guid>1226</guid>
                      <pubDate>Invalid Date</pubDate>
                      <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/9d50d8b6-bc59-43aa-8088-7e2b9973cdaa.jpg" />
                      <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/48a935a0-ac3b-46d4-8288-3130d196fadb.mp4" />
                      <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                      </item>
                    
                    <item>
                      <media:title>Concert of the string ensemble in the Kyiv metro during the air raid</media:title>
                      <media:description>The announcement of the air raid alert did not cause the music to stop for a string ensemble concert in the Kiev metro.</media:description>
                      <media:keywords>war,ukraine,kyiv,metro,Concert,air raid</media:keywords>
                      <media:city>Kyiv</media:city>
                      <media:country>Ukraine</media:country>
                      <media:regionCode>undefined</media:regionCode>
                      <media:categoryCode>undefined</media:categoryCode>
                      <media:category>Heartwarming</media:category>
                      <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                      <media:filmingDate>Invalid date</media:filmingDate>
                      <guid>1346</guid>
                      <pubDate>Invalid Date</pubDate>
                      <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1346.jpg" />
                      <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1346.mp4" />
                      <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                      </item>
                    
                    <item>
                      <media:title>It is so heartwarming! The blind cat cautious as he descends from chair</media:title>
                      <media:description>6 August 2022, Connecticut, USA
The author said: "Hoggle is an 8 years old male blind cat. He was born without eyes, so he has taught himself to go down objects and furniture backwards."
Credit to: @carolyngross2</media:description>
                      <media:keywords>heartwarming,animals,cat,pet,blind,furniture,USA,eyes</media:keywords>
                      <media:city>-</media:city>
                      <media:country>USA</media:country>
                      <media:regionCode>undefined</media:regionCode>
                      <media:categoryCode>undefined</media:categoryCode>
                      <media:category>Heartwarming</media:category>
                      <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                      <media:filmingDate>Sat, 6 Aug 2022</media:filmingDate>
                      <guid>1300</guid>
                      <pubDate>Invalid Date</pubDate>
                      <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1300.jpg" />
                      <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1300.mp4" />
                      <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                      </item>
                    
                    <item>
                      <media:title>The baby's sweet reaction to the food he tried for the first time!</media:title>
                      <media:description>14 September 2022, Penza, Russia
The baby 8 months old tried cottage cheese for the first time and is surprised by the new taste!
Credit to: @valeria_vodyanova</media:description>
                      <media:keywords>baby,kid,reaction,food,cottage cheese,surprise,taste,Russia</media:keywords>
                      <media:city>Penza</media:city>
                      <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                      <media:regionCode>undefined</media:regionCode>
                      <media:categoryCode>undefined</media:categoryCode>
                      <media:category>Heartwarming</media:category>
                      <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                      <media:filmingDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2022</media:filmingDate>
                      <guid>1292</guid>
                      <pubDate>Invalid Date</pubDate>
                      <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1292.jpg" />
                      <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1292.mp4" />
                      <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                      </item>
                    
                     </channel>
                  </rss>
                