<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
        xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
        xmlns:openSearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearchrss/1.0/"
        xmlns:dfpvideo="http://api.google.com/dfpvideo"
        xmlns:tms="http://data.tmsapi.com/v1.1"
        version="2.0">
         <channel>
           <title>ViralBear videos</title>
           <dfpvideo:version>2</dfpvideo:version><item>
             <media:title>Nature's fury unleashed: lightning strikes and flames explode in Shijiazhuang</media:title>
             <media:description>On July 24, 2023, in Shijiazhuang, northern China, a startling and unintentional event was captured on video by @HomelessYuanyuan. As she stood in front of her apartment window with her mobile phone, attempting to capture a street scene during a rainstorm and thunder, lightning struck the transformer below her building. The intense impact caused sparks of flames to erupt, scattering fiery fragments in all directions. Nature's fury was unleashed, and in a split second, the author found herself witnessing a breathtaking display of raw power and danger.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>lightning,sparks,flames,explosion,rainstorm,thunder,Shijiazhuang,China,video,mobile,window,street,nature,fury,power,danger,unpredictability,awe,humbled,@HomelessYuanyuan</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Shijiazhuang</media:city>
             <media:country>China</media:country>
             <media:category>News</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2604</guid>
             <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 13:16:50 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2604.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2604.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Terrifying Yokohama guerrilla rainstorm unleashes chaos with its fierce winds and torrential downpour</media:title>
             <media:description>In Yokohama, Japan, on August 1, 2023, @Tomo_YNU captured a chilling video of a rainstorm known as Guerrilla. This local phenomenon is characterized by an unpredictable formation of cumulonimbus clouds, resulting in a short but intense downpour of over 100 mm per hour of rain. The video showcases the fury of the Guerrilla rainstorm, with powerful winds swaying trees in its path. The dangerous nature of this event highlights the need for caution and preparedness during such occurrences in Yokohama.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>rainstorm,guerrilla,yokohama,japan,video,downpour,cumulonimbus,clouds,intense,winds,trees,dangerous,unpredictable,weather,phenomenon,local,short,mm,hour,rain</media:keywords>
             <media:city> Yokohama</media:city>
             <media:country>Japan</media:country>
             <media:category>Weather</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Tue, 1 Aug 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2601</guid>
             <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 13:12:08 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2601.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2601.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Tokyo's sideways rain: nature's dance of wind and water</media:title>
             <media:description>In a mesmerizing spectacle captured on August 1, 2023, from the heart of Tokyo, Japan, @4H6M8u0YmemZwmj shared a breathtaking video of sideways rain cascading down window panes. As nature's elements collided, the wind's mighty force compelled the raindrops to dance sideways, creating a captivating display of nature's power and beauty. The video serves as a vivid reminder of the unpredictable yet awe-inspiring wonders of the natural world, leaving viewers in awe of the harmonious choreography between wind and water. </media:description>
             <media:keywords>wind,rain,sideways,video,Tokyo,Japan,nature,spectacle,mesmerizing,window,panes,dance,elements,force,beauty,power,display,awe,urban,landscape</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Tokyo </media:city>
             <media:country>Japan</media:country>
             <media:category>Weather</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Tue, 1 Aug 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2600</guid>
             <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 13:12:22 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2600.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2600.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Playful and obedient: Khryapa's impressive 'swim' command!</media:title>
             <media:description>In a heartwarming video captured by @mokryi_nosik_ on June 17, 2020, in Voronezh, Russia, her beloved dog, Khryapa, stole the spotlight with her incredible obedience and playful nature. The footage shows @mokryi_nosik_ talking to Khryapa in one of the rooms, when suddenly, the clever canine dashes off towards the bathroom. Without hesitation, Khryapa leaps into the bathtub, showcasing her impressive execution of the "swim" command. The three-year-old furry friend proves to be not only obedient but also full of joy and enthusiasm. Her charming antics have won the hearts of viewers worldwide, leaving a lasting impression of her delightful personality and the strong bond between her and her owner.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>playful,obedient,dog,swim,command,video,Khryapa,Voronezh,Russia,bathtub,bathroom,three years old,pet,canine,joy,love,bond,clever,cute,charming</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Voronezh</media:city>
             <media:country>Russia</media:country>
             <media:category>Animals</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2598</guid>
             <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 10:57:32 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2598.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2598.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Playful corgi's adorable 'poof' act delights internet in St. Petersburg, Russia!</media:title>
             <media:description>In an endearing and amusing video that captured hearts on social media, a Corgi named Leo from St. Petersburg, Russia, showcased his unique talent for playing "dead." The video, shared by @prokopenkokate on April 29, 2023, depicts Leo sitting peacefully on the floor before his owner mimics a shooting gesture with her hands. Surprisingly, the adorable pup immediately flops down, pretending to be "shot" as part of a playful command he has mastered. As a reward for his impressive performance, Leo eagerly awaits a treat, proving that his favorite command is the delightful and harmless "poof," leaving viewers charmed by this clever and lovable canine's antics.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>playful,corgi,leo,video,internet,acting,dog,Russia,St. Petersburg,pet,owner,gun,pretend,cute,charm,humor,social media,adorable,command,sweet</media:keywords>
             <media:city>St. Petersburg</media:city>
             <media:country>Russia</media:country>
             <media:category>Animals</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Sat, 29 Apr 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2595</guid>
             <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 10:53:38 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2595.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2595.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>First-time rider's mishap: girl's scooter adventure ends with a bump!</media:title>
             <media:description>In a candid video captured by @wkmzxuk_ on July 15, 2023, in the City of Soligorsk, Minsk region, Belarus, a young girl's first-time experience with an electronic scooter took an unexpected turn. With enthusiasm and excitement, she hopped onto the scooter but found herself struggling to control its speed. Unaware of the gears and unfamiliar with braking, she careened toward a stationary sign near a building, unable to halt her momentum. The result was a comical yet cautionary collision, reminding viewers of the importance of learning the basics before embarking on new adventures. While the girl's misadventure might have left her a little shaken, it undoubtedly served as a valuable lesson for both her and others who dare to ride the scooters for the first time.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>scooter,mishap,video,girl,first-time,adventure,excitement,gears,braking,collision,cautionary,comical,lessons,learning,electronic,speed,sign,building,Belarus,Soligorsk</media:keywords>
             <media:city> City of Soligorsk, Minsk region</media:city>
             <media:country>Belarus</media:country>
             <media:category>Fails and Funnies</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2594</guid>
             <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 10:53:05 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2594.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2594.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Tranquil moments: Tokyo's beloved dog relishes in shallow creek at favorite park</media:title>
             <media:description>In a heartwarming scene captured on June 24, 2023, in Tokyo, Japan, @mr.donbei_inu shared a delightful video of his beloved dog finding sheer bliss in a small, slow creek at their favorite park. The four-legged companion appeared completely at ease, comfortably resting its head on the surface of the shallow water, joyfully savoring the gentle flow around it. Unlike most dogs, this furry friend chose not to swim but found pure contentment in merely basking in the refreshing water. With a serene expression, the canine seemed to have discovered a little piece of paradise amidst the bustling city, making this tranquil spot its most cherished destination in the park.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>dog,creek,park,Tokyo,Japan,chilling,water,shallow,serene,bliss,favorite,video,pet,companion,contentment,relaxation,joy,tranquility,peaceful,happiness</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Tokyo</media:city>
             <media:country>Japan</media:country>
             <media:category>Animals</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2593</guid>
             <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 10:52:42 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2593.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2593.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Love blossoms at a birthday party: tender smiles of a toddler</media:title>
             <media:description>In a heartwarming moment captured by @ayreeeshh_ on March 12, 2023, at a birthday party in Las Piñas, Manila, Philippines, a two-year-old boy named Drei melted hearts as he looked tenderly at a little girl named Aliah. The usually quiet and well-behaved toddler seemed to be smitten with Aliah, flashing sweet smiles and even raising his eyebrows at her, giving the impression of a young love in the making. Drei's mother shared the adorable video, describing how her son became seemingly interested in Aliah, and it quickly became a viral sensation, spreading joy and warmth across the internet. This endearing encounter serves as a reminder of the innocent and pure connections that can blossom even among the youngest of hearts.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>love,toddler,birthday,party,smiles,tender,falling,in,young,children,innocence,adorable,viral,internet,connections,heartwarming,Manila,Philippines,Aliah,Drei,@ayreeeshh_</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Las Piñas, Manila</media:city>
             <media:country>Philippines</media:country>
             <media:category>Heartwarming</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2592</guid>
             <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 10:51:48 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2592.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2592.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Tenacious twig tug-of-war: a dog's unyielding affair with nature's bounty</media:title>
             <media:description>In a delightful and amusing scene captured by @chelseareject on May 21, 2023, in Jersey City, New Jersey, USA, her four-legged companion exhibited an unshakeable determination during a playful encounter with nature. The video showcased the adorable pup clenching onto a sizable twig of a tree, despite the owner's best efforts to convince it otherwise. With @chelseareject's voice gently coaxing the dog to release its prized find, the resilient canine remained unyielding, steadfastly refusing to let go. Undeterred, they strolled along together, the furry protagonist proudly showcasing its prized possession in an endearing tug-of-war with the forces of nature. The heartwarming display of canine spirit and persistence resonated with viewers worldwide, capturing the essence of a special bond between humans and their loyal companions.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>tree,dog,twig,nature,Jersey City,USA,May,2023,video,pet,playful,determined,adorable,owner,walk,bonding,persistence,loyalty,companionship,endearing,capture</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Jersey City, New Jersey</media:city>
             <media:country>United States</media:country>
             <media:category>Animals</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Sun, 21 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2586</guid>
             <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 09:23:40 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2586.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2586.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Cake mishap: hilarious family moment in Ankara, Turkey</media:title>
             <media:description>In a heartwarming yet comical family moment captured in Ankara, Turkey, a video shared by @amywinehouzze on July 15, 2023, showcased their little one indulging in a cake while kneeling on a dining chair. The child's innocent delight was infectious as they merrily savored the cake in one hand, but alas, laughter ensued as the sweet treat slipped from their grasp while trying to juggle it with the other hand. Surrounding family members couldn't help but burst into fits of laughter, turning the mishap into an unforgettable memory. This endearing scene reminds us of the simple joys and shared laughter that bring families together, creating cherished moments to be cherished for years to come.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>cake,kid,dining,table,Ankara,Turkey,video,laughter,family,moment,comical,mishap,sweet,treat,delight,memorable,joy,shared,precious,memory</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Ankara</media:city>
             <media:country>Turkey</media:country>
             <media:category>Fails and Funnies</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2581</guid>
             <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023 17:45:47 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2581.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2581.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Intense hailstorm hits Central Ottawa: golf ball sized hail pummels the city for 5 minutes!</media:title>
             <media:description>On July 28, 2023, residents of Ottawa, Canada, experienced an intense hailstorm that left them astonished and wary. The event was captured on video by @paulajroy, who shared the gripping footage of the hailstorm outside her house. Lasting for approximately five minutes, the hailstones reached nearly the size of golf balls, causing significant concern for property damage and potential risks to individuals caught outdoors. The severe weather phenomenon swept through central Ottawa, leaving a trail of destruction in its wake.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>hailstorm,ottawa,canada,weather,intense,video,paulajroy,golfball,sized,hail,central,astonishment,damage,risk,outdoors,severe,phenomenon,destruction,warnings,precautions</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Ottawa </media:city>
             <media:country>Canada</media:country>
             <media:category>Weather</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2579</guid>
             <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023 17:39:58 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2579.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2579.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Resourceful feline masters the art of door-opening: a fascinating tale from Jepara, Indonesia!</media:title>
             <media:description>In a captivating video captured by @muktafil on April 24, 2023, in Jepara, Indonesia, an astonishing feat unfolded as their clever cat showcased its ingenuity. The footage showcases the feline effortlessly opening the door to the house, by jumping on the door handle leaving its owner in awe of its newfound talent. Expressing his astonishment, the author stated, "I was surprised that the cat opened the door by itself, now if you put it outside, it will open the door. Don't know where it learned from." The video has since captured the hearts of viewers worldwide, as they marvel at the resourceful cat's ability to conquer the seemingly insurmountable obstacle. This extraordinary tale serves as a reminder of the intelligence and adaptability possessed by our feline companions.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>clever,cat,door,opening,video,Jepara,Indonesia,surprise,talent,resourceful,ingenuity,amazement,owner,outside,learn,astonishment,heartwarming,intelligence,adaptability,feline</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Jepara</media:city>
             <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
             <media:category>Animals</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2578</guid>
             <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 07:29:30 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2578.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2578.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Bathroom bliss: Indonesian cat's unique way to beat the heat</media:title>
             <media:description>In Yogyakarta, Indonesia, a heartwarming video captured by @bagus_muhammad_ on March 28, 2023, showcases the adorable antics of his feline companion during a hot day. The short clip features his cat lying flat on its stomach in the cool confines of the bathroom, delightfully spreading its hind legs for ultimate relaxation. As temperatures rise, it seems this clever kitty has found its perfect oasis for beating the heat. With a contented expression on its face, it's evident that the bathroom has become the preferred spot for the cat to seek respite from the sweltering weather. </media:description>
             <media:keywords>cat,bathroom,Indonesia,Yogyakarta,video,pet,feline,hot,heat,adorable,antics,relaxation,hind legs,oasis,cool,weather,comfort,pets,content,warmer days</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Yogyakarta</media:city>
             <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
             <media:category>Animals</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2577</guid>
             <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 08:17:01 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2577.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2577.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Devastating wildfire strikes near Volos, Greece</media:title>
             <media:description>On July 27, 2023, a destructive wildfire ravaged the area near Volos, Greece, causing significant damage to an ammunition depot situated in the coastal town of Nea Aghialos. The depot, belonging to the Greek air force, was engulfed in flames, leading to powerful explosions that echoed through the region. Local media reported on the incident, and officials took immediate action, ordering the evacuation of several communities in the severely impacted Magnesia area along the northern coast of Athens. As the fires continued to spread, @peterjaygood captured a video showcasing smoke billowing from a distance from the fires near Volos. The situation remained critical, with authorities and emergency services working tirelessly to contain the blaze and protect the affected communities.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>wildfire,volos,greece,ammunition,depot,explosions,evacuation,magnesia,coastal,nea aghialos,greek air force,damage,smoke,fires,video,@peterjaygood,media,officials,communities,Athens</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Volos</media:city>
             <media:country>Greece</media:country>
             <media:category>News</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2575</guid>
             <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 07:26:05 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2575.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2575.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Adventurous Manda: a curious cat's high-rise escapades in Yogyakarta!</media:title>
             <media:description>In a captivating moment caught on video by @a.youu_ on July 4, 2023, in Yogyakarta, Indonesia, a curious cat named Manda was spotted perched atop an unfinished building. The enigmatic feline appeared unsure of its surroundings, leaving viewers both amused and intrigued by its daring escapade. With a playful spirit, the author decided to record the charming scene, showcasing Manda's adventurous nature and uncertain demeanor as it surveyed the world from its lofty vantage point.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>cat,video,Yogyakarta,Indonesia,Manda,building,perched,curious,confused,fun,playful,adventurous,daring,charming,uncertain,climb,pet,antics,moment,heartwarming</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Yogyakarta</media:city>
             <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
             <media:category>Animals</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Tue, 4 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2573</guid>
             <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 08:15:12 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2573.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2573.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Adventurous boat dog: a joyful journey on the waters of Posadas, Argentina</media:title>
             <media:description>In Posadas, Argentina, a heartwarming sight was captured by @fefu1408 on December 1, 2021. A video showcased a spirited dog perched confidently on the front of a speeding boat, appearing to relish every moment of the thrilling experience. As the author went rowing with a friend, they encountered this common occurrence of dogs joining the boating adventures. In this particular instance, the dog belonged to another boat that passed them by, showcasing the adventurous spirit and love for the water that these furry companions hold. </media:description>
             <media:keywords>rowing,boat,dog,adventure,Posadas,Argentina,speed,waters,joyful,companions,video,water,front,perched,passing,friend,common,furry,capture,spirit</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Posadas</media:city>
             <media:country>Argentina</media:country>
             <media:category>Animals</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Wed, 1 Dec 2021</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2572</guid>
             <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 07:28:52 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2572.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2572.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Enchanting fur patterns: unique cat in Blitar delights in friendly affection</media:title>
             <media:description>In a heartwarming scene captured on video by @polseksrengat on June 30, 2023, in Blitar, Indonesia, a cat with naturally polished fur became the center of attention among a group of friends. The cat sported a striking combination of white fur on its face and a mix of white and black fur on the rest of its body, making it truly unique. As the friends scratched the cat gently, it basked in their affectionate company, closing its eyes in contentment each time one of them touched its head. The endearing sight of this feline enjoying the camaraderie warmed the hearts of those who witnessed the adorable encounter, reminding us of the profound bond between humans and their feline companions.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>polished,fur,cat,white,black,unique,friends,affection,company,contentment,adorable,feline,bond,Indonesia,Blitar,video,captured,June30,2023,@polseksrengat</media:keywords>
             <media:city> Blitar</media:city>
             <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
             <media:category>Animals</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2571</guid>
             <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 08:08:02 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2571.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2571.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Quirky Yeti: cat asserts ownership over owner's resting foot in hilarious video!</media:title>
             <media:description>In a heartwarming yet amusing video captured by @dymova_brows on December 14, 2022, in Zaporozhye, Ukraine, a 7-year-old cat named Yeti showcases its unique character. The footage shows Yeti attempting to keep its owner's foot still under the blanket while playfully growling like a dog when met with resistance. The quirky feline's predilections include strolls on the balcony and relishing wet food, but it fiercely guards its delicious meals from fellow feline companions. The short video captures Yeti's endearing and assertive personality, providing a delightful glimpse into the fascinating world of this furry friend.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>cat,yeti,video,quirky,owner,foot,bed,blanket,growl,dog,character,Zaporozhye,Ukraine,balcony,wet food,delicious,unique,feline,playful,adorable</media:keywords>
             <media:city> Zaporozhye</media:city>
             <media:country>Ukraine</media:country>
             <media:category>Animals</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2569</guid>
             <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 07:20:35 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2569.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2569.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Emotional dilemma: heartwarming video shows child's tears turn into joy when offered money</media:title>
             <media:description>In a touching video captured by @yhangespela on June 2, 2023, in San Mateo, Rizal, Philippines, a young child's conflicting emotions towards money were showcased. The footage depicted the child initially crying but quickly becoming quiet and even expressing a desire for more when presented with money. The heartwarming scene left viewers pondering the complexities of children's perceptions of money and the diverse range of emotions it can evoke in young minds.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>crying,money,child,emotions,video,touching,Philippines,San Mateo,young,tears,joy,desire,perception,mother,quiet,conflicting,heartwarming,captured,presented,note</media:keywords>
             <media:city>San Mateo, Rizal</media:city>
             <media:country>Philippines</media:country>
             <media:category>Heartwarming</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Fri, 2 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2568</guid>
             <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 07:55:27 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2568.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2568.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Fearless driver defies odds: nonchalantly navigates car on swaying tow track through Minsk's road</media:title>
             <media:description>In a remarkable display of nonchalance, a video captured by @rrrinita on July 12, 2023, in Minsk, Belarus, showcased a driver unbothered by the perilous sight of a car being carried and swaying on the road. The onlooker initially suspected the driver might be feeling unwell, but to their surprise, the driver appeared utterly unfazed, revealing that it was not their first time engaging in such an audacious feat. Attached to the vehicle was a tow track where the car was mounted, causing it to sway dangerously from side to side. Despite the alarming spectacle, the driver calmly continued to navigate through the streets of Minsk, defying the odds and leaving witnesses astounded by their fearless determination.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>car,tow,swaying,road,driver,fearless,Minsk,Belarus,video,danger,audacious,nonchalant,astonishing,surprising,unfazed,daring,streets,spectacle,determination,amazed</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Minsk</media:city>
             <media:country>Belarus</media:country>
             <media:category>News</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2565</guid>
             <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 07:13:05 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2565.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2565.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Action-packed movie filming in Chisinau takes a dramatic turn as car rams parked bus!</media:title>
             <media:description>In a stunning turn of events in Chisinau, Moldova, a movie filming session took a thrilling and unexpected twist as a car intentionally rammed into a parked bus. The dramatic scene, captured by @nazligian_ on July 23, 2023, showcased the heart-pounding moment when the car, utilizing a purpose-built ramp, accelerated towards the stationary bus. With precision and skill, the car collided with the bus, creating a breathtaking spectacle that left onlookers in awe. Fortunately, there were no reported injuries as the filming was conducted in a closed-off area in the city center. The incident occurred as part of the action-packed movie production, adding an authentic touch to the adrenaline-filled scenes being brought to life on the silver screen.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>movie,filming,chisinau,moldova,car,bus,ramp,action,thrilling,unexpected,dramatic,spectacle,onlookers,injury-free,closed-off,center,adrenaline,scenes,silver screen,production</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Chisinau </media:city>
             <media:country>Moldova</media:country>
             <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Sun, 23 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2563</guid>
             <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 07:49:50 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2563.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2563.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Catnap couture: adorable feline caught napping in boutique's pink mavin!</media:title>
             <media:description>In the city of Borisov, Belarus, on July 16, 2023, a heartwarming scene unfolded in a second clothes boutique. Local resident @ugimaster stumbled upon a delightful sight as he entered the store - a contented cat fast asleep amidst the clothes. Its furry head was cozily nestled on a soft pink mavin, adding an extra touch of cuteness to the scene. The video captured by @ugimaster quickly went viral, spreading smiles and warming hearts across the internet.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>cat,sleeping,clothes,boutique,Borisov,Belarus,@ugimaster,video,peaceful,pink,mavin,adorable,feline,nap,city,viral,internet,heartwarming,cozy,cute</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Borisov</media:city>
             <media:country>Belarus</media:country>
             <media:category>Animals</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2562</guid>
             <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 07:47:37 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2562.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2562.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Raccoon's Miron misadventures: a heartwarming birthday surprise!</media:title>
             <media:description>In a heartwarming tale of misadventures, @raccoon_miron from St. Petersburg, Russia, captured a touching video while searching for her beloved raccoon pet, Miron on April 27, 2023. The furry troublemaker had managed to scatter her belongings all over the apartment on the eve of his birthday, leaving her in tears, fearing he had escaped through the window. However, to her relief, Miron was just being mischievous and had fallen asleep amidst her things. The emotional rollercoaster of worry and joy unfolded in the video.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>raccoon,miron,video,pet,birthday,surprise,misadventures,St. Petersburg,Russia,apartment,balcony,work,order,sobbing,window,smart,boy,asleep,things,love,joy.</media:keywords>
             <media:city> St. Petersburg</media:city>
             <media:country>Russia</media:country>
             <media:category>Animals</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2558</guid>
             <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 07:43:53 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2558.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2558.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Massive moth invasion: swarms of flying creatures fill the night skies in Yelets, Russia</media:title>
             <media:description>On the night of Monday, July 24, 2023, the city of Yelets in the Lipetsk region, Russia, experienced a bizarre phenomenon as drivers encountered a massive invasion of insects. Thousands of flying creatures, identified as moths, enveloped the road lights, creating "swarm clouds" that obstructed the path on the Karakum bridge. Disturbing footage recorded by a driver showcased the surreal scene, where the insects swarmed around vehicles, making navigation challenging. </media:description>
             <media:keywords>insects,invasion,Yelets,Russia,night,Monday,July 24,Lipetsk,drivers,filmed,massive,flying,creatures,swarm,clouds,Karakum,bridge,moths,video,way,drove</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Yelets, Lipetsk region</media:city>
             <media:country>Russia</media:country>
             <media:category>Animals</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2556</guid>
             <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 14:56:15 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2556.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2556.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Blaze breaks out on Panama-registered car carrier Fremantle Highway off Netherlands coast</media:title>
             <media:description>A fire broke out on the Panama-registered car carrier, Fremantle Highway, off the coast of the Netherlands near Ameland on July 26, 2023, as it was transporting 2,857 cars from Bremerhaven, Germany, to Port Said, Egypt. The blaze resulted in the evacuation of all 23 crew members, with seven rescued from the water and the rest airlifted by helicopter. Tragically, one crew member lost their life, and several others were injured during the incident. The fire, originating from one of the 25 electric cars onboard, proved difficult for the crew to control, and the vessel continued to burn approximately 27 nautical miles north of the Dutch island of Ameland, close to a major environmental and UNESCO heritage site. Images showed scorched areas and billowing smoke along the ship's side as emergency responders battled to contain the flames. @NicoGuud captured a video of smoke still coming from the vessel.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>fire,blaze,car carrier,Netherlands,coast,Fremantle Highway,smoke,evacuation,rescue,injuries,crew,incident,electric cars,tragedy,Ameland,environmental,UNESCO,scorched,emergency,responders</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Ameland</media:city>
             <media:country>Netherlands</media:country>
             <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2552</guid>
             <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023 20:11:03 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2552.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2552.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Skyscraper fire and crane collapse: dramatic scene unfolds at 41st and 10th Ave, New York</media:title>
             <media:description>In a harrowing incident on the 26th of July, 2023, at the intersection of 41st and 10th Ave in New York City, USA, a devastating fire broke out on top of a skyscraper, accompanied by a catastrophic crane collapse. The intense scene was captured by @akofink, who shared a chilling video showcasing smoke billowing from the building's pinnacle. The social media post was captioned, "Crane collapse and fire! 41st and 10th Ave. First responders on the scene." The incident prompted an immediate response from first responders who rushed to the location to combat the raging blaze and assess the extent of the damage. </media:description>
             <media:keywords>skyscraper,fire,crane,collapse,New York,USA,video,smoke,41st,10th Ave,incident,responders,damage,investigation,social media,tragedy,authorities,intersection,billowing,chilling</media:keywords>
             <media:city>New York City</media:city>
             <media:country>United States</media:country>
             <media:category>News</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2551</guid>
             <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023 18:25:43 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2551.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2551.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Wildfires ravage Cascais, Portugal: local residents and firefighters battle blaze in Sintra-Cascais Natural Park</media:title>
             <media:description>On July 25th, 2023, a devastating wildfire struck the picturesque region of Cascais, Portugal. The blaze originated at 5 p.m. in the mountainous terrain of the Sintra-Cascais natural park, covering an expansive 145 square kilometers of land west of Lisbon. At 6 p.m., @InVasconcellos captured a video of the raging inferno, as hundreds of Portuguese firefighters, supported by local residents, scrambled to contain the flames. However, their efforts were challenged by strong winds, complicating the firefighting process. The popular holiday destination of Cascais faced a threat to its natural beauty and wildlife as the fire continued to spread, prompting urgent action from the authorities to control the devastating situation.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>cascais,portugal,wildfires,2023,video,@InVasconcellos,july,25th,natural park,firefighters,blaze,mountainous,sintra-cascais,land,lisbon,winds,residents,holiday destination,effort,authorities.</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Cascais</media:city>
             <media:country>Portugal</media:country>
             <media:category>News</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2550</guid>
             <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 14:49:01 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2550.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2550.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Tornado-like waterspout seen on Minsk Sea: a captivating spectacle leaves locals amazed</media:title>
             <media:description>On July 22, 2023, @ikorvel captured a remarkable video of a tornado-like waterspout on the Minsk Sea in Belarus. Initially mistaken for smoke from a fire on the neighboring shore, the swirling air quickly revealed its true nature. Fortunately, the waterspout did not approach their location, and after 10 minutes, only an increased wind accompanied by rain reached them, causing no damage to the surroundings. The awe-inspiring sight left the witnesses astonished at the forces of nature on display.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>video,tornado,waterspout,Minsk,Belarus,July,2023,nature,phenomenon,captivating,swirling,air,smoke,fire,neighboring,wind,rain,amazed,forces,astonishing</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Minsk </media:city>
             <media:country>Belarus</media:country>
             <media:category>Weather</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2549</guid>
             <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023 17:52:04 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2549.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2549.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Silent expectations: a comical tale of leash mishaps and unspoken desires</media:title>
             <media:description>In a heartwarming yet amusing video captured by @bentleyandfinnn on June 12, 2023, in Texas, USA, a dog's expressive response to an unexpected leash mishap left viewers in stitches. The dog, eagerly anticipating a walk, stood still as its owner accidentally dropped the leash. With a look of anticipation and confusion, the canine waited for the owner to pick it up and continue the outing, but to no avail. The silence spoke volumes as the dog's expressive eyes and hopeful demeanor conveyed its desires without a single bark. Eventually, the dog took matters into its paws and returned to the owner, as if to say, "Let's try this again, but get it right this time!" The video exemplified the unspoken bond between pets and their owners, evoking laughter and heartwarming feelings all at once.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>dog,leash,video,Texas,USA,cute,funny,owner,walk,expectation,confusion,expressive,eyes,paws,bond,outing,pet,laughter,heartwarming,silent,mishap</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Texas</media:city>
             <media:country>United States</media:country>
             <media:category>Animals</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2547</guid>
             <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023 17:52:44 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2547.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2547.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Adorable new arrival: baby parrot dreams peacefully in loving hands</media:title>
             <media:description>On June 8th, 2023, in Izmir, Turkey, a heartwarming video captured by @hknyilmaz35 showcased a newly hatched parrot in the gentle hands of its caretaker, Hakan. The tiny parrot, peacefully asleep, melted hearts with its undeniable cuteness. The short clip resonated with viewers worldwide, celebrating the beauty of new life and the bond between humans and animals.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>adorable,parrot,hatchling,video,Izmir,Turkey,hands,caretaker,asleep,cute,newlife,bond,humans,animals,heartwarming,tiny,love,peaceful,@hknyilmaz35,June8th2023</media:keywords>
             <media:city> Izmir</media:city>
             <media:country>Turkey</media:country>
             <media:category>Animals</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Thu, 8 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2546</guid>
             <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023 18:03:14 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2546.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2546.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Mesmerizing moves: unique hand wiggles and curved back dance steals the show at Thai Binh wedding!</media:title>
             <media:description>In a captivating display of dance artistry, a recent wedding in Hai Thuy, Thai Binh, Vietnam witnessed an extraordinary performance that left guests in awe. The spotlight was stolen by a man whose innovative dance moves left everyone mesmerized. Captured on video by @hoanglequyen1712 and dated June 18, 2023, this incredible display showcased the man gracefully wiggling his hands while curving his back backwards, creating a dance like no other. His unique and skillful movements were a sight to behold, and the energy and passion he poured into his performance radiated throughout the venue.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>captivating,dance,artistry,innovative,mesmerizing,hands,curved,back,performance,wedding,video,unique,skillful,energy,passion,guests,cheers,unforgettable,moment,Vietnam</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Hai Thuy, Thai Binh</media:city>
             <media:country>Vietnam</media:country>
             <media:category>Cool</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2545</guid>
             <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023 11:14:25 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2545.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2545.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Wildfires force temporary shutdown of Palermo Airport in Sicily, Italy</media:title>
             <media:description>On July 25th, 2023, a wildfire broke out near the town of Cinisi, Italy, on the island of Sicily, endangering the Falcone Borsellino Airport, also known as Palermo airport. The escalating blaze reached the airport's perimeter, leading authorities to suspend all air traffic until 11 a.m. The intensity of the fire was captured in a video by @f3dericoooo, showing soaring flames along the Palermo-Cinisi highway. The situation prompted concerns for public safety and disrupted airport operations temporarily.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>wildfires,italy,sicily,cinisi,palermo,airport,falcone,borsellino,shutdown,flames,video,@f3dericoooo,highway,air traffic,danger,public safety,authorities,blaze,perimeter,disruption</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Cinisi, Sicily </media:city>
             <media:country>Italy</media:country>
             <media:category>News</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2539</guid>
             <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 14:18:09 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2539.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2539.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Intense storms ravage Northern Italy: Monza and Milan on high alert as heavy rain and strong winds unleash havoc</media:title>
             <media:description>On July 24th, 2023, Monza, Italy, experienced the wrath of an intense rainstorm accompanied by powerful winds, as captured in a video by @ylesweet666. The heavy downpour and strong gusts wreaked havoc on parts of northern Italy, leading to an orange alert in Monza and Milan on July 25th. The region faced challenging weather conditions, with the video depicting the impact on Monza.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>rainstorm,winds,northern Italy,Monza,Milan,intense,orange alert,weather,video,July 24th,2023,@ylesweet666,car,trees,havoc,disruptions,caution,storms,weather event,powerful,heavy rain</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Monza</media:city>
             <media:country>Italy</media:country>
             <media:category>Weather</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2538</guid>
             <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 14:18:52 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2538.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2538.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Genuine connection: Margot Robbie's heartwarming sign language interaction in London</media:title>
             <media:description>In a heartwarming moment captured by @Tom123jr in London, UK, on July 25, 2022, Australian actress and producer Margot Robbie, known for her impressive filmography and numerous accolades, showcased her compassionate side during the filming of "Amsterdam." The video featured Margot engaging in sign language with @Tom123jr, demonstrating her commitment to genuine connections with her fans and admirers. The simple yet meaningful interaction left an indelible mark on those who witnessed the encounter, showcasing Margot Robbie's endearing and inclusive nature beyond her successful career in the entertainment industry.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>actress,producer,blockbuster,independent,awards,nominations,film,London,UK,Amsterdam,video,signlanguage,connection,compassion,fans,admirers,interaction,heartwarming,genuine,inclusive</media:keywords>
             <media:city>London</media:city>
             <media:country>United Kingdom</media:country>
             <media:category>Cool</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Mon, 25 Jul 2022</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2537</guid>
             <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 14:19:30 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2537.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2537.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Unconventional cat and mouse chase: when the prey strikes back in Lviv, Ukraine!</media:title>
             <media:description>In a comical scene captured by @bohdansereda on June 11, 2023, in Lviv, Ukraine, a cat found itself in an amusing predicament with a crafty mouse. The video showcased the mouse perched confidently on the cat's back, seemingly taunting the feline as it attempted to catch its elusive companion. Despite the mouse's daring trickery, the determined cat valiantly pursued the rodent, refusing to give up the chase. After a series of entertaining antics, the mouse's luck eventually ran out, and it tumbled from the cat's back, leading to a swift and triumphant pounce by the feline. </media:description>
             <media:keywords>cat,mouse,lviv,ukraine,video,chase,trick,clever,funny,pursuit,adventure,pounce,whiskers,comical,scene,internet,sensation,playful,showdown,triumph,amusing</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Lviv</media:city>
             <media:country>Ukraine</media:country>
             <media:category>Animals</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2534</guid>
             <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 15:07:59 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2534.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2534.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>James Corden joins epic conga line at Harry Styles' final love on tour stop in Italy!</media:title>
             <media:description>James Corden, the former host of The Late Late Show, surprised fans by joining in on the fun at Harry Styles' final Love On Tour stop in Italy. Captured in a video by @alessiaslover on July 22, 2023, Corden was seen dancing and enthusiastically participating in a conga line with other concertgoers at the RCF Arena Reggio Emilia. The British comic was spotted enjoying himself both in the VIP area and amidst the general crowd, singing along to Styles' hit songs. Fans couldn't help but be amused by the unexpected and random moment of Corden's lively participation at the concert.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>dancing,conga,line,James Corden,partying,support,friend,Love On Tour,Italy,Harry Styles,final,concert,VIP,crowd,RCF Arena,Reggio Emilia,singing,hits,random,amusing</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Reggio Emilia</media:city>
             <media:country>Italy</media:country>
             <media:category>Cool</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2530</guid>
             <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 09:30:30 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2530.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2530.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Feathered frenzy: Loki the staffy takes on the seagull invasion in Hull, UK!</media:title>
             <media:description>On June 3, 2023, in Hull, UK, @zaynetowe witnessed an amusing sight in her garden as her dog, Loki the Staffy, took charge against a swarm of seagulls. The video captured the moment when numerous seagulls invaded the garden, prompting Loki to dash into action. With unyielding determination, Loki fearlessly chased the seagulls away, leaving the garden free from the feathery invaders. It was a comical display of canine bravery, as the loyal pup swiftly returned to the safety of the house after successfully warding off the feathered intruders.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>garden,dog,Loki,staffy,seagulls,chase,video,Hull,UK,funny,brave,invasion,action,loyal,pup,feathered,intruders,June,@zaynetowe,house</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Hull, England </media:city>
             <media:country>United Kingdom</media:country>
             <media:category>Animals</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Sat, 3 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2529</guid>
             <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 20:56:41 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2529.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2529.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Startling encounter: snake dangles and vanishes in Ho Chi Minh city home</media:title>
             <media:description>In a harrowing incident captured on a home camera in Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam, a resident, @congdonghoainhon, had an unsettling surprise. On May 12, 2023, the camera alerted him to movement in his bedroom, and upon checking the footage, he was startled to see a snake dangling near the camera. Moments later, the snake fell out of sight, leaving him alarmed. Rushing back home, he searched his room diligently but found no trace of the elusive serpent. Speculating that it might have taken refuge inside the air conditioner, the resident remains on edge, unable to locate the reptile.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>snake,camera,bedroom,video,home,work,warn,movement,shocked,rummage,find,air conditioner,Vietnam,Ho Chi Minh City,resident,encounter,alert,elusive,reptile,tags</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Ho Chi Minh City</media:city>
             <media:country>Vietnam</media:country>
             <media:category>Animals</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Fri, 12 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2528</guid>
             <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 20:58:54 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2528.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2528.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Slippery shenanigans: Fatty the dog's hilarious underground parking adventure!</media:title>
             <media:description>In Jiangxi province, China, on June 9th, 2023, a playful dog named Fatty found himself in a comical situation at the underground parking lot. His owner, Fatty, captured the moment on video as the excited canine ran towards her, only to slip on the wet floor. With a quick recovery, Fatty tried to hide his embarrassment by looking forward, creating a humorous and endearing scene. Thankfully, no harm was done, and Fatty's misadventures added a touch of laughter to an otherwise ordinary day at the parking lot.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>june 9th,2023,jiangxi province,china,fatty,dog,video,running,sliding,wet floor,underground parking,car,water,slip,embarrassment,owner,playfulness,comical,recovery,laughter,misadventure</media:keywords>
             <media:city> Jiangxi province</media:city>
             <media:country>China</media:country>
             <media:category>Animals</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Fri, 9 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2527</guid>
             <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 21:01:29 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2527.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2527.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Ageless bonds: heartwarming dinner with grandma and her furry companion</media:title>
             <media:description>In a touching video captured by @wolfchava on June 1, 2023, in Sums, Ukraine, viewers witnessed a heartwarming scene at a family dinner. The video showcased an 86-year-old grandmother sharing a meal with her wolf companion named Chavez. As the elderly woman sat at the table, the dog playfully approached, seemingly asking for some of the delicious food. This endearing moment beautifully highlighted the special bond between generations and the love shared within this standard family setting.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>grandmother,dinner,family,bond,love,ageless,heartwarming,video,Ukraine,Sums,@wolfchava,June,2023,table,meal,companion,touching,generations,standard,wolf</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Sumy</media:city>
             <media:country>Ukraine</media:country>
             <media:category>Heartwarming</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Thu, 1 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2526</guid>
             <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 15:09:50 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2526.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2526.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Crane catastrophe: dramatic bridge damage caught on video in Brooklyn</media:title>
             <media:description>On July 19th, 2023, in Brooklyn, New York, USA, a shocking incident occurred during which a crane collided with the lower side of a bridge. A witness, identified as @thisismathieu, captured the dramatic moment on video. As he was out for his morning run, he noticed the tall crane approaching the bridge but did not expect the disastrous outcome. The crane struck the bridge with a loud bang, causing significant damage as it dragged along the bottom. In the brief recording, the extent of the destruction became apparent.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>brooklyn,new york,usa,crane,bridge,damage,video,incident,witness,collision,morning,run,loud,bang,destruction,authorities,accident,investigate,damages,caught</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Brooklyn, New York</media:city>
             <media:country>United States</media:country>
             <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2525</guid>
             <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 21:04:22 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2525.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2525.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Charming canine shenanigans: dog delights in self-play on the couch!</media:title>
             <media:description>In a heartwarming video captured by @mia.the.staffy on June 16, 2023, in Örebro, Sweden, a delightful canine showcased its unique form of entertainment. The dog Mia, which is a staffy breed, was seen playfully folding itself on the couch, engrossed in the amusing activity of nibbling at its own leg. The endearing display of self-play charmed viewers, highlighting the joyful and quirky nature of our beloved four-legged companions.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>playful,canine,video,couch,leg,nibbling,adorable,@mia.the.staffy,Sweden,Örebro,charming,self-play,entertaining,dog,folding,heartwarming,quirky,delightful,nature,beloved</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Örebro</media:city>
             <media:country>Sweden</media:country>
             <media:category>Animals</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2524</guid>
             <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 09:32:57 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2524.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2524.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Love in a tray: a mother parrot's care for her little ones in Izmir, Turkey</media:title>
             <media:description>In a heartwarming scene captured on July 11th, 2023, in Izmir, Turkey, @hknyilmaz35 shared a touching video featuring a devoted mother parrot and her adorable young ones. The video showcases the loving care provided by Hakan, a parrot breeder, to a yellow parrot and her recently hatched chicks. As the camera rolls, the affectionate mother can be seen nurturing her little ones in a tray, chirping tender words of love and protection. Hakan's expertise in parrot breeding shines through as he highlights the fascinating distinction between the girls and one boy among the brood. This heartening display of maternal love and expert care reminds us of the remarkable bonds that exist in the animal kingdom, leaving viewers touched and captivated by the beautiful scene.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>parrot,young ones,tray,Izmir,Turkey,video,love,mother,chirping,breeding,Hakan,yellow,care,girls,boy,affectionate,maternal,expert,bonds,animal</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Izmir</media:city>
             <media:country>Turkey</media:country>
             <media:category>Heartwarming</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2523</guid>
             <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 21:06:46 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2523.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2523.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Makeup prank turns tears to smiles: a tale of fake eyebrows and sweet relief</media:title>
             <media:description>In a surprising turn of events during a makeup session on July 10, 2023 in Toronto, Canada, @artisanglow pulled off an eyebrow prank on her unsuspecting client who had come for makeup on her anniversary. Capturing the whole ordeal on video, the client's smile quickly faded into tears as she was appalled by the fake eyebrows. Unaware that it was all just a prank, the client's distress was evident. However, @artisanglow swiftly revealed the truth and corrected the brows, leading to a sigh of relief and a beaming smile from the client.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>anniversary,makeup,prank,client,eyebrows,video,Toronto,Canada,smile,tears,relief,artisanglow,fake,surprise,session,distress,correction,beaming,small,tags</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Toronto </media:city>
             <media:country>Canada</media:country>
             <media:category>Fails and Funnies</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2522</guid>
             <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 20:52:21 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2522.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2522.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Manila mayhem: emotional ball game takes a comical turn as man bowls and falls!</media:title>
             <media:description>In an amusing incident captured on video in Manila, Philippines, on July 9, 2023, an emotional ball game took an unexpected turn when a man, identified as @itzyoboymigi, fell while bowling. The video shows the man clutching the bowling ball, seemingly ready to throw it, when he lost his balance and tumbled onto his stomach. The hilarious moment quickly spread on social media, garnering plenty of laughs and reactions from netizens worldwide. </media:description>
             <media:keywords>bawling,manila,philippines,video,falling,comical,emotional,ball game,@itzyoboymigi,laughter,social media,hilarious,unexpected,balance,stomach,netizens,worldwide,ordinary,activities,lighthearted</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Manila </media:city>
             <media:country>Philippines</media:country>
             <media:category>Fails and Funnies</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Sun, 9 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2520</guid>
             <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 15:10:30 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2520.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2520.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Joy amidst the rain: a child's playful adventure at Quiapo church</media:title>
             <media:description>On July 4, 2023, at Quiapo Church in Manila, Philippines, a heartwarming scene unfolded amidst the rain. Captured by @karlalleeen, a video showcased a child joyfully playing with water in the downpour. While others sought shelter under their umbrellas, this carefree youngster found delight in sliding under rails using the rainwater. His infectious happiness served as a reminder of the simple joys in life, even in the midst of adverse weather conditions.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>playful,rain,child,video,water,joy,Quiapo Church,Manila,Philippines,sliding,rails,fun,umbrellas,happiness,carefree,downpour,weather,@karlalleeen,July 4,2023,adventure,delightful</media:keywords>
             <media:city> Manila</media:city>
             <media:country>Philippines</media:country>
             <media:category>Fails and Funnies</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Tue, 4 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2519</guid>
             <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 07:18:14 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2519.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2519.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Thunderous chaos: Lahore, Pakistan, hit by violent storm and electric explosions</media:title>
             <media:description>In a dramatic and electrifying scene captured by @salu_bava on April 5, 2023, Lahore, Pakistan experienced the wrath of a powerful thunderstorm that wreaked havoc on the city's electric infrastructure. The recorded video depicted an intense storm with booming thunder and dazzling lightning strikes illuminating the darkened skies. As the storm intensified, strong winds lashed at electric lines, causing them to malfunction and explode, creating an astonishing display of chaos and danger. </media:description>
             <media:keywords>thunderstorm,lightning,electric,malfunction,explode,Lahore,Pakistan,video,storm,winds,chaos,danger,darkness,sparks,nature,force,weather,phenomena,residents,caution</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Lahore</media:city>
             <media:country>Pakistan</media:country>
             <media:category>News</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Wed, 5 Apr 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2518</guid>
             <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 20:47:32 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2518.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2518.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Whimsical toy vendor takes flight: a hilarious surprise in Santa Rosa, Laguna!</media:title>
             <media:description>In a heartwarming and unexpected moment, a toy vendor in Santa Rosa, Laguna, Philippines, captured the attention and laughter of onlookers as he showcased his playful spirit. The vendor was seen passing by, holding a small plane toy aloft with a stick, pretending to soar through the skies as if he were flying the toy himself. The crowd couldn't help but be amused by his delightful antics, and the video shared by @masterbaehub on June 11, 2023, quickly went viral, spreading joy and smiles across social media. Sometimes, the simplest gestures can bring the greatest joy, and this charming toy vendor's playful spirit certainly brightened the day for many.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>joyful,playful,vendor,toy,plane,stick,flying,video,laughter,surprise,heartwarming,Santa Rosa,Laguna,Philippines,crowd,amused,social media,viral,simple,joyful,charming</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Santa Rosa, Laguna</media:city>
             <media:country>Philippines</media:country>
             <media:category>Fails and Funnies</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2512</guid>
             <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 08:51:39 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2512.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2512.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Joyful puddle escapade: a father's hilarious chase in Minsk</media:title>
             <media:description>In a heartwarming and lighthearted moment captured on June 21, 2023, on Nemiga Street in Minsk, Belarus, @tema_rai1986 shared a delightful video of a young boy's playful adventure. While out for a stroll, the boy's eyes lit up at the sight of a puddle, and he couldn't resist the temptation to run around in it. Amused and determined, his father tried to catch up, but the boy's splashing antics made it a challenging pursuit, as the father aimed to avoid getting soaked. Eventually, with a smile on his face, the father managed to scoop up his playful child, just as the boy reached the puddle's edge. </media:description>
             <media:keywords>boy,puddle,running,Minsk,Nemiga Street,Belarus,video,walking,splashing,water,father,catch,wet,joy,playful,adventure,chase,moment,smile,heartwarming.</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Minsk</media:city>
             <media:country>Belarus</media:country>
             <media:category>Fails and Funnies</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2511</guid>
             <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 06:56:54 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2511.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2511.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Thrills and tumbles: nighttime sign climbing adventure turns into chaos in Russia</media:title>
             <media:description>In a daring escapade caught on camera in Russia, a group of friends attempted to climb a signpost at night with the aid of another companion. However, the adventure took a disastrous turn when the sign suddenly collapsed, sending the friend tumbling to the ground. The shocking video, captured by @nihuya_sebe_struya_ on July 15th, 2023, showcases the exhilarating yet perilous consequences of their reckless undertaking.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>nighttime,russia,adventure,friends,climbing,sign,video,risky,assistance,collapse,chaos,thrill,excitement,caution,safety,stunt,authorities,capture,fall,daring</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Kaluga</media:city>
             <media:country>Russia</media:country>
             <media:category>Fails and Funnies</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2510</guid>
             <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 08:46:31 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2510.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2510.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item></channel>
           </rss>