<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
        xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
        xmlns:openSearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearchrss/1.0/"
        xmlns:dfpvideo="http://api.google.com/dfpvideo"
        xmlns:tms="http://data.tmsapi.com/v1.1"
        version="2.0">
         <channel>
           <title>ViralBear videos</title>
           <dfpvideo:version>2</dfpvideo:version><item>
             <media:title>Nature's fury unleashed: lightning strikes and flames explode in Shijiazhuang</media:title>
             <media:description>On July 24, 2023, in Shijiazhuang, northern China, a startling and unintentional event was captured on video by @HomelessYuanyuan. As she stood in front of her apartment window with her mobile phone, attempting to capture a street scene during a rainstorm and thunder, lightning struck the transformer below her building. The intense impact caused sparks of flames to erupt, scattering fiery fragments in all directions. Nature's fury was unleashed, and in a split second, the author found herself witnessing a breathtaking display of raw power and danger.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>lightning,sparks,flames,explosion,rainstorm,thunder,Shijiazhuang,China,video,mobile,window,street,nature,fury,power,danger,unpredictability,awe,humbled,@HomelessYuanyuan</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Shijiazhuang</media:city>
             <media:country>China</media:country>
             <media:regionCode>CN</media:regionCode>
            <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>      
             <media:category>News</media:category>
             <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
             <media:filmingDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2604</guid>
             <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 13:16:50 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2604.jpg" />
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2604.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Thrilling mishap: Audi drift attempt ends in guardrail collision at Suzhou GTshow </media:title>
             <media:description>During the annual Suzhou GTshow on July 22, 2023, a highly anticipated automotive cultural event in China, a heart-pounding incident occurred as an Audi car attempted a daring drift maneuver. The vehicle lost control and collided with a guardrail, sending shockwaves through the crowd of car enthusiasts. Thankfully, no one was injured in the dramatic collision. The video captured by @ShanghaiUPAutomotiveTechnicalService shows the intensity of the moment, serving as a reminder of the risks involved in high-speed automotive displays. Despite the unexpected mishap, the event continued, showcasing a spectacular display of Custom cars and Supercars to the delight of the attendees.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>drift,audi,collision,guardrail,suzhou,china,g t show,automotive,event,enthusiasts,custom,supercar,annual,mishap,excitement,car,culture,display,injured,risk</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Suzhou</media:city>
             <media:country>China</media:country>
             <media:regionCode>CN</media:regionCode>
             <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
             <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
             <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
             <media:filmingDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2603</guid>
             <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 13:19:39 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2603.jpg" />
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2603.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Bear brawl at Guaipo Tiger Park: two black bears engage in fierce fight over food</media:title>
             <media:description>In a thrilling and unexpected encounter at the Guaipo Tiger Park in Shenyang, Northeast China, two black bears engaged in a heated fight, captured on video by local resident @100millionfatballs on June 24, 2023. As she explored the living area of the black bears, the normally docile animals suddenly clashed, with their aggression escalating over a possible dispute for food. The shocking scene prompted the author to react quickly, loudly shouting in an attempt to intervene and put an end to the confrontation. Her bravery in the face of this intense encounter showcased the unpredictable nature of wildlife and served as a powerful reminder of the importance of respecting and preserving the delicate balance between humans and the animal kingdom.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>shenyang,china,black bears,fight,video,wildlife,park,encounter,food,aggression,shock,visitor,Guaipo Tiger Park,northeast,@100millionfatballs,nature,animals,conservation,bravery,balance</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Shenyang</media:city>
             <media:country>China</media:country>
             <media:regionCode>CN</media:regionCode>
             <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
             <media:category>Animals</media:category>
             <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
             <media:filmingDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2602</guid>
             <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 13:12:52 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2602.jpg" />
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2602.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Terrifying Yokohama guerrilla rainstorm unleashes chaos with its fierce winds and torrential downpour</media:title>
             <media:description>In Yokohama, Japan, on August 1, 2023, @Tomo_YNU captured a chilling video of a rainstorm known as Guerrilla. This local phenomenon is characterized by an unpredictable formation of cumulonimbus clouds, resulting in a short but intense downpour of over 100 mm per hour of rain. The video showcases the fury of the Guerrilla rainstorm, with powerful winds swaying trees in its path. The dangerous nature of this event highlights the need for caution and preparedness during such occurrences in Yokohama.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>rainstorm,guerrilla,yokohama,japan,video,downpour,cumulonimbus,clouds,intense,winds,trees,dangerous,unpredictable,weather,phenomenon,local,short,mm,hour,rain</media:keywords>
             <media:city> Yokohama</media:city>
             <media:country>Japan</media:country>
             <media:regionCode>JP</media:regionCode>
            <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>      
             <media:category>Weather</media:category>
             <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
             <media:filmingDate>Tue, 1 Aug 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2601</guid>
             <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 13:12:08 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2601.jpg" />
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2601.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Tokyo's sideways rain: nature's dance of wind and water</media:title>
             <media:description>In a mesmerizing spectacle captured on August 1, 2023, from the heart of Tokyo, Japan, @4H6M8u0YmemZwmj shared a breathtaking video of sideways rain cascading down window panes. As nature's elements collided, the wind's mighty force compelled the raindrops to dance sideways, creating a captivating display of nature's power and beauty. The video serves as a vivid reminder of the unpredictable yet awe-inspiring wonders of the natural world, leaving viewers in awe of the harmonious choreography between wind and water. </media:description>
             <media:keywords>wind,rain,sideways,video,Tokyo,Japan,nature,spectacle,mesmerizing,window,panes,dance,elements,force,beauty,power,display,awe,urban,landscape</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Tokyo </media:city>
             <media:country>Japan</media:country>
             <media:regionCode>JP</media:regionCode>
            <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>      
             <media:category>Weather</media:category>
             <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
             <media:filmingDate>Tue, 1 Aug 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2600</guid>
             <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 13:12:22 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2600.jpg" />
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2600.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Playful and obedient: Khryapa's impressive 'swim' command!</media:title>
             <media:description>In a heartwarming video captured by @mokryi_nosik_ on June 17, 2020, in Voronezh, Russia, her beloved dog, Khryapa, stole the spotlight with her incredible obedience and playful nature. The footage shows @mokryi_nosik_ talking to Khryapa in one of the rooms, when suddenly, the clever canine dashes off towards the bathroom. Without hesitation, Khryapa leaps into the bathtub, showcasing her impressive execution of the "swim" command. The three-year-old furry friend proves to be not only obedient but also full of joy and enthusiasm. Her charming antics have won the hearts of viewers worldwide, leaving a lasting impression of her delightful personality and the strong bond between her and her owner.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>playful,obedient,dog,swim,command,video,Khryapa,Voronezh,Russia,bathtub,bathroom,three years old,pet,canine,joy,love,bond,clever,cute,charming</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Voronezh</media:city>
             <media:country>Russia</media:country>
             <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
            <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>      
             <media:category>Animals</media:category>
             <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
             <media:filmingDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2598</guid>
             <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 10:57:32 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2598.jpg" />
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2598.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Playful corgi's adorable 'poof' act delights internet in St. Petersburg, Russia!</media:title>
             <media:description>In an endearing and amusing video that captured hearts on social media, a Corgi named Leo from St. Petersburg, Russia, showcased his unique talent for playing "dead." The video, shared by @prokopenkokate on April 29, 2023, depicts Leo sitting peacefully on the floor before his owner mimics a shooting gesture with her hands. Surprisingly, the adorable pup immediately flops down, pretending to be "shot" as part of a playful command he has mastered. As a reward for his impressive performance, Leo eagerly awaits a treat, proving that his favorite command is the delightful and harmless "poof," leaving viewers charmed by this clever and lovable canine's antics.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>playful,corgi,leo,video,internet,acting,dog,Russia,St. Petersburg,pet,owner,gun,pretend,cute,charm,humor,social media,adorable,command,sweet</media:keywords>
             <media:city>St. Petersburg</media:city>
             <media:country>Russia</media:country>
             <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
            <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>      
             <media:category>Animals</media:category>
             <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
             <media:filmingDate>Sat, 29 Apr 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2595</guid>
             <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 10:53:38 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2595.jpg" />
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2595.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>First-time rider's mishap: girl's scooter adventure ends with a bump!</media:title>
             <media:description>In a candid video captured by @wkmzxuk_ on July 15, 2023, in the City of Soligorsk, Minsk region, Belarus, a young girl's first-time experience with an electronic scooter took an unexpected turn. With enthusiasm and excitement, she hopped onto the scooter but found herself struggling to control its speed. Unaware of the gears and unfamiliar with braking, she careened toward a stationary sign near a building, unable to halt her momentum. The result was a comical yet cautionary collision, reminding viewers of the importance of learning the basics before embarking on new adventures. While the girl's misadventure might have left her a little shaken, it undoubtedly served as a valuable lesson for both her and others who dare to ride the scooters for the first time.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>scooter,mishap,video,girl,first-time,adventure,excitement,gears,braking,collision,cautionary,comical,lessons,learning,electronic,speed,sign,building,Belarus,Soligorsk</media:keywords>
             <media:city> City of Soligorsk, Minsk region</media:city>
             <media:country>Belarus</media:country>
             <media:regionCode>BY</media:regionCode>
            <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>      
             <media:category>Fails and Funnies</media:category>
             <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
             <media:filmingDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2594</guid>
             <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 10:53:05 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2594.jpg" />
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2594.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Tranquil moments: Tokyo's beloved dog relishes in shallow creek at favorite park</media:title>
             <media:description>In a heartwarming scene captured on June 24, 2023, in Tokyo, Japan, @mr.donbei_inu shared a delightful video of his beloved dog finding sheer bliss in a small, slow creek at their favorite park. The four-legged companion appeared completely at ease, comfortably resting its head on the surface of the shallow water, joyfully savoring the gentle flow around it. Unlike most dogs, this furry friend chose not to swim but found pure contentment in merely basking in the refreshing water. With a serene expression, the canine seemed to have discovered a little piece of paradise amidst the bustling city, making this tranquil spot its most cherished destination in the park.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>dog,creek,park,Tokyo,Japan,chilling,water,shallow,serene,bliss,favorite,video,pet,companion,contentment,relaxation,joy,tranquility,peaceful,happiness</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Tokyo</media:city>
             <media:country>Japan</media:country>
             <media:regionCode>JP</media:regionCode>
            <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>      
             <media:category>Animals</media:category>
             <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
             <media:filmingDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2593</guid>
             <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 10:52:42 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2593.jpg" />
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2593.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Love blossoms at a birthday party: tender smiles of a toddler</media:title>
             <media:description>In a heartwarming moment captured by @ayreeeshh_ on March 12, 2023, at a birthday party in Las Piñas, Manila, Philippines, a two-year-old boy named Drei melted hearts as he looked tenderly at a little girl named Aliah. The usually quiet and well-behaved toddler seemed to be smitten with Aliah, flashing sweet smiles and even raising his eyebrows at her, giving the impression of a young love in the making. Drei's mother shared the adorable video, describing how her son became seemingly interested in Aliah, and it quickly became a viral sensation, spreading joy and warmth across the internet. This endearing encounter serves as a reminder of the innocent and pure connections that can blossom even among the youngest of hearts.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>love,toddler,birthday,party,smiles,tender,falling,in,young,children,innocence,adorable,viral,internet,connections,heartwarming,Manila,Philippines,Aliah,Drei,@ayreeeshh_</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Las Piñas, Manila</media:city>
             <media:country>Philippines</media:country>
             <media:regionCode>PH</media:regionCode>
            <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>      
             <media:category>Heartwarming</media:category>
             <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
             <media:filmingDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2592</guid>
             <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 10:51:48 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2592.jpg" />
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2592.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Stranded in the muddy ravine: military jeep's dramatic rescue in Bakhmut, Ukraine</media:title>
             <media:description>In the rural outskirts of Bakhmut, Ukraine, an extraordinary scene unfolded on May 15, 2023, when a military jeep found itself trapped in the treacherous aftermath of a heavy rainstorm. Captured by @koshkarov_yarik, the vehicle was in the midst of pulling another stuck automobile when it succumbed to the thick mud, leaving its occupants in a precarious situation. As the hours passed and the sun began to set, tension mounted as the stranded group awaited assistance. To their surprise, it was an unexpected twist of fate that came to their aid. While waiting, a bizarre event occurred when their brother arrived to "shoot at the neighbor," causing an uproar of noisy birds. Remarkably, amid the chaos, a timely rescue operation led by fellow military personnel swooped in just in time, ensuring the safe extraction of both vehicles and their relieved occupants. The daring rescue, coupled with the unusual circumstances, left an unforgettable mark on the small community, showcasing the unwavering camaraderie and ingenuity of those serving in Ukraine's military.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>ravine,rain,stuck,jeep,evening,brother,shoot,neighbor,birds,lancet,rescue,mud,Bakhmut,Ukraine,military,daring,trapped,assistance,occupants,community</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Bakhmut</media:city>
             <media:country>Ukraine</media:country>
             <media:regionCode>UA</media:regionCode>
             <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
             <media:category>News</media:category>
             <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
             <media:filmingDate>Mon, 15 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2591</guid>
             <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 13:06:37 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2591.jpg" />
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2591.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Ukrainian drones strike Moscow: facades damaged, no casualties reported </media:title>
             <media:description>On the night of July 30, 2023, Moscow, Russia experienced another attack on its facilities by Ukrainian drones, as the ongoing conflict between the two nations continued. The Mayor of Moscow, Sergei Sobyanin, confirmed the incident, stating that the facades of two City office towers sustained slight damage, fortunately without any reported casualties or injuries. The Ministry of Defense revealed that one UAV was successfully destroyed in the air above the Odintsovo district, while two others were thwarted by electronic warfare, causing them to lose control and crash on the territory of Moscow City. Video footage captured the aftermath, depicting shattered glass scattered on the ground in front of the affected buildings. This incident marks yet another escalation in the year-long conflict between Ukraine and Russia, escalating tensions and raising concerns about the safety and stability of the region.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>attack,ukrainian,drones,moscow,russia,conflict,mayor,facades,damage,casualties,injured,ministry,defense,UAV,destroyed,Odintsovo,electronic warfare,crashed,territory,video footage</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Moscow</media:city>
             <media:country>Russia</media:country>
             <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
             <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
             <media:category>News</media:category>
             <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
             <media:filmingDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2590</guid>
             <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 13:05:13 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2590.jpg" />
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2590.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title> Ukrainian drones attack Moscow, captured on video by tourist amid ongoing conflict with Russia</media:title>
             <media:description>On the night of July 30, 2023, Moscow experienced an unsettling incident as two Ukrainian drones launched an attack on the capital. Fortunately, there were no reported casualties or injuries, but the facades of two City office towers were slightly damaged. Mayor Sergey Sobyanin confirmed the attack and stated that the military successfully destroyed one UAV with air defense systems in the Odintsovo district of the Moscow region. Additionally, two more drones were brought down by electronic warfare, losing control and crashing onto the grounds of the Moscow City non-residential building complex. Among the witnesses was a young girl visiting the city with her grandmother, who unintentionally captured the dramatic moment of a drone's fall and subsequent explosion on video. The attack adds to the ongoing tension between Ukraine and Russia, which has been engulfed in a military conflict for over a year.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>moscow,attack,drones,ukrainian,explosions,mayor,damaged,casualties,military,air defense,electronic warfare,crash,witness,girl,grandmother,video,tension,conflict,authorities,implications</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Moscow</media:city>
             <media:country>Ukraine</media:country>
             <media:regionCode>UA</media:regionCode>
             <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
             <media:category>News</media:category>
             <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
             <media:filmingDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2589</guid>
             <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 13:05:52 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2589.jpg" />
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2589.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Foiled Ukrainian drone attack on Moscow City tower amid ongoing Russia-Ukraine conflict</media:title>
             <media:description>On July 30, 2023, Moscow, Russia, experienced the consequences of a foiled drone attack on the Moscow City tower, caught on video. The explosion caused significant damage, shattering windows on the 11th floor and leaving fragments of the drone and glass near the building's entrance. Thankfully, there were no casualties reported, and emergency services quickly responded to the scene. The Russian Ministry of Defense confirmed the attack, attributing it to Ukrainian unmanned aerial vehicles engaged in attempted terrorism. According to the Ministry, two UAVs managed to suppress electronic warfare before losing control and crashing onto the territory of Moscow City. This incident adds to the escalating tensions between Ukraine and Russia, as both countries have been in conflict for some time now.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>explosion,drone,attack,Moscow,Russia,windows,fragments,entrance,casualties,emergency,services,foiled,Ukrainian,electronic,warfare,conflict,tension,video,11th floor,Ministry,July 30</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Moscow</media:city>
             <media:country>Russia</media:country>
             <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
             <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
             <media:category>News</media:category>
             <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
             <media:filmingDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2588</guid>
             <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 13:06:05 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2588.jpg" />
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2588.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Tenacious twig tug-of-war: a dog's unyielding affair with nature's bounty</media:title>
             <media:description>In a delightful and amusing scene captured by @chelseareject on May 21, 2023, in Jersey City, New Jersey, USA, her four-legged companion exhibited an unshakeable determination during a playful encounter with nature. The video showcased the adorable pup clenching onto a sizable twig of a tree, despite the owner's best efforts to convince it otherwise. With @chelseareject's voice gently coaxing the dog to release its prized find, the resilient canine remained unyielding, steadfastly refusing to let go. Undeterred, they strolled along together, the furry protagonist proudly showcasing its prized possession in an endearing tug-of-war with the forces of nature. The heartwarming display of canine spirit and persistence resonated with viewers worldwide, capturing the essence of a special bond between humans and their loyal companions.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>tree,dog,twig,nature,Jersey City,USA,May,2023,video,pet,playful,determined,adorable,owner,walk,bonding,persistence,loyalty,companionship,endearing,capture</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Jersey City, New Jersey</media:city>
             <media:country>United States</media:country>
             <media:regionCode>US</media:regionCode>
            <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>      
             <media:category>Animals</media:category>
             <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
             <media:filmingDate>Sun, 21 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2586</guid>
             <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 09:23:40 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2586.jpg" />
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2586.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Cat burglar in Buenos Aires: feline filches cash and cuddles up!</media:title>
             <media:description>In an amusing incident in Buenos Aires, Argentina, on July 6, 2023, a mischievous cat turned into a daring thief. A video captured by @gaston__joaquin showed the feline delving into a handbag and snatching a bundle of money before darting off towards the bedroom. The curious owner followed the sneaky cat's trail to find it lounging on the bed with the stolen cash. This lighthearted escapade left everyone amused and highlighted the unpredictable antics of our four-legged companions.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>cat,thief,money,video,Buenos Aires,Argentina,handbag,bed,owner,amusing,feline,daring,curious,sneaky,trail,lounging,stolen,cash,lighthearted,antics</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Buenos Aires</media:city>
             <media:country>Argentina</media:country>
             <media:regionCode>AR</media:regionCode>
             <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
             <media:category>Animals</media:category>
             <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
             <media:filmingDate>Thu, 6 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2585</guid>
             <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 09:24:40 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2585.jpg" />
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2585.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Fast-pass to thrills: a wild ride at Disneyland!</media:title>
             <media:description>In a heartwarming yet adrenaline-pumping moment at Disneyland, California, USA, a father's attempt to reassure his daughter during a roller coaster ride took an unexpected turn. Captured by @enrique7kcg on July 9, 2023, the video shows the duo enjoying the thrilling experience, but with a hilarious twist. As they embarked on the coaster adventure, the father promised his daughter that they would take it slow, only to find the roller coaster had other plans. Despite his reassurances, the ride took off at high speed, resulting in his daughter's excited yet terrified screams. Sharing the video on social media, @enrique7kcg humorously captioned it as "I got a fast-pass to hell for this one." The heartwarming father-daughter moment, coupled with the roller coaster's unexpected speed, made it a cherished memory for both, an unforgettable day of family fun at the magical land of Disneyland.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>roller coaster,disneyland,california,usa,father,daughter,ride,fast-pass,thrill,adventure,hilarious,social media,caption,screams,family,fun,magical,amusement park,memory,excitement</media:keywords>
             <media:city> California</media:city>
             <media:country>United States</media:country>
             <media:regionCode>US</media:regionCode>
             <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
             <media:category>Heartwarming</media:category>
             <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
             <media:filmingDate>Sun, 9 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2584</guid>
             <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 08:24:03 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2584.jpg" />
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2584.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Drone crashes into Moscow City tower in Russia</media:title>
             <media:description>An explosion occurred on 30 July 2023 in the 50-storey building of the IQ-quarter located in Moscow City.

The incident took place in the building at 10/2 Presnenskaya Embankment, at the level of the fifth or sixth floors, where the glazing was “broken”. No harm done.

The tower was evacuated, law enforcement agencies arrived at the scene.

Shortly before this, air defense systems repelled an attack by drones in the Moscow region. According to 112, the drones were shot down near Odintsovo and Krasnogorsk.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>moscow,russia,drone,crash,war,ukraine,moscow city,explosion</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Moscow</media:city>
             <media:country>Russia</media:country>
             <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
             <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
             <media:category>News</media:category>
             <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
             <media:filmingDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2582</guid>
             <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023 17:45:16 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2582.jpg" />
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2582.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Cake mishap: hilarious family moment in Ankara, Turkey</media:title>
             <media:description>In a heartwarming yet comical family moment captured in Ankara, Turkey, a video shared by @amywinehouzze on July 15, 2023, showcased their little one indulging in a cake while kneeling on a dining chair. The child's innocent delight was infectious as they merrily savored the cake in one hand, but alas, laughter ensued as the sweet treat slipped from their grasp while trying to juggle it with the other hand. Surrounding family members couldn't help but burst into fits of laughter, turning the mishap into an unforgettable memory. This endearing scene reminds us of the simple joys and shared laughter that bring families together, creating cherished moments to be cherished for years to come.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>cake,kid,dining,table,Ankara,Turkey,video,laughter,family,moment,comical,mishap,sweet,treat,delight,memorable,joy,shared,precious,memory</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Ankara</media:city>
             <media:country>Turkey</media:country>
             <media:regionCode>TR</media:regionCode>
            <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>      
             <media:category>Fails and Funnies</media:category>
             <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
             <media:filmingDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2581</guid>
             <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023 17:45:47 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2581.jpg" />
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2581.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Intense hailstorm hits Central Ottawa: golf ball sized hail pummels the city for 5 minutes!</media:title>
             <media:description>On July 28, 2023, residents of Ottawa, Canada, experienced an intense hailstorm that left them astonished and wary. The event was captured on video by @paulajroy, who shared the gripping footage of the hailstorm outside her house. Lasting for approximately five minutes, the hailstones reached nearly the size of golf balls, causing significant concern for property damage and potential risks to individuals caught outdoors. The severe weather phenomenon swept through central Ottawa, leaving a trail of destruction in its wake.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>hailstorm,ottawa,canada,weather,intense,video,paulajroy,golfball,sized,hail,central,astonishment,damage,risk,outdoors,severe,phenomenon,destruction,warnings,precautions</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Ottawa </media:city>
             <media:country>Canada</media:country>
             <media:regionCode>CA</media:regionCode>
            <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>      
             <media:category>Weather</media:category>
             <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
             <media:filmingDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2579</guid>
             <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023 17:39:58 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2579.jpg" />
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2579.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Resourceful feline masters the art of door-opening: a fascinating tale from Jepara, Indonesia!</media:title>
             <media:description>In a captivating video captured by @muktafil on April 24, 2023, in Jepara, Indonesia, an astonishing feat unfolded as their clever cat showcased its ingenuity. The footage showcases the feline effortlessly opening the door to the house, by jumping on the door handle leaving its owner in awe of its newfound talent. Expressing his astonishment, the author stated, "I was surprised that the cat opened the door by itself, now if you put it outside, it will open the door. Don't know where it learned from." The video has since captured the hearts of viewers worldwide, as they marvel at the resourceful cat's ability to conquer the seemingly insurmountable obstacle. This extraordinary tale serves as a reminder of the intelligence and adaptability possessed by our feline companions.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>clever,cat,door,opening,video,Jepara,Indonesia,surprise,talent,resourceful,ingenuity,amazement,owner,outside,learn,astonishment,heartwarming,intelligence,adaptability,feline</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Jepara</media:city>
             <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
             <media:regionCode>ID</media:regionCode>
            <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>      
             <media:category>Animals</media:category>
             <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
             <media:filmingDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2578</guid>
             <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 07:29:30 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2578.jpg" />
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2578.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Bathroom bliss: Indonesian cat's unique way to beat the heat</media:title>
             <media:description>In Yogyakarta, Indonesia, a heartwarming video captured by @bagus_muhammad_ on March 28, 2023, showcases the adorable antics of his feline companion during a hot day. The short clip features his cat lying flat on its stomach in the cool confines of the bathroom, delightfully spreading its hind legs for ultimate relaxation. As temperatures rise, it seems this clever kitty has found its perfect oasis for beating the heat. With a contented expression on its face, it's evident that the bathroom has become the preferred spot for the cat to seek respite from the sweltering weather. </media:description>
             <media:keywords>cat,bathroom,Indonesia,Yogyakarta,video,pet,feline,hot,heat,adorable,antics,relaxation,hind legs,oasis,cool,weather,comfort,pets,content,warmer days</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Yogyakarta</media:city>
             <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
             <media:regionCode>ID</media:regionCode>
            <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>      
             <media:category>Animals</media:category>
             <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
             <media:filmingDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2577</guid>
             <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 08:17:01 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2577.jpg" />
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2577.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Miraculous rescue: cat safely recovered from perilous heights in Minsk</media:title>
             <media:description>In a heartwarming incident in Minsk, Belarus, on July 19, 2023, a vigilant passerby, @victory_shh, captured a remarkable moment when a cat's life was saved from a precarious situation. The cat found itself in a perilous predicament, clinging onto a window pane on the outside of a story building. Curiosity piqued when the author noticed the presence of the Ministry of Emergencies' vehicle nearby. Upon approaching the scene, they witnessed the heartening sight of a rescue operation in progress. The skilled emergency responders swiftly rescued the cat after it appeared to fall and secured the frightened feline, bringing it to safety. Thankfully, the rescue was successful, and the cat was handed over to a man, presumably its owner.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>rescue,cat,building,Minsk,Belarus,window,emergency,passerby,video,heartwarming,precarious,Ministry,height,safe,owner,compassion,celebration,online,courage,grateful</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Minsk</media:city>
             <media:country>Belarus</media:country>
             <media:regionCode>BY</media:regionCode>
             <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
             <media:category>Rescue</media:category>
             <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
             <media:filmingDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2576</guid>
             <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 08:16:28 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2576.jpg" />
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2576.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Devastating wildfire strikes near Volos, Greece</media:title>
             <media:description>On July 27, 2023, a destructive wildfire ravaged the area near Volos, Greece, causing significant damage to an ammunition depot situated in the coastal town of Nea Aghialos. The depot, belonging to the Greek air force, was engulfed in flames, leading to powerful explosions that echoed through the region. Local media reported on the incident, and officials took immediate action, ordering the evacuation of several communities in the severely impacted Magnesia area along the northern coast of Athens. As the fires continued to spread, @peterjaygood captured a video showcasing smoke billowing from a distance from the fires near Volos. The situation remained critical, with authorities and emergency services working tirelessly to contain the blaze and protect the affected communities.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>wildfire,volos,greece,ammunition,depot,explosions,evacuation,magnesia,coastal,nea aghialos,greek air force,damage,smoke,fires,video,@peterjaygood,media,officials,communities,Athens</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Volos</media:city>
             <media:country>Greece</media:country>
             <media:regionCode>GR</media:regionCode>
            <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>      
             <media:category>News</media:category>
             <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
             <media:filmingDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2575</guid>
             <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 07:26:05 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2575.jpg" />
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2575.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Gas explosion rocks residential building in Nizhnekamsk</media:title>
             <media:description>On July 25, 2023, a devastating gas explosion shook a five-story residential building in Nizhnekamsk, Russia, leaving behind a trail of destruction and injuries. The incident resulted in two people being injured, while eight other residents managed to evacuate independently from the burning structure. The building suffered partial destruction, with the load-bearing structures being severely damaged and the windows of some apartments shattered. As the dust settled, the community was left in shock and uncertainty as authorities began their investigation into the cause of the explosion. With no information yet on the root of the tragedy, residents and officials are left grappling with the aftermath, seeking answers and support for the affected individuals and families.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>explosion,residential,building,nizhnekamsk,russia,injured,evacuation,fire,damage,gas,incident,cause,investigation,shattered,uncertainty,shock,community,support,tragedy,aftermath.</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Nizhnekamsk</media:city>
             <media:country>Russia</media:country>
             <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
             <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
             <media:category>News</media:category>
             <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
             <media:filmingDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2574</guid>
             <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 08:15:40 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2574.jpg" />
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2574.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Adventurous Manda: a curious cat's high-rise escapades in Yogyakarta!</media:title>
             <media:description>In a captivating moment caught on video by @a.youu_ on July 4, 2023, in Yogyakarta, Indonesia, a curious cat named Manda was spotted perched atop an unfinished building. The enigmatic feline appeared unsure of its surroundings, leaving viewers both amused and intrigued by its daring escapade. With a playful spirit, the author decided to record the charming scene, showcasing Manda's adventurous nature and uncertain demeanor as it surveyed the world from its lofty vantage point.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>cat,video,Yogyakarta,Indonesia,Manda,building,perched,curious,confused,fun,playful,adventurous,daring,charming,uncertain,climb,pet,antics,moment,heartwarming</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Yogyakarta</media:city>
             <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
             <media:regionCode>ID</media:regionCode>
            <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>      
             <media:category>Animals</media:category>
             <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
             <media:filmingDate>Tue, 4 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2573</guid>
             <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 08:15:12 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2573.jpg" />
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2573.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Adventurous boat dog: a joyful journey on the waters of Posadas, Argentina</media:title>
             <media:description>In Posadas, Argentina, a heartwarming sight was captured by @fefu1408 on December 1, 2021. A video showcased a spirited dog perched confidently on the front of a speeding boat, appearing to relish every moment of the thrilling experience. As the author went rowing with a friend, they encountered this common occurrence of dogs joining the boating adventures. In this particular instance, the dog belonged to another boat that passed them by, showcasing the adventurous spirit and love for the water that these furry companions hold. </media:description>
             <media:keywords>rowing,boat,dog,adventure,Posadas,Argentina,speed,waters,joyful,companions,video,water,front,perched,passing,friend,common,furry,capture,spirit</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Posadas</media:city>
             <media:country>Argentina</media:country>
             <media:regionCode>AR</media:regionCode>
            <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>      
             <media:category>Animals</media:category>
             <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
             <media:filmingDate>Wed, 1 Dec 2021</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2572</guid>
             <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 07:28:52 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2572.jpg" />
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2572.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Enchanting fur patterns: unique cat in Blitar delights in friendly affection</media:title>
             <media:description>In a heartwarming scene captured on video by @polseksrengat on June 30, 2023, in Blitar, Indonesia, a cat with naturally polished fur became the center of attention among a group of friends. The cat sported a striking combination of white fur on its face and a mix of white and black fur on the rest of its body, making it truly unique. As the friends scratched the cat gently, it basked in their affectionate company, closing its eyes in contentment each time one of them touched its head. The endearing sight of this feline enjoying the camaraderie warmed the hearts of those who witnessed the adorable encounter, reminding us of the profound bond between humans and their feline companions.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>polished,fur,cat,white,black,unique,friends,affection,company,contentment,adorable,feline,bond,Indonesia,Blitar,video,captured,June30,2023,@polseksrengat</media:keywords>
             <media:city> Blitar</media:city>
             <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
             <media:regionCode>ID</media:regionCode>
            <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>      
             <media:category>Animals</media:category>
             <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
             <media:filmingDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2571</guid>
             <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 08:08:02 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2571.jpg" />
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2571.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Autonomous appliance anomaly: the mysterious moving fan in Manila!</media:title>
             <media:description>In a bizarre and comical incident that unfolded on May 17, 2023, in Quezon City, Manila, Philippines, a peculiar electric fan caught the attention of @sindefelt. The fan seemed to have a mind of its own, making spontaneous movements while set to speed 3, prompting the astonished owner to exclaim, "It seems like the newly bought electric fan has its own life, at speed 3 it moves on its own." The situation took a humorous turn as a voice-over in the captured video expressed frustration, declaring, "I don't know what to do with you, I'm having a hard time dealing with you." With the scorching summer heat making speed 1 insufficient, and speed 3 causing the fan to mischievously distance itself from its user, @sindefelt found solace in the middle ground, claiming speed 2 to be the optimal choice. </media:description>
             <media:keywords>electric,fan,autonomous,movement,speed,comical,incident,video,capture,summer,Manila,Philippines,@sindefelt,quirky,frustration,amusing,mystery,internet,heat,optimal</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Quezon City, Manila</media:city>
             <media:country>Philippines</media:country>
             <media:regionCode>PH</media:regionCode>
             <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
             <media:category>Fails and Funnies</media:category>
             <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
             <media:filmingDate>Wed, 17 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2570</guid>
             <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 08:07:33 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2570.jpg" />
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2570.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Quirky Yeti: cat asserts ownership over owner's resting foot in hilarious video!</media:title>
             <media:description>In a heartwarming yet amusing video captured by @dymova_brows on December 14, 2022, in Zaporozhye, Ukraine, a 7-year-old cat named Yeti showcases its unique character. The footage shows Yeti attempting to keep its owner's foot still under the blanket while playfully growling like a dog when met with resistance. The quirky feline's predilections include strolls on the balcony and relishing wet food, but it fiercely guards its delicious meals from fellow feline companions. The short video captures Yeti's endearing and assertive personality, providing a delightful glimpse into the fascinating world of this furry friend.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>cat,yeti,video,quirky,owner,foot,bed,blanket,growl,dog,character,Zaporozhye,Ukraine,balcony,wet food,delicious,unique,feline,playful,adorable</media:keywords>
             <media:city> Zaporozhye</media:city>
             <media:country>Ukraine</media:country>
             <media:regionCode>UA</media:regionCode>
            <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>      
             <media:category>Animals</media:category>
             <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
             <media:filmingDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2569</guid>
             <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 07:20:35 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2569.jpg" />
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2569.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Emotional dilemma: heartwarming video shows child's tears turn into joy when offered money</media:title>
             <media:description>In a touching video captured by @yhangespela on June 2, 2023, in San Mateo, Rizal, Philippines, a young child's conflicting emotions towards money were showcased. The footage depicted the child initially crying but quickly becoming quiet and even expressing a desire for more when presented with money. The heartwarming scene left viewers pondering the complexities of children's perceptions of money and the diverse range of emotions it can evoke in young minds.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>crying,money,child,emotions,video,touching,Philippines,San Mateo,young,tears,joy,desire,perception,mother,quiet,conflicting,heartwarming,captured,presented,note</media:keywords>
             <media:city>San Mateo, Rizal</media:city>
             <media:country>Philippines</media:country>
             <media:regionCode>PH</media:regionCode>
            <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>      
             <media:category>Heartwarming</media:category>
             <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
             <media:filmingDate>Fri, 2 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2568</guid>
             <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 07:55:27 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2568.jpg" />
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2568.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Spooky encounter on Pasipit Road: terrified drivers mistake chilling figure for a ghost!</media:title>
             <media:description>On July 15, 2023, a chilling encounter took place in Silang, Cavite, Philippines, when a group of friends driving to Tagaytay found themselves on an unknown road due to a navigation mishap with the Waze app. As they ventured down Pasipit Road, their headlights illuminated a figure by the roadside, sending them into a panic. Screams filled the car as they initially believed they had come across a ghost. However, it turned out to be a guy leisurely relaxing beside the road. The eerie moment, captured on video by @ljculalic_, became a spooky tale for the adventurers, who eventually found their way back on track. </media:description>
             <media:keywords>silang,cavite,philippines,waze,navigation,lost,pasipit road,ghost,chilling,encounter,tagaytay,headlights,panic,screams,video,@ljculalic_,driving,spooky,laughter,relief</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Silang, Cavite</media:city>
             <media:country>Philippines</media:country>
             <media:regionCode>PH</media:regionCode>
             <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
             <media:category>Fails and Funnies</media:category>
             <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
             <media:filmingDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2567</guid>
             <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 07:54:50 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2567.jpg" />
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2567.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Cat chaos: Minsk feline's hilarious morning escape from the mysterious carrier bag!</media:title>
             <media:description>In a humorous yet chaotic scene captured by @vorobyov2021 on May 5, 2023, in Minsk, Belarus, a scared feline caused havoc as she ran around the house with a carrier bag caught on her back. The video showcases the frantic cat darting from room to room, desperately trying to escape the seemingly terrifying bag. According to the author, the unexpected morning commotion served as an amusing wake-up call, as the mischievous cat poked and prodded her way through the apartment in a comical attempt to be free from her unexpected accessory.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>cat,video,Minsk,Belarus,scared,carrier bag,back,running,banging,things,escape,hilarious,chaos,feline,apartment,wake-up,poke,capture,room,commotion</media:keywords>
             <media:city> Minsk</media:city>
             <media:country>Belarus</media:country>
             <media:regionCode>BY</media:regionCode>
             <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
             <media:category>Animals</media:category>
             <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
             <media:filmingDate>Fri, 5 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2566</guid>
             <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 07:53:24 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2566.jpg" />
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2566.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Fearless driver defies odds: nonchalantly navigates car on swaying tow track through Minsk's road</media:title>
             <media:description>In a remarkable display of nonchalance, a video captured by @rrrinita on July 12, 2023, in Minsk, Belarus, showcased a driver unbothered by the perilous sight of a car being carried and swaying on the road. The onlooker initially suspected the driver might be feeling unwell, but to their surprise, the driver appeared utterly unfazed, revealing that it was not their first time engaging in such an audacious feat. Attached to the vehicle was a tow track where the car was mounted, causing it to sway dangerously from side to side. Despite the alarming spectacle, the driver calmly continued to navigate through the streets of Minsk, defying the odds and leaving witnesses astounded by their fearless determination.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>car,tow,swaying,road,driver,fearless,Minsk,Belarus,video,danger,audacious,nonchalant,astonishing,surprising,unfazed,daring,streets,spectacle,determination,amazed</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Minsk</media:city>
             <media:country>Belarus</media:country>
             <media:regionCode>BY</media:regionCode>
            <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>      
             <media:category>News</media:category>
             <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
             <media:filmingDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2565</guid>
             <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 07:13:05 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2565.jpg" />
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2565.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Action-packed movie filming in Chisinau takes a dramatic turn as car rams parked bus!</media:title>
             <media:description>In a stunning turn of events in Chisinau, Moldova, a movie filming session took a thrilling and unexpected twist as a car intentionally rammed into a parked bus. The dramatic scene, captured by @nazligian_ on July 23, 2023, showcased the heart-pounding moment when the car, utilizing a purpose-built ramp, accelerated towards the stationary bus. With precision and skill, the car collided with the bus, creating a breathtaking spectacle that left onlookers in awe. Fortunately, there were no reported injuries as the filming was conducted in a closed-off area in the city center. The incident occurred as part of the action-packed movie production, adding an authentic touch to the adrenaline-filled scenes being brought to life on the silver screen.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>movie,filming,chisinau,moldova,car,bus,ramp,action,thrilling,unexpected,dramatic,spectacle,onlookers,injury-free,closed-off,center,adrenaline,scenes,silver screen,production</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Chisinau </media:city>
             <media:country>Moldova</media:country>
             <media:regionCode>MD</media:regionCode>
            <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>      
             <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
             <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
             <media:filmingDate>Sun, 23 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2563</guid>
             <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 07:49:50 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2563.jpg" />
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2563.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Catnap couture: adorable feline caught napping in boutique's pink mavin!</media:title>
             <media:description>In the city of Borisov, Belarus, on July 16, 2023, a heartwarming scene unfolded in a second clothes boutique. Local resident @ugimaster stumbled upon a delightful sight as he entered the store - a contented cat fast asleep amidst the clothes. Its furry head was cozily nestled on a soft pink mavin, adding an extra touch of cuteness to the scene. The video captured by @ugimaster quickly went viral, spreading smiles and warming hearts across the internet.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>cat,sleeping,clothes,boutique,Borisov,Belarus,@ugimaster,video,peaceful,pink,mavin,adorable,feline,nap,city,viral,internet,heartwarming,cozy,cute</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Borisov</media:city>
             <media:country>Belarus</media:country>
             <media:regionCode>BY</media:regionCode>
            <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>      
             <media:category>Animals</media:category>
             <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
             <media:filmingDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2562</guid>
             <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 07:47:37 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2562.jpg" />
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2562.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Resilience amidst adversity: heartwarming acts of kindness in the midst of conflict</media:title>
             <media:description>In the midst of an ongoing conflict between Russia and Ukraine, a heartwarming video captured by @sneg0111 on April 7, 2023, in Zaporozhye, Ukraine, showcased the unwavering spirit of the Ukrainian people. The footage depicted a woman and her dog walking home after grocery shopping in the midst of a blackout caused by shelling on infrastructure, including the thermal power plant. Despite the challenging circumstances, the woman ingeniously used her dog's help to carry the groceries with its mouth, highlighting the resourcefulness and unity of the community. In times of crisis, the residents of Ukraine rallied together, extending their compassion and support to one another, regardless of whether it was a person or a furry companion. This heartwarming act of kindness serves as a reminder of the resilience displayed by ordinary individuals in extraordinary times.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>resilience,conflict,video,woman,dog,grocery,shopping,blackout,infrastructure,unity,community,crisis,kindness,support,compassion,Russia,Ukraine,Zaporozhye,touching,heartwarming</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Zaporozhye</media:city>
             <media:country>Ukraine</media:country>
             <media:regionCode>UA</media:regionCode>
             <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
             <media:category>Heartwarming</media:category>
             <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
             <media:filmingDate>Fri, 7 Apr 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2561</guid>
             <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 07:46:09 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2561.jpg" />
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2561.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Nine-year-old boy hospitalized after tree collapse at Samara playground</media:title>
             <media:description>On July 10, 2023 evening in the Oktyabrsky district of Samara, Russia, a harrowing incident occurred on a playground when a tree unexpectedly fell on a nine-year-old boy. Despite initial fears, authorities determined that the tree was still alive and showed no signs of decay, raising questions about the cause of the collapse. The young victim was rushed to Seredavina Hospital, where medical professionals confirmed his condition to be stable and satisfactory. The child is currently under close observation by doctors as they work to ensure his recovery. Authorities are conducting a thorough investigation into the incident to understand the circumstances leading to the tree's collapse, offering insights to prevent similar accidents in the future.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>hospitalized,playground,tree,collapse,samara,russia,nine-year-old,incident,oktyabrsky,alive,decay,investigation,authorities,stable,satisfactory,doctors,observation,recovery,child,district</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Samara</media:city>
             <media:country>Russia</media:country>
             <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
             <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
             <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
             <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
             <media:filmingDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2559</guid>
             <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 06:58:05 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2559.jpg" />
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2559.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Raccoon's Miron misadventures: a heartwarming birthday surprise!</media:title>
             <media:description>In a heartwarming tale of misadventures, @raccoon_miron from St. Petersburg, Russia, captured a touching video while searching for her beloved raccoon pet, Miron on April 27, 2023. The furry troublemaker had managed to scatter her belongings all over the apartment on the eve of his birthday, leaving her in tears, fearing he had escaped through the window. However, to her relief, Miron was just being mischievous and had fallen asleep amidst her things. The emotional rollercoaster of worry and joy unfolded in the video.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>raccoon,miron,video,pet,birthday,surprise,misadventures,St. Petersburg,Russia,apartment,balcony,work,order,sobbing,window,smart,boy,asleep,things,love,joy.</media:keywords>
             <media:city> St. Petersburg</media:city>
             <media:country>Russia</media:country>
             <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
            <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>      
             <media:category>Animals</media:category>
             <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
             <media:filmingDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2558</guid>
             <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 07:43:53 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2558.jpg" />
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2558.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Record-breaking capture: the world's longest Burmese python defeated on US41</media:title>
             <media:description>In a remarkable feat of courage and teamwork, a group of adventurers on US41 between Naples and Miami, USA, captured the world's longest Burmese python ever documented. The incredible event was documented in a video by @gladesboys on July 10, 2023. Braving the late-night encounter at 1 am, the author and his three inexperienced companions faced the massive serpent on the road. With nerves of steel, he expertly dodged the snake's strikes, finally managing to grasp its tail and secure the head. Despite the dangers, the skilled team managed the capture flawlessly, ensuring that no one was harmed during the process. </media:description>
             <media:keywords>python,road,US41,Naples,Miami,USA,video,capture,longest,Burmese,record,encounter,hunters,tail,head,courageous,teamwork,adventure,wildlife,triumph,danger</media:keywords>
             <media:city>US41 between Naples and Miami</media:city>
             <media:country>United States</media:country>
             <media:regionCode>US</media:regionCode>
             <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
             <media:category>Animals</media:category>
             <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
             <media:filmingDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2557</guid>
             <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 14:58:10 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2557.jpg" />
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2557.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Massive moth invasion: swarms of flying creatures fill the night skies in Yelets, Russia</media:title>
             <media:description>On the night of Monday, July 24, 2023, the city of Yelets in the Lipetsk region, Russia, experienced a bizarre phenomenon as drivers encountered a massive invasion of insects. Thousands of flying creatures, identified as moths, enveloped the road lights, creating "swarm clouds" that obstructed the path on the Karakum bridge. Disturbing footage recorded by a driver showcased the surreal scene, where the insects swarmed around vehicles, making navigation challenging. </media:description>
             <media:keywords>insects,invasion,Yelets,Russia,night,Monday,July 24,Lipetsk,drivers,filmed,massive,flying,creatures,swarm,clouds,Karakum,bridge,moths,video,way,drove</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Yelets, Lipetsk region</media:city>
             <media:country>Russia</media:country>
             <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
            <media:categoryCode>ODD</media:categoryCode>      
             <media:category>Animals</media:category>
             <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
             <media:filmingDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2556</guid>
             <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 14:56:15 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2556.jpg" />
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2556.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Night of terror: families seek shelter from Russian rocket attacks in Odesa shopping mall garage</media:title>
             <media:description>In the midst of the ongoing military conflict between Russia and Ukraine, a chilling video has emerged, shedding light on the harrowing reality faced by the people of Odesa, Ukraine. On July 22, 2023, @stilianspai captured a heart-wrenching scene as families sought refuge from a night rocket attack in one of the city's shopping mall garages. The footage showed small children nestled in strollers, their parents anxiously huddled together, seeking safety from the relentless barrage of rockets raining down upon the city. The haunting image serves as a poignant reminder of the devastating toll this conflict has taken on innocent civilians, whose lives are forever impacted by the indiscriminate violence.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>attack,odesa,ukraine,russians,video,shelter,families,night,rocket,mall,garage,conflict,children,parents,fear,war,violence,civilians,safety,devastation</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Odesa</media:city>
             <media:country>Ukraine</media:country>
             <media:regionCode>UA</media:regionCode>
             <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
             <media:category>News</media:category>
             <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
             <media:filmingDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2555</guid>
             <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 14:59:50 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2555.jpg" />
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2555.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Tragedy strikes: pedestrian bridge collapse in Luga claims one life, leaves three injured</media:title>
             <media:description>In a devastating incident on July 22, 2023, a pedestrian bridge in the city of Luga, Leningrad Region, Russia, collapsed, resulting in one person losing their life and three others sustaining injuries. The regional Investigative Committee confirmed the tragic event, and harrowing video footage captured the moment when numerous people were standing on the bridge just before it gave way. The collapse has sent shockwaves through the community, prompting concerns about the safety and maintenance of such structures.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>tragedy,pedestrian,bridge,collapse,Luga,Russia,death,injury,incident,Investigative Committee,video,footage,community,safety,maintenance,structure,investigation,authorities,shockwaves,concerns</media:keywords>
             <media:city> Luga, Saint Petersburg region</media:city>
             <media:country>Russia</media:country>
             <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
             <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
             <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
             <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
             <media:filmingDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2554</guid>
             <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 07:29:36 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2554.jpg" />
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2554.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Tragedy unleashed: chilling footage reveals the day chaos struck Chaikovska Street</media:title>
             <media:description>On July 28, 2022, in Bakhmut, Donetsk, Ukraine, @coldmorion recorded a distressing video of a shelling incident that devastated Chaikovska Street. The footage captured the terrifying moment when Uragan MLRS and cluster munitions rained down on the area, resulting in the tragic loss of five lives. The video showcased the horrifying reality of the conflict, leaving no doubt about the impact on civilians caught in the crossfire.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>shelling,distress,video,Bakhmut,Donetsk,Ukraine,Chaikovska Street,Uragan MLRS,cluster munitions,tragedy,chaos,civilians,conflict,devastation,loss,lives,war,violence,footage,distressing</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Bakhmut, Donetsk</media:city>
             <media:country>Ukraine</media:country>
             <media:regionCode>UA</media:regionCode>
             <media:categoryCode>WAR</media:categoryCode>
             <media:category>News</media:category>
             <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
             <media:filmingDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2022</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2553</guid>
             <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023 20:10:16 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2553.jpg" />
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2553.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Blaze breaks out on Panama-registered car carrier Fremantle Highway off Netherlands coast</media:title>
             <media:description>A fire broke out on the Panama-registered car carrier, Fremantle Highway, off the coast of the Netherlands near Ameland on July 26, 2023, as it was transporting 2,857 cars from Bremerhaven, Germany, to Port Said, Egypt. The blaze resulted in the evacuation of all 23 crew members, with seven rescued from the water and the rest airlifted by helicopter. Tragically, one crew member lost their life, and several others were injured during the incident. The fire, originating from one of the 25 electric cars onboard, proved difficult for the crew to control, and the vessel continued to burn approximately 27 nautical miles north of the Dutch island of Ameland, close to a major environmental and UNESCO heritage site. Images showed scorched areas and billowing smoke along the ship's side as emergency responders battled to contain the flames. @NicoGuud captured a video of smoke still coming from the vessel.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>fire,blaze,car carrier,Netherlands,coast,Fremantle Highway,smoke,evacuation,rescue,injuries,crew,incident,electric cars,tragedy,Ameland,environmental,UNESCO,scorched,emergency,responders</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Ameland</media:city>
             <media:country>Netherlands</media:country>
             <media:regionCode>NL</media:regionCode>
            <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>      
             <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
             <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
             <media:filmingDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2552</guid>
             <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023 20:11:03 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2552.jpg" />
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2552.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Skyscraper fire and crane collapse: dramatic scene unfolds at 41st and 10th Ave, New York</media:title>
             <media:description>In a harrowing incident on the 26th of July, 2023, at the intersection of 41st and 10th Ave in New York City, USA, a devastating fire broke out on top of a skyscraper, accompanied by a catastrophic crane collapse. The intense scene was captured by @akofink, who shared a chilling video showcasing smoke billowing from the building's pinnacle. The social media post was captioned, "Crane collapse and fire! 41st and 10th Ave. First responders on the scene." The incident prompted an immediate response from first responders who rushed to the location to combat the raging blaze and assess the extent of the damage. </media:description>
             <media:keywords>skyscraper,fire,crane,collapse,New York,USA,video,smoke,41st,10th Ave,incident,responders,damage,investigation,social media,tragedy,authorities,intersection,billowing,chilling</media:keywords>
             <media:city>New York City</media:city>
             <media:country>United States</media:country>
             <media:regionCode>US</media:regionCode>
            <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>      
             <media:category>News</media:category>
             <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
             <media:filmingDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2551</guid>
             <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023 18:25:43 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2551.jpg" />
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2551.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Wildfires ravage Cascais, Portugal: local residents and firefighters battle blaze in Sintra-Cascais Natural Park</media:title>
             <media:description>On July 25th, 2023, a devastating wildfire struck the picturesque region of Cascais, Portugal. The blaze originated at 5 p.m. in the mountainous terrain of the Sintra-Cascais natural park, covering an expansive 145 square kilometers of land west of Lisbon. At 6 p.m., @InVasconcellos captured a video of the raging inferno, as hundreds of Portuguese firefighters, supported by local residents, scrambled to contain the flames. However, their efforts were challenged by strong winds, complicating the firefighting process. The popular holiday destination of Cascais faced a threat to its natural beauty and wildlife as the fire continued to spread, prompting urgent action from the authorities to control the devastating situation.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>cascais,portugal,wildfires,2023,video,@InVasconcellos,july,25th,natural park,firefighters,blaze,mountainous,sintra-cascais,land,lisbon,winds,residents,holiday destination,effort,authorities.</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Cascais</media:city>
             <media:country>Portugal</media:country>
             <media:regionCode>PT</media:regionCode>
            <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>      
             <media:category>News</media:category>
             <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
             <media:filmingDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2550</guid>
             <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 14:49:01 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2550.jpg" />
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2550.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Tornado-like waterspout seen on Minsk Sea: a captivating spectacle leaves locals amazed</media:title>
             <media:description>On July 22, 2023, @ikorvel captured a remarkable video of a tornado-like waterspout on the Minsk Sea in Belarus. Initially mistaken for smoke from a fire on the neighboring shore, the swirling air quickly revealed its true nature. Fortunately, the waterspout did not approach their location, and after 10 minutes, only an increased wind accompanied by rain reached them, causing no damage to the surroundings. The awe-inspiring sight left the witnesses astonished at the forces of nature on display.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>video,tornado,waterspout,Minsk,Belarus,July,2023,nature,phenomenon,captivating,swirling,air,smoke,fire,neighboring,wind,rain,amazed,forces,astonishing</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Minsk </media:city>
             <media:country>Belarus</media:country>
             <media:regionCode>BY</media:regionCode>
            <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>      
             <media:category>Weather</media:category>
             <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
             <media:filmingDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2549</guid>
             <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023 17:52:04 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2549.jpg" />
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2549.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Silent expectations: a comical tale of leash mishaps and unspoken desires</media:title>
             <media:description>In a heartwarming yet amusing video captured by @bentleyandfinnn on June 12, 2023, in Texas, USA, a dog's expressive response to an unexpected leash mishap left viewers in stitches. The dog, eagerly anticipating a walk, stood still as its owner accidentally dropped the leash. With a look of anticipation and confusion, the canine waited for the owner to pick it up and continue the outing, but to no avail. The silence spoke volumes as the dog's expressive eyes and hopeful demeanor conveyed its desires without a single bark. Eventually, the dog took matters into its paws and returned to the owner, as if to say, "Let's try this again, but get it right this time!" The video exemplified the unspoken bond between pets and their owners, evoking laughter and heartwarming feelings all at once.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>dog,leash,video,Texas,USA,cute,funny,owner,walk,expectation,confusion,expressive,eyes,paws,bond,outing,pet,laughter,heartwarming,silent,mishap</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Texas</media:city>
             <media:country>United States</media:country>
             <media:regionCode>US</media:regionCode>
            <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>      
             <media:category>Animals</media:category>
             <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
             <media:filmingDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2547</guid>
             <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023 17:52:44 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2547.jpg" />
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2547.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Adorable new arrival: baby parrot dreams peacefully in loving hands</media:title>
             <media:description>On June 8th, 2023, in Izmir, Turkey, a heartwarming video captured by @hknyilmaz35 showcased a newly hatched parrot in the gentle hands of its caretaker, Hakan. The tiny parrot, peacefully asleep, melted hearts with its undeniable cuteness. The short clip resonated with viewers worldwide, celebrating the beauty of new life and the bond between humans and animals.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>adorable,parrot,hatchling,video,Izmir,Turkey,hands,caretaker,asleep,cute,newlife,bond,humans,animals,heartwarming,tiny,love,peaceful,@hknyilmaz35,June8th2023</media:keywords>
             <media:city> Izmir</media:city>
             <media:country>Turkey</media:country>
             <media:regionCode>TR</media:regionCode>
            <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>      
             <media:category>Animals</media:category>
             <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
             <media:filmingDate>Thu, 8 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2546</guid>
             <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023 18:03:14 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2546.jpg" />
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2546.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item></channel>
           </rss>