<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
        xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
        xmlns:openSearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearchrss/1.0/"
        xmlns:dfpvideo="http://api.google.com/dfpvideo"
        xmlns:tms="http://data.tmsapi.com/v1.1"
        version="2.0">
         <channel>
           <title>ViralBear videos</title>
           <dfpvideo:version>2</dfpvideo:version><item>
             <media:title>Destruction of hydroelectric dam sparks water emergency and escalating tensions between Ukraine and Russia</media:title>
             <media:description>In a catastrophic turn of events, the upper part of the hydroelectric dam in Russian-occupied Novaya Kakhovka, located in the Kherson region of Ukraine, was destroyed on 6th June, 2023. This destructive act led to an uncontrolled discharge of water, triggering a series of alarming consequences. As the blame game ensues, both Ukraine and Russia accuse each other of undermining the hydroelectric power station, further fueling the already heightened tensions between the two nations.

The immediate aftermath of the dam's destruction was the flooding of the hydroelectric power station area, forcing authorities to initiate mass evacuations in the Kherson region. The fear of water scarcity in Crimea looms large, as the region heavily relies on the reservoir's supply. Additionally, the Zaporozhye nuclear power plant had to be shut down due to the incident, compounding the already pressing water shortage crisis in southern Ukraine.

The severity of the situation was highlighted by reports indicating that the Kakhovka Hydroelectric Power Station is beyond repair, a sentiment echoed by both Ukrainian and Russian authorities. Disturbingly, the collapse of the hydroelectric dam continues, with sources suggesting that 14 of the station's 28 spans have already been destroyed, rendering the entire power station completely submerged.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>hydroelectric,dam,destruction,water,evacuation,tensions,Ukraine,Russia,blame,crisis,flood,scarcity,reservoir,power,station,collapse,submerged,geopolitical,aftermath,incident</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Novaya Kakhovka, Kherson</media:city>
             <media:country>Ukraine</media:country>
             <media:category>News</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Tue, 6 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2211</guid>
             <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 09:37:15 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/cfbc6c9c-ac68-4c1a-8444-af9babe61bf2.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/206ffa4c-a665-4ac7-8c94-8b61cff1b5f8.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Hydroelectric dam catastrophe in Novaya Kakhovka: Ukraine-Russia water crisis looming</media:title>
             <media:description>In a devastating turn of events, the upper part of the hydroelectric dam in Novaya Kakhovka, located in the Russian-occupied region of Kherson, Ukraine, was destroyed on 6th June, 2023. This resulted in an uncontrolled discharge of water, triggering a dire situation for the residents in the surrounding areas. Both Ukraine and Russia have been quick to accuse each other of undermining the hydroelectric power station, further escalating tensions between the two nations.

The consequences of this catastrophe have been severe. The flooding caused by the collapsed dam has forced the evacuation of residents in the Kherson region, who now fear the impending water shortage in Crimea. Additionally, the Zaporozhye nuclear power plant had to be disabled, compounding the already existing water scarcity in southern Ukraine. With the Kakhovka HPP deemed beyond repair by authorities from both sides, the situation continues to worsen. According to sources from TASS, 14 of the station's 28 spans have been destroyed, leaving the hydroelectric power station completely submerged. This disaster marks a critical moment in the ongoing water crisis between Ukraine and Russia.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>hydroelectric,dam,catastrophe,Novaya Kakhovka,Kherson,Ukraine,uncontrolled,discharge,water,evacuation,Crimea,Zaporozhye,nuclear,power plant,Russian-occupied,collapse,tension,scarcity,submerged,crisis</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Novaya Kakhovka, Kherson</media:city>
             <media:country>Ukraine</media:country>
             <media:category>News</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Tue, 6 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2210</guid>
             <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 09:17:33 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/ee91ef8b-61f7-401d-8af8-054c4245d3d0.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/e187860f-2b92-4c6c-9b35-5f81d9907ef7.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Adorable toddler's hilarious twist: moldy bun served at playtime store!</media:title>
             <media:description>In a heartwarming moment captured by @kyliecgray in Barrie, Ontario, Canada, her young son embarked on his first imaginative play as a storekeeper on  May 28th, 2023. Little did she expect the unexpected twist that awaited her when she placed an order for a cheeseburger and fries. Instead of the anticipated treat, the adorable toddler handed her a random moldy bun With a mischievous smile. 

</media:description>
             <media:keywords>store,toddler,playtime,moldy,bun,cheeseburger,fries,imagination,Barrie,Ontario,Canada,laughter,adorable,video,creativity,surprise,make-believe,joy,memory,chuckle</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Barrie, Ontario</media:city>
             <media:country>Canada</media:country>
             <media:category>Heartwarming</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Sun, 28 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2208</guid>
             <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 08:13:07 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/74e45764-8058-48c8-99f0-aa3219399bb3.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/1b78bd31-48ac-40be-9379-a974ec5ddc87.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Cat chaos: Cuppa's tabletop tumble sends plate shattering!</media:title>
             <media:description>In a hilarious and unexpected turn of events, a live-streaming session captured an unforgettable moment between two mischievous cats named Cuppa and Berry. The incident took place on May 24, 2023, in Bekasi City, West Java, Indonesia, and left viewers in stitches. As Cuppa attempted to climb onto the table, a precarious plate teetering on the edge proved to be its downfall. In a split second, the plate crashed to the floor, shattering into countless pieces.

The video shared by @berrybellecat on social media showcased the playful antics of the two feline companions. Little did anyone expect that Cuppa's innocent attempt to reach higher ground would result in such comedic chaos. </media:description>
             <media:keywords>kittens,playfulness,live-streaming,antics,comedy,chaos,mishap,table,plate,breakage,Bekasi City,Indonesia,Cuppa,Berry,mischievous,adorable,curiosity,laughter,fragments,unpredictability.</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Bekasi City</media:city>
             <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
             <media:category>Animals</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Wed, 24 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2206</guid>
             <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 07:21:04 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/361d971e-592e-44a8-8394-8bbb9d243129.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/de3f10f9-f034-4d92-859c-4d7d59e0ce84.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Fury unleashed: a farmer's glimpse into Fuxin's terrifying tornado</media:title>
             <media:description>On June 1st, 2023, in Fuxin City, Northeast China, a farmer named had a harrowing encounter with an extreme weather phenomenon—a tornado. Engaged in his usual work in the field, the author was suddenly taken aback by a powerful gust of wind that swiftly intensified. Gripped by fear, he quickly sought refuge on the ground but managed to capture the awe-inspiring sight on video.

In a matter of moments, the tranquil landscape transformed into a scene of chaos and destruction. The swirling vortex of the tornado tore through the vicinity with unrelenting force.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>tornado,farmer,Fuxin,extreme weather,wind,fear,field,video,chaos,destruction,vortex,trees,debris,devastation,power,unpredictability,nature,fury,vulnerability,resilience</media:keywords>
             <media:city> Fuxin</media:city>
             <media:country>China</media:country>
             <media:category>Weather</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Thu, 1 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2205</guid>
             <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 07:05:33 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/935c7b17-a84f-4379-a3aa-fdb7212f7f0e.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/c1bf59be-6b3c-4868-b829-40a51d77837f.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Destructive fury unleashed: Fuxin City ravaged by terrifying tornado</media:title>
             <media:description>On June 1st, 2023, a terrifying tornado unleashed its destructive fury upon Fuxin City in Northeast China. Captured by a brave individual a video emerged, showcasing the raw power and devastation caused by this natural disaster. Filmed from the safety of a moving car, the footage revealed a large mass of circling winds and dirt, tearing through the city with relentless force.

As the video unfolded, it became evident that Fuxin City was under siege from the menacing tornado. The swirling winds and debris created a chaotic scene. </media:description>
             <media:keywords>tornado,devastation,Fuxin City,Northeast China,video,circling winds,dirt,destruction,brave,chaos,buildings,trees,debris,power,nature,unpredictable,storm,recovery,rebuilding,scars</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Fuxin City</media:city>
             <media:country>China</media:country>
             <media:category>Weather</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Thu, 1 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2203</guid>
             <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 06:53:31 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/499e4c1f-1d2c-4bc1-a8be-57442376d2b9.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/b7aa68b2-7c02-480d-b230-30b31ec8a83b.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Catastrophe in Santa Barbara: a feline's floral fiasco unfolds</media:title>
             <media:description>In a moment of mischief and curiosity, a mischievous feline in Santa Barbara, California, USA, found itself at the center of a floral fiasco that left shattered pieces in its wake. The incident, captured by @tatyana_mironova_real_estate on November 29th, 2022, shows the daring cat playfully pushing a flower pot off the counter, only to watch it plummet to the ground, breaking into several pieces. With a swift turn of its head, the cat's gaze fixates upon the fallen flower pot, seemingly assessing the aftermath of its daring feat.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>mischief,curiosity,feline,floral,fiasco,shattered,pieces,daring,playfully,plummet,broken,aftermath,gaze,fallen,assess,social,media,amused,inquisitive,unpredictable</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Santa Barbara, California</media:city>
             <media:country>United States</media:country>
             <media:category>Animals</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2022</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2202</guid>
             <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 06:24:12 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/6c57cd27-e791-4dd5-bd08-9d851f79d144.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/12065ac0-f624-4b15-a575-5f65869e65a3.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Upside-down feasting: clever parrot's unconventional snack retrieval technique</media:title>
             <media:description>In an adorable display of intelligence and dexterity, a parrot in Aichi, Japan, has astounded its owner with a unique snacking technique. Captured on video by @riyo.05 on May 8, 2023, the feathered companion can be seen using its beak to help itself perch its legs on the lower side of a sofa, effectively turning itself upside down. In this inverted position, the clever parrot skillfully sticks its head into a package to retrieve a tasty treat.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>parrot,treat,package,beak,upside down,sofa,dexterity,intelligence,clever,snack,video,Aichi,Japan,legs,perch,capture,adorable,ingenuity,problem-solving,avian</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Aichi</media:city>
             <media:country>Japan</media:country>
             <media:category>Animals</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Mon, 8 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2200</guid>
             <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 05:22:07 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/80715866-73d2-47ef-8f9f-e51d0ddfeb9c.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/db53ef75-c010-4592-97c1-27f80fd624ca.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Interspecies encounter: squirrel startles seagull, revealing unfriendly neighborhood dynamics</media:title>
             <media:description>
In a fascinating video captured by @belka.ulya on May 24th, 2023, in St. Petersburg, Russia, an unexpected encounter unfolded between a squirrel and a seagull. Perched outside her window, with a glass pane separating the seagull and her squirrel, @belka.ulya decided to bring the squirrel closer to the window to observe the interaction. However, as she approached with the squirrel in hand, the seagull abruptly took flight, displaying signs of fear. The intriguing moment left the author contemplating the coexistence of squirrels and other large birds, as it became evident that they may not be the most friendly neighbors.

The video, captioned "something tells me they are not friendly neighbors," sheds light on the dynamics between these two species. Despite their physical separation by the window, the seagull's swift departure suggests an underlying tension or fear towards the squirrel.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>squirrel,seagull,window,video,encounter,coexist,neighbors,fear,curiosity,wildlife,St. Petersburg,Russia,animals,glass,tension,dynamics,observation,interaction,species,behavior</media:keywords>
             <media:city>St. Petersburg</media:city>
             <media:country>Russia</media:country>
             <media:category>Animals</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Wed, 24 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2194</guid>
             <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 17:54:06 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/84d99477-3253-4882-b2e2-90456f969e36.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2194.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Falling camera: a serendipitous aesthetic mishap</media:title>
             <media:description>In a moment of uncertainty and against the backdrop of cloudy skies and a strong gust of wind in Wonosobo, Indonesia, @shierlya_ found herself capturing an unexpected and breathtaking video on  February 27, 2023. With initial hesitation, she pondered whether it was wise to proceed. However, succumbing to the thrill of the moment, she decided to hit the record button. Little did she know that fate had something extraordinary in store for her.

As the wind picked up, the unexpected occurred - her phone slipped from her grasp and began its descent, inadvertently continuing to record. In a split second, her friends' voices filled the air with a symphony of startled screams. The tumbling phone created a mesmerizing visual spectacle, capturing her friends' movements as if they were falling through the frame. </media:description>
             <media:keywords>cloudy,windy,video,aesthetic,uncertainty,friends,falling,mishap,serendipitous,moment,capture,thrill,descent,screams,spectacle,unexpected,mesmerizing,frame,captivate,awestruck</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Wonosobo</media:city>
             <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
             <media:category>Fails and Funnies</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2193</guid>
             <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 20:49:47 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/9c677eea-7585-42e6-8cdb-7778e8c4c6c9.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/cdf657b2-50a6-49aa-a2e6-2012d310aae8.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Unforgettable barefoot ride: sandal mishap captured in hilarious video</media:title>
             <media:description>A recent video captured in Tasikmalaya, West Java, Indonesia, has taken the internet by storm. The footage, shot by @alwidivraja on January 4th, 2023, shows him driving barefoot after his sandal accidentally fell off and got stuck in another motorbike passing by. In the video, the author can be heard laughing, while the oblivious owner of the other motorbike continues riding, seemingly unaware of the unusual situation.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>driving,barefoot,sandal,mishap,video,laughter,motorbike,stuck,hilarious,capture,Tasikmalaya,West Java,Indonesia,amusing,unexpected,carefree,social media,viral,joy,lighthearted</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Tasikmalaya, West Java</media:city>
             <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
             <media:category>Fails and Funnies</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Wed, 4 Jan 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2185</guid>
             <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 07:14:02 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/98013694-a007-4f14-b5f6-1865a6d09b9c.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/6c76aee7-e75d-4b22-ae86-afc25b30e53b.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Chaos at Nagoya Station: dangerous congestion captured in video at Shinkansen Ticket Gate</media:title>
             <media:description>Nagoya Station in Aichi, Japan, was engulfed in chaos on June 3rd, 2023, as a video captured by @B8BXHzu6CLcP52V revealed dangerous levels of congestion. The footage showed a swarm of people crammed together at the Nagoya Station Shinkansen ticket gate, painting a vivid picture of the overwhelming situation.

The heavy congestion portrayed in the video raises significant concerns about public safety and highlights the urgent need for improved crowd management measures. </media:description>
             <media:keywords>congestion,danger,Nagoya,Aichi,Japan,video,crowded,chaos,public safety,risk,transportation,commuters,overcrowding,personnel,crowd control,protocols,communication,authorities,ticket gate,Shinkansen,footage</media:keywords>
             <media:city> Nagoya, Aichi</media:city>
             <media:country>Japan</media:country>
             <media:category>News</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Sat, 3 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2183</guid>
             <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 06:26:25 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/90bb272c-7652-4ad8-991d-59c6f390d33c.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/283bfd2c-3849-4d40-89fd-f0eb6a15d5ef.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Devastating tornado approaching Samara: severe weather wreaks havoc</media:title>
             <media:description>On Friday, June 2, 2023, the Samara region in Russia experienced a rapid deterioration in weather conditions. Thunderstorms and heavy rain battered the area, causing concern among residents. The situation escalated when reports emerged of a tornado spotted in the Kinelsky district, heading towards the city of Samara.

Eyewitnesses recounted the sequence of events, stating that it all began with the sighting of a massive dust column in the village of Domashka. The swirling phenomenon gradually moved towards Barinovka, gaining strength and intensity along the way. Residents between Barinovka and Dmitrievka were the next to witness the tornado's awe-inspiring display. Presently, according to accounts from locals, the tornado is steadily advancing towards the city of Samara, heightening concerns for the safety and well-being of those in its path.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>thunderstorms,heavy rain,tornado,Samara region,weather deterioration,Kinelsky district,dust column,Barinovka,Dmitrievka,approaching,residents,concern,sequence,intensity,awe-inspiring,advancing,safety,precautions,emergency response,community</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Samara region</media:city>
             <media:country>Russia</media:country>
             <media:category>Weather</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Fri, 2 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2181</guid>
             <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 02:13:41 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/ae5023da-6a01-4aab-a65e-746d22e05425.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/80238bc9-4ded-461d-bfc1-0ea57b068b6d.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Mysterious water trench intruder: cat's nap halts the flow!</media:title>
             <media:description>In a quiet town of Kluang, Malaysia, a peculiar incident unfolded as a resident, @zurlhairy, discovered an unexpected obstruction in a water trench behind her house. On the fateful day of April 22, 2023, perplexed by the stagnant water, she ventured out to investigate the cause of the immobility.

As the author approached the middle of the trench, her curiosity was met with a heartwarming sight. Nestled comfortably in the trench, oblivious to its role in impeding the water's movement, was a feline companion. The sleeping cat stirred awake at the approaching footsteps but showed no signs of relinquishing its cozy spot.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>cat,water,trench,sleeping,obstruction,Kluang,Malaysia,video,peaceful,unaware,flow,halfway,snuggling,nap,stagnant,curiosity,tranquil,feline,online,amusement</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Kluang</media:city>
             <media:country>Malaysia</media:country>
             <media:category>Animals</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Sat, 22 Apr 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2180</guid>
             <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 20:14:14 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/96feb834-742d-4eb3-9269-335a68cccf00.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/d47eb2ec-3a40-4011-aecf-d5375ef16287.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Feline freedom fiesta: cats compete in treat-licking contest to celebrate Indonesia's Independence Day</media:title>
             <media:description>In a heartwarming display of feline patriotism, a viral video captured the spirited competition among cats to commemorate Indonesia's Independence Day. Filmed by @wulandapriliani on August 17, 2022, in Pauh, Sarolagun, Jambi, Indonesia, the footage showcases the playful yet competitive nature of these furry participants. The video reveals a unique contest where the cats engage in a treat-licking challenge, adding an adorable twist to the celebration.

With treats hanging enticingly in a line, the cats eagerly lick their treats, attempting to be the first to finish. </media:description>
             <media:keywords>cats,competition,treats,clicking,video,viral,patriotism,Indonesia,Independence Day,feline,contest,licking,Pauh,Sarolagun,Jambi,adorable,playful,unity,pets,celebration,bond</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Pauh, Sarolagun, Jambi</media:city>
             <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
             <media:category>Animals</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Wed, 17 Aug 2022</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2179</guid>
             <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 19:55:12 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/931447d1-9b79-4a35-8256-7bb02984dabf.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/b6fd8e7d-db7e-4caf-b45d-4ae2149e2058.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Feisty feline defends favorite find: Pandora's passion for bras unleashed</media:title>
             <media:description>In a heartwarming yet slightly puzzling incident, a cat named Pandora has shown an unwavering affection for a rather unconventional item: bras. A video captured by @chausie_pandora on January 11th, 2023, in Moscow, Russia, showcases Pandora's intense attachment to these undergarments. According to her owner, Pandora's love for bras knows no bounds, and once she gets her paws on one, it becomes an irrevocable possession.

The video reveals a glimpse into the battle between owner and feline over the cherished bra. The author bravely attempts to retrieve the garment, only to be met with fierce resistance from Pandora. The cat displays defensive behavior, actively tying to claw at her owner's hands in an effort to protect her prized possession. It's clear that Pandora's possessiveness over the bra has sparked a protective instinct, leading to an unexpected display of aggression.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>cat,bra,Pandora,video,Moscow,Russia,affection,love,possession,irrevocable,aggression,scratching,defensive,owner,feline,unique,obsession,amused,netizens,struggle,cherished</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Moscow </media:city>
             <media:country>Russia</media:country>
             <media:category>Animals</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2176</guid>
             <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 05:43:45 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/17e22521-b8d2-4a67-8f60-6fb8f32f3b42.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/1689e156-899f-4ed0-b815-90ad9898552e.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Intense duel: fierce canine clash over a chicken bone</media:title>
             <media:description>
In a captivating video captured by @richy_kira_thesalchis on May 3rd, 2023, in Santiago, Chile, two dogs engaged in a fierce growling battle over a single chicken bone. The dogs, both gripping one end of the bone, had their snouts touching as they vied for control. It all began when the author was in the process of cutting chicken for her beloved pets, and a chicken leg accidentally slipped from her grasp and fell. She realized that the dogs had taken the leg and had it in their mouths.

As soon as the author realized what had occurred, she quickly grabbed her camera to document the extraordinary scene unfolding before her eyes. The two dogs, determined not to let go of the precious bone, growled intensely at each other, their teeth clamped down firmly. Their fierce expressions and snarling noises painted a picture of rivalry and desire.

Realizing the potential danger and the need to intervene, the author bravely stepped in and took the bone away from the feuding canines. </media:description>
             <media:keywords>dogs,growling,chicken bone,rivalry,intense,video,capture,snouts,biting,duel,pets,instinct,domesticated,companions,confrontation,canines,fierce,gripping,determined,danger</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Santiago</media:city>
             <media:country>Chile</media:country>
             <media:category>Animals</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Wed, 3 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2175</guid>
             <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 05:24:42 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/8f8ca88a-6039-432f-aff8-e1487765bab6.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/aaf6d75d-31ad-4fe6-ba48-844ab6d32579.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Fire erupts during well repair at Severo-Labatyuganskoye field in Russia</media:title>
             <media:description>An explosion rattled the Severo-Labatyuganskoye field in the Surgut district of the Khanty-Mansiysk Autonomous region, Russia, as repair work was underway on a well. The incident occurred on 30th May, 2023, during which a fire broke out, damaging the body of the lifting unit of a car. Fortunately, the oil workers at the site managed to extinguish the fire before the arrival of the fire service, averting any casualties or injuries.

The Ministry of Emergency Situations reported that the fire had engulfed an area measuring approximately 0.5 square meters. Although the flames were successfully brought under control, investigators are now working diligently to establish the cause of the fire. The Severo-Labatyuganskoye field, being developed by Surgutneftegaz, is known for its significant oil reserves and plays a crucial role in Russia's energy sector.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>explosion,repair,well,fire,damage,car,workers,extinguished,arrival,firefighters,Ministry,Emergency Situations,cause,investigators,Severo-Labatyuganskoye,field,Surgutneftegaz,Khanty-Mansi,Autonomous Okrug,Russia</media:keywords>
             <media:city> Khanty-Mansiysk autonomous region</media:city>
             <media:country>Russia</media:country>
             <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Tue, 30 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2174</guid>
             <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 04:59:59 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/c945f894-5d73-40df-bbe5-bef926de87e7.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/df9ebb47-e472-4bb5-a3d5-338f8ff6aa36.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Cart-tastrophe in Boyolali: hilarious overload lifts cart and spirits!</media:title>
             <media:description>In a comical turn of events that left onlookers in stitches, a recent video captured in Boyolali, Indonesia has gone viral. The footage, recorded by @ariwibowo7224 on December 24, 2022, showcases a light-hearted incident involving an overloaded hand-pulled cart . Fortunately, no one was harmed during the incident, and the unexpected turn of events resulted in uncontrollable laughter from the amused bystanders. The traditional cart, which was overloaded with wood, lifted up the author's friend as he tried to pull it.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>overloaded,cart,wood,hand-pulled,lifted,friend,video,mishap,laughter,incident,humor,Boyolali,Indonesia,lighthearted,unexpected,hilarious,bystanders,amused,noharm,laughter</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Boyolali</media:city>
             <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
             <media:category>Fails and Funnies</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Sat, 24 Dec 2022</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2173</guid>
             <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 04:26:57 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2a7dde6e-b6f6-49af-9640-22a8ea07d6c3.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2e36dc55-9644-4c10-9906-ce3911ae2653.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Miraculous escape: lone boat circles on Kama River as navigator survives being thrown overboard</media:title>
             <media:description>In a dramatic incident on June 1st, 2023, emergency services in the Republic of Tatarstan, Russia, received a distress call about a solitary boat drifting aimlessly on the Kama River. The boat's engine was still running, but no occupants were found onboard or in the water nearby. Upon arrival at the scene, inspectors from the Chistopol inspection department, part of the Center for GIMS of the Ministry of Emergency Situations, uncovered the truth behind the mystery. It appeared that the navigator had been forcefully thrown out of the boat by a powerful wave. Fortunately, the individual managed to swim to safety along the shore.

The rescuers promptly towed the unmanned boat back to land, ensuring it didn't pose any further risk or become a hazard to others navigating the river. The Ministry of Emergency Situations took the opportunity to issue a vital safety reminder to boat owners and enthusiasts. Regardless of their level of experience, it is crucial to always have a boat motor safety check in place. This simple accessory, whether attached to one's hand or securely fastened to clothing, can be a lifesaver in situations where the boat operator unexpectedly falls overboard.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>boat,circling,water,incident,Kama River,Chistopol embankment,Markina Street,engine,people,inspectors,GIMS,Ministry of Emergency Situations,Tatarstan,Russia,navigator,thrown,wave,rescuers,towed,safety</media:keywords>
             <media:city> Republic of Tatarstan</media:city>
             <media:country>Russia</media:country>
             <media:category>News</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Thu, 1 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2172</guid>
             <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 04:07:03 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/fc0d68aa-0aa2-4628-995e-0959e868fb37.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/f58807ab-8d63-41f9-b0aa-8ee3cce7f628.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Terrifying encounter: polar bear narrowly misses attacking snowmobilers in Yakutia, Russia</media:title>
             <media:description>
In a heart-stopping incident in Yakutia, Russia, a polar bear nearly attacked a group of snowmobilers as they made their way to the village of Bykov. The encounter took place on the 31st of May, 2023, as the bear ran alongside the moving snowmobile, closely eyeing the people. Suddenly, it darted towards the sleigh where a passenger was seated, coming perilously close to biting him. The shocking moment was captured on video by a witness, who could only manage to shout out in alarm. Fortunately, the animal missed its target, leaving the snowmobilers shaken but unharmed.

Polar bears, known for their powerful land locomotion, can reach speeds of up to 40 km/h, making them formidable creatures capable of chasing down snowmobiles. Such encounters pose a significant risk to drivers and passengers, as demonstrated in this incident. While the motive behind the bear's actions remains unclear, it is speculated that the animal may have intended to frighten the people rather than actively attack them.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>polar bear,snowmobilers,Yakutia,Russia,Tiksi Bulunsky ulus,village,Bykov,chase,passenger,sleigh,attack,video,encounter,frightening,alarm,danger,remote,caution,wildlife,adrenaline</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Yakutia</media:city>
             <media:country>Russia</media:country>
             <media:category>Animals</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Wed, 31 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2170</guid>
             <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 03:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/814bafc6-05c6-4bbb-b43e-b73ebe43cbdc.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2170.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Battle against Tantallon wildfire intensifies as crews strive for control amid volatile conditions</media:title>
             <media:description>A wildfire that has ravaged the suburb of Tantallon, Nova Scotia, for the past four days is finally showing signs of containment. As of May 31st, 2023, the blaze, which has spread across 837 hectares of land encompassing Upper Tantallon, Hammonds Plains, and Pockwock, is now 50 percent contained. However, officials remain cautious, emphasizing the ongoing volatile and dangerous nature of the situation. Dave Steeves from the Nova Scotia Department of Natural Resources emphasized the importance of maintaining safety precautions, especially with hot and dry weather conditions expected on Thursday. The heat, coupled with wind speeds and humidity levels, poses a serious threat to the firefighting efforts.

Despite the progress made in containing the wildfire, officials are far from declaring victory over the relentless inferno. Dave Steeves, speaking from the incident command center in Upper Tantallon, stressed that the decrease in the fire's size does not equate to a decrease in the importance of safety. The unpredictable nature of the blaze, combined with soaring temperatures reaching the 30s, could lead to rapid and aggressive fire spread. The region is currently experiencing a "crossover" situation, with relative humidity levels nearing the forecasted temperature, exacerbating the risk. Every precaution is being taken to ensure the safety of firefighters and the public.

@baileyballum, who captured an aerial view of the Tantallon fire from an aircraft on May 31st, 2023, offers a visual view of the extend of the damage caused by the fire.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>wildfire,containment,dangerous,volatile,precautions,hot,dry,Halifax,Nova Scotia,suburbs,Tantallon,fire,spread,heat,crossover,humidity,wind,crews,battle,aerial view</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Tantallon, Nova Scotia</media:city>
             <media:country>Canada</media:country>
             <media:category>News</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Wed, 31 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2169</guid>
             <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 18:19:34 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/27558e70-9ed7-427b-a9f8-ccf26582f51c.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/b469091a-2a57-45f2-b752-5d1f5be51071.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Quick thinking saves the day: daughter's cool response stops stove fire</media:title>
             <media:description>In a remarkable display of composure and quick thinking, a young girl in Thái Bình province, Vietnam, averted a potential disaster when a fire broke out in her kitchen. The incident, captured by @ngothanhlam123456789 on April 8th, 2023, showcased the bravery and level-headedness of the daughter as she handled the situation with remarkable poise.

As the video footage reveals, the girl was cooking alone when the stove suddenly burst into flames. Instead of panicking, she immediately started looking for a way to put out the fire. Demonstrating her resourcefulness, she swiftly sought out a nearby fan to disperse the smoke and prevent the flames from spreading further. Miraculously, thanks to her calm and decisive actions, the fire was contained, with only the food falling victim to the incident.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>cooking,fire,stove,daughter,home,calm,quick-thinking,safety,protection,bravery,composure,resourcefulness,fan,smoke,emergency,incident,food,camera,thái bình,vietnam</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Quỳnh Phụ, Thái Bình province</media:city>
             <media:country>Vietnam</media:country>
             <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Fri, 7 Apr 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2167</guid>
             <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 17:30:35 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/cbe312de-92d8-4a3c-8ce3-d03f397363cc.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/18dedc10-1680-47cc-b710-a59d6aa14968.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Playful dog's spirited encounter with brother turns into a lively game in Buon Ma Thuot City</media:title>
             <media:description>In a captivating video captured by @le_xuanthao on April 11th, 2023, in Buon Ma Thuot City, Vietnam, a seemingly intense encounter between a dog and a person took an unexpected turn. As the person, who happened to be the owner's brother, entered the compound on a motorbike, the dog initially came running to the brother. The vigilant owner swiftly positioned himself between the dog and his brother, attempting to deter any harm. However, the dog persisted in its playful pursuit, circling around the person with uncontainable excitement.

To match the dog's exuberant antics, the brother displayed impressive agility, skillfully jumping from one side of the motorbike to the other. Although in the video the dog appeared hostile, the dog's intentions were not hostile, but rather a spirited invitation to play. Eventually, the dog's energy waned, and it joyfully disengaged from the interaction,</media:description>
             <media:keywords>dog,attack,video,Buon Ma Thuot City,Vietnam,owner,gate,motorbike,compound,deter,round,person,jumping,persistent,relent,protect,confrontation,fearless,footage,incident</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Buon Ma Thuot City</media:city>
             <media:country>Vietnam</media:country>
             <media:category>Animals</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2166</guid>
             <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 16:56:31 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/96e54591-1ef5-453b-82eb-c4ab17122b1b.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/37a362c5-990f-4097-bb38-8a3b14df0107.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>A serene escape turned into a close call: a local gardener saves belongings from rising waters</media:title>
             <media:description>In a tranquil escape to the upper area of La Ngâu Stream in Tánh Linh District, Bình Thuận Province, Vietnam, @_thien1409 found himself in a heart-stopping situation on May 16th, 2023. The picturesque location seemed like the perfect spot to unwind and soak in the beauty of nature. Little did he know that his peaceful retreat would turn into a race against time to save his belongings from the rapidly rising waters.

As @_thien1409 briefly left his spot near the riverbed to retrieve his belongings from his car, nature unleashed its fury. The water levels began to surge, threatening to wash away everything he had left behind. Fortunately, a local gardener happened to be nearby and noticed the perilous situation. Acting swiftly, the gardener bravely waded through the rising currents and managed to rescue @_thien1409's belongings, sparing them from being swept away by the unforgiving waters.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>serene,river,video,belongings,car,water,nature,environment,local,farmer,rescue,safety,escape,rising,rapidly,close call,race,time,threat,community</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Tánh Linh District, Bình Thuận Province</media:city>
             <media:country>Vietnam</media:country>
             <media:category>Weather</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Tue, 16 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2165</guid>
             <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 16:26:42 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/56842024-146b-4626-a311-5bd3532edda8.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/5cf0cbb0-15c3-44a6-9a47-ef6e5f137aef.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Alberta braces against relentless hailstorm assault as nature unleashes its fury</media:title>
             <media:description>In a stunning display of nature's power, Alberta, Canada found itself under siege from a relentless hailstorm. On the 31st of May, 2023, residents witnessed a disaster as large hailstones pounded homes and streets. A video captured by @SeskaFuze_ showcased the intensity of the storm, with the caption "Crazy hailstorm here. Sheeeesh. Power/internet is out."

The footage revealed the sheer force with which the hailstones descended upon the area. </media:description>
             <media:keywords>hailstorm,alberta,canada,weather,nature,destruction,intensity,power,internet,video,footage,storm,damage,force,awe,concern,community,resilience,recovery,aftermath</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Alberta </media:city>
             <media:country>Canada</media:country>
             <media:category>Weather</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Wed, 31 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2164</guid>
             <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 15:58:17 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/45c1bd2c-e188-4203-957a-a0ec0b691a4c.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/a02ba01a-5621-4846-8961-d0b689741b87.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Caught on camera: brazen thief strikes at Milky Way milk tea shop in Hanoi, Vietnam</media:title>
             <media:description>A shocking incident unfolded at the Milky Way milk tea shop located in Hai Ba Trung, Hanoi, Vietnam, as captured in a video shared by @toanphungdeyy on 11th May 2023. The footage shows a brazen thief snatching a phone from the shop's counter while the staff was preoccupied with preparing foodstuffs to serve customers. Taking advantage of the understaffed situation, the thief patiently waited on a bench until the staff member turned their attention away, allowing for the opportune moment to strike. Despite their efforts, the shop owner and staff were unable to apprehend the culprit.

According to the owner, that particular day witnessed a severe shortage of staff, leaving him with no choice but to leave only one person at the counter. Unfortunately, this created the perfect scenario for the thief to carry out their nefarious act. However, there was a silver lining to the incident, as the stolen phone was eventually returned to its rightful owner.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>theft,video,shop,snatching,phone,counter,staff,serving,thief,bench,opportunity,understaffed,Hanoi,Vietnam,owner,returned,caught,brazen,incident,security</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Hai Ba Trung, Hanoi</media:city>
             <media:country>Vietnam</media:country>
             <media:category>News</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Thu, 11 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2158</guid>
             <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 05:19:32 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/5a1b9b9b-c159-47b6-840d-316115b3f477.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/6812fecc-9d12-4b4d-b5d2-47fa9de2ddd9.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Father's love triumphs: heartwarming reconciliation with daughter over safety concerns</media:title>
             <media:description>In a heartwarming incident captured on video in Kendari City, South East Sulawesi, Indonesia, a concerned father was seen persuading his young daughter against crossing a busy road alone. The video, taken by user @gorogo_14 on May 23, 2023, showcases a tender moment between the father and his determined little girl. Despite her eagerness to explore a place filled with enchanting lights across the road, her father rightfully forbade her, emphasizing the potential dangers. Frustrated by his refusal, the girl refused to communicate with her father and turned away whenever he attempted to engage her face to face.

The video demonstrates the father's unwavering commitment to his daughter's safety. He patiently engages with her, explaining the risks involved in crossing the road independently. His persistence pays off as the young girl eventually agrees to converse with him. Overwhelmed by her father's love, she embraces him tightly, signaling their reconciliation. With their bond reaffirmed, the father scoops her up into his arms and they walk away together.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>father,daughter,road,safety,video,love,communication,parenting,concern,reconciliation,hug,persuasion,refusal,danger,trust,bonding,guidance,lights,capture,emotions</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Kendari City, South East Sulawesi</media:city>
             <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
             <media:category>Heartwarming</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Tue, 23 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2157</guid>
             <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 04:45:49 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/6042ac19-2173-4619-a4e3-6886625dcbbe.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/ad8c6c94-02d8-4121-9532-4a436b86ecc1.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Captivating discovery: stunning schools of fish thrive beneath coastal house </media:title>
             <media:description>In a mesmerizing video captured by @dindabajoe on May 19, 2023, in Central Sulawesi Province, Indonesia, an incredible sight unfolded beneath the floor of his coastal house. Built over the shimmering sea, the author lifted one of the wooden blocks that formed the house's floor, revealing an astonishing scene of large schools of small fish. The crystal-clear, blue water showcased the fish swimming gracefully, a sight that left the author pleasantly surprised.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>schools,fish,video,coastal,house,sea,wooden,blocks,floor,surprise,crystal,blue,water,mesmerizing,Indonesia,Central Sulawesi Province,marine,ecosystem,vibrant,interconnectedness</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Central Sulawesi Province</media:city>
             <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
             <media:category>Cool</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Fri, 19 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2155</guid>
             <pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 17:05:36 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/1764a5b8-b043-4216-8f27-d146e48f6cd1.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/ba5c44b7-f6fc-422f-88cb-ff18a5a3122a.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>The breakfast stampede: roaring fork ridgebacks' pups dash for delight</media:title>
             <media:description>In a heartwarming video captured by @roaringforkridgebacks on April 6th, 2023, in Dallas, Texas, USA, a pack of adorable Ridgeback puppies stole the show as they sprinted towards their breakfast. With the door swung wide open, their excited paws pounded the floor as they eagerly made their way to the designated breakfast area. The area was thoughtfully divided, ensuring each pup had their own bowl and space to enjoy their meal.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>puppies,breakfast,running,bulls,video,adorable,Ridgebacks,Texas,Dallas,USA,door,excitement,chaos,enthusiastic,love,food,heartwarming,furry companions,joy,pets</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Dallas, Texas</media:city>
             <media:country>United States</media:country>
             <media:category>Animals</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Thu, 6 Apr 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2154</guid>
             <pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 16:47:00 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/84323b6a-5b91-429a-8239-9d01879b225c.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/e9856778-4c23-4001-8db3-292baf04f115.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Bamboo bliss: adorable panda finds unusual dining style in Guangzhou!</media:title>
             <media:description>In a heartwarming scene captured by @Panda'sSlowLife, a renowned panda video photographer, a panda in Guangzhou, South China, was spotted enjoying a delightful meal of bamboo shoots while lying on its back. The adorable moment, captured on the 23rd of May, 2023, showcases the unique dining style of this furry creature.

The author, who specializes in filming the lives of pandas, was drawn to the panda's living area that afternoon. The sight of the panda munching on bamboo in such a charming manner was simply irresistible. With his camera ready, he filmed this captivating video, highlighting the sheer cuteness of the panda as it relished its meal while reclining on its back.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>panda,bamboo,shoots,video,photographer,Guangzhou,South China,cute,adorable,filming,living area,afternoon,munching,charming,reclining,endearing,surprising,gentle,giants,captivating</media:keywords>
             <media:city> Guangzhou</media:city>
             <media:country>China</media:country>
             <media:category>Heartwarming</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Tue, 23 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2153</guid>
             <pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 16:22:31 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/6b7feb5b-eb6f-4bc8-b753-a0ac40717eac.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/7f9c0da6-4841-4ba1-a35c-8837f5218066.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Close call: driver narrowly avoids collision with three cows on dark road in Jiangxi Province</media:title>
             <media:description>In a heart-stopping incident captured on video, a driver in Jiangxi Province, East China, had a close encounter with three cows on a dark road. The incident took place on the 24th of May, 2023, as the driver, who goes by the online handle @Can'taffordextremekryptonahsuper, was returning home after having dinner with friends. With few cars on the road at that late hour, he was navigating a particularly dimly lit section when the unexpected occurred.

As the driver approached a bend, three cows suddenly materialized on the road, catching him off guard. Reacting quickly, he slammed on the brakes, narrowly avoiding a collision with the bovine trio. The cows, seemingly unfazed by the near miss, calmly moved to the side of the road, allowing the driver to pass by safely. Thankfully, no one was injured in the incident.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>close call,video,driver,cows,road,night,dinner,friends,brakes,missed,dark,Jiangxi Province,East China,online,handle,unexpected,hazard,rural,reflexes,incident</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Jiangxi Province</media:city>
             <media:country>China</media:country>
             <media:category>News</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Wed, 24 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2151</guid>
             <pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 15:43:54 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/766a9f22-7941-40b7-812e-bd8e6f1c8abe.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/75a7e78b-9aa7-4d8f-86d9-1c1be6f0b1d4.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Unsuspecting passersby's goofy encounter with Goofy at Disneyland's Tower of Terror</media:title>
             <media:description>In a comical turn of events at Disneyland's Tower of Terror in Anaheim, California, USA, an unsuspecting woman encountered a sight that left her screaming and running for safety. On the 8th of May, 2023, as @morganmcnulty captured a footage of Goofy showing her a rubber chicken standing beside two pillars, a passerby was unaware of Goofy's presence as she was walking leading to an unexpected reaction.

As the woman passed by she turned around to find Goofy right beside the two pillars, holding out the rubber chicken, pure panic took hold. She let out a shriek that quickly caught the attention of others nearby. </media:description>
             <media:keywords>disneyland,anaheim,california,usa,goofy,filming,tower of terror,chicken rubber,prank,passerby,screaming,running,surprise,amusement,innocent,playful,encounter,reaction,bewildered,panic</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Anaheim, California</media:city>
             <media:country>United States</media:country>
             <media:category>Fails and Funnies</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Mon, 8 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2150</guid>
             <pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 15:25:54 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/d8ad1af0-7c84-4c23-a15b-b6911aa14ece.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2150.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Whisker whispers: the hilarious bedtime delivery!</media:title>
             <media:description>A heartwarming and hilarious moment was captured on video by @harryandeva from Adelaide, Australia, on the 21st of May, 2023. The footage shows her husband carrying a cat wrapped in a cozy comforter, cleverly mimicking the act of carrying a baby. 

As her husband gently placed the cat on her arms, a resident dog, already snuggled up and awaiting bedtime, couldn't resist the temptation. With affectionate licks, the dog enthusiastically welcomed the newest member of the bedtime crew. The heartwarming scene showcased the incredible bond between pets and their human companions, leaving @harryandeva in stitches as she aptly captioned the video, "when you tell your husband you are ready for bed and he delivers the goods."</media:description>
             <media:keywords>bedtime,surprise,cat,comforter,husband,delivery,goods,video,Adelaide,Australia,pet,dog,bond,laughter,joy,moment,heartwarming,affectionate,snuggled,companions</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Adelaide</media:city>
             <media:country>Australia</media:country>
             <media:category>Animals</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Sun, 21 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2147</guid>
             <pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 13:29:58 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/8557b920-df15-43c7-b7a7-ccad19e413cb.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/37d075b3-3380-4391-a48a-5b3fb9c3b9ec.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Adorable under-table pizza begging: hilarious canine surprise leaves diners in stitches!</media:title>
             <media:description>In a heartwarming and amusing scene captured in Oregon, USA, a video shared by @bri_nolan34 on May 8th, 2023, showcases an incredibly clever and food-loving dog. The short clip shows a furry companion sticking its muzzle through a hole underneath a table, eagerly seeking a delicious treat. Without hesitation, a piece of pizza is passed through the same opening, leaving the dog's face hidden but its excitement palpable. The sight instantly sparked laughter and joy among the diners present, turning an ordinary meal into an unforgettable and hilarious experience.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>dog,pizza,muzzle,hole,table,laughter,diners,adorable,clever,food-loving,hidden,excitement,joy,furry,treat,hilarious,video,capture,surprise,companionship</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Oregon</media:city>
             <media:country>United States</media:country>
             <media:category>Fails and Funnies</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Mon, 8 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2146</guid>
             <pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 13:07:27 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/1d382034-5bea-4a97-ac01-56036dfa32d0.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/dacc1410-8635-4330-8589-111913431688.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Feline felicity: a heartwarming homecoming meow!</media:title>
             <media:description>In a heartwarming moment captured on video, a cat from Boston, USA, demonstrated its boundless excitement as the door swung open to welcome its human companions. Shared by @big.al.fred on April 28, 2023, the footage showcases the feline's instantaneous transformation from a couch-dwelling slumberer to an energetic runner. With the caption, "When the gang is home for the weekend volume up to hear my big hello!!," the video reveals the cat dashing towards the open door, emitting a series of enthusiastic meows. The man entering the house was quick to scoop up the delighted feline, creating an endearing reunion that warms the hearts of viewers.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>cat,homecoming,excitement,video,Boston,USA,door,welcome,weekend,meow,loud,man,pick,sleepy,couch,dash,feline,companions,adorable,heartwarming</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Boston </media:city>
             <media:country>United States</media:country>
             <media:category>Animals</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2145</guid>
             <pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 12:52:01 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/bc9d8cdc-32ff-4981-8622-1bac8f4594eb.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/963ee331-53b8-44bf-9267-034364366953.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Storm in Ufa: ventilation duct collapse crushes parked car</media:title>
             <media:description>A severe storm in Ufa, Russia on 29th May, 2023, wreaked havoc in the Sosny residential complex as a ventilation duct from a high-rise building was demolished, resulting in a parked car being crushed under the debris. The alarming incident was captured on surveillance cameras, and images circulated on social media showing the extent of the damage. Fortunately, the Ufa Civil Protection Department confirmed that there were no casualties as a result of the incident.

In response to the incident, representatives from the Office of Civil Protection of Ufa and the administration of the Leninsky district swiftly arrived at the scene to assess the situation. Their primary objective is to determine the causes and circumstances that led to the ventilation duct's collapse. </media:description>
             <media:keywords>storm,Ufa,Russia,Sosny residential complex,ventilation duct,demolished,debris,car,surveillance cameras,crushed,Civil Protection Department,no casualties,Office of Civil Protection,Leninsky district,causes,circumstances,investigation,incident,fallen,high-rise building,social media</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Ufa </media:city>
             <media:country>Russia</media:country>
             <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Mon, 29 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2144</guid>
             <pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 12:30:55 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/da1341f5-5543-452e-82d4-faf619f1689d.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/89f87dd8-a932-4b44-bef0-ef185fef52a4.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title> Clever Chicago dog captivates owner by waving for treats on home camera!</media:title>
             <media:description>In a heartwarming display of intelligence and adorable antics, a dog in Chicago, USA named Pecan has become an internet sensation after her owner captured a video of her waving on a home camera on 25th April, 2023. The footage, shared on social media by user @onegoodnut, shows Pecan seated on her hind legs, diligently moving her front legs up and down as if she were waving to the camera. It turns out that Pecan has cleverly figured out that this gesture prompts her owner to watch the camera feed and reward her with a treat.

Pecan's remarkable behavior can be attributed to her exposure to a camera, which her owner uses to keep an eye on her while away at work. Over time, the smart canine has learned that when she waves to the camera, it notifies her owner, who promptly watches the feed and responds by giving her a well-deserved treat. In the captured video, Pecan's persistence pays off as her owner quickly notices her adorable wave and promptly sends her a reward.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>dog,waving,home camera,Pecan,treats,smart,Furbo,Chicago,USA,video,adorable,intelligence,internet,sensation,social media,owner,reward,persistence,bond,affection</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Chicago </media:city>
             <media:country>United States</media:country>
             <media:category>Animals</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Tue, 25 Apr 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2143</guid>
             <pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 11:43:59 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/0314d6ae-5ef3-45b8-a691-36896c779405.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/bab94367-f4c3-42af-bec9-5c866d9f41c1.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Drones strike Moscow residential buildings, causing damage but no serious injuries</media:title>
             <media:description>
In a series of alarming incidents, drones targeted residential buildings in Moscow, Russia on 30th May, 2023 causing damage but fortunately resulting in no serious injuries. The first incident occurred on Profsoyuznaya Street, where a drone crashed into the 16th floor, causing destruction to the building's facade and shattering windows. The second incident took place on Leninsky Prospekt, as a drone penetrated an apartment on the 14th floor but failed to explode. Lastly, on Atlasova Street in New Moscow, a drone collided with a 24-story building, triggering an explosion within the high-rise structure, according to reports from the Ministry of Emergencies cited by TASS. Moscow Mayor Sergei Sobyanin assured the public that although the attacks caused minor damages to the buildings, no individuals were seriously harmed.

Authorities in Moscow are now focusing on investigating the origins and motives behind these incidents. </media:description>
             <media:keywords>drones,residential,buildings,Moscow,Russia,attacks,damage,no injuries,Profsoyuznaya Street,Leninsky Prospekt,Atlasova Street,New Moscow,explosion,facade,shattered windows,investigation,authorities,security measures,vigilance,safety</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Moscow </media:city>
             <media:country>Russia</media:country>
             <media:category>News</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Tue, 30 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2140</guid>
             <pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 10:34:18 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/f0d8d180-d894-45a7-812e-3bcda1d1c169.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/3f4ed309-b055-4fef-9dda-45af5630524c.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Playful parrot: Freek's Coca-Cola serenade demands attention!</media:title>
             <media:description>In a delightful display of avian intelligence, a parrot named Freek from Rotterdam, Netherlands, recently caught the attention of its owner, @parrotfreek. Captured on May 18th, 2023, in a video that has since gone viral, Freek can be seen perched on the kitchen countertop, holding a Coca-Cola can in its beak and rhythmically patting it against the surface. The boisterous noise emitted from the clinking can was a clear cry for attention from the clever bird.

The footage showcases Freek's playful nature and his unique way of communicating with his human companions. As the parrot expertly taps the can, it is evident that he has learned that this action garners the desired response.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>parrot,freek,coca-cola,video,attention,kitchen,top,noise,can,patting,intelligence,Rotterdam,Netherlands,playful,viral,communication,clever,bird,owner,captivating,bond</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Rotterdam</media:city>
             <media:country>Netherlands</media:country>
             <media:category>Animals</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Thu, 18 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2139</guid>
             <pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2023 18:11:05 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/ab8016b1-740f-4adc-889b-e440d60db8a4.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/fb2541a9-0fc1-4b76-bab1-19d3567b235d.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Unfolding love: crafting a heart through book folding</media:title>
             <media:description>In a mesmerizing display of creativity, @d.hinklay, a talented origami artist from Tokyo, Japan, recently shared a captivating video showcasing the intricate process of transforming a simple book into a stunning heart-shaped sculpture. The video, filmed on December 1st, 2022, takes viewers on a journey from the initial folds to the final reveal of the completed masterpiece.

The author's skilled hands delicately manipulate the pages of the book, meticulously folding and shaping them into a work of art. With each fold, the heart takes form, gradually emerging from the once-unassuming pages. The mesmerizing time-lapse captures the artist's dedication and precision, as the transformation unfolds.

By the end of the video, the book is magically transformed into a symbol of love—a beautifully crafted heart sculpture. </media:description>
             <media:keywords>art,creativity,bookfolding,sculpture,craftsmanship,transformation,love,talent,Tokyo,Japan,video,pages,folding,process,mesmerizing,hands,precision,time-lapse,symbol,ingenuity</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Tokyo </media:city>
             <media:country>Japan</media:country>
             <media:category>Cool</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Thu, 1 Dec 2022</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2138</guid>
             <pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2023 17:55:07 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/5b0e37b4-c7cb-40aa-b226-91b219785ce0.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/a4ba40bf-40cd-4ffc-995f-bb617ecd4f71.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Incredible infinity: mesmerizing origami sculpture unveiled without cutting paper</media:title>
             <media:description>In a captivating display of artistic mastery in Tokyo, Japan, @d.hinklay astounded viewers with a mesmerizing video capturing the creation of an infinity origami sculpture. The renowned artist emphasized that no cuts were made to the paper throughout the entire process, showcasing the true essence of the Japanese art form. Origami, the ancient practice of folding paper, has evolved to encompass various cultures worldwide.

@d.hinklay's video captured on November 4th, 2022 offers a step-by-step journey into the intricate world of origami. Beginning with a simple square sheet of paper, the artist deftly manipulates the material, employing folding and sculpting techniques to transform it into a breathtaking sculpture. As the folds unfold, an infinite pattern emerges, seemingly defying the constraints of the paper's dimensions.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>origami,paper,folding,sculpture,art,creativity,mesmerizing,technique,craftsmanship,Japan,Tokyo,video,infinity,captivating,cultural,tradition,@d.hinklay,visual,transformation,skill</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Tokyo </media:city>
             <media:country>Japan</media:country>
             <media:category>Cool</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Fri, 4 Nov 2022</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2136</guid>
             <pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2023 17:19:18 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/8e96d081-e638-4918-b3fd-e4fb949c27d0.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/61ebe430-1d36-4092-b448-5fa072e9f8e7.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Paws-on assistance: feline helper joins the moving crew!</media:title>
             <media:description>In a heartwarming display of feline camaraderie, a cat in Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia, melted hearts as it attempted to lend a paw in moving a mattress. The adorable feline, captured on video by @pumpkin_pink on 1st March, 2023, showcased an uncanny desire to assist its owner with the heavy task. Walking on its hind legs and placing its front paws firmly on the mattress, the cat seemed determined to play a role in the moving process.

The video, shared on social media, quickly went viral, captivating viewers with the cat's earnest attempt to help. </media:description>
             <media:keywords>cat,mattress,help,moving,Kuala Lumpur,Malaysia,video,paws,hind legs,owner,adorable,feline,assistance,capture,viral,social media,bond,pets,heartwarming,gesture</media:keywords>
             <media:city> Kuala Lumpur </media:city>
             <media:country>Malaysia</media:country>
             <media:category>Animals</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Wed, 1 Mar 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2135</guid>
             <pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2023 16:50:15 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/5711b6f0-2c8e-4fcb-a784-b0059900ab34.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/260723a7-a3a0-4111-9e21-ba12cbe21bf8.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Yogyakarta's Mesozoic marvel: riding through time on a dinosaur rickshaw</media:title>
             <media:description>In a captivating video captured by @ferdinandyaa_ on May 5, 2023, in Bantul, Yogyakarta, Indonesia, an extraordinary sight unfolded. The footage showcased two individuals gleefully riding on a cart, seemingly pulled by a magnificent Tirex dinosaur. However, upon closer inspection, it became apparent that this was no living, breathing creature but an artful sculpture equipped with a clever peddling mechanism beneath its hind legs.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>dinosaur,rickshaw,sculpture,transportation,Yogyakarta,Indonesia,video,cart,Tirex,mechanism,hind legs,artful,captivating,prehistoric,cultural,heritage,tourists,locals,journey,time</media:keywords>
             <media:city> Bantul, Yogyakarta</media:city>
             <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
             <media:category>Cool</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Fri, 5 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2133</guid>
             <pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2023 15:59:57 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/ebddcd54-4cbd-493c-8680-21e8f7243c7d.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/507be42b-017e-49b5-be82-da68f1c039fc.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Chilling marvels: airplane journey transforms into cloudy wonder</media:title>
             <media:description>
On May 5th, 2023, a passenger named @LeiShao embarked on a remarkable flight from Fuzhou, China to the Philippines with Cebu Pacific Airlines. Little did she know that this journey would take an unexpected turn, as the air conditioning on the plane turned the cabin into a mesmerizing spectacle resembling clouds. Adjusted to an extremely low temperature, the air conditioning vents released a blast of cold air that transformed into mist, creating a breathtaking illusion of clouds emanating from the system.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>airplane,journey,clouds,mist,temperature,spectacle,illusion,video,experience,breathtaking,enchanting,world,wisps,ethereal,atmosphere,surreal,passengers,nature,technology,beauty</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Fuzhou</media:city>
             <media:country>China</media:country>
             <media:category>Cool</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Fri, 5 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2131</guid>
             <pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2023 11:26:26 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/ac7bcfbf-1fc5-4e85-a6d7-7793688ff490.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/0b742f24-956e-4bac-b467-0151ce7d6fc6.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Rural Kung Fu master shatters bricks with bare hands: a display of Chinese martial arts prowess</media:title>
             <media:description>In in Liaoning Province, Northeast China, a humble peasant farmer named @farmerkungfubrother has captivated social media with his extraordinary display of Chinese Kung Fu skills. With an unwavering passion for martial arts, @farmerkungfubrother has dedicated countless hours to mastering the ancient techniques. Recently, he took to recording a video on 23rd April, 2023 that has left viewers in awe, showcasing his incredible ability to effortlessly shatter bricks with his bare hands.

The video, recorded on a sunny afternoon, captures the author's focused demeanor as he approaches solid bricks arranged in a line. With precise technique and remarkable strength, he strikes the bricks with a swift and controlled motion, reducing them to rubble with each powerful blow. His remarkable display not only demonstrates the physical prowess acquired through years of dedicated practice but also showcases the rich heritage of Chinese martial arts.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>peasant,farmer,kungfu,martialarts,progress,video,bricks,barehands,passion,dedication,technique,strength,accomplishment,inspiration,socialmedia,determination,aspiration,power,skill,practice</media:keywords>
             <media:city> Liaoning Province</media:city>
             <media:country>China</media:country>
             <media:category>Cool</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Sun, 23 Apr 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2130</guid>
             <pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2023 11:17:28 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/6d7fb5f6-60b4-4e53-9c89-6bd2f02c6bd0.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/9bc5d64b-c0a3-494c-a401-b72d3c9eb8bb.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Woman and child embark on a dangerous scooter ride!</media:title>
             <media:description>In the Sokolinaya Gora district of Moscow, Russia, on May 26th, 2023, an intriguing sight caught the attention of passersby. A woman fearlessly maneuvered her scooter along the roadway, accompanied by a small child. In social networks, many people noted the carelessness of the mother, how dangerous it is.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>woman,scooter,roadway,child,Sokolinaya Gora,Moscow,Russia,ride,adventure,bond,joy,trust,companionship,unknown,caring,figure,spirited,reminder,everyday,open road,connections</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Sokolinaya Gora, Moscow</media:city>
             <media:country>Russia</media:country>
             <media:category>Cool</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Fri, 26 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2129</guid>
             <pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 18:44:41 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/27b3758b-9b79-4f4b-801d-934c638e197c.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/23b99a7a-e588-422e-a5e0-f992a7527a7c.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Enigmatic whirlpool unleashed: divers encounter nature's unpredictable power in Masbate waters</media:title>
             <media:description>In a breathtaking encounter with nature's awe-inspiring power, a group of divers in Masbate, Philippines, found themselves in the midst of a mesmerizing spectacle. On September 6th, 2022, as captured by @Angelvargas, a video emerged of a colossal whirlpool forming, extending from the clouds like a massive funnel. The divers, aboard a sturdy wooden boat, were exploring the pristine waters of Masbate when an unexpected turn of events unfolded.

As the divers marveled at the beauty of the ocean, the sky above them gradually darkened, casting an eerie gloom over the once serene surroundings. Within moments, a swirling vortex emerged on the horizon, drawing their attention. With each passing second, the whirlpool grew in size, its spiraling force intensifying, and its epicenter drawing closer to their location.

The divers braced themselves for the approaching natural phenomenon, a mixture of both excitement and trepidation coursing through their veins.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>whirlpool,clouds,funnel,divers,exploration,Masbate,Bicol,Philippines,video,gloomy,boat,nature,power,vortex,ocean,spectacle,encounter,forces,beauty,unpredictability</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Laurente, Masbate</media:city>
             <media:country>Philippines</media:country>
             <media:category>Weather</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Tue, 6 Sep 2022</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2124</guid>
             <pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 14:53:12 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2124.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2124.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Typhoon Mawar strikes Guam: devastation unleashed near hotel</media:title>
             <media:description>Guam, a U.S. Pacific territory, woke up to scenes of destruction on 24th May, 2023 as Typhoon Mawar wreaked havoc on the island. The howling winds and torrential rainfall that accompanied the typhoon left residents without power and caused significant damage across the region. As officials began to assess the aftermath, it became clear that the storm had uprooted trees, damaged cars, and blocked roads, leading to a state of emergency on the island.

Residents of Guam, still reeling from the impact of Typhoon Mawar, found themselves in a dire situation as essential services were disrupted. The widespread power outage meant that businesses were unable to operate normally, leaving many without access to vital supplies. Long queues formed outside the few shops that managed to stay open, where residents clamored to purchase food and other necessities. With limited access to internet and malfunctioning ATMs, cash became the only accepted form of payment in many establishments.

One particularly stark visual of the destruction was captured in a video footage taken by @T9Cryptonite. The clip showed uprooted trees scattered near a hotel, their roots ripping through the ground. The cars parked nearby were not spared either, as they bore the marks of the fallen trees, crushed and damaged. To add to the chaos, a road was completely blocked by an uprooted tree, further hampering recovery efforts and hindering residents' ability to move around the island.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>typhoon,Guam,winds,rainfall,power outage,damage,assessment,warnings,residents,survey,whipping,lightning storms,Mawar,coconut trees,mango trees,power,territory,shops,food,supplies,businesses</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Guam</media:city>
             <media:country>United States</media:country>
             <media:category>Weather</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Wed, 24 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2123</guid>
             <pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 14:40:12 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2123.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2123.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item><item>
             <media:title>Unlikely playmates: dog and owl share playful moments in Madrid</media:title>
             <media:description>In a heartwarming encounter captured on video by @zoeelabuha in Madrid, Spain, on 16th May, 2023, an unlikely duo caught everyone's attention. A dog, leisurely lying down, was suddenly joined by an adventurous owl seeking affection. The owl fearlessly climbed onto the dog's back, initiating a playful interaction that melted the hearts of onlookers.

As the owl perched on the dog's back, the canine responded with a playful nip, opening its mouth as if to gently bite the feathery intruder. Rather than being deterred, the owl mirrored the dog's playful gesture, attempting to peck back in a lighthearted manner. Their exchange was filled with joy and mutual understanding, as if they had developed an unspoken language of friendship.</media:description>
             <media:keywords>dog,owl,Madrid,Spain,love,playful,video,encounter,friendship,companionship,joy,unexpected,heartwarming,adventure,bite,peck,connection,smiles,magic,simplicity</media:keywords>
             <media:city>Madrid </media:city>
             <media:country>Spain</media:country>
             <media:category>Animals</media:category>
             <media:filmingDate>Tue, 16 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
             <guid>2122</guid>
             <pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 08:55:37 GMT</pubDate>
             <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2122.jpg"/>
             <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2122.mp4" />
             <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
             </item></channel>
           </rss>