<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
        <rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
        xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
        xmlns:openSearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearchrss/1.0/"
        xmlns:dfpvideo="http://api.google.com/dfpvideo"
        xmlns:tms="http://data.tmsapi.com/v1.1"
        version="2.0">
          <channel>
            <title>ViralBear videos</title>
            <dfpvideo:version>2</dfpvideo:version>
              
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Thrilling mishap: Audi drift attempt ends in guardrail collision at Suzhou GTshow </media:title>
                  <media:description>During the annual Suzhou GTshow on July 22, 2023, a highly anticipated automotive cultural event in China, a heart-pounding incident occurred as an Audi car attempted a daring drift maneuver. The vehicle lost control and collided with a guardrail, sending shockwaves through the crowd of car enthusiasts. Thankfully, no one was injured in the dramatic collision. The video captured by @ShanghaiUPAutomotiveTechnicalService shows the intensity of the moment, serving as a reminder of the risks involved in high-speed automotive displays. Despite the unexpected mishap, the event continued, showcasing a spectacular display of Custom cars and Supercars to the delight of the attendees.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>drift,audi,collision,guardrail,suzhou,china,g t show,automotive,event,enthusiasts,custom,supercar,annual,mishap,excitement,car,culture,display,injured,risk</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Suzhou</media:city>
                  <media:country>China</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>CN</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2603</guid>
                  <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 13:19:39 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2603.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2603.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Action-packed movie filming in Chisinau takes a dramatic turn as car rams parked bus!</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a stunning turn of events in Chisinau, Moldova, a movie filming session took a thrilling and unexpected twist as a car intentionally rammed into a parked bus. The dramatic scene, captured by @nazligian_ on July 23, 2023, showcased the heart-pounding moment when the car, utilizing a purpose-built ramp, accelerated towards the stationary bus. With precision and skill, the car collided with the bus, creating a breathtaking spectacle that left onlookers in awe. Fortunately, there were no reported injuries as the filming was conducted in a closed-off area in the city center. The incident occurred as part of the action-packed movie production, adding an authentic touch to the adrenaline-filled scenes being brought to life on the silver screen.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>movie,filming,chisinau,moldova,car,bus,ramp,action,thrilling,unexpected,dramatic,spectacle,onlookers,injury-free,closed-off,center,adrenaline,scenes,silver screen,production</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Chisinau </media:city>
                  <media:country>Moldova</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>MD</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sun, 23 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2563</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 07:49:50 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2563.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2563.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Nine-year-old boy hospitalized after tree collapse at Samara playground</media:title>
                  <media:description>On July 10, 2023 evening in the Oktyabrsky district of Samara, Russia, a harrowing incident occurred on a playground when a tree unexpectedly fell on a nine-year-old boy. Despite initial fears, authorities determined that the tree was still alive and showed no signs of decay, raising questions about the cause of the collapse. The young victim was rushed to Seredavina Hospital, where medical professionals confirmed his condition to be stable and satisfactory. The child is currently under close observation by doctors as they work to ensure his recovery. Authorities are conducting a thorough investigation into the incident to understand the circumstances leading to the tree's collapse, offering insights to prevent similar accidents in the future.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>hospitalized,playground,tree,collapse,samara,russia,nine-year-old,incident,oktyabrsky,alive,decay,investigation,authorities,stable,satisfactory,doctors,observation,recovery,child,district</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Samara</media:city>
                  <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2559</guid>
                  <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 06:58:05 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2559.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2559.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Tragedy strikes: pedestrian bridge collapse in Luga claims one life, leaves three injured</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a devastating incident on July 22, 2023, a pedestrian bridge in the city of Luga, Leningrad Region, Russia, collapsed, resulting in one person losing their life and three others sustaining injuries. The regional Investigative Committee confirmed the tragic event, and harrowing video footage captured the moment when numerous people were standing on the bridge just before it gave way. The collapse has sent shockwaves through the community, prompting concerns about the safety and maintenance of such structures.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>tragedy,pedestrian,bridge,collapse,Luga,Russia,death,injury,incident,Investigative Committee,video,footage,community,safety,maintenance,structure,investigation,authorities,shockwaves,concerns</media:keywords>
                  <media:city> Luga, Saint Petersburg region</media:city>
                  <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2554</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 07:29:36 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2554.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2554.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Blaze breaks out on Panama-registered car carrier Fremantle Highway off Netherlands coast</media:title>
                  <media:description>A fire broke out on the Panama-registered car carrier, Fremantle Highway, off the coast of the Netherlands near Ameland on July 26, 2023, as it was transporting 2,857 cars from Bremerhaven, Germany, to Port Said, Egypt. The blaze resulted in the evacuation of all 23 crew members, with seven rescued from the water and the rest airlifted by helicopter. Tragically, one crew member lost their life, and several others were injured during the incident. The fire, originating from one of the 25 electric cars onboard, proved difficult for the crew to control, and the vessel continued to burn approximately 27 nautical miles north of the Dutch island of Ameland, close to a major environmental and UNESCO heritage site. Images showed scorched areas and billowing smoke along the ship's side as emergency responders battled to contain the flames. @NicoGuud captured a video of smoke still coming from the vessel.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>fire,blaze,car carrier,Netherlands,coast,Fremantle Highway,smoke,evacuation,rescue,injuries,crew,incident,electric cars,tragedy,Ameland,environmental,UNESCO,scorched,emergency,responders</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Ameland</media:city>
                  <media:country>Netherlands</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>NL</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2552</guid>
                  <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023 20:11:03 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2552.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2552.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Crane catastrophe: dramatic bridge damage caught on video in Brooklyn</media:title>
                  <media:description>On July 19th, 2023, in Brooklyn, New York, USA, a shocking incident occurred during which a crane collided with the lower side of a bridge. A witness, identified as @thisismathieu, captured the dramatic moment on video. As he was out for his morning run, he noticed the tall crane approaching the bridge but did not expect the disastrous outcome. The crane struck the bridge with a loud bang, causing significant damage as it dragged along the bottom. In the brief recording, the extent of the destruction became apparent.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>brooklyn,new york,usa,crane,bridge,damage,video,incident,witness,collision,morning,run,loud,bang,destruction,authorities,accident,investigate,damages,caught</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Brooklyn, New York</media:city>
                  <media:country>United States</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>US</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2525</guid>
                  <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 21:04:22 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2525.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2525.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Rail rampage: freight train mishap causes havoc at Matveevskaya Station in Moscow</media:title>
                  <media:description>On July 18, 2023, at Moscow's Matveevskaya station in Russia, a freight train transporting rails experienced a serious accident. During transportation, one of the rails shifted and obstructed the train's path, causing extensive damage to everything in its way. The incident resulted in the destruction of the platform's pavilion and the damage of the driver's cab in an oncoming train. Fortunately, no injuries were reported among the people at the station. Despite the chaos caused by the runaway rail, there were no traffic delays along the route. </media:description>
                  <media:keywords>rail,accident,freight,train,platform,Moscow,Russia,transportation,damage,pavilion,oncoming,driver's cab,mishap,knockdown,path,havoc,delay,people,repairs,footage</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Matveevskaya, Moscow </media:city>
                  <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2494</guid>
                  <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 12:14:26 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2494.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2494.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Su-25 training flight ends in disaster: engine failure causes crash over sea of Azov, pilot survives ejection</media:title>
                  <media:description>On July 17th, 2023, a Su-25 attack aircraft crashed near the coast of Yeysk, Krasnodar Territory, Russia, while conducting a training flight over the Sea of Azov. The preliminary investigation points to an engine failure as the cause of the incident. Disturbingly, the crash occurred in close proximity to people who were resting on the coast at the time. Fortunately, the pilot successfully ejected from the aircraft before the impact and was rescued by emergency services. Currently, specialists from the Ministry of Defense of the Russian Federation and other relevant agencies are on-site, investigating the accident.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>crash,su-25,yeysk,krasnodar territory,russia,engine failure,training flight,sea of azov,incident,emergency services,pilot,eject,rescuers,ministry of defense,special services,scene,coast,rest,investigation,accident</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Yeysk, Krasnodar Territory</media:city>
                  <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2490</guid>
                  <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 09:40:33 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2490.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2490.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Su-25 aircraft crashes into sea of Azov during training flight in Yeysk, Russia, due to engine failure</media:title>
                  <media:description>On July 17th, 2023, a Su-25 aircraft crashed into the Sea of Azov near Yeysk, Krasnodar Territory, Russia, during a training flight. The incident occurred around 15:00, and according to the press service of the Southern Military District, the preliminary cause of the crash was attributed to engine failure. Fortunately, there were no reported casualties, and specialists from the Ministry of Defense and special services are currently investigating the accident on-site.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>crash,aircraft,sea,training,Yeysk,Russia,engine failure,incident,casualties,specialists,Ministry of Defense,special services,investigation,coast,Su-25,Azov,preliminary cause,spot,press service,Southern Military District</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Yeysk, Krasnodar Territory</media:city>
                  <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2489</guid>
                  <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 09:42:11 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2489.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2489.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Sanitary felling mishap: poplar collapses on residential building</media:title>
                  <media:description>In the Tyukhtet region of Russia, an incident occurred on July 5th, 2023, during a sanitary felling operation. Workers cut down a poplar tree, but it unexpectedly collapsed onto a residential building that also housed a pharmacy and a shop. Fortunately, local authorities reported that the damage was minor, and the house was promptly repaired on the same day. According to the first deputy head of the Tyukhtetsky municipal district, Vladimir Napryushkin, the poplar tree only touched a part of the roof with one of its branches, causing damage to several sheets. However, no injuries were reported in the incident. The tree felling is a preventive measure taken in the region to remove old trees that pose potential dangers to people and buildings. No one was injured as a result of the incident.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>residential,building,pharmacy,shop,poplar,collapse,incident,Tyukhtet,Russia,workers,tree,damage,repaired,roof,pediment,felling,danger,authorities,minor,no injuries</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Tyukhtet</media:city>
                  <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Wed, 5 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2487</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/b615cfb9-6dbd-42ac-968d-ea39c34fd49c.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/dca43876-b4c9-41fc-88c8-4178f529b1e9.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Near disaster at North Morowali's wooden bridge: motorbikes overload nearly causes collapse!</media:title>
                  <media:description>On June 27th, 2023, a heart-stopping incident occurred in North Morowali, Indonesia, when a wooden bridge came close to collapsing under the weight of multiple motorbikes. The alarming scene was captured on video by @srcyayaaa, who witnessed the incident unfold. Instead of crossing the bridge one by one as recommended, the riders decided to pass together, causing an overwhelming strain on the aging structure. Miraculously, the bridge managed to hold on, preventing a potentially catastrophic accident. </media:description>
                  <media:keywords>wooden,bridge,collapse,motorbike,weight,North Morowali,Indonesia,video,nearly,one by one,together,fall,repaired,incident,captured,@srcyayaaa,danger,structure,safety,guidelines</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>North Morowali</media:city>
                  <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>ID</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2472</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/626d8c53-00bd-4110-afc2-335d637a3843.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/8bafe67d-273c-44bc-a53a-82fe7c7888ac.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Tragic clash in Nerekhta: intoxicated foreign car driver hits pedestrian girl and crashes into building</media:title>
                  <media:description>A horrific incident occurred in Nerekhta, Kostroma region, Russia, as reported by the press service of the UGIBDD of the Ministry of Internal Affairs. On June 29th, 2023, a foreign car driver, under the influence of alcohol, recklessly crashed into a young girl before colliding into a residential building. Shocking video footage from CCTV cameras circulated on social media, capturing the car speeding towards the helpless victim. The impact was mitigated slightly by bushes, possibly saving the girl's life. Urgently hospitalized, she now fights for recovery, while the driver will be held accountable for his actions according to the law.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>accident,clash,nerekhta,kostroma,russia,foreign car,pedestrian,girl,building,video footage,cctv,social media,intoxicated,driver,hospitalization,bushes,speeding,accountable,law,tragic</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Nerekhta, Kostroma region</media:city>
                  <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2467</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/f50935ab-19a9-4134-9232-d6071d0d4327.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/801973da-a173-4cce-98bb-3a5004f60820.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Shocking gas stove explosion sends diners scrambling at restaurant</media:title>
                  <media:description>The video, shared by @a2tuinho100991 on September 9th, 2022, showcases the alarming moment when the gas stove malfunctioned, creating a chaotic scene inside the restaurant. In a startling incident captured on video, a gas stove exploded on a table at A Đạt Hot Pot Restaurant in Tra Vinh Province, Vietnam. The explosion occurred while people were seated at the table, enjoying their meal. The intense blast caused the diners to disperse rapidly in panic, seeking safety. All people are fine.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>explosion,gas stove,table,restaurant,Vietnam,diners,video,panic,safety,malfunction,chaos,incident,traumatic,startling,alarming,captured,shared,moment,scattered,meal</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Chau Thanh District, Tra Vinh Province</media:city>
                  <media:country>Vietnam</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>VN</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Fri, 9 Sep 2022</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2448</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/d1b7672c-f517-4cb7-8e7c-9a3f718d6dbb.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/0ab04f21-b28e-485b-bfa5-66f571266367.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Mother's instinct: a heartwarming moment of protection</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a remarkable display of maternal instinct, a video captured the heart-stopping moment on June 21st, 2023, when @sam.sam_022 stumbled and fell while carrying her baby in Buon Ma Thuot City, Vietnam. The incident occurred as she was returning from the bathroom, having just finished washing the little one. Despite the unexpected slip, the author managed to hold onto her precious bundle, ensuring the baby remained safe throughout the fall. With unwavering determination, she quickly regained her footing while still cradling her child, proving that a mother's love knows no bounds. </media:description>
                  <media:keywords>motherhood,love,instinct,protection,fall,baby,video,accident,safety,resilience,parenting,strength,bond,care,vulnerability,support,bravery,family,Buon Ma Thuot City,Vietnam</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Buon Ma Thuot City</media:city>
                  <media:country>Vietnam</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>VN</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2445</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/3dfe54e5-7f35-46f1-9a97-2d3f0f1ec43d.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/07c538fc-1992-4b42-ab56-6860785f5427.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Out of control: cow meant for Eid al-Adha rams elderly man in Yogyakarta, Indonesia</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a startling incident captured on video by @muhammadrifat_sb on June 29th, 2023, in Sleman, Yogyakarta, Indonesia, a cow meant for slaughter on Eid al-Adha took an unexpected turn. As the onlookers gathered around, the cow suddenly went berserk, charging towards the crowd. Tragically, it rammed into one of the elderly men present, causing a shocking and chaotic scene. </media:description>
                  <media:keywords>cow,video,incident,Eid al-Adha,berserk,old man,slaughter,capture,Yogyakarta,Indonesia,Sleman,shocking,chaotic,animals,unpredictability,caution,traditional,crowd,rammed,onlookers</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Sleman, Yogyakarta</media:city>
                  <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>ID</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2426</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/e417c6dd-271f-4a8f-ba1b-e537ccfcdab0.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2426.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Close call: son narrowly escapes door mishap as mother leaves on motorbike</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a heart-stopping incident captured on video on June 28th, 2023, a mother from Nam Dinh province, Vietnam, had a close call as her son narrowly escaped being struck by a falling door. The mother, identified as @kem.store0 on social media, was leaving on her motorbike parked inside the store. As she opened the door to exit, she left her son in charge of closing the store's doors. Unfortunately, one of the doors unexpectedly came off its hinges, causing it to crash down dangerously close to the young boy as he struggled to maintain his balance. Though he cried in fright, thankfully, he emerged from the incident unharmed. Unaware of the incident, the mother had already left.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>video,mother,son,door,mishap,escape,motorbike,parked,store,balance,cried,hurt,left,house,Nam Dinh province,Vietnam,social media,incident,close call,captured</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Nam Dinh province</media:city>
                  <media:country>Vietnam</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>VN</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2417</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/55394445-4e3d-4010-be03-66e74fa26c48.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/62d4848d-4142-45f6-a99e-c06ab6d4b5f9.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Shocking encounter: woman struck by lightning in Kolomna, Russia | caught on camera!</media:title>
                  <media:description>A shocking incident unfolded in Kolomna, Russia, on July 7, 2023, when a woman was struck by lightning during a heavy thunderstorm. The incident was captured on video by Alevtina Simonova, who had initially intended to document the deplorable weather conditions. The author said: "After work, as usual, I took the train to get home. I crossed a puddle, where a video was shot and decided to record a video about how deplorable the weather is. As a result, I filmed a video as if a girl was hit by lightning several times next to her. She could not walk and possibly speak because of the shock, a man helped her, carried her inside the station and put her on a bench, аfter that she was hospitalized". The girl's condition is now stable.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>lightning,Kolomna,Russia,incident,woman,scooter,thunderstorm,video,weather,shock,aid,station,bench,injuries,burn center,burns,footage,puddle,capture</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Kolomna</media:city>
                  <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Fri, 7 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2392</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/01b0dde6-c31f-4aa5-8fe0-2c7aa79e2f65.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/4f28c43f-eaec-4d71-90f0-394a2400e9b0.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Two 15-year-old girls injured in Orekhovo-Zuevo park ride accident, investigation underway</media:title>
                  <media:description>Two 15-year-old girls were injured in Orekhovo-Zuevo, Russia, when a cabin of a children's attraction in a local park suddenly fell. The incident occurred on July 5, 2023 and the girls were immediately rushed to a nearby medical facility for treatment. The Moscow Region prosecutor's office reported that a criminal case has been opened under Article 238 of the Criminal Code, which deals with the provision of services that fail to meet safety requirements. As a result, an investigation has been initiated to assess compliance with safety regulations regarding the operation of children's attractions in the park.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>injured,accident,girls,Orekhovo-Zuevo,Russia,park,ride,cabin,children's attraction,falls,prosecutor's office,criminal case,investigation,safety requirements,medical facility,inspection,compliance,Moscow Region,July 5,services</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Orekhovo-Zuevo</media:city>
                  <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Wed, 5 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2386</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/93021fff-031f-4990-bf06-6e31ef5d9294.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/f8185943-b50c-4997-b6b7-2e6992ca5ad9.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Emirates Airbus A380 encounters tire burst on landing at Birmingham Airport</media:title>
                  <media:description>An Emirates Airbus A380, operating as flight EK39 from Dubai to Birmingham, UK, experienced a tire burst upon landing at Birmingham Airport (BHX) on July 4th, 2023. The incident prompted an immediate response from emergency services, who swiftly met the aircraft upon arrival. The video captured by @raazy03 showcased the dramatic landing, highlighting the tire's rupture. Thankfully, no injuries were reported among the passengers or crew. </media:description>
                  <media:keywords>emirates,airbus,a380,tyre burst,landing,birmingham airport,emergency services,video,@raazy03,dubai,flight EK39,incident,response,passengers,crew,safety,aviation,unpredictable,puncture,dramatic</media:keywords>
                  <media:city> Birmingham</media:city>
                  <media:country>United Kingdom</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>GB</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Tue, 4 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2373</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/657b7de9-398c-473c-b06c-4f01d940a772.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/b93fe617-39fd-429d-8fdf-60530dcb222f.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Mud mishap: a mother's muddy misadventure with a tearful toddler</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a video captured by @irvanteguh65 on August 30, 2022, in Batu city, Indonesia, a mother found herself in a sticky situation while riding her bike. In a bizarre twist of events, she unintentionally veered off course and ended up in a muddy field. Covered in mud from head to toe, the distressed mother could be seen desperately searching for her shoes. Meanwhile, her crying toddler watched from the mud-free bank. The video showcases the comical yet challenging moment as the mother grapples with the unexpected predicament.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>mud,mother,bike,accident,muddy,toddler,crying,bank,shoes,face,covered,video,captured,Batu city,Indonesia,mishap,comical,challenging,unexpected,predicament</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Batu city</media:city>
                  <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>ID</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2022</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2357</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2ce35130-c0b2-4e7a-a24b-db28bf60cf75.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/044afb60-73dd-4da0-b373-399b27b15b4e.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Spectators narrowly escape injury as bike soars into crowd at Black Parade Hard Enduro event</media:title>
                  <media:description>During the Black Parade Hard Enduro event in Lumajang, Indonesia, a terrifying incident occurred when a motorbike lost control on the rugged terrain, hurtling towards spectators standing dangerously close to the racing track. In a harrowing moment captured by @anwerkofficial on May 17, 2023, the bike flew ahead, leaving the rider behind. Miraculously, no casualties were reported as the spectators narrowly escaped injury. </media:description>
                  <media:keywords>motorbike,falling,spectators,black parade,hard enduro,event,close,racing track,rider,lost control,rough terrain,bike,flew,behind,casualties,lumajang,indonesia,video,captured,may 17</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Lumajang</media:city>
                  <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>ID</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Wed, 17 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2347</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/461defe9-14ad-4715-add6-2b31bcad883e.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2347.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Perilous journey: boat mishap amid typhoon season in Mindanao, Philippines</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a chilling video captured by @angelicawander on October 18, 2022, off the coast of Mindanao, Philippines, a boat incident unfolded during the treacherous typhoon season. The footage showed a terrifying moment when a part of the boat suddenly broke away, plunging into the tumultuous ocean below. With a stark caption that warned against traveling during such hazardous conditions, the video serves as a harrowing reminder of the dangers posed by venturing out amidst a typhoon's fury.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>typhoon,travel,boat,mishap,Mindanao,Philippines,video,danger,caution,storm,ocean,incident,warning,treacherous,season,footage,adventure,safety,risk,explore</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Mindanao</media:city>
                  <media:country>Philippines</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>PH</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2022</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2352</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/ac405d73-4703-470b-8fc3-c554f99bb38e.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2352.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Driver Takamoto's spectacular roll and unyielding spirit in safari rally shakedown</media:title>
                  <media:description>During the recent Safari Rally in Naivasha, Kenya, an adrenaline-fueled moment unfolded as driver Takamoto faced a heart-stopping incident during a shakedown. Captured by @ItsMiller_G on June 21, 2023, the video showcased Takamoto's car rolling and losing its back part in a remarkable display of both danger and determination. However, instead of succumbing to the setback, Takamoto exhibited an unwavering spirit as he quickly regained his composure and continued driving mere seconds after the accident. This unforgettable incident demonstrated the indomitable nature of rally drivers and their relentless pursuit of victory, even in the face of unexpected challenges.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>safari rally,kenya,takamoto,driver,car,roll,shakedown,world rally championship,naivasha,adrenaline,video,capture,incident,determination,danger,spirit,setback,driving,accident,challenge</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Naivasha</media:city>
                  <media:country>Kenya</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>KE</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2343</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/9a9db162-a253-4d9b-ad69-f70e527729e4.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2343.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Startling workshop blast caught on camera!</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a shocking incident captured on camera, a workshop in Nghe An province, Vietnam became the site of a sudden explosion. On March 17th, 2023, @nghenhanmockhoanghethuat, the owner of the workshop, was engrossed in his work on the opposite side of the room. Out of nowhere, an item he had plugged in on the table erupted in a violent explosion. As it turned out later, the battery exploded. Reacting swiftly, @nghenhanmockhoanghethuat cautiously made his way towards the switch and swiftly unplugged it, bringing an end to the dangerous situation. </media:description>
                  <media:keywords>explosion,workshop,video,Nghe An province,Vietnam,@nghenhanmockhoanghethuat,March 17th,2023,danger,unplugged,table,incident,owner,camera,hazard,workspace,vigilant,responsive,shocking,small letters,tags</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Nghe An province</media:city>
                  <media:country>Vietnam</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>VN</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2338</guid>
                  <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 16:12:51 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/c42a4150-8f42-48bd-a75c-4d00c710f395.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/55e77597-13a8-4dc8-8b02-e2209ce35604.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Three-year-old girl's saga seed nose dilemma resolved through determined efforts</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a moment of panic, a three-year-old girl found herself with a saga seed lodged in her nose, causing her mother to seek immediate assistance. The incident, captured by @mabecca4 on June 19th, 2023, in Jakarta, Indonesia, showcased the family's desperate attempts to remove the seed. Despite initial failed efforts using tweezers, the astute observation of the toddler's slowed dinner consumption led to the discovery of the foreign object. Eventually, through careful and determined manual extraction, the saga seed was successfully removed, bringing relief to the distressed family.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>panic,toddler,saga seed,nose,video,Jakarta,Indonesia,mother,tweezers,failed,observation,dinner,rice,slow,removal,hand,girl,captured,relieved,attempts</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Jakarta</media:city>
                  <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>ID</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2306</guid>
                  <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 10:54:44 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/736a6678-612c-4b25-9f22-5a13744361a9.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/943e75ba-7839-4e90-9da2-e07a076f1fbe.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Fatal AN-24 Aircraft crash near Kantemirovka village in Voronezh region</media:title>
                  <media:description>An AN-24 aircraft crashed near the village of Kantemirovka in the Voronezh region of Russia on June 24th, 2023, resulting in at least three fatalities. The incident occurred amidst an ongoing counter-terrorism operation led by the Russian Armed Forces in the region. Governor Alexander Gusev dismissed reports of military equipment movements as unreliable, while also revealing the closure of over 300 kilometers of the M-4 Don highway in the affected area. </media:description>
                  <media:keywords>crash,aircraft,Voronezh,Russia,Kantemirovka,fatalities,counter-terrorism,operation,Russian Armed Forces,governor,Alexander Gusev,unreliable,data,military equipment,region,M-4 Don highway,investigations,cause,authorities,management</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Voronezh</media:city>
                  <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2303</guid>
                  <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 10:03:38 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/34c0760a-2bb4-426e-82ed-9e9458b9636a.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2303.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Explosive chaos: massive fireworks mishap on Simferopol Highway sends shockwaves</media:title>
                  <media:description>A disastrous incident unfolded on the night of June 23, 2023, as chaos erupted on the Simferopol highway (M-2) between Podolsk and the village of Aleksandrovka in the Moscow region, Russia. The calamity originated when a trailer, laden with pyrotechnics, detached from a truck traveling towards Moscow. The jolting caused by the explosive cargo potentially triggered the detonation, although the exact cause remains uncertain.

At approximately 23:45, the trailer became unhinged at the 42nd kilometer mark of the Simferopol highway, leading to a fiery accident. The driver, sensing trouble, swiftly maneuvered to the roadside and hastily abandoned the cab. For the next half an hour, a dazzling yet perilous fireworks display unfolded, with volleys detonating around the burning wreckage. Astonishingly, despite the reverberations being heard within a five-kilometer radius, no other vehicles were harmed. The prompt response from the fire department managed to quell the open flames by 00:34. Thankfully, the proximity of the incident to the surrounding forest, coupled with the region's prolonged drought, did not ignite a potentially catastrophic forest fire. By morning, the remnants of the trailer and cab were carefully dismantled and removed from the road, ensuring minimal disruption to traffic.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>trailer,accident,fire,pyrotechnics,detonation,emergency,truck,explosion,highway,fireworks,performance,cab,volleys,sound,surprise,burning,forest,drought,remains,traffic</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Moscow region</media:city>
                  <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2311</guid>
                  <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 11:35:01 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/7b626fae-d959-4613-bcba-ddc0ae1af6f0.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2a154364-32cb-45de-a866-abd706da10bb.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Drunk driver crashes into parked cars, injures 19-year-old in Narimanov District, Russia</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a shocking incident that unfolded in the village of Starokucherganovka, Narimanov district, Russia, a 54-year-old driver of a Lexus RX200 lost control of their vehicle, leading to a series of unfortunate events. On May 17th, 2022, while navigating the parking area of a store on Lenin Street, the driver skidded and collided with a 19-year-old pedestrian who was standing beside his own car. The impact left the young man injured and necessitated immediate medical attention.

As if the initial collision was not enough, the momentum of the out-of-control Lexus caused it to crash into several parked vehicles nearby. The unsuspecting victims of this chain reaction were a LADA Priora, VAZ-2114, UAZ, and IZH-2126, all fortunately unoccupied at the time. Thankfully, there were no additional injuries reported from these subsequent collisions.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>drunk driving,accident,collision,pedestrian,injuries,Lexus,parking,store,village,Narimanov district,Russia,19-year-old,chain reaction,parked cars,investigation,biomaterial,intoxication,authorities,decision,victims</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Starokucherganovka</media:city>
                  <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Tue, 17 May 2022</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2286</guid>
                  <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 17:39:58 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/4d164723-510f-4988-913f-225e43f0c427.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/d4a0d169-bd87-4f64-92c4-b7c3f1eb94b6.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Terrifying gas explosion at family party leaves dishes shattered </media:title>
                  <media:description>In a shocking incident that unfolded during a family party in Chon Thanh town, Binh Phuoc province, Vietnam on October 12, 2022, a gas explosion sent shockwaves through the gathering, leaving dishes shattered. The explosion occurred without warning, while everyone was enjoying a meal prepared by the author. Amidst the joyous atmosphere, the sudden blast sent pieces of meat flying towards the ceiling, causing chaos and panic among the attendees.

The cause of the explosion is believed to be an old mini gas tank that had been repainted and repaired to appear brand new by the seller. @n07071990 who captured the video  recounts that there were no visible signs of leaks or any other indications of trouble prior to the incident. The force of the explosion was so intense that it took more than two hours for one person, dressed in a blue shirt, to regain mobility after being struck by one of the materials shattered by the gas. The aftermath of the incident left the guests traumatized, with many hesitant to use mini gas stoves in the future.
</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>explosion,gas,party,guests,dishes,bacon,grilled,stove,old,repaired,brand new,witnesses,fear,chaos,panic,injuries,shattered,leaks,intense,trauma</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Chon Thanh town, Binh Phuoc province</media:city>
                  <media:country>Vietnam</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>VN</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2022</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2260</guid>
                  <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 20:31:50 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/6de1372d-4bb2-4424-a2d6-71fe88782b42.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/c19ed9e3-0190-41ac-b8f6-d1c76aa35f81.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Hit-and-run incident in Novosibirsk: child survives as driver flees the scene</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a distressing incident that occurred on October 30, 2022, in the Novosibirsk region of Russia, a child was struck and run over by a RAV4 driver. Shocking video footage captured the incident, revealing that the driver initially attempted to lift the injured boy before abruptly fleeing the scene in his vehicle. According to reports from the AST-54 group on the VKontakte social network, which cited eyewitnesses, the young victim, aged 6, miraculously survived the accident and is currently receiving medical treatment at a local hospital.

Authorities have yet to comment on the incident, as a request for information has been sent to the press service of the Main Directorate of the Ministry of Internal Affairs for the Novosibirsk Region. Meanwhile, speculation has arisen on social media that the driver involved may be a deputy working as a director of a municipal institution. However, there is no official confirmation of this allegation at the time of writing.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>accident,hit-and-run,Novosibirsk,Russia,RAV4,child,video,driver,hospital,survival,investigation,authorities,eyewitnesses,social media,speculation,deputy,municipal institution,press service,community,updates</media:keywords>
                  <media:city> Novosibirsk region</media:city>
                  <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2022</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2207</guid>
                  <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 09:22:21 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/1c408366-4764-4bef-a715-2d3ca421e52f.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/c60c9865-aea0-436a-8ee5-e5fc1de88a1b.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Unusual catfish deluge: road accident unleashes aquatic chaos</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a bizarre incident that unfolded on the Sragen-Jogoro route in Central Java, Indonesia, a road accident led to a remarkable sight of live catfish scattered across the asphalt. The incident was captured on video by @choiiiikayuuu on November 20, 2020, who transporting the catfish through the area. The footage shows numerous catfish wriggling and flopping around on the road, while a group of people swiftly gathered to help collect the disoriented fish.

According to @choiiiikayuuu, the mishap occurred when his pickup truck, loaded with a cargo of catfish stored in white drums, experienced a tire explosion. The sudden impact caused the vehicle to sway, resulting in the scattering of the slippery cargo onto the road. Fortunately, the accident didn't lead to a more disastrous outcome, as the fish managed to avoid falling into nearby ditches filled with water. The unexpected scene attracted the attention of bystanders and passersby who lent a hand in the rescue efforts, working diligently to gather the stranded catfish and return them to safety.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>catfish,scattered,road,alive,waggling,video,people,collecting,Grobogan,Sragen-Jogoro,pick up,white drum,tire,exploded,accident,swayed,ditch,water,Indonesia,unusual</media:keywords>
                  <media:city> Glonggong, Sragen, Central Java</media:city>
                  <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>ID</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Fri, 20 Nov 2020</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2228</guid>
                  <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 16:56:46 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/0596d608-c539-4c06-b873-f615d597864a.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/3fb40772-9ab4-42b5-ab4e-4ec8086eb350.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Fiery blaze engulfs foam board truck in Linyi: driver escapes unharmed</media:title>
                  <media:description>A truck carrying foam boards caught fire in Linyi, Shandong province, China, causing a dramatic scene captured on video by @Anquanshengchan on May 25th, 2023. The incident occurred at 6 o'clock in the morning when the driver suddenly detected a burning odor. To his horror, he realized that the foam boards on the top of the truck were engulfed in flames. Despite his quick efforts to unload the cargo, his attempts proved futile, and he could only stand helplessly as the foam boards burned on the ground. Thankfully, the driver managed to drive the truck away from the area, ensuring that no injuries were reported.

The video footage showcases the intense nature of the fire, with billowing smoke and bright orange flames consuming the foam boards. The driver's prompt action to remove the truck from potential danger was crucial in preventing any further complications. </media:description>
                  <media:keywords>burning,foam,boards,truck,fire,video,incident,Linyi,Shandong,China,driver,smell,top,unloaded,useless,watch,ground,offloaded,fortunate,injured</media:keywords>
                  <media:city> Linyi of Shandong province</media:city>
                  <media:country>China</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>CN</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Thu, 25 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2233</guid>
                  <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 11:29:08 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/835177d6-f84b-464a-9fda-b503181c42e5.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2233.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Terrifying moment: motorbike plunges into water as floating bridge swings wildly</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a heart-stopping incident captured on video by @ferdipratamaa, a man's motorbike plummeted into the water after the floating bridge he was crossing swung violently due to strong winds. The dramatic footage, filmed on April 24, 2023, in Gunung Megang, South Sumatra, Indonesia, shows the man losing control of his bike as it teeters on the swaying bridge. Despite his desperate efforts to regain balance, he ultimately succumbs to the uncontrollable forces, toppling into the water below.

 Fortunately, the man escaped the incident with no serious injuries. The strong winds that day created a treacherous situation, causing the bridge to sway violently and making it nearly impossible for the motorist to maintain control.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>floating bridge,motorbike,incident,video,strong winds,swinging,dramatic,control,water,balance,danger,unpredictable,weather,risk,injuries,caution,preparedness,structure,adverse conditions,Indonesia</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Gunung Megang, South Sumatra</media:city>
                  <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>ID</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2190</guid>
                  <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 20:48:59 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/374b5994-6b55-416e-a875-a3d8bca3b4c4.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/9c20e511-d7af-4cb3-883a-00765728c6d0.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Fire erupts during well repair at Severo-Labatyuganskoye field in Russia</media:title>
                  <media:description>An explosion rattled the Severo-Labatyuganskoye field in the Surgut district of the Khanty-Mansiysk Autonomous region, Russia, as repair work was underway on a well. The incident occurred on 30th May, 2023, during which a fire broke out, damaging the body of the lifting unit of a car. Fortunately, the oil workers at the site managed to extinguish the fire before the arrival of the fire service, averting any casualties or injuries.

The Ministry of Emergency Situations reported that the fire had engulfed an area measuring approximately 0.5 square meters. Although the flames were successfully brought under control, investigators are now working diligently to establish the cause of the fire. The Severo-Labatyuganskoye field, being developed by Surgutneftegaz, is known for its significant oil reserves and plays a crucial role in Russia's energy sector.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>explosion,repair,well,fire,damage,car,workers,extinguished,arrival,firefighters,Ministry,Emergency Situations,cause,investigators,Severo-Labatyuganskoye,field,Surgutneftegaz,Khanty-Mansi,Autonomous Okrug,Russia</media:keywords>
                  <media:city> Khanty-Mansiysk autonomous region</media:city>
                  <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Tue, 30 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2174</guid>
                  <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 10:13:17 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/c945f894-5d73-40df-bbe5-bef926de87e7.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/df9ebb47-e472-4bb5-a3d5-338f8ff6aa36.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Brave biker's close call: dismantled motorbike catches fire during test run</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a harrowing incident captured on video, @rohadysajiedin of Serdang Deli, North Sumatra, Indonesia, narrowly escaped disaster when the engine of his dismantled motorbike caught fire during a test run on April 29, 2023. The heart-stopping footage shows him riding the bike before stopping for a moment when suddenly  flames engulf the engine. Reacting swiftly, the author brought jumped off the motorbike. 

Risking his own safety, he wasted no time in attempting to extinguish the growing flames. Everything ended well.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>video,testing,motorbike,dismantled,fire,engine,caught,flames,stopped,extinguish,Serdang Deli,North Sumatra,Indonesia,close,call,bravery,danger,quick thinking,safety,courageous,incident</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Serdang Deli, North Sumatra</media:city>
                  <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>ID</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sat, 29 Apr 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2187</guid>
                  <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 20:45:42 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/04a13c6d-18ad-4dd4-ac23-c488c20c1e4e.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/d8515096-6195-4be7-b38f-a5663ceffdac.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Unexpected pitfall: friend's close call during inflatable pool adventure</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a bizarre incident captured on video by @anjarsuzu, a day of fun turned into a close call for a friend in Muko Regency, Bengkulu Province, Indonesia on July 18, 2022. The video shows a friend, unknowingly, stepping into a hole pit while moving backward, moments after helping tie the children's pool on the car. The friend quickly regained his balance and lifted himself out of the hole.

The incident occurred when the author decided to inflate a children's pool and secure it on top of a car. With his friend's assistance, he successfully tied the pool to the vehicle. However, as the friend stepped back, he failed to notice the nearby pit and accidentally slid into it. Fortunately, his reflexes kicked in, allowing him to swiftly lift himself out of harm's way.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>pit,fall,video,friend,inflatable,pool,air,tying,car,hole,leg,quick,close call,adventure,incident,Muko Regency,Bengkulu Province,Indonesia,funny,captured,unaware</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Muko Regency, Bengkulu Province</media:city>
                  <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>ID</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2022</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2191</guid>
                  <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 20:49:36 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/136a1d01-99c4-4d56-a76d-6b67f2c3c56c.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/6ab75d3b-050f-4de3-9580-ae72da1c0acc.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Unattended gear mishap: car rolls out and damages neighbor's house</media:title>
                  <media:description>In Bandung, Indonesia, a car mishap occurred when a driver, Yuda Aminurahman, experienced an unfortunate incident on May 20, 2023. Yuda had washed his car and intended to warm up the engine. However, in a moment of carelessness, he failed to check the gears before starting the ignition. As a result, the car unexpectedly rolled out of its parking spot and came to a halt against his neighbor's house.

A video he captured showcased his desperate attempts to prevent the car from colliding with the neighboring property. Despite his efforts from outside, he was unable to halt the car's momentum. Fortunately, the car itself sustained minimal damage. However, the neighbor's house was not as fortunate, it suffered damage.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>car,mishap,video,roll,ignition,gears,damage,neighbor,house,incident,Bandung,Indonesia,morning,wash,engine,careless,stop,outside,minimal,attention</media:keywords>
                  <media:city> Bandung</media:city>
                  <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>ID</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sat, 20 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2188</guid>
                  <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 19:53:15 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2188.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2188.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Quick thinking saves the day: daughter's cool response stops stove fire</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a remarkable display of composure and quick thinking, a young girl in Thái Bình province, Vietnam, averted a potential disaster when a fire broke out in her kitchen. The incident, captured by @ngothanhlam123456789 on April 8th, 2023, showcased the bravery and level-headedness of the daughter as she handled the situation with remarkable poise.

As the video footage reveals, the girl was cooking alone when the stove suddenly burst into flames. Instead of panicking, she immediately started looking for a way to put out the fire. Demonstrating her resourcefulness, she swiftly sought out a nearby fan to disperse the smoke and prevent the flames from spreading further. Miraculously, thanks to her calm and decisive actions, the fire was contained, with only the food falling victim to the incident.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>cooking,fire,stove,daughter,home,calm,quick-thinking,safety,protection,bravery,composure,resourcefulness,fan,smoke,emergency,incident,food,camera,thái bình,vietnam</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Quỳnh Phụ, Thái Bình province</media:city>
                  <media:country>Vietnam</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>VN</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Fri, 7 Apr 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2167</guid>
                  <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 18:21:58 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/cbe312de-92d8-4a3c-8ce3-d03f397363cc.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/18dedc10-1680-47cc-b710-a59d6aa14968.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Night market mishap: woman falls from 'banyu wave' ride in Sragen, Indonesia</media:title>
                  <media:description>A woman had a terrifying accident at a night market in Cembreng, Sragen, Indonesia. The incident occurred on May 15, 2023, when everyone was in the process of getting off the "Banyu Wave" ride. It is believed that the woman fell due to nervousness or a lack of focus, possibly resulting in her holding on less tightly and suddenly losing her balance. the video footage was captured by @rian.sanjaya931. 

The victim, whose identity remains undisclosed, is currently receiving medical treatment at a hospital. The extent of her injuries has not been disclosed, but it is clear that the incident was serious enough to require immediate attention.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>accident,night market,woman,fall,ride,Banyu Wave,Sragen,Indonesia,nervousness,lack of focus,tight grip,balance,hospital,treatment,investigation,safety,precautions,mechanical failure,amusement park,attractions</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Cembreng, Sragen</media:city>
                  <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>ID</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Mon, 15 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2178</guid>
                  <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 17:53:23 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/bc0dcde2-678c-4bc5-9147-e0c84b7161f8.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/9d52f2d2-b987-4be0-aaaf-812d71f8afaa.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Acrobatic mishap: high-flying stunt goes wrong</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a heart-stopping incident in Jiangsu Province, East China, a high-altitude acrobatic stunt took a dangerous turn, leading to a colleague's neck injury. The incident, captured on video by @dragondragon on May 18th, 2023, showcased the acrobat's colleague practicing daring maneuvers on a springboard. However, concerns arose among the group as they worried he might miss the sponge pad meant to cushion his fall.

In an attempt to reduce the risk, another colleague quickly placed an extra sponge in front of the acrobat's expected landing site. Fortunately, this movement softened the fall of the acrobat. Everything could have ended much worse.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>acrobat,high-altitude,springboard,colleague,practice,movement,sponge pad,fall,twist,neck,injury,video,stunt,Jiangsu Province,East China,worry,risk,landing,head,safety</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Jiangsu Province</media:city>
                  <media:country>China</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>CN</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Thu, 18 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2134</guid>
                  <pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 07:36:06 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/bfa7f4d8-6ee4-4dca-969b-8747a1e0abde.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/b1549029-1798-4bd6-b892-1c34b6ea5e51.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Mother's swift action: a heart-stopping moment captured in Bali</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a heart-stopping moment captured on home camera footage, a mother's swift actions saved her children from a potentially dangerous situation in Karangasem, Bali, Indonesia. The video, recorded by @aryawiryaatmaja on April 9, 2023, showcases a scene where the mother is tending to her two young kids in front of their house.

The incident unfolded when the older child suddenly skidded and fell, resulting in a loud cry. The mother instinctively shifted her attention to attend to the fallen toddler, momentarily leaving the other child in a baby walker unattended. Little did she know that a shallow pit, a remnant of a religious ceremony, lay dangerously close to the path the baby walker was traversing.

As the child in the baby walker pushed it around, unaware of the potential danger, disaster seemed imminent. However, luck was on their side that day. The mother, displaying remarkable reflexes and agility, swiftly intercepted the baby walker just in the nick of time. She pulled both children closer to her, providing solace and comfort to the one who had fallen.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>mother,children,home camera,Bali,Indonesia,incident,rescue,swift,danger,toddler,fallen,baby walker,pit,religious ceremony,attention,love,vigilance,safety,parenting,social media</media:keywords>
                  <media:city> Karangasem, Bali</media:city>
                  <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>ID</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sun, 9 Apr 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2156</guid>
                  <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 07:40:55 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/8c1ac402-7344-4666-b3a2-3a54ec547fa7.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/cca6dd9a-df17-4f00-835a-3bb9944a0557.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Storm in Ufa: ventilation duct collapse crushes parked car</media:title>
                  <media:description>A severe storm in Ufa, Russia on 29th May, 2023, wreaked havoc in the Sosny residential complex as a ventilation duct from a high-rise building was demolished, resulting in a parked car being crushed under the debris. The alarming incident was captured on surveillance cameras, and images circulated on social media showing the extent of the damage. Fortunately, the Ufa Civil Protection Department confirmed that there were no casualties as a result of the incident.

In response to the incident, representatives from the Office of Civil Protection of Ufa and the administration of the Leninsky district swiftly arrived at the scene to assess the situation. Their primary objective is to determine the causes and circumstances that led to the ventilation duct's collapse. </media:description>
                  <media:keywords>storm,Ufa,Russia,Sosny residential complex,ventilation duct,demolished,debris,car,surveillance cameras,crushed,Civil Protection Department,no casualties,Office of Civil Protection,Leninsky district,causes,circumstances,investigation,incident,fallen,high-rise building,social media</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Ufa </media:city>
                  <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Mon, 29 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2144</guid>
                  <pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 12:41:33 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/da1341f5-5543-452e-82d4-faf619f1689d.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/89f87dd8-a932-4b44-bef0-ef185fef52a4.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Terrifying escape: surviving the devastating landslide in Palapay, Gingoog city</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a heart-stopping turn of events, a group of individuals narrowly escaped a catastrophic landslide while driving through Palapay, Gingoog City, Philippines. The incident occurred on a 26th March, 2023, as @DanteSalang captured the harrowing event on video. Travelling at a moderate speed of 50 to 60 kilometers per hour, their pickup truck suddenly encountered falling stones at the mountainside. Within seconds, a massive landslide ensued, prompting the driver to slam the brakes and swiftly retreat to safety.

As they hastily turned back, the scene unfolded before their eyes, painting a picture of sheer chaos and terror. A house, caught in the landslide's wrath, was swiftly washed away, leaving behind a devastated landscape. Amidst the chaos, a mother desperately clutched her baby and fled from the collapsing dwelling, fear etched on her face. A teenage girl, displaying tremendous courage and resilience, carried an infant in her arms as she sprinted for safety. Children, their innocence shattered by the calamity, sprinted with all their might, desperate to outrun the advancing destruction.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>landslide,escape,danger,survival,Palapay,Gingoog City,video,driving,pickup truck,stones,mountain,house,mother,baby,teenager,infant,children,chaos,resilience,nature</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Palapay Gingoog city</media:city>
                  <media:country>Philippines</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>PH</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sun, 26 Mar 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2091</guid>
                  <pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 18:36:48 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2091.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2091.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Powerful explosion rocks gas supply station in Samarkand, Uzbekistan</media:title>
                  <media:description>A powerful explosion has rocked a gas supply station in the Samarkand region of Uzbekistan, leaving one person injured. The incident occurred on May 10th, 2023, and was reportedly caused by a violation of safety techniques during the draining of fuel from a gas tanker into the reserve tank.

Eyewitnesses reported that the explosion was preceded by a fire that broke out in a truck at the gas supply station. The fire then spread to several LNG cylinders, causing a series of explosions that shook the area and sent plumes of smoke billowing into the sky.

Emergency services were quickly dispatched to the scene, and the injured person was taken to a nearby hospital for treatment.

The cause of the explosion is currently under investigation, and authorities have warned that it is too early to speculate on the exact cause. However, initial reports suggest that the accident was caused by a failure to follow proper safety protocols when transferring fuel from the gas tanker to the reserve tank.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>explosion,gas,supply,station,Samarkand,Uzbekistan,truck,fire,LNG,cylinders,injured,safety,techniques,violation,draining,fuel,reserve,tank,accident,investigation</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Samarkand region</media:city>
                  <media:country>Uzbekistan</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>UZ</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Wed, 10 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2058</guid>
                  <pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 11:25:53 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2058.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2058.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Gravity's harvest: a fruitful climb turns into a tumbling adventure</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a incident that unfolded in East Luwu, South Sulawesi, Indonesia, a simple task of plucking rambutan fruit from a tree turned into a memorable sudden fall. @jentitorlawyer96, who happened to be present at the scene, captured the entire escapade on video.

On the 9th of December, 2022, East Luwu's a rambutan tree served as the backdrop for an impromptu expedition. Fueled by a craving for the delectable tropical fruit, @jentitorlawyer96's ex-girlfriend embarked on a daring quest to collect the rambutans above a wall.

As she delicately plucked a ripe rambutan, fate intervened, and an unexpected loss of balance ensued. The ladder, serving as both a stepping stone and an unfortunate catalyst, teetered precariously, sending her and the ladder on a chaotic descent. A mix of surprise, amusement, and concern filled the air as she tried to regain her balance during the tumble.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>exgirlfriend,rambutan,tree,wall,ladder,balance,fall,video,capture,adventure,laughter,unexpected,EastLuwu,SouthSulawesi,Indonesia,mishap,amusement,suspense,comedy,moment</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>East Luwu, South Sulawesi</media:city>
                  <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>ID</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Fri, 9 Dec 2022</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2055</guid>
                  <pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 11:31:01 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2055.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2055.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Unstoppable lady rider's calmness amidst chaos: a remarkable incident at a general store</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a small village in Masaran, Sragen, Central Java, Indonesia, a remarkable incident unfolded at a local general store. On May 12, 2023, a CCTV camera captured the astonishing actions of a lady motorbike rider who found herself in an unexpected predicament.

The video footage reveals that the motorbike experienced a malfunction, causing the gas to remain engaged, rendering it impossible for the vehicle to come to a stop. Unfazed by the situation, the determined rider made her way into the general store, the motorbike's engine still roaring.

With remarkable skill and composure, she navigated through the narrow spaces between the shelves. Onlookers were left in awe.

However, as fate would have it, the motorbike eventually collided with one of the shelves, causing both the rider and the bike to fall. Astonishingly, the lady remained calm and composed throughout the incident, never displaying a hint of panic. On the other hand, the onlookers were left bewildered, unable to comprehend the rider's intentions.

As the dust settled, the store owner and the concerned spectators gathered around the lady rider. To everyone's surprise, the owner did not demand compensation for the damaged mop or any other potential losses incurred during the incident. 

As news of this incident spread on social media, the video shared by @Yunitaardiva2 quickly went viral. </media:description>
                  <media:keywords>motorbike,rider,store,incident,gas problem,unstoppable,composure,chaos,shelves,determination,precision,astonishment,onlookers,mystery,generosity,speculation,resilience,calmness,viral,unconventional</media:keywords>
                  <media:city> Masaran, Sragen, Central Java</media:city>
                  <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>ID</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Fri, 12 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2071</guid>
                  <pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 14:47:13 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2071.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2071.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Unintentional collision: young girl in mosque runs into pillar while being recorded</media:title>
                  <media:description>The footage, recorded by a user with the handle @syafiqikhwannnnn on 17th April, 2023, shows a young girl playing in a mosque in Bachok, Kelantan, Malaysia. However, things take a turn for the worse when the girl notices that she is being recorded and runs straight into a nearby pillar.

In the video, the little girl can be seen standing against the wall, playing with her hands. She appears to be lost in her own world, enjoying the peaceful atmosphere of the mosque. However, as soon as she notices that she is being recorded, she runs away from the camera without looking where she is going.

Unfortunately, the girl's carelessness leads to a painful collision with the pillar. She bumps into it with considerable force. The girl is fine.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>girl,mosque,playing,wall,accident,carelessness,impulsive,safety,parents,children,social media,recording,sharing,online,privacy,consent,cautionary,reminder,awareness,environment</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Bachok, Kelantan</media:city>
                  <media:country>Malaysia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>MY</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2050</guid>
                  <pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 11:17:48 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2050.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2050.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Motorcycle mishap: video captures rider's tumble on Indonesian Road</media:title>
                  <media:description>A video filmed by @dhony_bagas on August 10, 2022, in Banyuwangi, Indonesia, captured the moment a person riding an extended motorcycle veered off the road and toppled over.

The video, which has since been widely shared on social media, shows the person driving in front of @dhony_bagas before suddenly losing control of the motorcycle and crashing to the ground beside the road. It is not clear from the video whether the person sustained any injuries.

In Indonesia, where motorcycles are a common form of transportation, road safety is a major concern. According to data from the Indonesian Ministry of Transportation, there were over 128,000 motorcycle accidents in the country in 2020, resulting in more than 29,000 fatalities.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>motorcycle,mishap,Indonesia,Banyuwangi,road,safety,driving,accident,vulnerability,risk,enforcement,regulations,infrastructure,awareness,social media,video,transportation,fatalities,injuries,reminder</media:keywords>
                  <media:city> Banyuwangi</media:city>
                  <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>ID</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2022</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2049</guid>
                  <pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 12:33:40 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2049.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2049.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Large fire along Virgin River in St. George contained after threatening 100 structures</media:title>
                  <media:description>Firefighters battled a large fire along the Virgin River in St. George, Utah, USA, on May 9th, 2023. The fire broke out around 3 p.m. near a residential area at 2580 E. Waters Edge Circle, just south of the Virgin River near Mall Drive. Fire departments from across Washington County responded to the scene to fight the blaze.

Although the cause of the fire is currently unknown, it is suspected to have been a controlled burn that got out of control. The fire spread quickly, covering an estimated 40 acres and threatening more than 100 structures. Some residents in nearby condos were urged to voluntarily evacuate, but no mandatory evacuations were ordered.

State fire managers reported that the fire was mostly contained within two hours of firefighters being called to the scene. By 8 p.m., the fire was 100% contained, and there were no injuries or structures lost.

St. George Fire Chief Robert Stoker warned that this fire season could be tough in southern Utah due to the wet winter and rainy spring, which have created new vegetation growth on top of years of dead fuels just beneath the surface. @cairochris who captured a clip of the fire commented "Fire along the Virgin River currently…about a half mile from my place."</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>fire,firefighters,Utah,St. George,Virgin River,blaze,evacuation,response,spectators,danger,containment,investigation,structures,vegetation,controlled burn,resources,crowds,residential,police,tough season</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Virgin River, St. George</media:city>
                  <media:country>United States</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>US</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Tue, 9 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2042</guid>
                  <pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 20:33:21 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2042.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2042.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Driver flees after Lada Priora crashes at toll booth on M-4 Don Highway in Voronezh Region, Russia</media:title>
                  <media:description>A Lada Priora crashed into a fence and broke the barrier at a toll booth on the M-4 Don highway in the Voronezh region of Russia on May 4th, 2023. The incident was reported by the Telegram channel "Atypical Pavlovsk". According to the public, the accident occurred on the 636th km of the highway near the village of Shestakovo in the Bobrovsky district.

Eyewitnesses reported that the driver of the car fled the scene after the accident. It is not known what caused the accident or if there were any injuries or fatalities as a result.

The M-4 Don highway is one of the major highways in Russia and connects Moscow with the southern regions of the country, including Rostov-on-Don and Krasnodar.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>car,crash,toll,booth,highway,Voronezh,Russia,Lada,Priora,fence,barrier,accident,driver,flee,scene,investigation,charges,safety,driving,responsibility</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Voronezh Region</media:city>
                  <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Thu, 4 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2011</guid>
                  <pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2023 09:55:16 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2011.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2011.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                     </channel>
                  </rss>
                