<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
        <rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
        xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
        xmlns:openSearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearchrss/1.0/"
        xmlns:dfpvideo="http://api.google.com/dfpvideo"
        xmlns:tms="http://data.tmsapi.com/v1.1"
        version="2.0">
          <channel>
            <title>ViralBear videos</title>
            <dfpvideo:version>2</dfpvideo:version>
              
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Unconventional tennis: when dormitory fun goes ball-less</media:title>
                  <media:description>In an amusing and inventive twist on traditional tennis, a group of female college students in Chongqing, China, decided to trade in the ball for a bit of imaginative fun. Captured in a delightful video by @YukoHara on June 17, 2023, the girls were seen energetically wielding tennis rackets as if engaged in a competitive match. However, there was one crucial element missing from their game: the tennis ball itself. Undeterred by its absence, the students turned their playful attention to their dormitory, transforming it into an impromptu court. Laughter filled the air as they comically mimicked the motions of a real game, their movements synchronized as they volleyed invisible balls back and forth. One classmate, seated on a bed, even joined in on the fun by rhythmically patting her stomach, creating a playful imitation of the iconic tennis ball sound. In this lighthearted display of camaraderie, these innovative young women showed that the joy of sport knows no bounds, even when the ball takes an unexpected leave of absence.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>tennis,fun,creativity,camaraderie,laughter,dormitory,imagination,ball-less,playful,students,Chongqing,China,rackets,game,inventive,video,mimicry,energetic,classmates,sound</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Chongqing </media:city>
                  <media:country>China</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>CN</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Fails and Funnies</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2672</guid>
                  <pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023 12:42:28 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2672.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2672.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Mysterious nighttime spectacle: enigmatic lights over Hoyts Docklands spark meteor shower speculation</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a captivating video captured by @mahekinaus on August 7, 2023, a mesmerizing display of bright, moving objects illuminated the night sky near Hoyts Docklands, Australia. The video, accompanied by the caption "Was that a meteor shower that we just saw? Witnessed it near Hoyts Docklands. </media:description>
                  <media:keywords>night,lights,sky,video,meteor,shower,spectacle,Hoyts Docklands,Australia,mystery,captivation,curiosity,enthusiasts,phenomenon,onlookers,anticipation,speculation,celestial,updates,community</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Docklands</media:city>
                  <media:country>Australia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>AU</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>News</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Mon, 7 Aug 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2668</guid>
                  <pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 21:20:40 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2668.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2668.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Playful pups on a wild slide: adventures of Stavropol's Cane Corso and American Bully duo</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a charming woodland escapade captured by @naa2699 on November 7, 2021, in Stavropol, Russia, two lively dogs reveled in the simple joy of sliding down fallen tree foliage. The heartwarming video showcases the playful antics of a Cane Corso puppy named Pepsi, distinguished by a vibrant green collar. Chasing and frolicking, the young pup embarked on an impromptu slide down a steep incline, much to the amusement of its American Bully companions. The author, who proudly tends to a home kennel of Cane Corso and American Bully breeds, affectionately shared this delightful moment with the world, capturing the essence of carefree companionship and the boundless exuberance of four-legged friends.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>playful,dogs,video,woodland,slide,adventure,Cane Corso,American Bully,puppy,Stavropol,Russia,foliage,chase,collar,kennel,laughter,companionship,joy,escapade,antics</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Stavropol</media:city>
                  <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sun, 7 Nov 2021</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2667</guid>
                  <pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 11:21:25 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2667.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2667.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Joseph the berry-eating 'vacuum cleaner' dog</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a delightful scene captured by @iosif20.05.2020 on June 16, 2023, in St. Petersburg, Russia, a video showcases a furry culinary enthusiast named Joseph. The adorable dog found himself amidst an accidental spill of blueberries, creating a vibrant mess on the floor. Seizing the opportunity, Joseph channeled his inner vacuum cleaner, meticulously devouring the succulent blueberries one by one. </media:description>
                  <media:keywords>dog,berries,spill,St. Petersburg,Russia,video,Joseph,vacuum,homage,Brodsky,adorable,culinary,enthusiast,vibrant,mess,opportunity,munching,playful,exploration,literary</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>St. Petersburg</media:city>
                  <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2666</guid>
                  <pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 11:35:16 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2666.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2666.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Kangaroo-inspired leap: Bull Arab and Catahoula mix masters the fence jump</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a remarkable display of agility and boundless energy, a video captured by @zoecarter_aus on July 11, 2023, in Victoria, Australia, showcases an extraordinary feat by his unique canine companion. The mixed breed dog, a fusion of Bull Arab and Catahoula, astounds viewers as it effortlessly leaps off a farm fence with a striking resemblance to a kangaroo in motion. With powerful hind legs propelling it skyward, the dog's graceful airborne maneuver and uncanny emulation of a kangaroo's iconic bounce leave a lasting impression. This captivating demonstration of athleticism not only highlights the remarkable abilities of our four-legged friends but also serves as a testament to the boundless wonders of the animal kingdom.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>kangaroo,leap,agility,canine,farm,fence,Victoria,Australia,Bull Arab,Catahoula,video,energy,motion,hind legs,bounce,athleticism,demonstration,animals,wonder,unique,captivating</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Victoria</media:city>
                  <media:country>Australia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>AU</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2664</guid>
                  <pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 11:39:46 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2664.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2664.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Frozen in feline hilarity: Maryland's playful mother and kitten duo stun the shelter!</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a heartwarming scene captured by veterinary technician @meo.cats on May 12, 2023, at the Cat's Life Rescue Shelter in Maryland, USA, two feline companions – a devoted mother cat and her adorable kitten – stole the show with their frozen yet utterly hilarious expressions. The video, which quickly went viral, showcased the pair seemingly caught in a moment of playful bewilderment. As the mother cat and her tiny offspring momentarily froze in their tracks, their comical and endearing facial expressions left viewers in stitches. </media:description>
                  <media:keywords>playful,adorable,heartwarming,viral,companions,expressions,shelter,feline,bewilderment,comical,endearing,glimpse,residents,joy,laughter,kittens,freeze,captivating,bonding,connection</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Maryland</media:city>
                  <media:country>United States</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>US</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Fri, 12 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2663</guid>
                  <pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 08:31:29 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2663.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2663.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Farewell to a musical icon: thousands gather in Bray to celebrate Sinéad O'Connor's life and legacy</media:title>
                  <media:description>Thousands of mourners and fans gathered along the seafront in Bray, County Wicklow, Ireland, to bid a heartfelt farewell to the renowned singer Sinéad O'Connor on August 8, 2023. The emotional gathering began before sunrise, as individuals came to both grieve her passing and celebrate her remarkable life. By midday, the seafront was teeming with people, forming a poignant backdrop for the funeral cortege. Led by police motorcycles and accompanied by the resonating strains of Bob Marley &amp; The Wailers' "Natural Mystic," the procession saw O'Connor's hearse adorned with flowers tossed by the crowd. A video captured by @lalordarren showed the procession as people followed her hearse. As it approached her former home, the crowd erupted in applause, while heartfelt renditions of "Nothing Compares 2 U" echoed and banners carried messages of gratitude and remembrance. Among those paying their respects were Irish President Michael D Higgins and his wife Sabina, underscoring the profound impact that Sinéad O'Connor had on Ireland and the world.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>singer,tribute,farewell,Bray,Ireland,crowd,cortege,music,legacy,mourners,fans,hearse,flowers,applause,banners,president,impact,grief,remembrance,iconic</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Bray </media:city>
                  <media:country>Ireland</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>IE</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>News</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Tue, 8 Aug 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2662</guid>
                  <pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 07:53:49 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2662.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2662.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Corn connoisseur cat: a hilarious tale of Coconut's seasonal delight</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a heartwarming and humorous scene captured by @plukchi__ on July 30, 2023, in Odesa, Ukraine, a feline friend named Coconut has become an internet sensation for his unique love of corn. The video depicts Coconut indulging in his favorite seasonal treat – corn on the cob – alongside the author's friend, @maks_elash. Previously known as Cosmos, the cat earned the endearing moniker Coconut due to his passion for the vegetable. Despite initial restrictions, Coconut's determination led him to master the art of opening a garbage drawer to savor corn cobs. The footage not only showcases Coconut's adorable corn-eating technique but also highlights the strong bond between the cat and his human. </media:description>
                  <media:keywords>corn,cat,coconut,friendship,humor,video,Odesa,Ukraine,TikTok,viral,pet,feline,delight,seasonal,treat,bond,quirky,munching,adorable,internet</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Odesa </media:city>
                  <media:country>Ukraine</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>UA</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2660</guid>
                  <pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 07:24:01 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2660.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2660.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Fisherman's tale: the one that got away - a Baltimore fishing adventure</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a picturesque scene on July 18, 2023, in Baltimore, Maryland, USA, avid angler @a.blair_fishing shared a captivating moment from their fishing escapade. The video captures the excitement of a successful catch being proudly displayed. Amidst the triumph, however, a playful twist unfolds as one spirited fish manages to wriggle free from the hook's grasp, deftly slipping back into the glistening waters below. This unexpected turn of events adds a touch of nature's unpredictability to the serene day by the water, reminding us that even the best-laid plans can be thwarted by the wild spirit of the aquatic realm. </media:description>
                  <media:keywords>fishing,catch,water,adventure,nature,escapade,video,Maryland,Baltimore,fisherman,excitement,hook,playful,unpredictability,serenity,aquatic,realm,joys,challenges,wonders</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Baltimore, Maryland</media:city>
                  <media:country>United States</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>US</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Fails and Funnies</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2657</guid>
                  <pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 07:34:19 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2657.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2657.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Adorable attic antics: playful kittens' hilarious escapade in Bym Village!</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a heartwarming scene captured by @palinkagut on August 4, 2023, in Bym Village of the Kungursky district in Russia's Perm region, a delightful display of feline frolic unfolded. The video reveals a pair of playful kittens engaging in an endearing game within the confines of an attic. Amidst their lively play, one daring kitten leaped out of the attic space. However, its mischievous sibling promptly intervenes, swiftly and comically pulling the adventurous jumper right back to the attic's haven. The heartwarming interaction showcases the inseparable bond between the two siblings and offers a charming glimpse into the world of these furry companions.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>kittens,play,attic,siblings,village,Russia,video,capture,adorable,antics,hide-and-seek,leap,interaction,laughter,awe,companions,heartwarming,Bym,Kungursky,Perm</media:keywords>
                  <media:city> Bym village, Kungursky district, Perm region</media:city>
                  <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Fri, 4 Aug 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2655</guid>
                  <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 10:36:13 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2655.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2655.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Muddy adventures: Shiba the samurai girl finds refreshing escape near Narach Lake</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a charming scene captured by @siba_hani_ on June 18, 2023, near Narach Lake in Minsk Province, Belarus, a spirited dog named Shiba embraces the role of a playful samurai as it frolics in the cooling embrace of mud amidst the woodland. The video showcases Shiba's lighthearted antics as she indulges in the muddy terrain, dipping her snout and sauntering with abandon. With the sun's heat in the air, Shiba's instinctual cooling strategy draws a smile from onlookers as she revels in the joy of the moment, leaving a comical imprint of her adventurous escapade on both herself and her owner.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>playful,woodland,escapade,samurai,dog,mud,cooling,frolics,adventure,joy,antics,sun,Minsk,Belarus,Narach Lake,Shiba,snout,embrace,video,owner</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Minsk Province </media:city>
                  <media:country>Belarus</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>BY</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2654</guid>
                  <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 10:36:43 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2654.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2654.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Heartwarming canine companion: dog comforts "crying" owner in Can Tho City, Vietnam</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a touching display of empathy and companionship, a heartwarming video captured by @nhaco6conheooo on June 24, 2023, in Can Tho City, Vietnam, showcased the unwavering support of a loyal dog towards its owner. The footage featured a lady pretending to cry while sitting on the floor with her hand on her face, and her canine companion immediately rushed to her side. With gentle paws and a warm presence, the dog attempted to console the distressed owner, sliding under her arms and getting close to her face. Undeterred by the presence of another dog nearby, this compassionate furry friend proved that unconditional love knows no bounds. The poignant moment reached its climax when the lady ceased her pretense, rewarding the dog's comforting efforts with a tender scratch on its head, demonstrating the strong bond between human and canine. This heartening scene serves as a reminder of the extraordinary capacity for compassion that our furry companions bring into our lives.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>comfort,empathy,companionship,dog,crying,Can Tho,Vietnam,video,pawing,support,love,furry,bond,human,canine,pretend,touching,pets,affectionate,heartwarming</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Can Tho City</media:city>
                  <media:country>Vietnam</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>VN</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2651</guid>
                  <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 10:38:20 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2651.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2651.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Adorable Coco the Shih Tzu spins into sleepy delight chasing its tail!</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a heartwarming scene from San Mateo, Rizal, Philippines, captured by @coconabi_shihtzu on June 23, 2023, a delightful puppy named Coco found itself in a playful predicament on a cozy mat. As bedtime approached, the energetic little Shih Tzu couldn't resist the allure of its own tail. With excitement and determination, Coco spun around and around, trying to catch hold of the elusive target. The endearing video showcases the pure joy and innocence of a puppy at play, bringing smiles to the faces of viewers worldwide. It's moments like these that remind us of the simple pleasures in life and the unbreakable bond we share with our furry companions.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>puppy,coco,playing,tail,mat,floor,cute,adorable,San Mateo,Rizal,Philippines,video,joy,excitement,bedtime,shih tzu,spinning,delight,pet,fun,love</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>San Mateo, Rizal</media:city>
                  <media:country>Philippines</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>PH</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2650</guid>
                  <pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 11:20:09 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2650.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2650.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Discipline drenched: mother's flogging lesson backfires in Enrile, Cagayan</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a captivating and somewhat comical incident in Enrile, Cagayan, Philippines, a video captured by @edison_fayfi on July 5, 2023, has been making rounds on social media. The footage shows a determined mother chasing her mischievous son in an attempt to discipline him. The young boy had apparently made a mistake that warranted his mother's firm response. However, in a twist of events, the son managed to evade her skillfully, leading her to stumble and fall into a large pond of water. As the video circulated online, netizens couldn't help but chuckle at the irony of the situation, where the intended lesson ended up soaked in humor. </media:description>
                  <media:keywords>discipline,mother,son,flogging,lesson,mistake,Enrile,Cagayan,Philippines,video,chase,evade,pond,water,parenting,humor,social media,netizens,incident,capture</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Enrile, Cagayan</media:city>
                  <media:country>Philippines</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>PH</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Fails and Funnies</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Wed, 5 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2649</guid>
                  <pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 11:19:32 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2649.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2649.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Sweet serenity: a head massage exchange between human and feline in General Santos City</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a heartwarming and endearing scene in General Santos City, South Cotabato, Philippines, a beautiful connection between a woman and her feline companion was captured on video by @jiannmay on July 29, 2023. The footage shows the remarkable bond between the two as the woman communicates with her cat, guiding it to massage her head gently using its delicate paws. The intimate exchange of affection and trust is a testament to the deep connection that can exist between humans and their beloved pets, showcasing the profound understanding and love that can transcend species boundaries. This heart-melting moment serves as a delightful reminder of the joy and comfort animals can bring into our lives.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>cat,massage,head,video,jiannmay,General Santos City,South Cotabato,Philippines,connection,bond,affection,trust,pets,love,animals,joy,comfort,feline,human,paws,endearing</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>General Santos City, South Cotabato</media:city>
                  <media:country>Philippines</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>PH</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2648</guid>
                  <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 15:33:08 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2648.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2648.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Adorable Shih Tzu puppy Miyo masters sit and stand commands with delight in Manila, Philippines!</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a heartwarming scene captured by @miyopuppy on November 12, 2022, in Manila, Philippines, her precious Shih Tzu puppy, Miyo, showcased her impeccable training skills by executing sit and stand commands with sheer joy. The video captured the endearing moments of Miyo gracefully obeying her owner's cues. Whenever instructed to sit, the puppy would happily curl up on her stomach, while on the command to stand, she would eagerly rise onto all fours. With an unmistakable look of happiness in her eyes, Miyo's enthusiasm for learning was evident, making the entire experience a delightful display of the loving bond between a pet and its owner.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>adorable,puppy,shih tzu,commands,video,miyo,sit,stand,Manila,Philippines,happy,training,obedience,joy,owner,love,cute,pet,bond,delightful</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Manila </media:city>
                  <media:country>Philippines</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>PH</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sat, 12 Nov 2022</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2647</guid>
                  <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 15:34:50 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2647.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2647.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Typhoon Dussuri aftermath: government trucks extracting water from flooded road tunnel in Fuzhou, Southeast China</media:title>
                  <media:description>In the aftermath of Typhoon Dussuri's devastating impact on Fuzhou, Southeast China, a resident known as @Tenglovehourglass captured a compelling video of government trucks diligently working to extract water from a flooded road tunnel on August 1, 2023. The typhoon's relentless heavy rainfall left the area inundated, and the roadways submerged in mud and standing water. Living nearby, The author witnessed the dire conditions firsthand, as the government staff tirelessly utilized specialized equipment to clean and restore the once-swamped road. As the community grapples with the aftermath of the natural disaster, these efforts serve as a testament to the resilience and determination of those involved in the recovery process.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>typhoon,dussuri,fuzhou,china,flood,rainfall,water,road,tunnel,mud,government,trucks,extraction,cleaning,aftermath,southeast,video,equipment,standing,window</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Fuzhou</media:city>
                  <media:country>China</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>CN</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>News</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Tue, 1 Aug 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2646</guid>
                  <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 15:31:51 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2646.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2646.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Devastating flash floods sever rural road in Zhuozhou, North China</media:title>
                  <media:description>In the aftermath of Typhoon Dussuri, the rural area of Zhuozhou in North China has been hit hard by continuous heavy rainfall, leading to flash floods that have wreaked havoc on the region. In a poignant video captured by @XiaoXiao on August 1, 2023, floodwaters can be seen having mercilessly cut a rural road into two, leaving the village isolated and vulnerable. The author, a resident of the affected village, witnessed firsthand the destructive power of nature as the torrential waters inundated the landscape, disrupting the lives of the local community. With the area bordering Beijing to the north, the impact of this natural disaster has been significant, raising concerns about the safety and well-being of the residents in the wake of this devastating flood event.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>floods,typhoon,rainfall,disaster,Zhuozhou,NorthChina,@XiaoXiao,video,rural,road,flashfloods,aftermath,impact,nature,isolated,community,Beijing,heavyrain,devastation,vulnerability</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Zhuozhou</media:city>
                  <media:country>China</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>CN</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>News</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Tue, 1 Aug 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2645</guid>
                  <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 15:31:31 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2645.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2645.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Frenzy in Gomel: throngs of youth storm second-hand store for bargains</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a stunning display of enthusiasm, young people in Gomel, Belarus, were captured in a video frenzy as they lined up outside a second-hand store, eagerly awaiting its opening. The footage, shot by @yyakirill on August 2, 2023, showcased the intensity of the crowd's eagerness, as they pushed and jostled to secure their positions at the store's entrance. The moment the doors finally opened, a whirlwind of excitement engulfed the scene, with each individual vying to be the first to enter. The author aptly captioned the video, "young people literally storm second-hand shops in Gomel. The crowd pushes into the store, and the strength of the doors can only be envied." This snapshot of consumer zeal underscores the allure of thrifting and the growing trend of sustainable shopping among the youth in the city.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>storm,second-hand,shop,gomel,belarus,frenzy,young,people,crowds,pushing,excitement,bargains,thrifting,sustainable,shopping,trend,@yyakirill,video,doors,enthusiasm</media:keywords>
                  <media:city> Gomel</media:city>
                  <media:country>Belarus</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>BY</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Fails and Funnies</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Wed, 2 Aug 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2644</guid>
                  <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 15:35:26 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2644.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2644.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Touching reunion: emotional dog embraces owner after time apart</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a heartwarming display of affection, a golden retriever named Timber captured the internet's attention with a touching video that showcased her emotional reunion with her owner. The video, shot by @timber.the.golden on July 27, 2023, in Chicago, Illinois, USA, depicted Timber eagerly embracing her owner as they were reunited after a few hours apart. The dog lovingly removed the cape from her owner and showered them with cries of joy, clearly showing how deeply she missed her human companion during their brief separation. According to the owner, Timber always gets emotional whenever they are separated and greets them with overwhelming happiness upon their return. The heartwarming footage quickly went viral, resonating with countless viewers who were moved by the undeniable bond between man and his best friend. </media:description>
                  <media:keywords>emotional,dog,reunion,video,Timber,owner,Chicago,Illinois,USA,embrace,cries,groomer,welcome,affection,bond,love,viral,bestfriend,heartwarming,connection,pets</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Chicago, Illinois</media:city>
                  <media:country>United States</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>US</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2643</guid>
                  <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 15:32:29 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2643.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2643.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Enchanting moments: little boy joins the Yangko Dance, spreading joy in Heilongjiang Province, China</media:title>
                  <media:description>In the heartwarming province of Heilongjiang, China, a captivating scene unfolded during a traditional Yangko Dance activity. Local resident @happy captured a delightful moment on July 9, 2023, as a little boy couldn't resist joining the dancers while watching the mesmerizing performance. The Yangko Dance, renowned in northern China, saw its spirit come alive as the young boy wholeheartedly embraced the rhythmic moves, adding his own touch of innocence and joy to the age-old tradition. The video shared by the author quickly went viral, spreading smiles and warmth across social media platforms, reminding us all of the universal language of dance and the pure happiness it brings.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>happy,dance,yangko,china,heilongjiang,traditional,boy,video,viral,community,performance,northern,joy,heartwarming,moment,captivating,innocence,socialmedia,tradition,smiles</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Heilongjiang province</media:city>
                  <media:country>China</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>CN</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Heartwarming</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sun, 9 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2639</guid>
                  <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 08:10:17 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2639.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2639.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Rainy day joy: a hilarious puddle jump gone wrong!</media:title>
                  <media:description>In the picturesque landscapes of Heilongjiang Province, a heartwarming and comical scene unfolded on July 4, 2023. As captured by @sweetandsourplumspine, a father took his young son for a leisurely stroll after a refreshing rain shower. The boy's innocent eyes spotted a small puddle on the roadside, and with unwavering enthusiasm, he declared his intention to jump over it. Brimming with excitement, he took a brave leap, but fate had other plans. Alas, the little adventurer lost his footing, slipping right into the puddle, much to the amusement of his father and the video's viewers. Laughter erupted, and the adorable mishap turned into a heartwarming moment that encapsulated the joy and spontaneity of childhood.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>rain,walk,puddle,jump,slip,cute,laughter,joy,Heilongjiang,father,son,video,July,2023,roadside,adventure,innocence,amusement,childhood,landscapes</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Heilongjiang Province</media:city>
                  <media:country>China</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>CN</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Fails and Funnies</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Tue, 4 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2638</guid>
                  <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 07:49:12 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2638.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2638.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Driving triumph: conquering the flooded tunnel in Shandong's heavy downpour</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a daring and adrenaline-pumping feat, @3ThousandG found himself navigating through a tunnel submerged in water in Shandong province, China, on July 12, 2023. Caught in the midst of a torrential downpour that left the tunnel flooded, he resorted to using his dash cam camera to capture the nerve-wracking journey home. Braving the uncertain depths, he cautiously steered his vehicle through the water-laden tunnel, relieved to witness his car withstand the challenge without malfunctioning. The video serves as a testament to his determination and driving skills, showcasing his triumphant passage through the submerged tunnel amid the elements' fury.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>downpour,tunnel,water,dashcam,driving,flooded,Shandong,China,heavy,video,journey,brave,vehicle,triumph,adrenaline,challenge,weather,floodedtunnel,drivingtriumph,rain</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Shandong</media:city>
                  <media:country>China</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>CN</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Cool</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2637</guid>
                  <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 07:55:49 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2637.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2637.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Typhoon no. 6: from fun to forecast - Araha beach experience captured on video</media:title>
                  <media:description>On August 5th, 2023, @lycomoca captured a thrilling video of strong winds at Araha Beach in Chatan Town, Okinawa Prefecture, Japan. Playfully seeking to experience a typhoon's force, the videographer braved the intense gusts as Typhoon No. 6 raged across the area. Thankfully, the winds eventually subsided on the main island of Okinawa. However, authorities warn that the typhoon is expected to regain strength and move north along the west coast of Kyushu from August 8th to 9th. A forecast map revealed the trajectory, spanning from 12:00 on the 8th to 24:00 on the 9th. Despite the weakened force in the video, the strong winds showcased the awe-inspiring power of nature during this captivating encounter with Typhoon No. 6.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>typhoon,winds,video,experience,fun,Araha Beach,Chatan Town,Okinawa Prefecture,Japan,forecast,map,strength,north,west coast,Kyushu,August,gusts,nature,power,encounter,captivating</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Chatan Town, Okinawa Prefecture</media:city>
                  <media:country>Japan</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>JP</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Weather</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sat, 5 Aug 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2635</guid>
                  <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 07:45:32 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2635.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2635.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Playful corgi Jam from Belarus delights in dandelions</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a heartwarming video captured by @no_fans_only_plants on May 18, 2023, in St. Petersburg, Russia, a delightful corgi named Jam stole the spotlight as he frolicked in a field of dandelions. The playful pup, originally hailing from Belarus, exhibited his exuberance and love for life, embodying the typical corgi spirit. However, what sets Jam apart is his endearing habit of munching on dandelions, which his owner allows without any reservations. Emphasizing the importance of letting pets be themselves, the author expressed a deep understanding and appreciation for Jam's individuality. This heartening tale of a free-spirited corgi cherishing life's simple pleasures reminds us to embrace our loved ones for who they truly are.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>playful,corgi,jam,video,Belarus,dandelions,field,StPetersburg,Russia,pets,love,individuality,free-spirited,happiness,nature,adorable,canine,companionship,joy,outdoor,embrace</media:keywords>
                  <media:city> St. Petersburg</media:city>
                  <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Thu, 18 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2631</guid>
                  <pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 14:06:33 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2631.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2631.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Oscar the cat's unconventional healing: a funny tale of biting plaster and broken leg</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a heartwarming yet peculiar display of feline caregiving, a cat named Oscar, belonging to @oskar_kitty_ from Kharkiv, Ukraine, was captured on video tenderly attacking his owner's broken foot and biting on the plaster. In the footage shared on July 17, 2023, Oscar's owner jokingly revealed that the cat's unusual behavior served as a form of treatment. Evidently, Oscar had developed a fondness for nibbling on his owner's leg, and the plaster provided a surprisingly effective and protective solution. The four-year-old feline's unexpected aid showcased the deep bond between pets and their owners, demonstrating how even in their playful antics, cats can express concern and offer comfort during times of need.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>cat,oscar,kitty,ukraine,kharkiv,video,attack,broken,foot,plaster,treatment,bites,healing,love,pets,owner,bonding,playful,caregiving,feline</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Kharkiv</media:city>
                  <media:country>Ukraine</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>UA</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2630</guid>
                  <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 08:09:39 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2630.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2630.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Unexpected chair collapse turns dining mishap into laughter at Semarang restaurant</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a heartwarming yet amusing incident at a restaurant in Semarang, Indonesia, a woman had a lighthearted response to an unexpected mishap. On July 18, 2023, @sambel.pinuk.alisamu captured a video that quickly gained attention on social media. The footage showed the woman falling off her chair as it collapsed beneath her while she was eating. However, instead of being flustered or embarrassed, she laughed it off with good humor. The man she was dining with rushed to her aid and helped her back up. According to the author it seemed that the chair had shifted and hit a gap between the tiles, leading to the unexpected accident. The heartwarming display of laughter and camaraderie in the face of a minor mishap brought a smile to many as the video went viral, reminding us all to find joy in life's little moments.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>restaurant,semarang,indonesia,video,woman,chair,collapse,unexpected,help,dining,laughter,mishap,socialmedia,humor,viral,camaraderie,joy,permission,tiles,accident</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Semarang </media:city>
                  <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>ID</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Fails and Funnies</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2629</guid>
                  <pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 14:04:14 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2629.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2629.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Enigmatic equine enigma: a horse's puzzled encounter with a horse coat</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a heartwarming yet amusing scene at @abbottsviewlivery in Aston Abbotts, UK, a delightful video captured by the account owner on June 11, 2023, showcased their horse donning a horse coat. The comical attire covered the horse entirely, except for two eye holes, leaving the majestic creature looking perplexed and inquiring about the peculiar get-up. As the laughter of the onlookers filled the air, the horse appeared to be seeking answers from its amused companions, making for an endearing moment that truly highlighted the unique bond between humans and their equine companions.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>horse,coat,confused,video,Aston Abbotts,UK,laughter,equine,companions,amusement,head-to-hoof,enigma,bond,unique,moment,animals,livery,eye holes,inquiring,delightful,June 11</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Aston Abbotts</media:city>
                  <media:country>United Kingdom</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>GB</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2626</guid>
                  <pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 14:00:21 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2626.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2626.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Reckless white SUV causes collision with street light: violation of traffic rules in Jiangxi Province, China</media:title>
                  <media:description>In Jiangxi Province, China, a recent traffic incident captured on video by @Jiangxitrafficpolice has brought attention to the dangers of reckless driving. On June 15, 2023, a driver was maneuvering their vehicle along a normal route when disaster struck. As they passed an uphill section, a white SUV suddenly appeared, overtaking on the hill and violating traffic regulations. The video shows the desperate attempt of the driver to avoid the SUV, but tragically, they collided with a street light post instead. The footage clearly highlights the white SUV's failure to adhere to road rules as the main cause of the accident. As a result, no one was hurt.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>accident,video,traffic,jiangxi,china,collision,streetlight,SUV,overtaking,hill,regulations,responsible,driving,safety,road,incident,reckless,footage,violation,driver</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Jiangxi</media:city>
                  <media:country>China</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>CN</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Road accidents</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2625</guid>
                  <pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 13:59:40 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2625.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2625.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Unusual collision in Jiangsu: scooters smile and carry on despite impact at crossing</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a peculiar incident captured by @trafficsafetyeveryday in Jiangsu Province, China, on July 24, 2023, two motorists collided in front of a moving car at a crossing area. The collision involved a woman driving an electric scooter and a delivery rider, both also on electric scooters. Surprisingly, despite the impact, the two parties showed an unexpected reaction. Instead of anger and frustration, they exchanged smiles after checking for injuries and continued on their way. The scene left the author intrigued, leading them to save the video. The incident serves as a unique reminder of how even in the midst of accidents, a moment of understanding and positivity can arise on the roads.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>collision,motorists,Jiangsu,China,video,crossing,traffic lights,electric bicycles,delivery rider,interesting,smile,accident,understanding,positivity,roads,@trafficsafetyeveryday,July 24,2023,intriguing,motorists,movement</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Jiangsu</media:city>
                  <media:country>China</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>CN</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Road accidents</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2624</guid>
                  <pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 13:57:46 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2624.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2624.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Friend's car narrowly avoids major collision with large truck on rural road in Heilongjiang Province</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a heart-stopping incident captured by @trafficsafetyeveryday on July 20, 2023, in Heilongjiang Province, China, a group of friends experienced a harrowing moment while driving to the countryside. As they were passing through a rural road, their friend's car, positioned in front of the author's vehicle, collided with the body of a large truck. The tense situation unfolded when the truck abruptly slammed on its brakes, causing the vehicle to lose control and veer towards the back of the truck. Fortunately, luck was on their side as the collision was not as severe as it could have been, considering it occurred just as they were nearly past each other. No harm done.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>accident,traffic,safety,video,friends,car,truck,collision,countryside,rural,road,Heilongjiang,China,brake,control,closecall,tense,vigilance,luck,reminder</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Heilongjiang Province</media:city>
                  <media:country>China</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>CN</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Road accidents</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2623</guid>
                  <pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 13:55:37 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2623.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2623.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Laughing in the face of disaster: Cotabato City's titanic-style flood adventure</media:title>
                  <media:description>In the midst of a devastating flood in Cotabato City, Philippines, @‌_kathlilies captured a heartwarming video that showcased the remarkable resilience and humor of the residents. Waist-high waters flooded their home, but one of them ventured inside, playfully recreating a scene from the movie "Titanic" in a lighthearted manner. The video, filmed on July 12, 2023, quickly went viral, spreading joy and inspiration worldwide. Despite the chaos and destruction caused by the flood, the residents' ability to find humor amidst adversity served as a powerful reminder of the human spirit's indomitable nature. </media:description>
                  <media:keywords>flood,resilience,humor,CotabatoCity,Philippines,video,Titanic,lighthearted,disaster,community,unity,inspiration,viral,chaos,destruction,adversity,laughter,camaraderie,uncertainty,positivity</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Cotabato City</media:city>
                  <media:country>Philippines</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>PH</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Fails and Funnies</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2621</guid>
                  <pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 08:00:43 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2621.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2621.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Ezro John's hilarious CPR lesson: from jokes to saving lives</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a video captured on July 21, 2023, at Saint Louis University in Baguio City, Philippines, a medical technologist student named Ezro, with the social media handle @‌ezrojohn_rmt, took part in Basic Life Support training. Amidst the CPR lesson, Ezro humorously slapped the mannequin patient, jokingly captioning the moment, "POV: You are saving lives but has anger issues. Doesn't want to wake up, sooo." However, as the training progressed, Ezro and his fellow students were taught the proper and serious way of performing CPR. Learning the vital techniques to potentially save lives, the lighthearted start of the session eventually transitioned into a valuable lesson on the importance of the life-saving skill.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>cpr,training,medical,technologist,student,mannequin,lesson,humor,serious,life-saving,skills,education,practice,Saint Louis University,Baguio City,Philippines,video,caption,CPR training,Basic Life Support</media:keywords>
                  <media:city> Baguio City</media:city>
                  <media:country>Philippines</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>PH</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Fails and Funnies</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2620</guid>
                  <pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 08:01:41 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2620.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2620.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Meet the canine chauffeurs: Jack Russells take the wheel in Minsk's unconventional photo shoot!</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a captivating and unconventional photo shoot in Minsk, Belarus, Dmitry Zhilinsky, a talented trainer and owner of three Jack Russells, showcased his furry companions' incredible skills behind the wheel. Captured by @luckyshowby on August 1, 2021, the video featured Rick, Lucky, and Eva comfortably seated in the car, with one of them seemingly attempting to take the driver's role. Not only does Dmitry arrange corporate performances with his furry companions, but he also organizes delightful photo shoots that showcase the dogs' extraordinary abilities. This heartwarming display of intelligence and companionship between man and his loyal Jack Russells is sure to put a smile on anyone's face and highlight the incredible bond between humans and their four-legged friends.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>jack russells,dogs,car,driving,photo shoot,Minsk,Belarus,Dmitry Zhilinsky,canine,chauffeurs,talent,companions,intelligence,performance,video,pets,animals,wheel,corporate,@luckyshowby,August 1</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Minsk</media:city>
                  <media:country>Belarus</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>BY</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sun, 1 Aug 2021</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2619</guid>
                  <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 07:48:24 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2619.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2619.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Persistent feline pursuit: hilarious toilet time with a tenacious cat</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a comical and relatable scene, @badnotwolf from Vinnytsia, Ukraine, shared a video of his persistent cat, Roxy attempting to join him in the bathroom. On July 11, 2023, while seated in front of the camera, the cat made numerous unsuccessful leaps towards its owner, who was simply seeking a moment of relaxation on the toilet. With only the legs visible in the video, viewers were left amused by the feline's determined efforts to be part of the action.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>cat,toilet,video,legs,Ukraine,Vinnytsia,July,2023,hilarious,comical,pet,owner,persistent,attempts,relaxation,funny,feline,jump,bathroom,amusing,scene</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Vinnytsia</media:city>
                  <media:country>Ukraine</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>UA</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2618</guid>
                  <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 13:20:43 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2618.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2618.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Adorable foster kittens indulge in a 'paws'-itively messy drink!</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a heartwarming scene captured by @emiliexfosters on July 18, 2023, in Milwaukee, USA, three adorable foster kittens were caught on video enjoying a drink from a bowl. However, one mischievous kitten had its legs dipped into the liquid as it drank, resulting in a cute yet messy moment. With quick reflexes, the author lifted the little one out of the bowl, revealing its front paws soaked in the brown liquid used for weaning them. Despite the adorable mishap, the sight of these tiny furballs brought smiles to viewers' faces, showcasing the joys of caring for foster animals.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>adorable,foster,kittens,video,drink,bowl,legs,soaked,weaning,messy,cute,moment,reflexes,furballs,caring,animals,pets,@emiliexfosters,Milwaukee,USA</media:keywords>
                  <media:city> Milwaukee </media:city>
                  <media:country>United States</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>US</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2615</guid>
                  <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 13:22:47 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2615.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2615.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Capturing the moon's enigmatic beauty: a nighttime zoom adventure in Texas, USA</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a captivating night under the Texas, USA skys on August 2, 2023, @alexanmurphy unveiled a breathtaking video of the moon, showcasing its enigmatic beauty like never before. Armed with a Nikon COOLPIX P900 camera, she skillfully zoomed in and out, revealing the moon's intricate details against the backdrop of the dark night atmosphere. The author's mesmerizing footage serves as a reminder of the wonders that lie above us each night, awaiting discovery and appreciation by those with an eye for beauty and a passion for exploring the cosmos.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>night,moon,video,zoom,details,Texas,USA,Nikon,COOLPIX,P900,clear,atmosphere,beauty,celestial,sky,captivate,enchanting,mesmerizing,advanced,wonders,exploration</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Texas</media:city>
                  <media:country>United States</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>US</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Cool</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Wed, 2 Aug 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2614</guid>
                  <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 13:18:10 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2614.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2614.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Boomer's midnight mischief: possum party at home!</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a humorous and slightly mischievous incident captured by @ndnchic33 on June 17, 2023, in Chelsea, Alabama, USA, her adorable dog, Boomer, became the center of attention. The video shows Boomer lounging on the couch late at night, accompanied by an unexpected guest - possums! Apparently, Boomer had invited his possum friend over to join him indoors, much to his owner's surprise. In the video, we hear the author playfully scolding Boomer, reminding him that bringing friends into the house is not allowed. The adorable footage showcases Boomer's nocturnal adventures and his owner's delightful reaction to the unusual situation. It's a heartwarming reminder of the unexpected antics our furry friends can get up to when the world sleeps.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>night,dog,Boomer,possums,couch,house,video,Chelsea,Alabama,USA,friends,mischief,adorable,owner,surprise,nocturnal,antics,furry,funny,pets</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Chelsea, Alabama</media:city>
                  <media:country>United States</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>US</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2613</guid>
                  <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 08:13:17 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2613.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2613.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Enchanting double rainbow delights travelers in Rakov, Belarus</media:title>
                  <media:description>On July 30, 2023, a mesmerizing sight graced the city of Rakov, Belarus, as @lucyfer_da captured a stunning video of a rainbow during her return journey. After a trip to Nalibokskaya Pushcha, she noticed a remarkably bright and clear rainbow hovering over a distant lake. Throughout the drive, the rainbow remained elusive, often obscured by trees and buildings. However, as they ventured onto the track and turned a corner, the rainbow revealed its full splendor, stretching wider than the entire roadway. Onlookers were left in awe, with people pulling over to capture the spectacle with their cameras. Curiously, there was no rain preceding or following the rainbow, but within its vivid hues, a fine drizzle could be seen, akin to droplets from a spray bottle. As if one rainbow wasn't enough, a larger, fainter one appeared above the brilliant arc, adding to the enchantment of the moment. Nature's breathtaking display left a lasting impression on all who bore witness to this extraordinary occurrence.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>rainbow,rakov,belarus,video,lake,trees,buildings,travel,enchanting,double,stunning,splendor,onlookers,cameras,drizzle,nature,display,breathtaking,moment,occurrence</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Rakov</media:city>
                  <media:country>Belarus</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>BY</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Cool</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2612</guid>
                  <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 08:14:07 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2612.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2612.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Swaddle buddies: heartwarming video shows cat and baby bonding in Ciamis, Indonesia</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a heartwarming display of unlikely companionship, a video captured by @sheisseu malikeymouse on July 22, 2023, in Ciamis, Indonesia, has taken the internet by storm. The footage shows a swaddled baby peacefully lying next to a swaddled cat, with the feline seemingly unfazed by the tiny human's presence. According to the account owner, the cat has a penchant for disturbing the child, prompting the clever idea of swaddling them both together. </media:description>
                  <media:keywords>swaddle,baby,cat,companionship,bond,video,Indonesia,Ciamis,heartwarming,pets,harmony,unexpected,love,animals,internet,admiration,unique,clever,touching,footage</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Ciamis</media:city>
                  <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>ID</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Heartwarming</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2611</guid>
                  <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 08:15:55 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2611.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2611.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Midnight motorbike melody: barking serenade by excited street dogs</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a captivating video captured by @abdullaev.222 on July 9, 2023, in Saratov Rakhova, Russia, a group of street dogs showcased their curious behavior towards a motorbike. As the rider turned on the engine, the dogs immediately came rushing towards him, barking excitedly. However, whenever the engine was switched off, they would retreat, only to return with renewed enthusiasm once it roared to life again. The intriguing scene unfolded during the night when the rider stopped to answer a phone call, catching the dogs' attention and prompting him to start recording the delightful encounter. It's a heartwarming reminder of the special bond between humans and their four-legged companions, even in unexpected and amusing circumstances.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>motorbike,dogs,street,night,Russia,Saratov,barking,excitement,video,capture,curious,engine,retreat,enthusiasm,phone,call,recording,bond,humans,companions</media:keywords>
                  <media:city> Saratov Rakhova</media:city>
                  <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sun, 9 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2609</guid>
                  <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 08:12:32 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2609.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2609.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Unsuspecting seaside silliness: a chair, a wave, and laughter in Banda Aceh!</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a moment of pure beachside amusement, an unexpected encounter with a massive wave turned into a hilarious spectacle for @aleshafamily_ on July 6, 2023, in Banda Aceh, Indonesia. Seated comfortably in her chair by the water's edge, little did she anticipate the waves reaching her spot. As if to playfully challenge her, a colossal wave surged forward just as she attempted to escape its reach with her chair. Instead of escaping unscathed, she found herself tumbling onto the sandy shore, bursts of laughter echoing around her. The video she captured quickly spread, showcasing the joyous mishap that made the internet chuckle along with her seaside antics.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>beach,waves,chair,laughter,video,unexpected,Banda Aceh,Indonesia,amusement,moment,water,edge,hilarious,encounter,summer,sea,shoreline,sand,mishap,internet</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Banda Aceh</media:city>
                  <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>ID</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Fails and Funnies</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Thu, 6 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2607</guid>
                  <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 08:03:37 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2607.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2607.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Adorable cashier's assistant: the beloved parking lot cat of Odessa, Ukraine</media:title>
                  <media:description>In the bustling city of Odessa, Ukraine, a heartwarming scene unfolded at a local parking lot on July 29, 2023. @40medok, an observant passerby, captured a heart-melting moment as a charming cat sat gracefully at the cashier's window, patiently awaiting attention. With affectionate pets and gentle caresses, the feline earned its rightful place as the "Cashier's Assistant." Customers and visitors passing by couldn't resist showering the cat with respect and tenderness, creating a sense of community around this adorable furball. This endearing sight has become a cherished part of the parking lot's atmosphere, leaving everyone with a smile as they complete their errands, knowing that a little feline guardian watches over them.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>adorable,cat,cashier,window,parking lot,Odessa,Ukraine,pet,picture,baby,cute,good,respect,tenderness,community,furball,atmosphere,guardian,smile,errands</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Odessa</media:city>
                  <media:country>Ukraine</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>UA</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2605</guid>
                  <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 07:59:28 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2605.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2605.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Nature's fury unleashed: lightning strikes and flames explode in Shijiazhuang</media:title>
                  <media:description>On July 24, 2023, in Shijiazhuang, northern China, a startling and unintentional event was captured on video by @HomelessYuanyuan. As she stood in front of her apartment window with her mobile phone, attempting to capture a street scene during a rainstorm and thunder, lightning struck the transformer below her building. The intense impact caused sparks of flames to erupt, scattering fiery fragments in all directions. Nature's fury was unleashed, and in a split second, the author found herself witnessing a breathtaking display of raw power and danger.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>lightning,sparks,flames,explosion,rainstorm,thunder,Shijiazhuang,China,video,mobile,window,street,nature,fury,power,danger,unpredictability,awe,humbled,@HomelessYuanyuan</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Shijiazhuang</media:city>
                  <media:country>China</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>CN</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>News</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2604</guid>
                  <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 13:16:50 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2604.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2604.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Terrifying Yokohama guerrilla rainstorm unleashes chaos with its fierce winds and torrential downpour</media:title>
                  <media:description>In Yokohama, Japan, on August 1, 2023, @Tomo_YNU captured a chilling video of a rainstorm known as Guerrilla. This local phenomenon is characterized by an unpredictable formation of cumulonimbus clouds, resulting in a short but intense downpour of over 100 mm per hour of rain. The video showcases the fury of the Guerrilla rainstorm, with powerful winds swaying trees in its path. The dangerous nature of this event highlights the need for caution and preparedness during such occurrences in Yokohama.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>rainstorm,guerrilla,yokohama,japan,video,downpour,cumulonimbus,clouds,intense,winds,trees,dangerous,unpredictable,weather,phenomenon,local,short,mm,hour,rain</media:keywords>
                  <media:city> Yokohama</media:city>
                  <media:country>Japan</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>JP</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Weather</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Tue, 1 Aug 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2601</guid>
                  <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 13:12:08 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2601.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2601.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Tokyo's sideways rain: nature's dance of wind and water</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a mesmerizing spectacle captured on August 1, 2023, from the heart of Tokyo, Japan, @4H6M8u0YmemZwmj shared a breathtaking video of sideways rain cascading down window panes. As nature's elements collided, the wind's mighty force compelled the raindrops to dance sideways, creating a captivating display of nature's power and beauty. The video serves as a vivid reminder of the unpredictable yet awe-inspiring wonders of the natural world, leaving viewers in awe of the harmonious choreography between wind and water. </media:description>
                  <media:keywords>wind,rain,sideways,video,Tokyo,Japan,nature,spectacle,mesmerizing,window,panes,dance,elements,force,beauty,power,display,awe,urban,landscape</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Tokyo </media:city>
                  <media:country>Japan</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>JP</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Weather</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Tue, 1 Aug 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2600</guid>
                  <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 13:12:22 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2600.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2600.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Playful and obedient: Khryapa's impressive 'swim' command!</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a heartwarming video captured by @mokryi_nosik_ on June 17, 2020, in Voronezh, Russia, her beloved dog, Khryapa, stole the spotlight with her incredible obedience and playful nature. The footage shows @mokryi_nosik_ talking to Khryapa in one of the rooms, when suddenly, the clever canine dashes off towards the bathroom. Without hesitation, Khryapa leaps into the bathtub, showcasing her impressive execution of the "swim" command. The three-year-old furry friend proves to be not only obedient but also full of joy and enthusiasm. Her charming antics have won the hearts of viewers worldwide, leaving a lasting impression of her delightful personality and the strong bond between her and her owner.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>playful,obedient,dog,swim,command,video,Khryapa,Voronezh,Russia,bathtub,bathroom,three years old,pet,canine,joy,love,bond,clever,cute,charming</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Voronezh</media:city>
                  <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2598</guid>
                  <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 10:57:32 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2598.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2598.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Playful corgi's adorable 'poof' act delights internet in St. Petersburg, Russia!</media:title>
                  <media:description>In an endearing and amusing video that captured hearts on social media, a Corgi named Leo from St. Petersburg, Russia, showcased his unique talent for playing "dead." The video, shared by @prokopenkokate on April 29, 2023, depicts Leo sitting peacefully on the floor before his owner mimics a shooting gesture with her hands. Surprisingly, the adorable pup immediately flops down, pretending to be "shot" as part of a playful command he has mastered. As a reward for his impressive performance, Leo eagerly awaits a treat, proving that his favorite command is the delightful and harmless "poof," leaving viewers charmed by this clever and lovable canine's antics.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>playful,corgi,leo,video,internet,acting,dog,Russia,St. Petersburg,pet,owner,gun,pretend,cute,charm,humor,social media,adorable,command,sweet</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>St. Petersburg</media:city>
                  <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sat, 29 Apr 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2595</guid>
                  <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 10:53:38 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2595.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2595.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>First-time rider's mishap: girl's scooter adventure ends with a bump!</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a candid video captured by @wkmzxuk_ on July 15, 2023, in the City of Soligorsk, Minsk region, Belarus, a young girl's first-time experience with an electronic scooter took an unexpected turn. With enthusiasm and excitement, she hopped onto the scooter but found herself struggling to control its speed. Unaware of the gears and unfamiliar with braking, she careened toward a stationary sign near a building, unable to halt her momentum. The result was a comical yet cautionary collision, reminding viewers of the importance of learning the basics before embarking on new adventures. While the girl's misadventure might have left her a little shaken, it undoubtedly served as a valuable lesson for both her and others who dare to ride the scooters for the first time.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>scooter,mishap,video,girl,first-time,adventure,excitement,gears,braking,collision,cautionary,comical,lessons,learning,electronic,speed,sign,building,Belarus,Soligorsk</media:keywords>
                  <media:city> City of Soligorsk, Minsk region</media:city>
                  <media:country>Belarus</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>BY</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Fails and Funnies</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2594</guid>
                  <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 10:53:05 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2594.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2594.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Tranquil moments: Tokyo's beloved dog relishes in shallow creek at favorite park</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a heartwarming scene captured on June 24, 2023, in Tokyo, Japan, @mr.donbei_inu shared a delightful video of his beloved dog finding sheer bliss in a small, slow creek at their favorite park. The four-legged companion appeared completely at ease, comfortably resting its head on the surface of the shallow water, joyfully savoring the gentle flow around it. Unlike most dogs, this furry friend chose not to swim but found pure contentment in merely basking in the refreshing water. With a serene expression, the canine seemed to have discovered a little piece of paradise amidst the bustling city, making this tranquil spot its most cherished destination in the park.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>dog,creek,park,Tokyo,Japan,chilling,water,shallow,serene,bliss,favorite,video,pet,companion,contentment,relaxation,joy,tranquility,peaceful,happiness</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Tokyo</media:city>
                  <media:country>Japan</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>JP</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2593</guid>
                  <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 10:52:42 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2593.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2593.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                     </channel>
                  </rss>
                