<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
            <rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
            xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
            xmlns:openSearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearchrss/1.0/"
            xmlns:dfpvideo="http://api.google.com/dfpvideo"
            xmlns:tms="http://data.tmsapi.com/v1.1"
            version="2.0">
              <channel>
                <title>ViralBear videos</title>
                <dfpvideo:version>2</dfpvideo:version>
                  
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Enigmatic light figure plays ball over St James' Park</media:title>
                          <media:description>In a captivating video captured by @IanScott_01 on October 2, 2023, at St James' Park in Newcastle, UK, a remarkable nighttime spectacle unfolded. The footage revealed a colossal light figure of a man hovering over the iconic stadium, seemingly engaged in an ethereal game of football. The figure moved in perfect harmony with the ball's every twist and turn, creating an enchanting display of synchronized movement that left spectators in awe. </media:description>
                          <media:keywords>night,spectacle,light,figure,man,ball,Newcastle,UK,video,captivating,ethereal,football,synchronized,movement,mysterious,enchanting,event,St James' Park,awe,sky</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Newcastle</media:city>
                          <media:country>United Kingdom</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>GB</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Cool,Sport</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Mon, 2 Oct 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>3162</guid>
                          <pubDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2023 14:16:11 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/3162.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/3162.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Severe weather delays Austin FC vs. LA Galaxy game at Q2 Stadium in Austin, Texas</media:title>
                          <media:description>Severe weather conditions wreaked havoc in Austin, Texas, USA, on the night of September 24, 2023, forcing a delay in the highly anticipated match between Austin FC and LA Galaxy at Q2 Stadium. The stadium was shrouded in mist, with spectators waving green flags as gusty winds and hail battered the area. Q2 Stadium officials announced a mandatory shelter-in-place protocol after lightning was detected within the safety perimeter. The National Weather Service had issued warnings about showers and thunderstorms in the region.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>severe weather,delay,Austin FC,LA Galaxy,Q2 Stadium,mist,gusts,hail,safety,protocol,rain,thunderstorms,spectators,flags,postponement,National Weather Service,Austin,Texas,game,Sunday night</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Austin, Texas</media:city>
                          <media:country>United States</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>US</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>News,Sport,Weather</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>3126</guid>
                          <pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2023 10:31:01 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/3126.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/3126.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Climate Protesters evicted from Arthur Ashe Stadium after halting U.S. open women's semi-final</media:title>
                          <media:description>In a dramatic turn of events at the U.S. Open women's semi-final held at Arthur Ashe Stadium in New York City on September 7, 2023, climate protesters brought the tennis match between American Coco Gauff and Czech Karolina Muchova to a standstill for nearly an hour. The demonstrators, rallying against fossil fuel use, managed to infiltrate the stadium and stage a protest, causing a significant delay in the highly anticipated match. However, their disruption was short-lived as security swiftly removed the protesters from the venue, allowing the game to finally resume. </media:description>
                          <media:keywords>protesters,tennis,disruption,climate,fossil,fuel,match,security,removed,delay,stadium,New York,U.S. Open,Arthur Ashe,American,Czech,Gauff,Muchova,demonstration,urgency</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>New York</media:city>
                          <media:country>United States</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>US</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>News,Sport</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Thu, 7 Sep 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>2981</guid>
                          <pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 12:49:16 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2981.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2981.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>High-flying slackline duo: thrilling moves in Fronalpstock</media:title>
                          <media:description>In a jaw-dropping display of balance and skill,  @timodermatt and @_lipsie_ recently wowed spectators as they defied gravity on a rope suspended in the breathtaking Fronalpstock mountains of Schwyz,  Switzerland. Captured on video by @samuelvolery on June 5, 2023, the two talented slackliners executed a mesmerizing array of maneuvers high above the Swiss landscape. Their gravity-defying feats showcased not only their unwavering focus but also their unmatched coordination and courage. Against the backdrop of the majestic Swiss Alps, this daring duo's performance left onlookers and viewers in awe. </media:description>
                          <media:keywords>mountains,slacklining,Switzerland,Fronalpstock,daring,balance,skill,rope,high-flying,performance,courage,coordination,awe-inspiring,nature,adrenaline,adventure,breathtaking,outdoor,Samuel Volery,Timo Dermatt,Lipsie</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Schwyz</media:city>
                          <media:country>Switzerland</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>CH</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Cool,Sport</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Mon, 5 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>2968</guid>
                          <pubDate>Sun, 10 Sep 2023 14:20:17 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2968.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2968.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Remembering a legend: one-minute silence for Sir Michael Parkinson at Yorkshire County Cricket Club game</media:title>
                          <media:description>On August 17, 2023, the world bid a fond farewell to esteemed broadcaster Sir Michael Parkinson, who graced television screens for an impressive seven decades. As news of his passing spread, Yorkshire County Cricket Club's match against Hampshire Cricket at Clifton Park, Rotherham, South Yorkshire, England, UK became a poignant moment of remembrance, as players and fans observed a solemn one-minute silence in his honor. Sir Michael Parkinson's enduring legacy was marked by his iconic talk show, where he interviewed global luminaries, etching his name into entertainment history. Passing away peacefully at the age of 88 after a brief illness, Sir Michael Parkinson's influence on the broadcasting world remains timeless, leaving an irreplaceable void.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>broadcasting,legacy,tribute,interview,cricket,legend,remembrance,passing,television,icon,Yorkshire,silence,farewell,entertainment,Rotherham,Michael Parkinson,Hampshire,peace,decades,screen</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Rotherham, South Yorkshire, England</media:city>
                          <media:country>United Kingdom</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>GB</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>News,Sport</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>2772</guid>
                          <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 10:27:30 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2772.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2772.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Cortnee Vine's winning penalty ignites joyous celebration at Cathy Freeman Park as Matildas secure semi-finals spot in Women's World Cup</media:title>
                          <media:description>In a historic moment for Australian sports, Cathy Freeman Park outside Stadium Australia in Sydney Olympic Park witnessed a jubilant eruption of cheers and celebration as the national women's soccer team, the Matildas, clinched a dramatic victory over France in the Quarter Finals of the FIFA Women’s World Cup™ on August 12, 2023. Captured by @accorstadium, the atmosphere was electrifying as fans gathered to support their team, who ultimately emerged triumphant in a nail-biting penalty shootout. The winning penalty, skillfully converted by Cortnee Vine, sent the Matildas into the Semi-Finals of the tournament, marking a memorable 'Where were you moment' in Australian sporting history. With the park echoing with chants of victory and national pride, the scene symbolized the passion and dedication of both the team and its fervent supporters. The Matildas' remarkable journey continues as they prepare to face their next challenge with unwavering enthusiasm.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>celebration,victory,soccer,Matildas,fans,history,moment,Quarter Finals,France,shootout,Sydney,Olympic Park,excitement,passion,pride,triumph,Semi-Finals,tournament,Cathy Freeman Park,Cortnee Vine</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Sydney </media:city>
                          <media:country>Australia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>AU</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>News,Sport,Heartwarming</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>2699</guid>
                          <pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2023 09:32:38 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2699.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2699.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Unforgettable victory: Australia triumphs over France in epic penalty shootout to secure historic semifinal spot</media:title>
                          <media:description>In a historic match that will be etched into the annals of sporting history, Australia's women's football team emerged triumphant over France in a nail-biting penalty shootout during the quarter-finals of the Women's World Cup. The encounter, held at Brisbane's Suncorp Stadium in Australia on August 12, 2023, saw both teams battle relentlessly, resulting in a goalless deadlock even after extra time. The tension reached its zenith as the penalty shootout unfolded, with Australia's goalkeeper Mackenzie Arnold rising as the hero by thwarting three French penalty attempts and even making her mark with a penalty miss of her own. However, it was the young Vicki Becho's unfortunate collision with the post on the 12th spot-kick that swung the pendulum in Australia's favor, propelling them to a 7-6 victory. The stadium erupted in a cacophony of cheers and exultation from the Australian fans, marking a historic first entry into the Women's World Cup semifinals for the co-hosts. @markgottlieb captured a video footage showing the celebration erupting after the penalty goal. </media:description>
                          <media:keywords>Australia,women's football,historic match,sporting history,France,penalty shootout,quarter-finals,Women's World Cup,Brisbane,Suncorp Stadium,goalless deadlock,extra time,Mackenzie Arnold,hero,Vicki Becho,collision,post,pendulum swing,victory,Australian fans,Women's World Cup semifinals,celebration,video footage</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Brisbane</media:city>
                          <media:country>Australia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>AU</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Sport,News</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>2697</guid>
                          <pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2023 09:32:05 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2697.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2697.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>How to quickly cross the river? Vietnamese surfer conquers new heights!</media:title>
                          <media:description>Vietnamese surfer, @chuongfoil, made waves in Dien Chau district, Nghe An province, Vietnam, on April 23, 2023, with his exceptional hydrofoil surfing skills. After dedicating two years to rigorous training, he finally achieved success, gliding effortlessly on the river's surface. Overcoming initial struggles where he frequently sank, @chuongfoil's perseverance and determination paid off, allowing him to conquer the water's edge with finesse and mastery. </media:description>
                          <media:keywords>surfing,hydrofoil,lake,Vietnam,@chuongfoil,adventure,water,skill,perseverance,success,training,mastery,waves,gliding,surfboard,journey,transformation,enthusiasm,determination,athlete</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Dien Chau district, Nghe An province</media:city>
                          <media:country>Vietnam</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>VN</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Sport</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Sun, 23 Apr 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>2497</guid>
                          <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 12:53:46 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2497.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2497.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Remarkable skills: young basketball prodigy amazes all at Ketintang vocational school</media:title>
                          <media:description>In a captivating video captured by @suryaabaiq on May 29th, 2023, at Ketintang Vocational School in Surabaya, East Java, Indonesia, a small boy displayed extraordinary basketball skills. The footage showcased the young prodigy dribbling and shooting with remarkable precision, never missing a shot. The boy's ability to excel in the sport despite his tender age left everyone astonished. His talent on the school court demonstrated an exceptional level of skill and potential. Without a doubt, this young basketball player has a bright future ahead, captivating onlookers with his remarkable abilities.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>basketball,prodigy,skills,talent,amazing,young,child,Surabaya,Indonesia,Ketintang,school,court,dribbling,shooting,precision,astonishing,future,potential,video,captured</media:keywords>
                          <media:city> Surabaya, East Java</media:city>
                          <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>ID</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Sport</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Mon, 29 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>2420</guid>
                          <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/8e66e8e9-0fe0-4479-87a6-900a3d912f85.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/231e7501-a0a3-443d-a423-06abfb52b67b.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Unbelievable goal from corner kick leaves football fans in awe</media:title>
                          <media:description>In an extraordinary football match held in Jambi, Indonesia, on March 12, 2023, an incredible goal from a corner kick left fans speechless. The breathtaking moment was captured by @mrival__ who shared the video on social media, instantly gaining viral attention. The footage shows a player confidently stepping up to take a corner kick, but what unfolded next was nothing short of astonishing. As the ball left the player's foot, it soared through the air with remarkable precision, curving towards the net. To the astonishment of everyone present, the ball sailed past defenders and found the back of the net, resulting in an unforgettable goal.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>goal,corner,football,rare,video,Jambi,Indonesia,kick,scoring,ball,player,high-five,fans,viral,astonishing,precision,excitement,unforgettable,unpredictable,skill</media:keywords>
                          <media:city> Jambi</media:city>
                          <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>ID</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Sport</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>2243</guid>
                          <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 19:56:01 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/98c3fddd-5387-43b4-a5ab-2c82e10f252f.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/1ae823c4-df7a-4c47-aa8c-b46f95cc7e00.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>West Ham's epic celebration in Prague: players party all night after Europa Conference League triumph</media:title>
                          <media:description>West Ham United players extended their victorious celebrations into the night after their historic win in the Europa Conference League. Following their triumph at the final held in Prague, Czech Republic, the team opted to skip their initial flight back to London and continue reveling in the moment. The club had wisely arranged for two flights, allowing the players an additional four hours to bask in their achievement.

Captured by @MrMarkCorner on 8th June, 2023, a video from the festivities showcased the players back at their hotel, embracing the joyous atmosphere. The caption accompanying the video read, "Back at the hotel with the boys! Love you." It was a testament to the camaraderie and unity that fueled their success throughout the competition. </media:description>
                          <media:keywords>party,celebration,West Ham,Europa Conference League,win,Prague,Czech Republic,players,flight,London,hotel,teammates,unity,camaraderie,victory,joy,revelry,memorable,unforgettable,championship,elation</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Prague </media:city>
                          <media:country>Czechia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>CZ</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Sport</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Thu, 8 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>2226</guid>
                          <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 16:50:01 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/85cd9f13-1605-4611-903b-b98a4dac7a67.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/fcf838cd-52a4-46ec-95ac-4f79ab59cd6d.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Manchester City's epic victory propels them to the Champions League Final, igniting fan euphoria</media:title>
                          <media:description>In a stunning turn of events, Manchester City emerged triumphant in the semi-finals of the UEFA Champions League, securing a resounding 4-0 victory against Real Madrid. The match took place on the 17th of May, 2023, at Manchester's home ground, Etihad Stadium, sending shockwaves through the football world.

The atmosphere in the stadium was electric as fans eagerly awaited the kickoff. The tension was palpable, with both teams vying for a spot in the prestigious final. As the match unfolded, Manchester City exhibited a display of extraordinary skill, leaving the Spanish giants stunned and struggling to keep up.

@SpibySalford, a devoted Manchester City fan, captured the moment of celebration in a video clip from the stands. Overwhelmed with emotions, he shared his thoughts on social media, writing, "Can't even begin to process that!!! Absolutely unbelievable night... all them years of getting the piss took out of us, all the laughing at us! Never have I seen a performance as good as that... MANCHESTER CITY I WILL LOVE YOU FOREVER."

The victory not only secured Manchester City's place in the finals but also marked a significant milestone for the club. Over the years, they had faced criticism and skepticism, with many doubting their ability to compete at the highest level. However, with this commanding performance, they silenced their critics and proved their mettle on the grandest stage of European football.
</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>manchestercity,victory,championsleague,football,semifinals,realmadrid,euphoria,fans,celebration,performance,historic,istanbul,intermilan,teamwork,determination,disbelief,socialmedia,global,anticipation,journey</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Manchester, England</media:city>
                          <media:country>United Kingdom</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>GB</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Sport</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Wed, 17 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>2078</guid>
                          <pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 10:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2078.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2078.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Manchester City's epic victory propels them to the Champions League Final, igniting fan euphoria</media:title>
                          <media:description>In a stunning turn of events, Manchester City emerged triumphant in the semi-finals of the UEFA Champions League, securing a resounding 4-0 victory against Real Madrid. The match took place on the 17th of May, 2023, at Manchester's home ground, Etihad Stadium, sending shockwaves through the football world.

The atmosphere in the stadium was electric as fans eagerly awaited the kickoff. The tension was palpable, with both teams vying for a spot in the prestigious final. As the match unfolded, Manchester City exhibited a display of extraordinary skill, leaving the Spanish giants stunned and struggling to keep up.

@SpibySalford, a devoted Manchester City fan, captured the moment of celebration in a video clip from the stands. Overwhelmed with emotions, he shared his thoughts on social media, writing, "Can't even begin to process that!!! Absolutely unbelievable night... all them years of getting the piss took out of us, all the laughing at us! Never have I seen a performance as good as that... MANCHESTER CITY I WILL LOVE YOU FOREVER."

The victory not only secured Manchester City's place in the finals but also marked a significant milestone for the club. Over the years, they had faced criticism and skepticism, with many doubting their ability to compete at the highest level. However, with this commanding performance, they silenced their critics and proved their mettle on the grandest stage of European football.
</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>manchestercity,victory,championsleague,football,semifinals,realmadrid,euphoria,fans,celebration,performance,historic,istanbul,intermilan,teamwork,determination,disbelief,socialmedia,global,anticipation,journey</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Manchester, England</media:city>
                          <media:country>United Kingdom</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>GB</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Sport</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Wed, 17 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>2077</guid>
                          <pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 11:00:31 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2077.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2077.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Fun hockey training session for Kkds in Yalta, Russia</media:title>
                          <media:description>On March 1, 2022, in the city of Yalta, Russia, an unusual ice hockey training session took place. The HK Avangard team was practicing, and one parent captured a heartwarming moment on video. The author, who is also a parent, shared that her 3-year-old son is the youngest hockey player in their city.

In the video, the coach can be seen playing an unconventional game with the young players. Although the training sessions are usually serious, on Fridays, they have fun with the kids. This unique approach makes the game enjoyable for everyone, including the young hockey players.</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>Yalta,Russia,hockey training,Avangard HC,coach,unconventional method,children,serious,fun,video,3-year-old,youngest hockey player,city,Friday games,amusing</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Yalta</media:city>
                          <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>undefined</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>undefined</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Sport</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Tue, 1 Mar 2022</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>1827</guid>
                          <pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2023 11:06:30 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/1827.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/1827.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Snowboarding Run in Alaska Gone Wrong: Cam FitzPatrick's Humbling Experience</media:title>
                          <media:description>On February 24, 2023, Cam FitzPatrick, a snowboarder from the United States, had an unforgettable experience in Alaska. Cam was snowboarding down the mountain at great speed, and he described it as "probably the fastest I’ve ever gone on a snowboard." He added, "HOLY MOLY AK is humbling!"

Cam FitzPatrick had been snowboarding for years, but he had never experienced anything quite like Alaska. 

However, as Cam was snowboarding down the mountain, he encountered a trough. As he accelerated even faster, the trough began to come off, and Cam fell. It was a terrifying experience, but thankfully, he managed to get up quickly and was not injured.

The video was filmed by @camfitzpatrick</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>Snowboarding,Alaska,Cam FitzPatrick,Safety,Thrill,Mountains,Trough,Protective Gear,Risk,Skiing,sport</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Alaska</media:city>
                          <media:country>USA</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>undefined</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>undefined</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Sport</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2023</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>1688</guid>
                          <pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 18:21:46 GMT</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1688.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1688.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>The reaction of the boy after the victory of Argentina in football in the World Cup!</media:title>
                          <media:description>17-year-old Jay is overjoyed after his favorite team wins the World Cup final!

Credit to: @alinaspadfoot</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>football,sport,boy,happiness,Argentina,world cup,emotions</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>-</media:city>
                          <media:country>Slovenia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>undefined</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>undefined</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Sport</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Invalid date</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>1430</guid>
                          <pubDate>Invalid Date</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1430.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1430.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>A little boy expresses feelings about his favorite team in the World Cup 2022</media:title>
                          <media:description>Aif 4 years old expresses his feelings for his favorite World Cup team, Argentina, after they lose to Saudi Arabia on November 22, 2022.

Credit to: @kokka_ma</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>World cup,Argentina,Saudi Arabia,Football,FIFA,boy,Team,Indonesia</media:keywords>
                          <media:city> Ternate City</media:city>
                          <media:country> Indonesia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>undefined</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>undefined</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Sport</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2022</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>1321</guid>
                          <pubDate>Invalid Date</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1321.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/1321.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>The guy, instead of sports equipment, uses his bed for training!</media:title>
                          <media:description>The author said: "The reason for making this video is only to create workout content. The estimated weight of the mattress is 40kg."</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>sport,bed,training</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Depok</media:city>
                          <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>undefined</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>undefined</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Sport</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2022</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>1168</guid>
                          <pubDate>Invalid Date</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/22deee0c-edf1-4a12-91b2-6d4bc8d3aca0.png" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/dab5dff4-0083-4442-a42d-a0b419825280.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                        <item>
                          <media:title>Bird on the field at Dodger Stadium steals show during Game 2 between Padres and Dodgers!</media:title>
                          <media:description>12 October 2022, Los Angeles, USA

While the Dodgers and Padres were locked in a tight battle during Game 2 of the National League Division Series, they had a very special fan join the proceedings.

As Los Angeles tried to rally from a 5-3 deficit in the bottom of the eighth inning with Gavin Lux at the plate, a duck appeared just outside the infield. With the wild animal likely confused and in the middle of the action, play was halted for a bit as stadium officials tried to figure out what to do.

Eventually, the duck was safely corralled by workers at the stadium.

Credit to: @Mymomswhite</media:description>
                          <media:keywords>duck,bird,usa,baseball</media:keywords>
                          <media:city>Los Angeles</media:city>
                          <media:country>USA</media:country>
                          <media:regionCode>undefined</media:regionCode>
                          <media:categoryCode>undefined</media:categoryCode>
                          <media:category>Sport</media:category>
                          <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                          <media:filmingDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2022</media:filmingDate>
                          <guid>1112</guid>
                          <pubDate>Invalid Date</pubDate>
                          <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/b2977394-fa8a-4a2b-96a3-535c31f7be23.jpg" />
                          <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/images/0622d49b-407a-4b23-88c4-12b58296e096.mp4" />
                          <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                          </item>
                        
                         </channel>
                      </rss>
                    