<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
        <rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
        xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
        xmlns:openSearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearchrss/1.0/"
        xmlns:dfpvideo="http://api.google.com/dfpvideo"
        xmlns:tms="http://data.tmsapi.com/v1.1"
        version="2.0">
          <channel>
            <title>ViralBear videos</title>
            <dfpvideo:version>2</dfpvideo:version>
              
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Playful corgi's adorable 'poof' act delights internet in St. Petersburg, Russia!</media:title>
                  <media:description>In an endearing and amusing video that captured hearts on social media, a Corgi named Leo from St. Petersburg, Russia, showcased his unique talent for playing "dead." The video, shared by @prokopenkokate on April 29, 2023, depicts Leo sitting peacefully on the floor before his owner mimics a shooting gesture with her hands. Surprisingly, the adorable pup immediately flops down, pretending to be "shot" as part of a playful command he has mastered. As a reward for his impressive performance, Leo eagerly awaits a treat, proving that his favorite command is the delightful and harmless "poof," leaving viewers charmed by this clever and lovable canine's antics.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>playful,corgi,leo,video,internet,acting,dog,Russia,St. Petersburg,pet,owner,gun,pretend,cute,charm,humor,social media,adorable,command,sweet</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>St. Petersburg</media:city>
                  <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sat, 29 Apr 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2595</guid>
                  <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 10:53:38 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2595.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2595.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Playful and obedient: Khryapa's impressive 'swim' command!</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a heartwarming video captured by @mokryi_nosik_ on June 17, 2020, in Voronezh, Russia, her beloved dog, Khryapa, stole the spotlight with her incredible obedience and playful nature. The footage shows @mokryi_nosik_ talking to Khryapa in one of the rooms, when suddenly, the clever canine dashes off towards the bathroom. Without hesitation, Khryapa leaps into the bathtub, showcasing her impressive execution of the "swim" command. The three-year-old furry friend proves to be not only obedient but also full of joy and enthusiasm. Her charming antics have won the hearts of viewers worldwide, leaving a lasting impression of her delightful personality and the strong bond between her and her owner.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>playful,obedient,dog,swim,command,video,Khryapa,Voronezh,Russia,bathtub,bathroom,three years old,pet,canine,joy,love,bond,clever,cute,charming</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Voronezh</media:city>
                  <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2598</guid>
                  <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 10:57:32 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2598.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2598.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Tenacious twig tug-of-war: a dog's unyielding affair with nature's bounty</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a delightful and amusing scene captured by @chelseareject on May 21, 2023, in Jersey City, New Jersey, USA, her four-legged companion exhibited an unshakeable determination during a playful encounter with nature. The video showcased the adorable pup clenching onto a sizable twig of a tree, despite the owner's best efforts to convince it otherwise. With @chelseareject's voice gently coaxing the dog to release its prized find, the resilient canine remained unyielding, steadfastly refusing to let go. Undeterred, they strolled along together, the furry protagonist proudly showcasing its prized possession in an endearing tug-of-war with the forces of nature. The heartwarming display of canine spirit and persistence resonated with viewers worldwide, capturing the essence of a special bond between humans and their loyal companions.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>tree,dog,twig,nature,Jersey City,USA,May,2023,video,pet,playful,determined,adorable,owner,walk,bonding,persistence,loyalty,companionship,endearing,capture</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Jersey City, New Jersey</media:city>
                  <media:country>United States</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>US</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sun, 21 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2586</guid>
                  <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 09:23:40 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2586.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2586.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Cat burglar in Buenos Aires: feline filches cash and cuddles up!</media:title>
                  <media:description>In an amusing incident in Buenos Aires, Argentina, on July 6, 2023, a mischievous cat turned into a daring thief. A video captured by @gaston__joaquin showed the feline delving into a handbag and snatching a bundle of money before darting off towards the bedroom. The curious owner followed the sneaky cat's trail to find it lounging on the bed with the stolen cash. This lighthearted escapade left everyone amused and highlighted the unpredictable antics of our four-legged companions.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>cat,thief,money,video,Buenos Aires,Argentina,handbag,bed,owner,amusing,feline,daring,curious,sneaky,trail,lounging,stolen,cash,lighthearted,antics</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Buenos Aires</media:city>
                  <media:country>Argentina</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>AR</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Thu, 6 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2585</guid>
                  <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 09:24:40 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2585.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2585.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Resourceful feline masters the art of door-opening: a fascinating tale from Jepara, Indonesia!</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a captivating video captured by @muktafil on April 24, 2023, in Jepara, Indonesia, an astonishing feat unfolded as their clever cat showcased its ingenuity. The footage showcases the feline effortlessly opening the door to the house, by jumping on the door handle leaving its owner in awe of its newfound talent. Expressing his astonishment, the author stated, "I was surprised that the cat opened the door by itself, now if you put it outside, it will open the door. Don't know where it learned from." The video has since captured the hearts of viewers worldwide, as they marvel at the resourceful cat's ability to conquer the seemingly insurmountable obstacle. This extraordinary tale serves as a reminder of the intelligence and adaptability possessed by our feline companions.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>clever,cat,door,opening,video,Jepara,Indonesia,surprise,talent,resourceful,ingenuity,amazement,owner,outside,learn,astonishment,heartwarming,intelligence,adaptability,feline</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Jepara</media:city>
                  <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>ID</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2578</guid>
                  <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 07:29:30 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2578.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2578.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Bathroom bliss: Indonesian cat's unique way to beat the heat</media:title>
                  <media:description>In Yogyakarta, Indonesia, a heartwarming video captured by @bagus_muhammad_ on March 28, 2023, showcases the adorable antics of his feline companion during a hot day. The short clip features his cat lying flat on its stomach in the cool confines of the bathroom, delightfully spreading its hind legs for ultimate relaxation. As temperatures rise, it seems this clever kitty has found its perfect oasis for beating the heat. With a contented expression on its face, it's evident that the bathroom has become the preferred spot for the cat to seek respite from the sweltering weather. </media:description>
                  <media:keywords>cat,bathroom,Indonesia,Yogyakarta,video,pet,feline,hot,heat,adorable,antics,relaxation,hind legs,oasis,cool,weather,comfort,pets,content,warmer days</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Yogyakarta</media:city>
                  <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>ID</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2577</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 08:17:01 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2577.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2577.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Tranquil moments: Tokyo's beloved dog relishes in shallow creek at favorite park</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a heartwarming scene captured on June 24, 2023, in Tokyo, Japan, @mr.donbei_inu shared a delightful video of his beloved dog finding sheer bliss in a small, slow creek at their favorite park. The four-legged companion appeared completely at ease, comfortably resting its head on the surface of the shallow water, joyfully savoring the gentle flow around it. Unlike most dogs, this furry friend chose not to swim but found pure contentment in merely basking in the refreshing water. With a serene expression, the canine seemed to have discovered a little piece of paradise amidst the bustling city, making this tranquil spot its most cherished destination in the park.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>dog,creek,park,Tokyo,Japan,chilling,water,shallow,serene,bliss,favorite,video,pet,companion,contentment,relaxation,joy,tranquility,peaceful,happiness</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Tokyo</media:city>
                  <media:country>Japan</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>JP</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2593</guid>
                  <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 10:52:42 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2593.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2593.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Bear brawl at Guaipo Tiger Park: two black bears engage in fierce fight over food</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a thrilling and unexpected encounter at the Guaipo Tiger Park in Shenyang, Northeast China, two black bears engaged in a heated fight, captured on video by local resident @100millionfatballs on June 24, 2023. As she explored the living area of the black bears, the normally docile animals suddenly clashed, with their aggression escalating over a possible dispute for food. The shocking scene prompted the author to react quickly, loudly shouting in an attempt to intervene and put an end to the confrontation. Her bravery in the face of this intense encounter showcased the unpredictable nature of wildlife and served as a powerful reminder of the importance of respecting and preserving the delicate balance between humans and the animal kingdom.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>shenyang,china,black bears,fight,video,wildlife,park,encounter,food,aggression,shock,visitor,Guaipo Tiger Park,northeast,@100millionfatballs,nature,animals,conservation,bravery,balance</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Shenyang</media:city>
                  <media:country>China</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>CN</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2602</guid>
                  <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 13:12:52 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2602.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2602.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Enchanting encounter: friendly dolphin delights swimmer at Suishohama Beach, Japan</media:title>
                  <media:description>On July 17th, 2023, at Suishohama Beach in Mihama, Mikata District, Japan, a remarkable scene unfolded as a curious dolphin made a surprise appearance near the shore. @Ooo_MEN_ captured the heartwarming moment on video, showing the dolphin playfully interacting with a lone swimmer using a floater. The extraordinary encounter left beachgoers in awe as they witnessed the gentle marine creature approaching and engaging with the delighted individual. </media:description>
                  <media:keywords>dolphin,beach,interaction,swimmer,floater,video,Japan,Mihama,Mikata District,Suishohama Beach,nature,wildlife,encounter,playful,surprise,curious,harmony,awe,enchanting,filmed</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Mihama, Mikata District</media:city>
                  <media:country>Japan</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>JP</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2481</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/401402ff-22eb-4a49-9a06-dfbde13add42.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/cef347b0-35ba-4fd5-bd4e-6ef4fc575661.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Dirty surprise: cat returns home with sewage water makeover!</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a surprising turn of events, a video captured by @ayumispa from Madiun, Indonesia on May 2, 2023, revealed the unanticipated return of her cat, sporting a face covered in dirty sewage water. Despite having groomed the feline just the day before, it seemed that mischievous curiosity had led the adventurous cat to an unexpected encounter with the unpleasant liquid.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>sewage,water,dirty,cat,face,groomed,video,captured,@ayumispa,Madiun,Indonesia,surprising,unanticipated,adventurous,curiosity,mischievous,encounter,messy,makeover,attention</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Madiun</media:city>
                  <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>ID</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Tue, 2 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2356</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/1abc7114-68f8-4ac1-ac99-cbf5d30b4de3.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/39903d9d-202a-42c4-9282-60b37cded5da.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Amazing escape: brave cat Oyen breaks free from locked cage!</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a captivating video captured by @amrhasyiqin, on June 5th, 2023, in Selangor, Malaysia, a remarkable feline escapade unfolded. A vigilant cat owner had locked her cats in a cage to prevent them from running off, only to witness a daring escape. As time passed, one of the cats, named Oyen, astounded everyone by maneuvering through one of the small holes in the cage. Oyen's determination and agility allowed the courageous cat to break free from confinement. </media:description>
                  <media:keywords>escape,cage,locked,cats,Oyen,run,holes,video,owner,Malaysia,Selangor,captivate,daring,maneuver,determination,agility,confinement,ingenuity,resourcefulness,resilience</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Selangor</media:city>
                  <media:country>Malaysia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>MY</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Mon, 5 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2358</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/0471d728-271c-4634-91a9-2049aae243fb.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/4d1840f0-6c16-4e77-b6c7-eb4d167aad14.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Raccoon's Miron misadventures: a heartwarming birthday surprise!</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a heartwarming tale of misadventures, @raccoon_miron from St. Petersburg, Russia, captured a touching video while searching for her beloved raccoon pet, Miron on April 27, 2023. The furry troublemaker had managed to scatter her belongings all over the apartment on the eve of his birthday, leaving her in tears, fearing he had escaped through the window. However, to her relief, Miron was just being mischievous and had fallen asleep amidst her things. The emotional rollercoaster of worry and joy unfolded in the video.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>raccoon,miron,video,pet,birthday,surprise,misadventures,St. Petersburg,Russia,apartment,balcony,work,order,sobbing,window,smart,boy,asleep,things,love,joy.</media:keywords>
                  <media:city> St. Petersburg</media:city>
                  <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2558</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 07:43:53 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2558.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2558.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Startling encounter: snake dangles and vanishes in Ho Chi Minh city home</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a harrowing incident captured on a home camera in Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam, a resident, @congdonghoainhon, had an unsettling surprise. On May 12, 2023, the camera alerted him to movement in his bedroom, and upon checking the footage, he was startled to see a snake dangling near the camera. Moments later, the snake fell out of sight, leaving him alarmed. Rushing back home, he searched his room diligently but found no trace of the elusive serpent. Speculating that it might have taken refuge inside the air conditioner, the resident remains on edge, unable to locate the reptile.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>snake,camera,bedroom,video,home,work,warn,movement,shocked,rummage,find,air conditioner,Vietnam,Ho Chi Minh City,resident,encounter,alert,elusive,reptile,tags</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Ho Chi Minh City</media:city>
                  <media:country>Vietnam</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>VN</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Fri, 12 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2528</guid>
                  <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 20:58:54 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2528.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2528.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Unlikely confrontation: tourist's dog faces fierce cat at Irganai reservoir</media:title>
                  <media:description>In an unexpected turn of events at the picturesque Irganai reservoir in Dagestan, Russia, a tourist's leisurely day took a surprising twist when their four-legged companion faced off against a disgruntled cat. On June 11, 2023, @dag.travel captured a video showing the intense encounter. The cat lunged at the dog, prompting the owner to swiftly intervene, pulling the dog away and moving to a safer distance. Despite the distance, the persistent cat continued its pursuit, leading the dog's owner to carry their pet to avoid further confrontation. The serene outing turned into an unusual showdown, leaving both the onlookers and the tourists in awe of the unexpected clash between these unlikely adversaries.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>dog,cat,attack,Irganai,reservoir,Dagestan,Russia,tourist,owner,atmosphere,video,confront,surprising,encounter,lunge,persistent,pursuit,carry,onlookers,clash</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Dagestan</media:city>
                  <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2503</guid>
                  <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 19:17:00 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2503.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2503.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Fierce yet gentle: Russian serval cat's playful encounter with watchful dog</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a captivating video captured by @mainecoonnhaching on July 8th, 2023, in Dau Mot city, Binh Duong province, Vietnam, a serval cat imported from Russia displayed a striking mix of ferocity and tenderness. The video shows the cat enthusiastically chasing after an object thrown towards their glass door, revealing the curious dog outside. The cat runs straight to the door and, though fierce in appearance, slumps its head while retrieving the toy. The dog, kept outside to prevent accidents indoors, remains safe behind a fenced gate, thanks to careful guarding.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>cat,video,serval,Russia,fierce,gentle,dog,play,glass,door,chase,curious,outside,safe,fenced,gate,guarding,harmony,environment,adorable</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Dau Mot city, Binh Duong province</media:city>
                  <media:country>Vietnam</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>VN</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sat, 8 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2498</guid>
                  <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 13:13:12 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2498.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2498.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Paws-itively independent: clever canine takes treat shopping to new heights!</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a heartwarming display of intelligence and independence, a remarkable dog named LeeRoy has stolen the hearts of locals in Tuckerman, Arkansas, USA. A video captured by @mikey35232 on April 7th, 2023, shows LeeRoy confidently strolling in a mart with its owner, carefully selecting his favorite treat, and astonishingly making his way to the counter with its owner. According to his proud owner, Mikey, this impressive feat is a testament to their strong bond, as he has been taking LeeRoy everywhere since he was a mere 4 weeks old. Last year, LeeRoy began demonstrating his incredible ability to choose his own treats.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>dog,mart,treat,shopping,independence,intelligence,bond,video,Arkansas,Tuckerman,LeeRoy,owner,favorite,pay,confidence,remarkable,awe,loyalty,capture,heartwarming</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Tuckerman, Arkansas</media:city>
                  <media:country>United States</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>US</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Fri, 7 Apr 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2440</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/8384c6d8-bb0a-4b78-be59-5860b954b152.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/d42f7d6e-76c5-4cb0-8612-81466a1ac76f.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Muddy mishap: hilarious cat battle ends in gutter adventure!</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a surprising turn of events on June 28, 2023, a cat's fierce fight with an intruder ended with a comical twist. While cleaning their boarding house in Sungai Liat, Indonesia, @nikywlndri_ and her brother stumbled upon their beloved feline engaged in a heated battle with another cat. Unable to separate the feuding felines due to the distance between them, both cats suddenly tumbled into a nearby gutter. As the dust settled, the intruder swiftly escaped. The author's cat emerged from the gutter, covered head to toe in black, dirty mud. Overwhelmed with laughter, the siblings couldn't resist capturing the hilarious moment on video.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>cat,muddy,water,cleaning,boarding house,home town,Eid al-Adha,noises,fighting,distance,gutter,laughter,video,siblings,Indonesia,Bangka Belitung,Sungai Liat,dirty,comical,mishap,viral</media:keywords>
                  <media:city> Bangka Belitung, Sungai Liat</media:city>
                  <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>ID</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2407</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/15226983-8aa1-46e2-a0f3-d91605f7ae5a.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2407.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Runaway cow wreaks havoc on parked motorbikes</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a surprising turn of events, chaos unfolded outside a hospital entrance in Balikpapan, Indonesia, on June 28th, 2023 when a cow dashed through the area and collided with parked motorbikes. A quick-thinking individual, who goes by the name @myselfmyenemy, managed to capture the bizarre incident on video. Fear gripped him as he watched the cow hurtling toward him, prompting him to swiftly record the scene on his phone. Fortunately, the motorbikes emerged unscathed.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>cow,motorbikes,incident,video,Balikpapan,Indonesia,chaos,hospital,entrance,@myselfmyenemy,fear,collision,parked,unexpected,astonished,moment,captured,unscathed,injuries,turn of events</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Balikpapan</media:city>
                  <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>ID</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2361</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/4fa1c59a-7447-4973-94aa-8d5d4714a91a.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/ee139c81-052c-4891-b39b-51d951c723d0.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Catnap couture: adorable feline caught napping in boutique's pink mavin!</media:title>
                  <media:description>In the city of Borisov, Belarus, on July 16, 2023, a heartwarming scene unfolded in a second clothes boutique. Local resident @ugimaster stumbled upon a delightful sight as he entered the store - a contented cat fast asleep amidst the clothes. Its furry head was cozily nestled on a soft pink mavin, adding an extra touch of cuteness to the scene. The video captured by @ugimaster quickly went viral, spreading smiles and warming hearts across the internet.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>cat,sleeping,clothes,boutique,Borisov,Belarus,@ugimaster,video,peaceful,pink,mavin,adorable,feline,nap,city,viral,internet,heartwarming,cozy,cute</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Borisov</media:city>
                  <media:country>Belarus</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>BY</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2562</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 07:47:37 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2562.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2562.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Massive moth invasion: swarms of flying creatures fill the night skies in Yelets, Russia</media:title>
                  <media:description>On the night of Monday, July 24, 2023, the city of Yelets in the Lipetsk region, Russia, experienced a bizarre phenomenon as drivers encountered a massive invasion of insects. Thousands of flying creatures, identified as moths, enveloped the road lights, creating "swarm clouds" that obstructed the path on the Karakum bridge. Disturbing footage recorded by a driver showcased the surreal scene, where the insects swarmed around vehicles, making navigation challenging. </media:description>
                  <media:keywords>insects,invasion,Yelets,Russia,night,Monday,July 24,Lipetsk,drivers,filmed,massive,flying,creatures,swarm,clouds,Karakum,bridge,moths,video,way,drove</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Yelets, Lipetsk region</media:city>
                  <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ODD</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2556</guid>
                  <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 14:56:15 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2556.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2556.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Retired military working Dog's instinct shines through: a playful encounter with a puffy jacket</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a heartwarming video captured by @boepeepk9 on May 27th, 2023, in Crestview, Florida, USA, her 10-year-old retired Military Working Dog named Gina displayed her training instincts. While trying on a puffy jacket resembling the bite suit tops used in Controlled Aggression training, the author noticed Gina eyeing the jacket intently. Curious to test her response, she jerked her arm, expecting Gina to bite. True to her training, Gina gently bit the jacket, demonstrating her obedience and quick reflexes. With a soft verbal correction, the author reassured Gina, who immediately showed remorse. </media:description>
                  <media:keywords>retired,military,working dog,video,dogs,puffy jacket,bite suit,training,controlled aggression,eyeing,bite,instincts,obedience,reflexes,verbal correction,remorse,love,affection,commands,capture</media:keywords>
                  <media:city> Crestview, Florida</media:city>
                  <media:country>United States</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>US</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sat, 27 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2438</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/55726dec-a97e-49d6-8f33-28effcccf647.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/3ce0ec3f-93df-4e12-ae64-57cd1de0bbcd.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Playful pursuit: Sasuke the dog's hilarious chase with a clever crow</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a delightful scene captured by @sasuke_2017.0808 on June 14th, 2023, in Tokyo, Japan, a video showcased the amusing encounter between a persistent dog named Sasuke and a clever black crow. The canine's excitement was sparked as it spotted the crow perched on the balcony. However, instead of flying away, the mischievous bird continuously relocated to different parts of the balcony, keeping Sasuke in a constant pursuit. The author, found great amusement in witnessing this comical interaction between his dog and the crafty crow, creating a moment filled with laughter and joy.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>dog,crow,chase,balcony,Tokyo,Japan,video,Sasuke,amusement,laughter,pets,animals,funny,entertaining,playful,clever,mischievous,owner,encounter,joy</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Tokyo </media:city>
                  <media:country>Japan</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>JP</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2328</guid>
                  <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 11:51:52 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/7c1bad1f-9d05-4c66-bca4-754b7fa5d8d5.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/77ce2601-f34d-4050-a660-13c350ae6a0b.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Slippery shenanigans: Fatty the dog's hilarious underground parking adventure!</media:title>
                  <media:description>In Jiangxi province, China, on June 9th, 2023, a playful dog named Fatty found himself in a comical situation at the underground parking lot. His owner, Fatty, captured the moment on video as the excited canine ran towards her, only to slip on the wet floor. With a quick recovery, Fatty tried to hide his embarrassment by looking forward, creating a humorous and endearing scene. Thankfully, no harm was done, and Fatty's misadventures added a touch of laughter to an otherwise ordinary day at the parking lot.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>june 9th,2023,jiangxi province,china,fatty,dog,video,running,sliding,wet floor,underground parking,car,water,slip,embarrassment,owner,playfulness,comical,recovery,laughter,misadventure</media:keywords>
                  <media:city> Jiangxi province</media:city>
                  <media:country>China</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>CN</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Fri, 9 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2527</guid>
                  <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 21:01:29 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2527.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2527.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Bra brawl: furry guardians turn fashion feud in Selangor, Malaysia!</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a surprising and amusing spectacle captured by @rita_roslie in Selangor, Malaysia on June 28, 2023, two dogs were caught on camera engaging in a hilarious tug-of-war over a bra. The canines seemed to have stumbled upon the lingerie in question and were passionately tugging at each end, playfully bickering over their newfound treasure. As one dog clenched its teeth onto one side of the bra, the other dog stubbornly held onto the opposite end, creating a comical fashion feud. The author, the eyewitness, revealed that one of the dogs involved was her loyal garden guardian, but she was clueless about where they had discovered the bra.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>dogs,fighting,bra,tugofwar,hilarious,spectacle,Malaysia,Selangor,video,canines,fashion,feud,treasure,comical,viral,pets,quirky,antics,animals,guardians</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Selangor</media:city>
                  <media:country>Malaysia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>MY</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2500</guid>
                  <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 14:26:17 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2500.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2500.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Snake's surprise: when a reptile acts like a cat!</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a surprising and adorable video captured by @children.of.loki on June 13th, 2023, in Texas, USA, a snake displayed remarkably cat-like behavior. The footage shows the snake slithering around the house until its owner scratches its back. Astonishingly, the reptile bends the area where it receives the scratch, seemingly relishing the affectionate gesture. Captioned as "My snake is a cat," this extraordinary behavior showcases the fascinating and unexpected similarities between these two vastly different creatures.
</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>snake,reptile,pet,Texas,USA,video,cat-like,behavior,adorable,surprising,scratch,slithering,house,owner,affectionate,gesture,fascination,creature,similarities,captivating</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Texas</media:city>
                  <media:country>United States</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>US</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2484</guid>
                  <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 09:35:26 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/dccfb477-e6cb-4f39-a2e9-be93aaab4eff.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/30a86124-8fc3-4dc2-89dc-ffb246cfc1f3.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Doggie oasis: Beha finds refreshing relief from the heat by the shore</media:title>
                  <media:description>On June 17th, 2023, in Balashikha, Moscow, Russia, a heartwarming video captured the attention of many as @nemez_bexa shared a delightful moment with her dog. The scorching heat couldn't keep Beha away from cooling off in the water near the shore. In the short clip, the dog is seen seated in the water, content and relaxed. </media:description>
                  <media:keywords>dog,water,shore,hot,Beha,play,video,Balashikha,Moscow,Russia,heat,pet,playful,refresh,summer,cool,socialmedia,cute,joy,happiness,retrieve</media:keywords>
                  <media:city> Balashikha, Moscow</media:city>
                  <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2477</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/ed8cd420-ed98-48df-9484-6be4d907eff5.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/9b1fdfa0-bae1-40b8-8d27-d41efc0aac8a.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Fearful furry friends: Ball the dog and a playful deer's zoo encounter in Beijing!</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a heartwarming yet cautious encounter at a zoo in Beijing, China, a dog named Ball had a surprising interaction with a curious deer. The moment was captured on video by @todaythemoonisnotopen on July 3rd, 2023. As Ball sat inside the car, a deer approached, seemingly eager to engage in a kiss. However, the dog's apprehension was evident, and it quickly retreated back into the safety of the vehicle. Despite the brief interaction, the endearing exchange between the two animals left a lasting impression, highlighting the beauty of unexpected connections in the animal kingdom.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>playful,deer,dog,zoo,Beijing,China,encounter,video,July3rd,2023,curious,kiss,car,interaction,animals,connection,heartwarming,cautious,moment,captured</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Beijing</media:city>
                  <media:country>China</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>CN</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Mon, 3 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2465</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/291686df-edaf-40a2-b29e-324e7310ae8e.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/59533475-0fb1-4a59-b179-39812ed84054.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Miraculous animal bond: minke whale saves ailing boar in Saint Petersburg region</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a heartwarming incident captured on video by @PavelGlazkov in the Priozersky district of the Leningrad region, Russia on June 27th, 2023, a boar found itself in distress, struggling to stand on its feet. Its mother sensed the urgency and immediately took action, giving her ailing piglet a massage around the heart area with her sinewy heel. Despite her efforts, the baby showed no signs of life. However, a surprising turn of events unfolded as another minke whale rushed to the scene and took over the care. This compassionate whale diligently massaged the body of its sibling, and astonishingly, the piglet regained consciousness. Without hesitation, the piglet resumed eating, showcasing the remarkable bond between animals and their capacity for empathy and aid in the most unexpected circumstances.

Credit to: https://t.me/kazdoytvaripopare</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>boar,mother,massage,illness,consciousness,minke whale,Russia,Priozersky district,Leningrad region,baby,sibling,empathy,help,video,trap,heart,feet,eating,distress,remarkable,bond.</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Priozersky district of the Saint Petersburg region</media:city>
                  <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2455</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/c239ec24-bc12-4273-a7eb-f9c3314253d5.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2682e9db-1a8c-4e27-a201-c6cb1390260a.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Quirky Yeti: cat asserts ownership over owner's resting foot in hilarious video!</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a heartwarming yet amusing video captured by @dymova_brows on December 14, 2022, in Zaporozhye, Ukraine, a 7-year-old cat named Yeti showcases its unique character. The footage shows Yeti attempting to keep its owner's foot still under the blanket while playfully growling like a dog when met with resistance. The quirky feline's predilections include strolls on the balcony and relishing wet food, but it fiercely guards its delicious meals from fellow feline companions. The short video captures Yeti's endearing and assertive personality, providing a delightful glimpse into the fascinating world of this furry friend.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>cat,yeti,video,quirky,owner,foot,bed,blanket,growl,dog,character,Zaporozhye,Ukraine,balcony,wet food,delicious,unique,feline,playful,adorable</media:keywords>
                  <media:city> Zaporozhye</media:city>
                  <media:country>Ukraine</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>UA</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2569</guid>
                  <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 07:20:35 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2569.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2569.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Hilarious dinner table antics: dog seeks special treats in Baguio City!</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a delightful video captured by @maui_theeb on May 27, 2023, in Baguio City, Philippines, a comical dog stole the show with its amusing dinner table antics. The furry friend, seated on a chair atop the table, was seen hilariously tapping a gentleman on the shoulders, seemingly asking for a treat or some attention. The heartwarming interaction between the dog and the person brought smiles to viewers' faces, showcasing the bond between humans and their beloved pets in the most endearing way possible.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>funny,dog,interaction,dinner table,Baguio City,Philippines,video,tapping,gentleman,chair,adorable,pets,bond,cute,hilarious,canine,comedy,heartwarming,love,companionship,amusing</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Baguio City</media:city>
                  <media:country>Philippines</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>PH</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sat, 27 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2505</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 08:31:02 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2505.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2505.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Whiskers in a bind: cat sits between rooms in Majalengka home</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a captivating video captured by @egiagstiann_ on  April 22, 2023, a cat found itself in an amusing predicament in Majalengka, Indonesia. The feline managed to sit in a tight spot, with its body wedged between a hole above the door and window, dividing two rooms. The video shows the cat's comical situation, as its bottom can be seen in one room, while its head pokes out into another. </media:description>
                  <media:keywords>cat,stuck,hole,door,window,Majalengka,Indonesia,video,captured,bottom,head,room,amusing,predicament,feline,wedged,tight,comical,adorable,bewildering</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Majalengka</media:city>
                  <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>ID</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sat, 22 Apr 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2397</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/ec6e7875-0d3a-481b-b275-ba4a9b61ad8c.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/8ff6c3f6-558d-4081-b92c-8da4071ff801.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Adventurous Manda: a curious cat's high-rise escapades in Yogyakarta!</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a captivating moment caught on video by @a.youu_ on July 4, 2023, in Yogyakarta, Indonesia, a curious cat named Manda was spotted perched atop an unfinished building. The enigmatic feline appeared unsure of its surroundings, leaving viewers both amused and intrigued by its daring escapade. With a playful spirit, the author decided to record the charming scene, showcasing Manda's adventurous nature and uncertain demeanor as it surveyed the world from its lofty vantage point.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>cat,video,Yogyakarta,Indonesia,Manda,building,perched,curious,confused,fun,playful,adventurous,daring,charming,uncertain,climb,pet,antics,moment,heartwarming</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Yogyakarta</media:city>
                  <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>ID</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Tue, 4 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2573</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 08:15:12 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2573.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2573.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Enchanting fur patterns: unique cat in Blitar delights in friendly affection</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a heartwarming scene captured on video by @polseksrengat on June 30, 2023, in Blitar, Indonesia, a cat with naturally polished fur became the center of attention among a group of friends. The cat sported a striking combination of white fur on its face and a mix of white and black fur on the rest of its body, making it truly unique. As the friends scratched the cat gently, it basked in their affectionate company, closing its eyes in contentment each time one of them touched its head. The endearing sight of this feline enjoying the camaraderie warmed the hearts of those who witnessed the adorable encounter, reminding us of the profound bond between humans and their feline companions.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>polished,fur,cat,white,black,unique,friends,affection,company,contentment,adorable,feline,bond,Indonesia,Blitar,video,captured,June30,2023,@polseksrengat</media:keywords>
                  <media:city> Blitar</media:city>
                  <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>ID</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2571</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 08:08:02 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2571.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2571.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Unconventional cat and mouse chase: when the prey strikes back in Lviv, Ukraine!</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a comical scene captured by @bohdansereda on June 11, 2023, in Lviv, Ukraine, a cat found itself in an amusing predicament with a crafty mouse. The video showcased the mouse perched confidently on the cat's back, seemingly taunting the feline as it attempted to catch its elusive companion. Despite the mouse's daring trickery, the determined cat valiantly pursued the rodent, refusing to give up the chase. After a series of entertaining antics, the mouse's luck eventually ran out, and it tumbled from the cat's back, leading to a swift and triumphant pounce by the feline. </media:description>
                  <media:keywords>cat,mouse,lviv,ukraine,video,chase,trick,clever,funny,pursuit,adventure,pounce,whiskers,comical,scene,internet,sensation,playful,showdown,triumph,amusing</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Lviv</media:city>
                  <media:country>Ukraine</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>UA</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2534</guid>
                  <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 15:07:59 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2534.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2534.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Amusing cat drama unfolds: playful feline duo turns kitchen mishap into entertainment!</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a heartwarming yet comical scene captured by @thanhtam8880 on June 14th, 2023, in Thanh Xuan district, Hanoi, Vietnam, two cats shared a playful moment in the kitchen. As one curious feline inadvertently stuck its tail between the cupboard door, its furry friend mistook the situation for a game and started playfully tugging at the trapped tail. While the incident might have seemed concerning at first, it quickly turned into a delightful display of camaraderie as the mischievous companion successfully freed its tail.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>cat,video,playful,kitchen,cupboard,tail,stuck,comical,companionship,feline,heartwarming,Hanoi,Thanh Xuan district,Vietnam,friends,entertaining,cooking,mishap,funny,moment</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Thanh Xuan district, Hanoi</media:city>
                  <media:country>Vietnam</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>VN</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2496</guid>
                  <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 12:28:49 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2496.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2496.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Harv's chicken house harmony: cat and chickens live in paw-sitive coexistence!</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a heartwarming display of unexpected camaraderie, a captivating video captured by @harvs.gamla.skola on July 3rd, 2023 from Harv, Sweden, showcased a remarkable scene in her chicken house. The footage revealed her feline companion perched gracefully on one of the chicken trays while the feathered inhabitants remained surprisingly calm and at ease in the presence of their newfound friend. Captioned with a touch of amusement, "I'm not even surprised anymore...," the video serves as a testament to the harmonious coexistence between the cat and the chickens. </media:description>
                  <media:keywords>cat,chicken,harmony,coexistence,video,Sweden,Harv,pets,animals,friendship,unexpected,bond,companionship,feathers,tray,love,heartwarming,amusement,captivated,surprising,delightful</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Harv</media:city>
                  <media:country>Sweden</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>SE</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Mon, 3 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2479</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/bad55bf2-197f-4722-8387-d12a5844b496.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/86f6ba64-461f-4f45-922c-f0d129b95f61.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Acrobatic feline: Simba's clever bed maneuver stuns owner</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a remarkable display of feline ingenuity, a video captured by @simbikorm in Lviv, Ukraine, on June 19th, 2023, showcases a cat named Simba engaging in a unique method to slide under the bed. The footage reveals Simba pushing itself on its hind legs against the wall, using its claws to grip the bed legs, and skillfully maneuvering its body under the bed while still lying on its back. According to Simba's owner, this unconventional approach allows the curious cat to effortlessly explore cozy spaces without expending unnecessary energy. Simba's ability to think outside the box and execute such acrobatic moves has left viewers amazed and delighted by the feline's cleverness.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>cat,video,Simba,pushing,hind legs,wall,bed,claws,under,lying,back,energy,explore,acrobatic,cleverness,unique,maneuver,curious,amazed,delighted</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Lviv</media:city>
                  <media:country>Ukraine</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>UA</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2423</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/62f8a1d4-8d88-46f2-9b9a-b9ebf755fd37.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/a9083bd4-c06d-46ef-91a4-cc127f91edac.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Fierce guardian or adorable companion? Unraveling the mystery of the wool-loving cat!</media:title>
                  <media:description>A recent video captured by @mitya_bengalcat on June 7th, 2023, in Moscow, Russia, showcases a cat fiercely defending a wool ball it clings onto. Despite its defensive behavior, the cat is described as incredibly cute and friendly by its owner. Visitors to their home can vouch for the cat's amiable nature, as it enjoys having its claws trimmed and being groomed while purring contentedly. However, when confronted with wool balls, the cat's reaction remains consistent, hissing and attempting to claw at anyone who approaches. The underlying reason for this behavior remains a mystery, leaving its owner perplexed.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>cat,wool,defensive,cute,friendly,video,Moscow,Russia,paws,mouth,hiss,claw,visitors,home,grooming,purring,behavior,mystery,perplexed</media:keywords>
                  <media:city> Moscow</media:city>
                  <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Wed, 7 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2409</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/09673e0a-479f-49da-9bf3-692eeaa2656c.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/4c628002-231b-4392-b99e-094630d63755.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Rolling cat's unique talent stuns viewers: a heartwarming tale of rescue and playfulness</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a heartwarming display of feline playfulness, a video captured by @ochocofanclub on July 3rd, 2023, in Wakayama Prefecture, Japan, has taken the internet by storm. The footage showcases a remarkable cat who has mastered the art of rolling, using an unconventional technique. The cat, now seven years old, was rescued as a tiny kitten by the owner of an ironworks. However, it wasn't until she turned two that she began to showcase her unique talent of rolling by placing her head between her legs.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>cat,rolling,video,Wakayama Prefecture,Japan,rescue,ironworks,owner,playful,unique,talent,internet,storm,kitten,unconventional,technique,bond,joy,delight,pets</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Wakayama Prefecture</media:city>
                  <media:country>Japan</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>JP</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Mon, 3 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2382</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/7dfa4826-1002-43e5-95c9-d5a2c1c677a9.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/00b069e2-96d4-4cff-ab65-78dc094860a4.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Feathered frenzy: Loki the staffy takes on the seagull invasion in Hull, UK!</media:title>
                  <media:description>On June 3, 2023, in Hull, UK, @zaynetowe witnessed an amusing sight in her garden as her dog, Loki the Staffy, took charge against a swarm of seagulls. The video captured the moment when numerous seagulls invaded the garden, prompting Loki to dash into action. With unyielding determination, Loki fearlessly chased the seagulls away, leaving the garden free from the feathery invaders. It was a comical display of canine bravery, as the loyal pup swiftly returned to the safety of the house after successfully warding off the feathered intruders.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>garden,dog,Loki,staffy,seagulls,chase,video,Hull,UK,funny,brave,invasion,action,loyal,pup,feathered,intruders,June,@zaynetowe,house</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Hull, England </media:city>
                  <media:country>United Kingdom</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>GB</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sat, 3 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2529</guid>
                  <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 20:56:41 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2529.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2529.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Crazy cockatoo's bell-ringing fiasco: hilarious feathery antics unfold!</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a delightful and comical incident captured on video by @bon_bon_the_cockatoo on June 27th, 2023, a white parrot in Arlington, Texas, USA, showcased its mischievous side. The footage revealed the parrot skillfully ringing a small bell with its beak on a table, displaying an impressive level of dexterity. However, the unexpected occurred when the bell slipped from the table's edge, causing the parrot to react in the most amusing way possible. Raising the feathers on its head and shaking its head in apparent disbelief, the feathered performer left viewers in fits of laughter. The video quickly went viral, captivating audiences worldwide with the playful antics of this talented and seemingly expressive cockatoo.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>cockatoo,parrot,video,Arlington,Texas,USA,bird,bell,table,funny,comical,antics,viral,feathers,dexterity,laughter,mischievous,talent,expressive,bon_bon_the_cockatoo,amusing</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Arlington, Texas</media:city>
                  <media:country>United States</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>US</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2441</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/4a11e02b-fcd1-4d5f-98fa-b62d416991a0.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/c3ce357e-41d8-46db-8bc2-783ff07f794b.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Curious cat snatches leftover delight: a hasty escape!</media:title>
                  <media:description>In Central Jakarta, Indonesia, a captivating moment unfolded as a cat stumbled upon a paper bag filled with leftover food on a terrace. Caught on video by @billacarmell on December 1st, 2021, the feline snatched the tempting morsels and hastily attempted to make its escape. However, as the author approached, the cat's curiosity turned into panic causing it to flee.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>cat,food,terrace,paper bag,video,capture,Central Jakarta,Indonesia,leftovers,panic,run,curious,delight,escape,Billacarmell,December,2021,near,hasty,small</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Central Jakarta</media:city>
                  <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>ID</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Wed, 1 Dec 2021</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2431</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/0606d44c-095d-482a-8e5c-3afb7d14705e.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/bf6dc436-1635-430f-b7f6-1f5cf6938a3d.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Whiskered surprise: playful cat in a cute box captivates Siheung City</media:title>
                  <media:description>In Siheung City, Korea, a heartwarming incident occurred on June 3, 2023, as a video captured by @goarongggoo went viral. The clip featured a curious cat tucked away inside a cute box. The man behind the camera revealed that he was selling these delightful boxes when he stumbled upon the feline surprise. With a playful knock on the box resembling a door, he decided to unveil the mystery. Upon opening the box, a charming cat emerged. </media:description>
                  <media:keywords>cat,box,video,cute,Siheung City,Korea,surprise,viral,@goarongggoo,June 3,2023,knock,door,feline,playful,charming,joy,wonder,internet,community,moment</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Siheung City</media:city>
                  <media:country>South Korea</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>KR</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sat, 3 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2480</guid>
                  <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 09:31:32 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/71eed083-e8af-46f6-8c74-09a7128c2948.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2480.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Dual Shiba Inu delight: father and son's playful bonding on human perch!</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a heartwarming video captured by @tsumasaki_mame on 1st April, 2023, two Shiba Inus, a father named Tsumasaki and his son Hadashi, showcased their playful bond in an adorable display. The footage, filmed in Vermont, USA, showed the furry duo barking at each other and engaging in gentle nibbling while perched atop their human companion, Sir_Phrozen. This endearing interaction gave a glimpse into their typical play style, with Tsumasaki and Hadashi choosing an unconventional stage for their antics. </media:description>
                  <media:keywords>playful,Shiba Inus,bonding,dogs,video,father,son,barking,nibbling,couch,Vermont,USA,pets,human,companionship,adorable,heartwarming,connection,joyful,unconventional</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Vermont</media:city>
                  <media:country>United States</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>US</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sat, 1 Apr 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2442</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/915b3136-9f0c-462f-a938-ac2d5d7df46a.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/7ce686ab-fb03-42fe-9218-26052f0e79fc.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Hilarious horse spooked by twig: yard clean-up turns into equine feast and fright</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a humorous turn of events, a video captured by @sofieburman on 4th July, 2023, in Stockholm, Sweden, shows a mischievous mare named Bibbi getting spooked by a simple twig. The incident occurred after the yard was cleared of small trees and bushes, which were then given to the horses as an additional treat and plaything. However, Bibbi's curiosity got the best of her as she picked up the twig, only to be startled and dash away. Undeterred by Bibbi's momentary fright, the other horses happily devoured everything in sight. It was a comical reminder that even the most ordinary objects can lead to unexpected reactions among our equine friends.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>horse,video,twig,running,away,biting,yard,clean-up,horses,eat,play,mare,Bibbi,spooked,friends,funny,curiosity,feast,Stockholm,Sweden</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Stockholm </media:city>
                  <media:country>Sweden</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>SE</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Tue, 4 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2401</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/7abd777e-3093-4639-93f2-acbbb89a2a66.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/d990db56-d4e1-4bc4-8f6e-4f7dcb5d992f.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Feline paradise: Simba's ultimate vacation spot atop the door!</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a captivating video captured by @simbikorm on February 1st, 2023, in Lviv, Ukraine, their feline companion named Simba found the most peculiar yet fascinating vacation spot. As the camera panned across the scene, Simba was seen peacefully perched on top of the door, in a position defying gravity. With its stomach resting on the door and legs gracefully positioned on either side, Simba had discovered a unique and undeniably comfortable spot.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>cat,video,Simba,door,sleeping,stomach,legs,vacation,spot,favorite,Lviv,Ukraine,captured,peculiar,gravity,comfort,shut-eye,beloved,unique,February</media:keywords>
                  <media:city> Lviv</media:city>
                  <media:country>Ukraine</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>UA</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Wed, 1 Feb 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2391</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/552b190b-1bea-4da8-94b8-bbbced7cf05b.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/3ef89ae5-e30d-4ff4-9b68-98758938188f.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Captivating canine concert: witness the enchanting howl of a Weimaraner!</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a charming display of canine vocal prowess, a Weimaraner in La Crosse, Wisconsin, USA, has captivated the internet with its melodious howl. Shared by @mizj3n on May 21st, 2023, a video captured the precious moment as the Weimaraner let out a soulful cry from the comforts of its home. The caption accompanying the footage reads, " You ever seen a Weimaraner howl?... Now you have." The enchanting video quickly garnered attention, drawing viewers into the captivating world of this elegant breed.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>weimaraner,dog,howl,video,La Crosse,Wisconsin,USA,mizj3n,captivating,enchanting,melodious,soulful,internet,moment,precious,caption,attention,breed,elegant,haunting,heartwarming</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>La Crosse, Wisconsin</media:city>
                  <media:country>United States</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>US</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sun, 21 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2314</guid>
                  <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 11:16:27 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/b26d2ddf-bb9e-472c-b048-66136fed54d7.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/af7d812c-a21e-4821-9de5-238246397706.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Mischievous mac n' cheese muncher: wombat breaks into camper's tent in Melbourne!</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a surprising turn of events, a video captured by @charliefowlvr on June 24, 2023, in Melbourne, Australia, shows a cheeky wombat making its way into a camper's tent. The mischievous creature apparently had a craving for mac n' cheese, as it had chewed its way through the tent to get a taste of the cheesy delight. In the footage, the wombat's head can be seen peeking inside the tent, while its body remains outside. This unexpected encounter highlights the resourcefulness and determination of Australia's native wildlife, even when it comes to satisfying their unusual appetites.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>wombat,tent,Melbourne,Australia,video,mac n cheese,chewed,wildlife,encounter,curious,mischief,resourcefulness,appetites,unexpected,capture,cheeky,craving,taste,camper,head</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Melbourne</media:city>
                  <media:country>Australia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>AU</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2317</guid>
                  <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 11:14:44 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/25ed8c77-d811-4f5d-983f-d624ee57c5a3.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/c3722437-b69d-4adc-a6e4-971a6ab6d62f.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Cat chaos: Minsk feline's hilarious morning escape from the mysterious carrier bag!</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a humorous yet chaotic scene captured by @vorobyov2021 on May 5, 2023, in Minsk, Belarus, a scared feline caused havoc as she ran around the house with a carrier bag caught on her back. The video showcases the frantic cat darting from room to room, desperately trying to escape the seemingly terrifying bag. According to the author, the unexpected morning commotion served as an amusing wake-up call, as the mischievous cat poked and prodded her way through the apartment in a comical attempt to be free from her unexpected accessory.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>cat,video,Minsk,Belarus,scared,carrier bag,back,running,banging,things,escape,hilarious,chaos,feline,apartment,wake-up,poke,capture,room,commotion</media:keywords>
                  <media:city> Minsk</media:city>
                  <media:country>Belarus</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>BY</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Fri, 5 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2566</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 07:53:24 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2566.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2566.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Adorable new arrival: baby parrot dreams peacefully in loving hands</media:title>
                  <media:description>On June 8th, 2023, in Izmir, Turkey, a heartwarming video captured by @hknyilmaz35 showcased a newly hatched parrot in the gentle hands of its caretaker, Hakan. The tiny parrot, peacefully asleep, melted hearts with its undeniable cuteness. The short clip resonated with viewers worldwide, celebrating the beauty of new life and the bond between humans and animals.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>adorable,parrot,hatchling,video,Izmir,Turkey,hands,caretaker,asleep,cute,newlife,bond,humans,animals,heartwarming,tiny,love,peaceful,@hknyilmaz35,June8th2023</media:keywords>
                  <media:city> Izmir</media:city>
                  <media:country>Turkey</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>TR</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>Animals</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Thu, 8 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2546</guid>
                  <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023 18:03:14 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2546.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2546.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                     </channel>
                  </rss>
                