<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
        <rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
        xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
        xmlns:openSearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearchrss/1.0/"
        xmlns:dfpvideo="http://api.google.com/dfpvideo"
        xmlns:tms="http://data.tmsapi.com/v1.1"
        version="2.0">
          <channel>
            <title>ViralBear videos</title>
            <dfpvideo:version>2</dfpvideo:version>
              
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Training for the frontlines: tactical medicine in the heart of the conflict</media:title>
                  <media:description>Amidst the ongoing conflict between Ukraine and Russia, a recent video captured by @bullt_ on July 31st, 2023, in the Mar'ins'kyi district of Donbas, Ukraine, sheds light on the intense training that soldiers undergo. The footage reveals soldiers engaged in tactical medicine training, a crucial skillset for those newly arrived and deployed to the Bakhmut direction. The voiceover in the video emphasizes the significance of self-application of tourniquets in the critical "red zone." The caption, "we train as we fight and we fight as we train," encapsulates the dedication and readiness exhibited by Ukrainian fighters as they prepare for the challenges on the frontlines.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>conflict,training,soldiers,tactical,medicine,frontline,Ukraine,Russia,video,Bakhmut,direction,Mar'ins'kyi,Donbas,@bullt_,tourniquet,red zone,readiness,fighters,caption,dedication</media:keywords>
                  <media:city> Mar'ins'kyi, Donbas</media:city>
                  <media:country>Ukraine</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>UA</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>News</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2674</guid>
                  <pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023 13:24:04 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2674.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2674.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Massive explosion rocks Sergiev Posad: pyrotechnics warehouse blast shatters windows and sends shockwaves across the region</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a startling incident that shook Sergiev Posad, Russia, an explosion of immense magnitude occurred at an optical-mechanical plant on August 9, 2023. The blast, which was captured by surveillance cameras, emanated from a warehouse housing pyrotechnics within the plant's premises. Astonishingly, despite the deafening noise and mushroom-shaped cloud that billowed into the sky, local residents appeared surprisingly nonchalant, going about their daily routines as fragments of shattered glass and mosquito nets rained down around them. The explosion's impact was so severe that windows in numerous nearby buildings were blown out by the powerful shockwave, and car alarms were triggered by the force. More than ten individuals sustained injuries in the incident, prompting a swift evacuation of all plant facilities, including rented spaces. Law enforcement personnel and district leader Dmitry Akulov promptly arrived at the scene, aiming to manage the aftermath of this alarming event.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>explosion,surveillance,residents,pyrotechnics,plant,injuries,evacuation,law enforcement,district,mushroom cloud,shockwave,windows,glass,mosquito nets,car alarms,impact,blast,incident,aftermath,Sergiev Posad</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Sergiev Posad</media:city>
                  <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>News</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Wed, 9 Aug 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2670</guid>
                  <pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 21:15:42 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2670.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2670.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Mass evacuation underway at ZOMZ plant in Sergiev Posad following explosive incident</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a startling turn of events, the Zagorsk Optical and Mechanical Plant (ZOMZ) located in Sergiev Posad, Russia, has been rocked by a mysterious explosion on August 9, 2023. The incident prompted an immediate and complete evacuation of all structures within the plant, with security forces swiftly mobilizing to the scene. Dmitry Akulov, the head of the urban district, arrived alongside representatives of law enforcement agencies to assess the situation. Preliminary reports suggest that the explosion originated within the optical-mechanical plant, shrouding the vicinity in a massive cloud of smoke, as captured by video footage. The incident has left the local community on edge as authorities work to uncover the cause behind the unsettling occurrence at the heart of this industrial facility.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>explosion,evacuation,ZOMZ,incident,smoke,security,authorities,plant,Sergiev Posad,Russia,cloud,workshop,community,industrial,mystery,forces,district,optical,mechanical,video</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Sergiev Posad</media:city>
                  <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>News</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Wed, 9 Aug 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2669</guid>
                  <pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 21:15:59 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2669.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2669.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Mysterious nighttime spectacle: enigmatic lights over Hoyts Docklands spark meteor shower speculation</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a captivating video captured by @mahekinaus on August 7, 2023, a mesmerizing display of bright, moving objects illuminated the night sky near Hoyts Docklands, Australia. The video, accompanied by the caption "Was that a meteor shower that we just saw? Witnessed it near Hoyts Docklands. </media:description>
                  <media:keywords>night,lights,sky,video,meteor,shower,spectacle,Hoyts Docklands,Australia,mystery,captivation,curiosity,enthusiasts,phenomenon,onlookers,anticipation,speculation,celestial,updates,community</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Docklands</media:city>
                  <media:country>Australia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>AU</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>News</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Mon, 7 Aug 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2668</guid>
                  <pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 21:20:40 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2668.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2668.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Farewell to a musical icon: thousands gather in Bray to celebrate Sinéad O'Connor's life and legacy</media:title>
                  <media:description>Thousands of mourners and fans gathered along the seafront in Bray, County Wicklow, Ireland, to bid a heartfelt farewell to the renowned singer Sinéad O'Connor on August 8, 2023. The emotional gathering began before sunrise, as individuals came to both grieve her passing and celebrate her remarkable life. By midday, the seafront was teeming with people, forming a poignant backdrop for the funeral cortege. Led by police motorcycles and accompanied by the resonating strains of Bob Marley &amp; The Wailers' "Natural Mystic," the procession saw O'Connor's hearse adorned with flowers tossed by the crowd. A video captured by @lalordarren showed the procession as people followed her hearse. As it approached her former home, the crowd erupted in applause, while heartfelt renditions of "Nothing Compares 2 U" echoed and banners carried messages of gratitude and remembrance. Among those paying their respects were Irish President Michael D Higgins and his wife Sabina, underscoring the profound impact that Sinéad O'Connor had on Ireland and the world.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>singer,tribute,farewell,Bray,Ireland,crowd,cortege,music,legacy,mourners,fans,hearse,flowers,applause,banners,president,impact,grief,remembrance,iconic</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Bray </media:city>
                  <media:country>Ireland</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>IE</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>News</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Tue, 8 Aug 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2662</guid>
                  <pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 07:53:49 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2662.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2662.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Soldier's valor: battling adversity on the frontline - a tale from Kurdyumivka</media:title>
                  <media:description>In the heart of the conflict between Russia and Ukraine, a video captured by @kaban.0666 on July 19, 2023, provides a poignant glimpse into the life of a Ukrainian soldier stationed at the frontline in Kurdyumivka, Donetsk Oblast. Amidst the chaos and danger, the soldier recounts his brave efforts to repel the opposing forces, driving them to seek refuge in the trenches. Displaying remarkable precision, he meticulously adjusts a drone while under fire, firing over 20 shots within a span of 20 minutes to accomplish his mission. Yet, even in the face of triumph, adversity strikes, as an explosive head injury and contusion leave him injured and hospitalized. </media:description>
                  <media:keywords>valor,frontline,conflict,Ukraine,soldier,trenches,drone,shots,adversity,injury,hospital,treatment,courage,sacrifice,resilience,video,Kurdyumivka,Donetsk,@kaban.0666</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Kurdyumivka, Donetsk</media:city>
                  <media:country>Ukraine</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>UA</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>WAR</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>News</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2656</guid>
                  <pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 07:17:24 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2656.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2656.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Typhoon Dussuri aftermath: government trucks extracting water from flooded road tunnel in Fuzhou, Southeast China</media:title>
                  <media:description>In the aftermath of Typhoon Dussuri's devastating impact on Fuzhou, Southeast China, a resident known as @Tenglovehourglass captured a compelling video of government trucks diligently working to extract water from a flooded road tunnel on August 1, 2023. The typhoon's relentless heavy rainfall left the area inundated, and the roadways submerged in mud and standing water. Living nearby, The author witnessed the dire conditions firsthand, as the government staff tirelessly utilized specialized equipment to clean and restore the once-swamped road. As the community grapples with the aftermath of the natural disaster, these efforts serve as a testament to the resilience and determination of those involved in the recovery process.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>typhoon,dussuri,fuzhou,china,flood,rainfall,water,road,tunnel,mud,government,trucks,extraction,cleaning,aftermath,southeast,video,equipment,standing,window</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Fuzhou</media:city>
                  <media:country>China</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>CN</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>News</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Tue, 1 Aug 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2646</guid>
                  <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 15:31:51 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2646.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2646.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Devastating flash floods sever rural road in Zhuozhou, North China</media:title>
                  <media:description>In the aftermath of Typhoon Dussuri, the rural area of Zhuozhou in North China has been hit hard by continuous heavy rainfall, leading to flash floods that have wreaked havoc on the region. In a poignant video captured by @XiaoXiao on August 1, 2023, floodwaters can be seen having mercilessly cut a rural road into two, leaving the village isolated and vulnerable. The author, a resident of the affected village, witnessed firsthand the destructive power of nature as the torrential waters inundated the landscape, disrupting the lives of the local community. With the area bordering Beijing to the north, the impact of this natural disaster has been significant, raising concerns about the safety and well-being of the residents in the wake of this devastating flood event.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>floods,typhoon,rainfall,disaster,Zhuozhou,NorthChina,@XiaoXiao,video,rural,road,flashfloods,aftermath,impact,nature,isolated,community,Beijing,heavyrain,devastation,vulnerability</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Zhuozhou</media:city>
                  <media:country>China</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>CN</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>News</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Tue, 1 Aug 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2645</guid>
                  <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 15:31:31 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2645.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2645.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Gas station brawl: shocking video goes viral as customers seek justice for dubious fuel</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a shocking incident at a gas station in Barabash, Primorsky Krai, Russia, on July 28, 2023, an aggressive altercation erupted after customers experienced engine troubles following a refueling with suspected low-quality fuel. The situation escalated when two cars failed to start immediately after refueling, and one of the vehicle owners confronted the gas station employee. Instead of addressing the issue, the gas station employee responded with violence, attacking the outraged customers with her fists. The entire episode was caught on camera and quickly spread across the internet, causing outrage among viewers. The affected motorists, determined not to let this go unnoticed, promptly reported the incident to the police in search of justice for their ordeal. Authorities are currently investigating the matter, and public sentiment is demanding appropriate action be taken against those responsible for this appalling act of aggression.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>gas,station,employee,customers,refueling,dubious,fuel,viral,internet,tanker,motorists,brawl,incident,Barabash,Primorsky,Krai,Russia,violence,police,justice</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Barabash, Primorsky</media:city>
                  <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>News</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2642</guid>
                  <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 09:26:09 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2642.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2642.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Beach brawl in Primorye: woman takes down two in fiery verbal skirmish</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a shocking incident near Vladivostok on the beach in Shamora Bay, Primorye, Russia, a woman wearing a black bikini unleashed a display of aggression and martial skill after a heated verbal altercation with her companions on July 27, 2023. Eyewitnesses reported that the women were drinking and quarreling when the woman in the black bikini decided to settle the matter physically. She swiftly attacked the offending woman, sending her sprawling to the floor, and then turned her fury towards a man who attempted to intervene. With precise boxing techniques, she swiftly subdued the man, hoisted him over her shoulder, and delivered a final blow, leaving him on the floor. The relentless attacker then returned to her group, seemingly unaffected by the intense brawl. As of now, it remains unclear whether any of the participants involved in the altercation have filed a complaint with the police.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>beach,brawl,primorye,russia,vladivostok,shamora bay,woman,black bikini,aggression,martial skill,verbal altercation,drinking,quarreling,attack,man,boxing techniques,intervention,relentless,group,police</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Primorye </media:city>
                  <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>News</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2641</guid>
                  <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 09:28:41 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2641.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2641.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>George Strait's Nashville stadium show: an abrupt end in the pouring rain sparks outrage among fans</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a highly anticipated event at Nissan Stadium, country music legend George Strait's performance in Nashville, Tennessee, USA, came to an abrupt halt as the rain poured down on July 29th, 2023. Despite efforts to fit in as much music as possible before impending storms, Strait's set was cut short, leaving fans disappointed and outraged. The decision not to offer refunds or reschedule the show infuriated concertgoers who expected a full performance from the iconic singer. With tickets for Strait's limited 2023 shows being highly priced and sought after, the disappointment was intensified. While safety concerns regarding lightning and severe weather were cited as reasons for the abrupt ending, fans questioned whether the show could have resumed later. As concert organizers become increasingly cautious about weather-related risks, this incident adds to the ongoing debate on balancing entertainment with safety at outdoor events. @magsd94 captured a video of with the stadium full f people despite the drizzling. </media:description>
                  <media:keywords>concert,music,country,legend,nashville,nissan stadium,george strait,rain,storm,disappointment,outrage,tickets,performance,abrupt,safety,lightning,outdoor,event,fans,iconic</media:keywords>
                  <media:city> Nashville, Tennessee</media:city>
                  <media:country>United States</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>US</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>News</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2636</guid>
                  <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 07:46:14 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2636.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2636.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Convicted thief escapes Blagoveshchensk pre-trial detention center through transmission window</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a daring escape, a young man convicted of theft managed to break free from a pre-trial detention center in Blagoveshchensk, Russia, through a transmission window on July 30, 2023. The incident occurred on Sunday during a visitation and transfer session, taking advantage of the warden's absence. After being on the run for a few hours, the fugitive was finally apprehended on the night of July 31st. According to the Russian Federal Penitentiary Service for the Amur Region, the escapee had been in detention since December 2022. Now facing severe consequences, the convict may be sentenced to forced labor or imprisonment for up to four years, as per Article 313 of the Criminal Code of Russia. Additionally, the court will charge him for the expenses incurred during the search operation. The Federal Penitentiary Service is currently conducting an internal audit to assess the security breach that allowed this escape to occur.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>escape,convict,theft,pretrial,detention,Blagoveshchensk,Russia,transmission,window,caught,criminal,penalty,fugitive,imprisonment,search,audit,warden,apprehended,visitation,expenses</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Blagoveshchensk</media:city>
                  <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>News</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2617</guid>
                  <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 13:22:11 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2617.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2617.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Intense firepower unleashed: Ukrainian forces train and prepare for confrontation between Donbass and Bakhmut</media:title>
                  <media:description>In the tense and war-torn between Donbass and Bakhmut, Ukraine, a harrowing video emerged on July 24, 2023, capturing the relentless firing of warheads by soldiers in the fields. The footage was attributed to @vladhalidov, shedding light on the activity of the Sheikh Mansour Battalion (BShM) and the Special Tactical Army Group LOM. Under the command of Muhammad-Aslan, the group conducted a strategic briefing on the impending storming of Russian positions, while also providing crucial training to the Ukrainian army. The conflict between Ukraine and Russia had persisted for over a year, with this latest display of firepower indicating the ongoing severity of the situation in the region. As tensions escalated, the international community remained on high alert, closely monitoring the developments in this volatile conflict zone.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>soldiers,firing,warheads,Donbass,Bakhmut,Ukraine,video,Sheikh Mansour Battalion,BShM,Special Tactical Army Group LOM,commander,Muhammad-Aslan,briefing,storming,Russian positions,training,armed conflict,tension,international community,escalation</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Donbass</media:city>
                  <media:country>Ukraine</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>UA</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>News</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2606</guid>
                  <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 08:28:15 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2606.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2606.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Nature's fury unleashed: lightning strikes and flames explode in Shijiazhuang</media:title>
                  <media:description>On July 24, 2023, in Shijiazhuang, northern China, a startling and unintentional event was captured on video by @HomelessYuanyuan. As she stood in front of her apartment window with her mobile phone, attempting to capture a street scene during a rainstorm and thunder, lightning struck the transformer below her building. The intense impact caused sparks of flames to erupt, scattering fiery fragments in all directions. Nature's fury was unleashed, and in a split second, the author found herself witnessing a breathtaking display of raw power and danger.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>lightning,sparks,flames,explosion,rainstorm,thunder,Shijiazhuang,China,video,mobile,window,street,nature,fury,power,danger,unpredictability,awe,humbled,@HomelessYuanyuan</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Shijiazhuang</media:city>
                  <media:country>China</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>CN</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>News</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2604</guid>
                  <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 13:16:50 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2604.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2604.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Stranded in the muddy ravine: military jeep's dramatic rescue in Bakhmut, Ukraine</media:title>
                  <media:description>In the rural outskirts of Bakhmut, Ukraine, an extraordinary scene unfolded on May 15, 2023, when a military jeep found itself trapped in the treacherous aftermath of a heavy rainstorm. Captured by @koshkarov_yarik, the vehicle was in the midst of pulling another stuck automobile when it succumbed to the thick mud, leaving its occupants in a precarious situation. As the hours passed and the sun began to set, tension mounted as the stranded group awaited assistance. To their surprise, it was an unexpected twist of fate that came to their aid. While waiting, a bizarre event occurred when their brother arrived to "shoot at the neighbor," causing an uproar of noisy birds. Remarkably, amid the chaos, a timely rescue operation led by fellow military personnel swooped in just in time, ensuring the safe extraction of both vehicles and their relieved occupants. The daring rescue, coupled with the unusual circumstances, left an unforgettable mark on the small community, showcasing the unwavering camaraderie and ingenuity of those serving in Ukraine's military.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>ravine,rain,stuck,jeep,evening,brother,shoot,neighbor,birds,lancet,rescue,mud,Bakhmut,Ukraine,military,daring,trapped,assistance,occupants,community</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Bakhmut</media:city>
                  <media:country>Ukraine</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>UA</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>News</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Mon, 15 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2591</guid>
                  <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 13:06:37 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2591.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2591.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Ukrainian drones strike Moscow: facades damaged, no casualties reported </media:title>
                  <media:description>On the night of July 30, 2023, Moscow, Russia experienced another attack on its facilities by Ukrainian drones, as the ongoing conflict between the two nations continued. The Mayor of Moscow, Sergei Sobyanin, confirmed the incident, stating that the facades of two City office towers sustained slight damage, fortunately without any reported casualties or injuries. The Ministry of Defense revealed that one UAV was successfully destroyed in the air above the Odintsovo district, while two others were thwarted by electronic warfare, causing them to lose control and crash on the territory of Moscow City. Video footage captured the aftermath, depicting shattered glass scattered on the ground in front of the affected buildings. This incident marks yet another escalation in the year-long conflict between Ukraine and Russia, escalating tensions and raising concerns about the safety and stability of the region.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>attack,ukrainian,drones,moscow,russia,conflict,mayor,facades,damage,casualties,injured,ministry,defense,UAV,destroyed,Odintsovo,electronic warfare,crashed,territory,video footage</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Moscow</media:city>
                  <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>News</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2590</guid>
                  <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 13:05:13 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2590.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2590.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title> Ukrainian drones attack Moscow, captured on video by tourist amid ongoing conflict with Russia</media:title>
                  <media:description>On the night of July 30, 2023, Moscow experienced an unsettling incident as two Ukrainian drones launched an attack on the capital. Fortunately, there were no reported casualties or injuries, but the facades of two City office towers were slightly damaged. Mayor Sergey Sobyanin confirmed the attack and stated that the military successfully destroyed one UAV with air defense systems in the Odintsovo district of the Moscow region. Additionally, two more drones were brought down by electronic warfare, losing control and crashing onto the grounds of the Moscow City non-residential building complex. Among the witnesses was a young girl visiting the city with her grandmother, who unintentionally captured the dramatic moment of a drone's fall and subsequent explosion on video. The attack adds to the ongoing tension between Ukraine and Russia, which has been engulfed in a military conflict for over a year.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>moscow,attack,drones,ukrainian,explosions,mayor,damaged,casualties,military,air defense,electronic warfare,crash,witness,girl,grandmother,video,tension,conflict,authorities,implications</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Moscow</media:city>
                  <media:country>Ukraine</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>UA</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>News</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2589</guid>
                  <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 13:05:52 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2589.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2589.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Foiled Ukrainian drone attack on Moscow City tower amid ongoing Russia-Ukraine conflict</media:title>
                  <media:description>On July 30, 2023, Moscow, Russia, experienced the consequences of a foiled drone attack on the Moscow City tower, caught on video. The explosion caused significant damage, shattering windows on the 11th floor and leaving fragments of the drone and glass near the building's entrance. Thankfully, there were no casualties reported, and emergency services quickly responded to the scene. The Russian Ministry of Defense confirmed the attack, attributing it to Ukrainian unmanned aerial vehicles engaged in attempted terrorism. According to the Ministry, two UAVs managed to suppress electronic warfare before losing control and crashing onto the territory of Moscow City. This incident adds to the escalating tensions between Ukraine and Russia, as both countries have been in conflict for some time now.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>explosion,drone,attack,Moscow,Russia,windows,fragments,entrance,casualties,emergency,services,foiled,Ukrainian,electronic,warfare,conflict,tension,video,11th floor,Ministry,July 30</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Moscow</media:city>
                  <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>News</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2588</guid>
                  <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 13:06:05 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2588.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2588.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Drone crashes into Moscow City tower in Russia</media:title>
                  <media:description>An explosion occurred on 30 July 2023 in the 50-storey building of the IQ-quarter located in Moscow City.

The incident took place in the building at 10/2 Presnenskaya Embankment, at the level of the fifth or sixth floors, where the glazing was “broken”. No harm done.

The tower was evacuated, law enforcement agencies arrived at the scene.

Shortly before this, air defense systems repelled an attack by drones in the Moscow region. According to 112, the drones were shot down near Odintsovo and Krasnogorsk.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>moscow,russia,drone,crash,war,ukraine,moscow city,explosion</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Moscow</media:city>
                  <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>News</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2582</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023 17:45:16 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2582.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2582.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Devastating wildfire strikes near Volos, Greece</media:title>
                  <media:description>On July 27, 2023, a destructive wildfire ravaged the area near Volos, Greece, causing significant damage to an ammunition depot situated in the coastal town of Nea Aghialos. The depot, belonging to the Greek air force, was engulfed in flames, leading to powerful explosions that echoed through the region. Local media reported on the incident, and officials took immediate action, ordering the evacuation of several communities in the severely impacted Magnesia area along the northern coast of Athens. As the fires continued to spread, @peterjaygood captured a video showcasing smoke billowing from a distance from the fires near Volos. The situation remained critical, with authorities and emergency services working tirelessly to contain the blaze and protect the affected communities.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>wildfire,volos,greece,ammunition,depot,explosions,evacuation,magnesia,coastal,nea aghialos,greek air force,damage,smoke,fires,video,@peterjaygood,media,officials,communities,Athens</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Volos</media:city>
                  <media:country>Greece</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>GR</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>News</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2575</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 07:26:05 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2575.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2575.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Gas explosion rocks residential building in Nizhnekamsk</media:title>
                  <media:description>On July 25, 2023, a devastating gas explosion shook a five-story residential building in Nizhnekamsk, Russia, leaving behind a trail of destruction and injuries. The incident resulted in two people being injured, while eight other residents managed to evacuate independently from the burning structure. The building suffered partial destruction, with the load-bearing structures being severely damaged and the windows of some apartments shattered. As the dust settled, the community was left in shock and uncertainty as authorities began their investigation into the cause of the explosion. With no information yet on the root of the tragedy, residents and officials are left grappling with the aftermath, seeking answers and support for the affected individuals and families.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>explosion,residential,building,nizhnekamsk,russia,injured,evacuation,fire,damage,gas,incident,cause,investigation,shattered,uncertainty,shock,community,support,tragedy,aftermath.</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Nizhnekamsk</media:city>
                  <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>News</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2574</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 08:15:40 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2574.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2574.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Fearless driver defies odds: nonchalantly navigates car on swaying tow track through Minsk's road</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a remarkable display of nonchalance, a video captured by @rrrinita on July 12, 2023, in Minsk, Belarus, showcased a driver unbothered by the perilous sight of a car being carried and swaying on the road. The onlooker initially suspected the driver might be feeling unwell, but to their surprise, the driver appeared utterly unfazed, revealing that it was not their first time engaging in such an audacious feat. Attached to the vehicle was a tow track where the car was mounted, causing it to sway dangerously from side to side. Despite the alarming spectacle, the driver calmly continued to navigate through the streets of Minsk, defying the odds and leaving witnesses astounded by their fearless determination.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>car,tow,swaying,road,driver,fearless,Minsk,Belarus,video,danger,audacious,nonchalant,astonishing,surprising,unfazed,daring,streets,spectacle,determination,amazed</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Minsk</media:city>
                  <media:country>Belarus</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>BY</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>News</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2565</guid>
                  <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 07:13:05 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2565.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2565.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Night of terror: families seek shelter from Russian rocket attacks in Odesa shopping mall garage</media:title>
                  <media:description>In the midst of the ongoing military conflict between Russia and Ukraine, a chilling video has emerged, shedding light on the harrowing reality faced by the people of Odesa, Ukraine. On July 22, 2023, @stilianspai captured a heart-wrenching scene as families sought refuge from a night rocket attack in one of the city's shopping mall garages. The footage showed small children nestled in strollers, their parents anxiously huddled together, seeking safety from the relentless barrage of rockets raining down upon the city. The haunting image serves as a poignant reminder of the devastating toll this conflict has taken on innocent civilians, whose lives are forever impacted by the indiscriminate violence.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>attack,odesa,ukraine,russians,video,shelter,families,night,rocket,mall,garage,conflict,children,parents,fear,war,violence,civilians,safety,devastation</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Odesa</media:city>
                  <media:country>Ukraine</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>UA</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>News</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2555</guid>
                  <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 14:59:50 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2555.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2555.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Tragedy unleashed: chilling footage reveals the day chaos struck Chaikovska Street</media:title>
                  <media:description>On July 28, 2022, in Bakhmut, Donetsk, Ukraine, @coldmorion recorded a distressing video of a shelling incident that devastated Chaikovska Street. The footage captured the terrifying moment when Uragan MLRS and cluster munitions rained down on the area, resulting in the tragic loss of five lives. The video showcased the horrifying reality of the conflict, leaving no doubt about the impact on civilians caught in the crossfire.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>shelling,distress,video,Bakhmut,Donetsk,Ukraine,Chaikovska Street,Uragan MLRS,cluster munitions,tragedy,chaos,civilians,conflict,devastation,loss,lives,war,violence,footage,distressing</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Bakhmut, Donetsk</media:city>
                  <media:country>Ukraine</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>UA</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>WAR</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>News</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2022</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2553</guid>
                  <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023 20:10:16 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2553.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2553.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Skyscraper fire and crane collapse: dramatic scene unfolds at 41st and 10th Ave, New York</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a harrowing incident on the 26th of July, 2023, at the intersection of 41st and 10th Ave in New York City, USA, a devastating fire broke out on top of a skyscraper, accompanied by a catastrophic crane collapse. The intense scene was captured by @akofink, who shared a chilling video showcasing smoke billowing from the building's pinnacle. The social media post was captioned, "Crane collapse and fire! 41st and 10th Ave. First responders on the scene." The incident prompted an immediate response from first responders who rushed to the location to combat the raging blaze and assess the extent of the damage. </media:description>
                  <media:keywords>skyscraper,fire,crane,collapse,New York,USA,video,smoke,41st,10th Ave,incident,responders,damage,investigation,social media,tragedy,authorities,intersection,billowing,chilling</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>New York City</media:city>
                  <media:country>United States</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>US</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>News</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2551</guid>
                  <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023 18:25:43 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2551.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2551.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Wildfires ravage Cascais, Portugal: local residents and firefighters battle blaze in Sintra-Cascais Natural Park</media:title>
                  <media:description>On July 25th, 2023, a devastating wildfire struck the picturesque region of Cascais, Portugal. The blaze originated at 5 p.m. in the mountainous terrain of the Sintra-Cascais natural park, covering an expansive 145 square kilometers of land west of Lisbon. At 6 p.m., @InVasconcellos captured a video of the raging inferno, as hundreds of Portuguese firefighters, supported by local residents, scrambled to contain the flames. However, their efforts were challenged by strong winds, complicating the firefighting process. The popular holiday destination of Cascais faced a threat to its natural beauty and wildlife as the fire continued to spread, prompting urgent action from the authorities to control the devastating situation.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>cascais,portugal,wildfires,2023,video,@InVasconcellos,july,25th,natural park,firefighters,blaze,mountainous,sintra-cascais,land,lisbon,winds,residents,holiday destination,effort,authorities.</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Cascais</media:city>
                  <media:country>Portugal</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>PT</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>News</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2550</guid>
                  <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 14:49:01 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2550.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2550.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Devastation in Chernihiv: aftermath of a missile strike in the Ukrainian-Russian war</media:title>
                  <media:description>In the wake of a missile strike during the debut of the Ukrainian-Russian war, the city of Chernihiv, Ukraine, witnessed scenes of utter devastation. A video captured by @rama_sparta on March 1, 2022, revealed the grim aftermath of the attack on soldiers in the area. The footage showcased bullet shells scattered across the landscape and heavy machinery left severely damaged. The haunting images depicted a city engulfed in chaos and destruction as it grappled with the harrowing realities of war.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>destruction,war,missile,strike,soldiers,Chernihiv,Ukraine,aftermath,devastation,video,@rama_sparta,bullet shells,heavy machinery,chaos,attack,landscape,grim,harrowing,reality,footage</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Chernihiv</media:city>
                  <media:country>Ukraine</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>UA</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>News</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Tue, 1 Mar 2022</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2542</guid>
                  <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023 08:19:32 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2542.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2542.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Prisoners of war exchange: a harrowing scene near Bakhmut, Ukraine</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a tense and harrowing scene near Bakhmut, Ukraine, a video captured by @bakhmutkholodnyyyar on May 25, 2023, showcased the exchange of prisoners of war between Ukraine and Russia. The haunting footage revealed the prisoners walking from both sides, surrounded by heavily armored tankers. As the two sides cautiously carried out the exchange, the somber atmosphere reflected the gravity of the ongoing conflict. The video serves as a stark reminder of the human cost and the tense conditions on the ground amid the war's persisting hostility.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>prisoners,war,exchange,Ukraine,Russia,video,Bakhmut,bear,field,tankers,tense,conflict,footage,human cost,soldiers,captivity,exchange,hostility,somber,video</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Bakhmut</media:city>
                  <media:country>Ukraine</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>UA</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>News</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Thu, 25 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2541</guid>
                  <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023 08:20:14 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2541.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2541.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Wildfires force temporary shutdown of Palermo Airport in Sicily, Italy</media:title>
                  <media:description>On July 25th, 2023, a wildfire broke out near the town of Cinisi, Italy, on the island of Sicily, endangering the Falcone Borsellino Airport, also known as Palermo airport. The escalating blaze reached the airport's perimeter, leading authorities to suspend all air traffic until 11 a.m. The intensity of the fire was captured in a video by @f3dericoooo, showing soaring flames along the Palermo-Cinisi highway. The situation prompted concerns for public safety and disrupted airport operations temporarily.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>wildfires,italy,sicily,cinisi,palermo,airport,falcone,borsellino,shutdown,flames,video,@f3dericoooo,highway,air traffic,danger,public safety,authorities,blaze,perimeter,disruption</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Cinisi, Sicily </media:city>
                  <media:country>Italy</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>IT</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>News</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2539</guid>
                  <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 14:18:09 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2539.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2539.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Devastation in Odesa: unleashing destruction - a glimpse of the aftermath from Russian missile attacks</media:title>
                  <media:description>On July 23, 2023, the city center of Odesa, Ukraine, bore witness to the grim consequences of the ongoing conflict with Russia. A video captured by @nepaxyua revealed the harrowing aftermath of a missile attack that occurred the previous night. The footage depicted leaves scattered on pavements, and amidst the ruins, people were seen diligently cleaning shattered glass in their shops. The devastating scene showcased the extent of damage and the toll the conflict has taken on the lives and livelihoods of the city's residents.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>damage,missile,attack,Odesa,Ukraine,conflict,video,aftermath,leaves,pavements,people,cleaning,shattered,glass,shop,devastation,Russian,city center,war,destruction</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Odesa</media:city>
                  <media:country>Ukraine</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>UA</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>News</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sun, 23 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2533</guid>
                  <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 09:27:35 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2533.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2533.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Unmanned aerial vehicle attack in Moscow business center amid ongoing Russia-Ukraine conflict</media:title>
                  <media:description>On July 24th, 2023, a significant incident occurred in Moscow, Russia, as an unmanned aerial vehicle struck a business center on Likhachev Avenue, resulting in an explosion. The impact caused extensive damage to the building, with fragments of the apparatus shattering glass on an area measuring 50 square meters across the 17th and 18th floors. Due to the severity of the situation, authorities temporarily blocked vehicular movement along Likhachev Avenue, as reported by the Moscow Department of Transport. Emergency services and law enforcement swiftly responded to the scene. This occurrence took place amid an ongoing conflict between Ukraine and Russia, adding further tension and concern to the region.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>explosion,uav,business center,damage,glass,fragments,Moscow,Russia,conflict,vehicular movement,block,emergency services,law enforcement,tension,ongoing,Ukraine,Telegram,department of transport,incident,17th floor</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Moscow</media:city>
                  <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>News</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2532</guid>
                  <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 09:27:55 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2532.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2532.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Drone attacks thwarted in Moscow: no casualties reported as electronic warfare saves the day</media:title>
                  <media:description>In the early hours of July 24, 2023, Moscow, Russia faced a potential threat as two drones targeted non-residential buildings. However, thanks to swift action and the use of electronic warfare, the attempted terrorist attack by the Kyiv regime was successfully thwarted. According to the Mayor of Moscow, Sergei Sobyanin, there were no serious damages or casualties resulting from the incident. Eyewitnesses captured footage of one of the drones flying in the Nagatino-Sadovniki area, with one drone hitting the business center on Likhachev Avenue, causing broken windows on the 17th and 18th floors. The wreckage of the second drone was discovered at 17 Komsomolsky Prospekt. While the incident caused temporary traffic disruptions, normalcy was restored in Moscow shortly after the attack.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>moscow,russia,drone,attack,electronic warfare,kyiv regime,terrorism,casualties,damages,eyewitnesses,footage,business center,leroy merlin,komsomolsky prospekt,nagatino-sadovniki,mayor,sergei sobyanin,traffic,disruption,normalcy,thwarted</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Moscow  </media:city>
                  <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>News</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2531</guid>
                  <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 09:28:10 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2531.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2531.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Thunderous chaos: Lahore, Pakistan, hit by violent storm and electric explosions</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a dramatic and electrifying scene captured by @salu_bava on April 5, 2023, Lahore, Pakistan experienced the wrath of a powerful thunderstorm that wreaked havoc on the city's electric infrastructure. The recorded video depicted an intense storm with booming thunder and dazzling lightning strikes illuminating the darkened skies. As the storm intensified, strong winds lashed at electric lines, causing them to malfunction and explode, creating an astonishing display of chaos and danger. </media:description>
                  <media:keywords>thunderstorm,lightning,electric,malfunction,explode,Lahore,Pakistan,video,storm,winds,chaos,danger,darkness,sparks,nature,force,weather,phenomena,residents,caution</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Lahore</media:city>
                  <media:country>Pakistan</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>PK</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>News</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Wed, 5 Apr 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2518</guid>
                  <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 20:47:32 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2518.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2518.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Armed forces of Ukraine foiled in attempted drone attack on Crimea's Krasnogvardeisky District</media:title>
                  <media:description>On July 22, 2023, an attempted drone attack on infrastructure facilities in the Krasnogvardeisky district of Crimea was thwarted by the Armed Forces of Ukraine. The head of the Republic of Crimea, Sergei Aksyonov, revealed that enemy UAVs made an effort to raid the area, but were intercepted before any damage could be inflicted. The prompt response of the Ukrainian troops prevented potential harm to the district's critical assets. The situation prompted the dispatch of emergency response teams from the Ministry of Emergency Situations to ensure any potential consequences were addressed swiftly.
</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>attack,drones,infrastructure,krasnogvardeisky,crimea,ukrainian,troops,raid,interception,damage,response,emergency,ministry,situation,facilities,district,aksyonov,enemy,attempt,consequences</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Krasnogvardeisky district, Crimea</media:city>
                  <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>CWP</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>News</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2515</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 14:54:06 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2515.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2515.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Drunken man survives fall from fifth floor, saved by antenna in Georgievsk, Stavropol</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a remarkable incident that occurred on July 5th, 2023, in Georgievsk, Stavropol Territory, a 56-year-old man, well-known to local rescuers for his troubled lifestyle, survived a fall from the fifth floor thanks to an antenna. The drunken man stumbled at an open window, plummeting to the ground, but miraculously caught his foot on an antenna at the third floor level. Rescuers arrived at the scene and carefully removed him from the antenna before providing necessary assistance. Despite serious leg injuries, the man's life was saved by the antenna, and he was hospitalized in stable condition, no longer in danger.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>drunken,man,survived,fall,antenna,Georgievsk,Stavropol,rescuers,incident,miraculous,hospitalization,stable,leg,injuries,intoxicated,neighbor,fifth floor,assistance,known,lifestyle</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Georgievsk, Stavropol</media:city>
                  <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>News</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Wed, 5 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2488</guid>
                  <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 10:12:53 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2488.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2488.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Mesmerizing aerial encounter: epic dust storm sweeps towards Phoenix, Arizona</media:title>
                  <media:description>On July 17th, 2023, @philthatremains, while flying over Arizona, USA, managed to capture an incredible video of a massive dust storm heading towards Phoenix. The mesmerizing aerial footage showcased the sheer power and scale of the natural phenomenon as it engulfed the landscape. The video quickly gained attention on social media, leaving viewers in awe of the intense dust storm's raw force and impact on the region.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>arizona,usa,dust storm,video,capture,aerial,@philthatremains,flying,incredible,landscape,power,scale,phenomenon,social media,awe,intense,force,impact,region,weather</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Arizona</media:city>
                  <media:country>United States</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>US</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>News</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2475</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/408b4c20-59c2-4abf-a242-ab15055c3047.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/cd205368-0f69-4c6b-a0ef-954866dd4755.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Secret snack: crafty courier caught on camera enjoying customer's pie in Yakutia</media:title>
                  <media:description>In a surprising incident caught on camera on June 30th, 2023 in Yakutia, Russia, a daring courier decided to indulge in a customer's order, leaving onlookers stunned. The footage shows the crafty courier skillfully slicing the pie, ensuring his act remained unnoticed, as he devoured the treat with a small knife. With calculated precision, he closed the pie back up, seamlessly concealing any evidence of his secret snack, and continued on his delivery route. The video has sparked both amusement and disbelief.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>feast,courier,footage,eyewitnesses,yakutia,russia,pie,bike,motorbike,careful,crime,small knife,eating,delivery,secret,snack,indulgence,skillful,amusement,disbelief</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Yakutia</media:city>
                  <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>News</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2470</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/a7ac6ccf-a978-41ad-b5d9-62de66fbfd80.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2470.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Missing nursing student Carlee Russell found safe after mysterious disappearance near Alabama highway</media:title>
                  <media:description>Carlethia "Carlee" Nichole Russell, the 25-year-old nursing student who went missing on Thursday night after calling 911 to report a male toddler walking along an Alabama highway, USA, has returned home. The search for Russell had commenced immediately after her distress call, with search parties in full force. @loganwadams captured a video police looking for Carlee Russell near hoover/Bessemer exit on July 14th, 2023. However, she was found safe and sound on Saturday night, prompting police to take her to a hospital for evaluation. The details of her disappearance and reappearance are now part of an ongoing investigation, according to a statement from Hoover Police Lt. Daniel Lowe.

On her way home from work in Birmingham, Russell had stopped to pick up food when she made the emergency call about the child she had seen. Subsequent attempts to contact her during the call were unsuccessful, leading to her family losing communication with her. When officers arrived at the scene, they discovered Russell's car, wig, and cellphone abandoned, but there were no signs of her or the child. Up until her return, the 911 call remained the only report of a child on the interstate, leaving officials with no further leads on the mysterious case.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>nursing,student,missing,Alabama,USA,CarleeRussell,search,parties,police,toddler,highway,return,hospital,investigation,Birmingham,911,abandoned,mysterious,safe,Interstate459</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Alabama</media:city>
                  <media:country>United States</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>US</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>News</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Fri, 14 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2458</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/b1d4fff1-c5db-48c2-8806-28a7a6c44f05.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/ddb68fb4-8ae6-45e1-b6b0-cf1756dc696b.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Torrential thunderstorm turns Krasnodar streets into rivers as tractor battles flooding</media:title>
                  <media:description>On July 8, 2023, Krasnodar, Russia experienced a severe thunderstorm accompanied by heavy rainfall that lasted over an hour. The downpour resulted in extensive flooding on the streets, parking lots, and even the Mega shopping center in neighboring Yablonovsky. The floodwaters turned many roads into fast-flowing rivers, leading to traffic disruptions and paralysis in some areas. In an attempt to mitigate the flooding, a tractor was seen valiantly collecting water from the inundated streets and channeling it away from the affected areas. </media:description>
                  <media:keywords>storm,floods,Krasnodar,Russia,thunder,downpour,streets,cars,parking lots,Mega shopping center,Yablonovsky,rivers,traffic,paralyzed,tractor,water,waves,afternoon,July 8,2023</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Krasnodar</media:city>
                  <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>News</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sat, 8 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2454</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/636aab4b-dbef-4f15-895c-2d903e2cacac.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/91b737c1-9e39-42a7-af8a-cc23a7405858.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Massive blaze strikes Changzhou food processing factory</media:title>
                  <media:description>On June 28th, 2023, a massive fire broke out in a food processing factory in Changzhou, China, causing thick smoke to billow from the scene and the fire to rapidly expand. @ChangzhouXinbeiPhysicalChemistryTeacher captured this video footage of the raging inferno while passing by the area. The cause of the fire is still under investigation, but officials have confirmed that there were no casualties resulting from the incident.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>fire,factory,changzhou,china,smoke,blaze,video,footage,accident,investigation,officials,casualties,inferno,nearby,raging,food,processing,thick,billowing,expanding</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Changzhou</media:city>
                  <media:country>China</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>CN</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>News</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2452</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/ba2676b5-b683-4842-b9c2-b654355ffb33.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/bfa4d7bf-92bc-4a13-8d48-f1622e36d1f3.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Tuapse's mop-wielding heroine: the savior of a flooded city</media:title>
                  <media:description>In the flooded city of Tuapse, Russia, a remarkable woman with nothing but a mop in hand emerged as a local hero on July 12th, 2023. Fearlessly standing in the water, she took it upon herself to clear the storm drain from debris, preventing further flooding in the area. Social media was abuzz with admiration for her courageous act, and a video capturing her determined efforts quickly gained attention online. Many hailed her as the savior of the city, and the mop became a symbol of her selflessness and resilience in the face of adversity.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>tuapse,russia,woman,mop,storm drain,debris,flooding,local,hero,social media,admiration,video,savior,courageous,water,city,fearless,selflessness,resilience,adversity</media:keywords>
                  <media:city> Tuapse</media:city>
                  <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>News</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2450</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/9b1d4d58-31cc-4c4c-8acd-0a47379bd97a.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/bf97ebff-d629-4265-b5df-78e9946f6cb3.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Devastating tornado strikes Barrhaven, Ottawa: 125 houses damaged, no serious injuries reported</media:title>
                  <media:description>A tornado wreaked havoc in Barrhaven, Ottawa, Canada on July 13th, 2023, leaving approximately 125 houses damaged in its wake. The storm struck the area in the early afternoon, prompting two tornado warnings. Fortunately, there have been no reports of serious injuries, with only one person taken to the hospital in stable condition. The City of Ottawa conducted a thorough assessment of the affected houses, going door-to-door to gather information. A family reunification center was set up at the Minto Recreation Complex in Barrhaven to provide support and assistance to those affected by the destructive tornado. @Mbeintema captured an aerial view of the area after the storm had passed. </media:description>
                  <media:keywords>storm,tornado,Barrhaven,Ottawa,Canada,houses,damage,injuries,assessment,door-to-door,warnings,family,reunification,center,support,assistance,Minto Recreation Complex,afternoon,media,briefing,stable condition</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Barrhaven, Ottawa</media:city>
                  <media:country>Canada</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>CA</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>News</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2446</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/d88f91a2-e9c7-4db3-8658-06a5d93b2a1b.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2446.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Devastating tornado strikes Barrhaven, Ottawa: homes damaged, power outages reported</media:title>
                  <media:description>A powerful tornado struck the suburban area of Barrhaven in Ottawa, Canada, on July 13th, 2023, causing significant damage to homes and leaving a trail of destruction. A video captured by @TheShagtor showed the tornado trying to form near his house. David Sills, the executive director of the Northern Tornadoes Project, confirmed the tornado's occurrence, which hit approximately 25 kilometers south of downtown Ottawa. Reports indicated that around 125 homes in the affected area suffered various degrees of damage, ranging from roofs being torn off to broken windows and downed trees. Moreover, approximately 1,600 homes were left without power, with concerns of potential gas leaks due to the destruction. The impact of the tornado left residents in shock and authorities working diligently to restore normalcy and provide assistance to those affected by the incident.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>tornado,barrhaven,ottawa,canada,damage,homes,destruction,power outages,gas leaks,emergency,assistance,suburb,roofs,windows,trees,devastation,residents,authorities,recovery,Northern Tornadoes Project</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Barrhaven </media:city>
                  <media:country>Canada</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>CA</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>News</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2444</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/eb78110f-e301-42a2-983f-0e3e94641f4f.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/23469efd-d9fe-4693-8c06-f13d258b0925.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Devastating tornado outbreak strikes Chicago: multiple touchdowns and widespread damage reported</media:title>
                  <media:description>Chicago, USA, experienced a devastating tornado outbreak on July 13th, 2023, as confirmed by the National Weather Service. At least 11 tornadoes touched down in the area, with damage assessment teams still evaluating whether additional touchdowns occurred. The powerful storms caused widespread destruction, leaving a trail of damaged homes, uprooted trees, and battered businesses in their wake. @merglio captured a video with sirens being heard in the background in the South Loop Chicago area in response to the tornadoes. 

Among the tornadoes, three were classified as EF-1, boasting wind speeds exceeding 100 miles per hour. One of these tornadoes struck suburban Elgin, with a track stretching from Route 47 to the west of Villa Olivia Golf Course. Another EF-1 tornado hit Elgin south of the first one, causing damage along McDonald Road and Hopps Road. The most powerful tornado of the outbreak, measuring over 110 miles per hour, tore through Burr Ridge and moved towards Stickney. Numerous trees were shredded, and several businesses suffered significant damage due to the destructive force of the tornadoes. Authorities continue to assess the extent of the devastation caused by this unprecedented tornado outbreak in the Chicago area.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>tornadoes,chicago,south loop,usa,sirens,damage,assessment,officials,EF-1,EF-0,wind speeds,suburban,Elgin,Burr Ridge,Stickney,outbreak,destruction,homes,trees,businesses</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Chicago</media:city>
                  <media:country>United States</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>US</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>News</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2443</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/a3a51b9a-aefb-48e2-a5af-e4f6dedf036a.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/ee7648b7-3433-424d-87fa-5ee0b9799d2d.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Torrential deluge engulfs Fairfax Falls: record rainfall ravages Vermont</media:title>
                  <media:description>In an alarming display of nature's power, Fairfax Falls in Fairfax, Vermont, USA, witnessed a scene of torrential water captured on video by @noblinkyblinky on July 11th, 2023. The video showcased the devastating effects of record-breaking rainfall that had engulfed Vermont over the past 48 hours. The once tranquil Lamoille River, home to the falls, now raged with an overwhelming surge of water, leaving onlookers in awe of the destructive force unleashed by the deluge.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>record rainfall,torrential,Fairfax Falls,Vermont,USA,@noblinkyblinky,video,water,caption,Lamoille River,ranging,surge,deluge,inundation,nature,extreme weather,power,impact,spectacle,surroundings</media:keywords>
                  <media:city> Fairfax Falls, Vermont</media:city>
                  <media:country>United States</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>US</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>News</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2428</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/0ad61a6b-ee19-4f19-82d2-378a496471c7.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/2428.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Devastating floods and torrential rain ravage Oita Prefecture, Japan</media:title>
                  <media:description>Heavy rainfall and relentless floods have struck Oita Prefecture in southwestern Japan, leading to a tragic loss of life and several people reported missing. The Japan Meteorological Agency has issued an urgent emergency warning, signaling the unprecedented intensity of the rain in Fukuoka and Oita prefectures. Residents residing in riverside and hillside areas have been urged to exercise extreme caution. A video captured by @TakaZkasa on July 10th, 2023, highlights the alarming situation, showing floodwaters perilously nearing a bridge in Kagetsu River, upstream of Chikugo River in Hita City. </media:description>
                  <media:keywords>floods,rainfall,Japan,Oita Prefecture,emergency warning,torrential rain,tragedy,missing,riverside,hillside,caution,video,Kagetsu River,Chikugo River,Hita City,southwest,intense,crisis,preparedness,action</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Hita City, Oita Prefecture</media:city>
                  <media:country>Japan</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>JP</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>News</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2406</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/25c6037e-5e6d-4c44-9a68-dd98626e49d6.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/889e2119-cc45-433f-9d04-4bba989eb71e.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Devastating floods ravage Hirogawa-cho: unprecedented rainfall triggers floods in Southwest Japan</media:title>
                  <media:description>Hirogawa-cho, a town located in Fukuoka Prefecture, Japan, was engulfed in a catastrophe as torrential rains caused devastating floods and triggered deadly landslides. The region experienced its heaviest rainfall ever recorded, leading to authorities issuing the highest-level warning for heavy rain in parts of Fukuoka and Oita prefectures. Captured in a video by @suppaman002 on July 10th, 2023, the streets of Hirogawa-cho were filled with dirty, fast-flowing water, showcasing the magnitude of the disaster. Tragically, at least one person lost their life, and three individuals remain missing. While the water has receded considerably, the scars of this calamity remain hauntingly visible. Thousands of residents were ordered to evacuate their homes, highlighting the urgency and severity of the situation. </media:description>
                  <media:keywords>floods,landslides,japan,hirogawa-cho,heavy rain,catastrophe,evacuation,devastation,tragedy,torrential,water,receded,missing,rainfall,warning,video,authorities,southwest,recovery,rebuilding</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Hirogawa-cho, Fukuoka Prefecture</media:city>
                  <media:country>Japan</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>JP</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>News</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2405</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/ab5efd4e-6a0d-4967-9122-619731455b7e.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/9a01a086-8f66-4199-985f-34d7ba4281fb.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Torrential rain triggers devastating floods: witness captures stunning video of Kurume City's deluge</media:title>
                  <media:description>Heavy rainfall in Kurume City, Fukuoka Prefecture, Japan, led to devastating floods, as captured in a video by @xWwp5zbdf5AGUY0 on July 10th, 2023. The footage shows the road in front of their house transformed into a rapid-flowing river. In the video, a test object is thrown into the water, highlighting the force and intensity of the floodwaters. The scenes depict the gravity of the situation, as Kurume Zendoji becomes submerged under the rising waters.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>flooding,rainfall,Kurume City,Fukuoka Prefecture,Japan,video,floods,heavy,water,road,river,fast,Zendoji,house,test,flow,weather,disaster,nature,challenges,residents</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>Kurume City, Fukuoka Prefecture</media:city>
                  <media:country>Japan</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>JP</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>News</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2403</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/73eb2a0f-cd3b-4728-bd53-c442a0536c0d.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/a616fd83-8011-4861-8e17-0d679b8bf985.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Resident bravely navigates flooded streets of Kurume City, Fukuoka Prefecture</media:title>
                  <media:description>A video captured by @TAIGA_hrkw on July 10th, 2023, in Kurume City, Fukuoka Prefecture, Japan, shows a brave individual fearlessly driving through the flooded waters in front of their house. The heavy rainfall in the area had caused significant flooding, and amidst the chaos, this courageous resident stood out. With the caption, "In front of my house in Kurume City, Fukuoka Prefecture. A fierce man appears. There is a lot of news out there," the video showcases the determination and resilience of individuals in the face of adversity.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>floods,rainfall,Kurume City,Fukuoka Prefecture,Japan,video,brave,resident,driving,flooded waters,heavy,weather,chaos,determination,resilience,adversity,news,house,fierce,captured,individual</media:keywords>
                  <media:city> Kurume City, Fukuoka Prefecture</media:city>
                  <media:country>Japan</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>JP</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>News</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2402</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/6a62bd1e-3987-4812-bf72-7cb65d2bbc13.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/fdd7ddb4-0979-4acf-9993-52d561da4233.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                  <item>
                  <media:title>Scarlet sails 2023: a majestic graduation celebration in St. Petersburg captured in stunning video</media:title>
                  <media:description>The highly anticipated anniversary holiday of "Scarlet Sails - 2023" took place on the night of June 24-25 at Palace Square in St. Petersburg, Russia. The event, which coincided with the year of the teacher and mentor in Russia, was meticulously planned by a dedicated team of 10 thousand individuals over several months. Graduates from all over the country gathered at the square, eagerly awaiting the main graduation ceremony.

The festivities commenced with an opening speech by the governor of St. Petersburg, Alexander Beglov. He declared that for this night, the most enchanting embankment and beautiful square belonged solely to the graduates. As anticipation built, the iconic brig "Russia" adorned with scarlet sails made its way in front of the former schoolchildren. The sight of the majestic ship gliding through the water evoked sheer delight, causing the crowd to erupt in joyful shouts and applause. @korolev_svel, capturing the breathtaking moment on video, immortalized the excitement as people rushed towards the ship, expressing their admiration and celebration for the remarkable event.</media:description>
                  <media:keywords>anniversary,holiday,scarlet sails,2023,project team,graduation,Russia,Palace Square,St. Petersburg,concept,teacher,mentor,ceremony,governor,embankment,beautiful,brig,Russia,applause,video</media:keywords>
                  <media:city>St. Petersburg</media:city>
                  <media:country>Russia</media:country>
                  <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
                  <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
                  <media:category>News</media:category>
                  <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
                  <media:filmingDate>Sun, 25 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
                  <guid>2394</guid>
                  <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
                  <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/37f9935c-af8c-464e-80f0-53bc69dbdeed.jpg" />
                  <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/videos/9b9fcb8a-6ca3-49d5-88b2-efcd713ded6c.mp4" />
                  <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
                  </item>
                           
                     </channel>
                  </rss>
                