<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
        xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
        xmlns:openSearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearchrss/1.0/"
        xmlns:dfpvideo="http://api.google.com/dfpvideo"
        xmlns:tms="http://data.tmsapi.com/v1.1"
        version="2.0">
         <channel>
           <title>ViralBear videos</title>
           <dfpvideo:version>2</dfpvideo:version><item>
            <media:title>Destruction of hydroelectric dam sparks water emergency and escalating tensions between Ukraine and Russia</media:title>
            <media:description>In a catastrophic turn of events, the upper part of the hydroelectric dam in Russian-occupied Novaya Kakhovka, located in the Kherson region of Ukraine, was destroyed on 6th June, 2023. This destructive act led to an uncontrolled discharge of water, triggering a series of alarming consequences. As the blame game ensues, both Ukraine and Russia accuse each other of undermining the hydroelectric power station, further fueling the already heightened tensions between the two nations.

The immediate aftermath of the dam's destruction was the flooding of the hydroelectric power station area, forcing authorities to initiate mass evacuations in the Kherson region. The fear of water scarcity in Crimea looms large, as the region heavily relies on the reservoir's supply. Additionally, the Zaporozhye nuclear power plant had to be shut down due to the incident, compounding the already pressing water shortage crisis in southern Ukraine.

The severity of the situation was highlighted by reports indicating that the Kakhovka Hydroelectric Power Station is beyond repair, a sentiment echoed by both Ukrainian and Russian authorities. Disturbingly, the collapse of the hydroelectric dam continues, with sources suggesting that 14 of the station's 28 spans have already been destroyed, rendering the entire power station completely submerged.</media:description>
            <media:keywords>hydroelectric,dam,destruction,water,evacuation,tensions,Ukraine,Russia,blame,crisis,flood,scarcity,reservoir,power,station,collapse,submerged,geopolitical,aftermath,incident</media:keywords>
            <media:city>Novaya Kakhovka, Kherson</media:city>
            <media:country>Ukraine</media:country>
            <media:regionCode>UA</media:regionCode>
           <media:categoryCode>CWP</media:categoryCode>      
            <media:category>News</media:category>
            <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
            <media:filmingDate>Tue, 6 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
            <guid>2211</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 09:37:15 GMT</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/cfbc6c9c-ac68-4c1a-8444-af9babe61bf2.jpg" />
            <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/reuters-videos/e52380c6-d422-482a-ba51-4c6e055d02c4.mp4" />
            <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
            </item><item>
            <media:title>Hydroelectric dam catastrophe in Novaya Kakhovka: Ukraine-Russia water crisis looming</media:title>
            <media:description>In a devastating turn of events, the upper part of the hydroelectric dam in Novaya Kakhovka, located in the Russian-occupied region of Kherson, Ukraine, was destroyed on 6th June, 2023. This resulted in an uncontrolled discharge of water, triggering a dire situation for the residents in the surrounding areas. Both Ukraine and Russia have been quick to accuse each other of undermining the hydroelectric power station, further escalating tensions between the two nations.

The consequences of this catastrophe have been severe. The flooding caused by the collapsed dam has forced the evacuation of residents in the Kherson region, who now fear the impending water shortage in Crimea. Additionally, the Zaporozhye nuclear power plant had to be disabled, compounding the already existing water scarcity in southern Ukraine. With the Kakhovka HPP deemed beyond repair by authorities from both sides, the situation continues to worsen. According to sources from TASS, 14 of the station's 28 spans have been destroyed, leaving the hydroelectric power station completely submerged. This disaster marks a critical moment in the ongoing water crisis between Ukraine and Russia.</media:description>
            <media:keywords>hydroelectric,dam,catastrophe,Novaya Kakhovka,Kherson,Ukraine,uncontrolled,discharge,water,evacuation,Crimea,Zaporozhye,nuclear,power plant,Russian-occupied,collapse,tension,scarcity,submerged,crisis</media:keywords>
            <media:city>Novaya Kakhovka, Kherson</media:city>
            <media:country>Ukraine</media:country>
            <media:regionCode>UA</media:regionCode>
           <media:categoryCode>CWP</media:categoryCode>      
            <media:category>News</media:category>
            <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
            <media:filmingDate>Tue, 6 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
            <guid>2210</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 09:17:33 GMT</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/ee91ef8b-61f7-401d-8af8-054c4245d3d0.jpg" />
            <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/reuters-videos/d0f0eacc-519c-47dd-9dc0-c6b4b3865ff5.mp4" />
            <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
            </item><item>
              <media:title>Heroic fighter saves life: Dzhakhar Mazhidov's quick action averts tragedy during epilepsy attack</media:title>
              <media:description>In a remarkable display of bravery and quick thinking, hardcore FC fighter Dzhakhar Mazhidov came to the rescue of a St. Petersburg, Russia, resident who experienced an epileptic attack on June 3rd, 2023. Mazhidov recounted the incident, explaining how he witnessed the person's sudden collapse and immediately sprang into action. Without hesitation, he moved the victim onto their right side to alleviate pressure on the heart, and even risked his own safety by using his fingers to prevent the individual from swallowing their tongue. Mazhidov's selfless determination to provide first aid until medical professionals arrived highlights his unwavering commitment to saving lives.

Adhering to the recommended guidelines, Mazhidov refrained from attempting to pinch the person's mouth, aware of the potential danger of getting his fingers bitten off during the convulsions. Despite this risk, he steadfastly remained by the patient's side, willing to sacrifice his own well-being for their survival. Miraculously, the victim's condition improved before the arrival of an ambulance, at which point Mazhidov handed over the responsibility to the medical team. The entire episode lasted a mere eight minutes, yet the impact of Mazhidov's heroic intervention will undoubtedly leave a lasting impression on all those who witnessed it.</media:description>
              <media:keywords>bravery,rescue,epilepsy,athlete,first aid,hero,determination,selflessness,survival,intervention,critical,convulsions,sacrifice,fingers,improvement,ambulance,cashier,diabetes,urgency,bystanders</media:keywords>
              <media:city> St. Petersburg</media:city>
              <media:country>Russia</media:country>
              <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
              <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
              <media:category>News</media:category>
              <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
              <media:filmingDate>Sat, 3 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
              <guid>2209</guid>
              <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 08:55:29 GMT</pubDate>
              <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/944d8a58-8517-468f-8ca9-d34f386551a3.jpg" />
              <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/reuters-videos/b33994d0-99d4-40df-8fab-320b1bcb6f6d.mp4" />
              <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
              </item><item>
            <media:title>Adorable toddler's hilarious twist: moldy bun served at playtime store!</media:title>
            <media:description>In a heartwarming moment captured by @kyliecgray in Barrie, Ontario, Canada, her young son embarked on his first imaginative play as a storekeeper on  May 28th, 2023. Little did she expect the unexpected twist that awaited her when she placed an order for a cheeseburger and fries. Instead of the anticipated treat, the adorable toddler handed her a random moldy bun With a mischievous smile. 

</media:description>
            <media:keywords>store,toddler,playtime,moldy,bun,cheeseburger,fries,imagination,Barrie,Ontario,Canada,laughter,adorable,video,creativity,surprise,make-believe,joy,memory,chuckle</media:keywords>
            <media:city>Barrie, Ontario</media:city>
            <media:country>Canada</media:country>
            <media:regionCode>CA</media:regionCode>
           <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>      
            <media:category>Heartwarming</media:category>
            <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
            <media:filmingDate>Sun, 28 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
            <guid>2208</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 08:13:07 GMT</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/74e45764-8058-48c8-99f0-aa3219399bb3.jpg" />
            <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/reuters-videos/bc3f869a-0cf8-433d-909f-51ad6e6873b1.mp4" />
            <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
            </item><item>
              <media:title>Hit-and-run incident in Novosibirsk: child survives as driver flees the scene</media:title>
              <media:description>In a distressing incident that occurred on October 30, 2022, in the Novosibirsk region of Russia, a child was struck and run over by a RAV4 driver. Shocking video footage captured the incident, revealing that the driver initially attempted to lift the injured boy before abruptly fleeing the scene in his vehicle. According to reports from the AST-54 group on the VKontakte social network, which cited eyewitnesses, the young victim, aged 6, miraculously survived the accident and is currently receiving medical treatment at a local hospital.

Authorities have yet to comment on the incident, as a request for information has been sent to the press service of the Main Directorate of the Ministry of Internal Affairs for the Novosibirsk Region. Meanwhile, speculation has arisen on social media that the driver involved may be a deputy working as a director of a municipal institution. However, there is no official confirmation of this allegation at the time of writing.</media:description>
              <media:keywords>accident,hit-and-run,Novosibirsk,Russia,RAV4,child,video,driver,hospital,survival,investigation,authorities,eyewitnesses,social media,speculation,deputy,municipal institution,press service,community,updates</media:keywords>
              <media:city> Novosibirsk region</media:city>
              <media:country>Russia</media:country>
              <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
              <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
              <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
              <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
              <media:filmingDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2022</media:filmingDate>
              <guid>2207</guid>
              <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 07:53:50 GMT</pubDate>
              <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/1c408366-4764-4bef-a715-2d3ca421e52f.jpg" />
              <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/reuters-videos/0a811c08-a099-4060-aae1-5102693d258b.mp4" />
              <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
              </item><item>
            <media:title>Cat chaos: Cuppa's tabletop tumble sends plate shattering!</media:title>
            <media:description>In a hilarious and unexpected turn of events, a live-streaming session captured an unforgettable moment between two mischievous cats named Cuppa and Berry. The incident took place on May 24, 2023, in Bekasi City, West Java, Indonesia, and left viewers in stitches. As Cuppa attempted to climb onto the table, a precarious plate teetering on the edge proved to be its downfall. In a split second, the plate crashed to the floor, shattering into countless pieces.

The video shared by @berrybellecat on social media showcased the playful antics of the two feline companions. Little did anyone expect that Cuppa's innocent attempt to reach higher ground would result in such comedic chaos. </media:description>
            <media:keywords>kittens,playfulness,live-streaming,antics,comedy,chaos,mishap,table,plate,breakage,Bekasi City,Indonesia,Cuppa,Berry,mischievous,adorable,curiosity,laughter,fragments,unpredictability.</media:keywords>
            <media:city>Bekasi City</media:city>
            <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
            <media:regionCode>ID</media:regionCode>
           <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>      
            <media:category>Animals</media:category>
            <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
            <media:filmingDate>Wed, 24 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
            <guid>2206</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 07:21:04 GMT</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/361d971e-592e-44a8-8394-8bbb9d243129.jpg" />
            <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/reuters-videos/e77e42da-54fd-4b31-8867-19f4f954ff5d.mp4" />
            <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
            </item><item>
            <media:title>Fury unleashed: a farmer's glimpse into Fuxin's terrifying tornado</media:title>
            <media:description>On June 1st, 2023, in Fuxin City, Northeast China, a farmer named had a harrowing encounter with an extreme weather phenomenon—a tornado. Engaged in his usual work in the field, the author was suddenly taken aback by a powerful gust of wind that swiftly intensified. Gripped by fear, he quickly sought refuge on the ground but managed to capture the awe-inspiring sight on video.

In a matter of moments, the tranquil landscape transformed into a scene of chaos and destruction. The swirling vortex of the tornado tore through the vicinity with unrelenting force.</media:description>
            <media:keywords>tornado,farmer,Fuxin,extreme weather,wind,fear,field,video,chaos,destruction,vortex,trees,debris,devastation,power,unpredictability,nature,fury,vulnerability,resilience</media:keywords>
            <media:city> Fuxin</media:city>
            <media:country>China</media:country>
            <media:regionCode>CN</media:regionCode>
           <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>      
            <media:category>Weather</media:category>
            <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
            <media:filmingDate>Thu, 1 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
            <guid>2205</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 07:05:33 GMT</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/935c7b17-a84f-4379-a3aa-fdb7212f7f0e.jpg" />
            <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/reuters-videos/f7bf37b0-8f7e-4748-af07-7a9fda5f6d4f.mp4" />
            <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
            </item><item>
            <media:title>Destructive fury unleashed: Fuxin City ravaged by terrifying tornado</media:title>
            <media:description>On June 1st, 2023, a terrifying tornado unleashed its destructive fury upon Fuxin City in Northeast China. Captured by a brave individual a video emerged, showcasing the raw power and devastation caused by this natural disaster. Filmed from the safety of a moving car, the footage revealed a large mass of circling winds and dirt, tearing through the city with relentless force.

As the video unfolded, it became evident that Fuxin City was under siege from the menacing tornado. The swirling winds and debris created a chaotic scene. </media:description>
            <media:keywords>tornado,devastation,Fuxin City,Northeast China,video,circling winds,dirt,destruction,brave,chaos,buildings,trees,debris,power,nature,unpredictable,storm,recovery,rebuilding,scars</media:keywords>
            <media:city>Fuxin City</media:city>
            <media:country>China</media:country>
            <media:regionCode>CN</media:regionCode>
           <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>      
            <media:category>Weather</media:category>
            <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
            <media:filmingDate>Thu, 1 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
            <guid>2203</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 06:53:31 GMT</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/499e4c1f-1d2c-4bc1-a8be-57442376d2b9.jpg" />
            <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/reuters-videos/2669731b-b8a7-4725-a06e-975f16a304bd.mp4" />
            <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
            </item><item>
            <media:title>Catastrophe in Santa Barbara: a feline's floral fiasco unfolds</media:title>
            <media:description>In a moment of mischief and curiosity, a mischievous feline in Santa Barbara, California, USA, found itself at the center of a floral fiasco that left shattered pieces in its wake. The incident, captured by @tatyana_mironova_real_estate on November 29th, 2022, shows the daring cat playfully pushing a flower pot off the counter, only to watch it plummet to the ground, breaking into several pieces. With a swift turn of its head, the cat's gaze fixates upon the fallen flower pot, seemingly assessing the aftermath of its daring feat.</media:description>
            <media:keywords>mischief,curiosity,feline,floral,fiasco,shattered,pieces,daring,playfully,plummet,broken,aftermath,gaze,fallen,assess,social,media,amused,inquisitive,unpredictable</media:keywords>
            <media:city>Santa Barbara, California</media:city>
            <media:country>United States</media:country>
            <media:regionCode>US</media:regionCode>
           <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>      
            <media:category>Animals</media:category>
            <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
            <media:filmingDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2022</media:filmingDate>
            <guid>2202</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 06:24:12 GMT</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/6c57cd27-e791-4dd5-bd08-9d851f79d144.jpg" />
            <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/reuters-videos/79476890-3e6b-45af-b9df-6e8ae642aa06.mp4" />
            <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
            </item><item>
              <media:title>Beachside fun turns into a sticky situation: friend's head gets stuck in anchor rock!</media:title>
              <media:description>A leisurely day at the beach took a surprising turn of events when a group of friends encountered a rather sticky situation.  @arulbinhamid12, found himself filming a video that would soon go viral. In Buton Regency, South East Sulawesi, Indonesia, specifically in the Pasarwajo district, their recreational trip took an unexpected twist when one of his friends playfully attempted to stick his head into an unused anchor rock on January 8, 2023.

What began as a harmless joke quickly transformed into a nerve-wracking predicament. The friend's head became wedged tightly within the anchor rock. After several trials to free him, their efforts paid off, and their friend was finally freed from the anchor rock's clutches, much to everyone's relief.</media:description>
              <media:keywords>recreation,beach,waves,friends,video,stuck,anchor rock,Buton Island,Pasarwajo district,fun,adventure,viral,prank,panic,relief,peril,unexpected,predicament,capture,moments</media:keywords>
              <media:city>Buton Island, Pasarwajo district</media:city>
              <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
              <media:regionCode>ID</media:regionCode>
              <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
              <media:category>Fails and Funnies</media:category>
              <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
              <media:filmingDate>Sun, 8 Jan 2023</media:filmingDate>
              <guid>2201</guid>
              <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 06:00:07 GMT</pubDate>
              <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/f8996a9e-44c4-4283-8a61-8e81c213f01f.jpg" />
              <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/reuters-videos/86b92331-77c6-48cd-bb72-25afbd2c37dc.mp4" />
              <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
              </item><item>
            <media:title>Upside-down feasting: clever parrot's unconventional snack retrieval technique</media:title>
            <media:description>In an adorable display of intelligence and dexterity, a parrot in Aichi, Japan, has astounded its owner with a unique snacking technique. Captured on video by @riyo.05 on May 8, 2023, the feathered companion can be seen using its beak to help itself perch its legs on the lower side of a sofa, effectively turning itself upside down. In this inverted position, the clever parrot skillfully sticks its head into a package to retrieve a tasty treat.</media:description>
            <media:keywords>parrot,treat,package,beak,upside down,sofa,dexterity,intelligence,clever,snack,video,Aichi,Japan,legs,perch,capture,adorable,ingenuity,problem-solving,avian</media:keywords>
            <media:city>Aichi</media:city>
            <media:country>Japan</media:country>
            <media:regionCode>JP</media:regionCode>
           <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>      
            <media:category>Animals</media:category>
            <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
            <media:filmingDate>Mon, 8 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
            <guid>2200</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 05:22:07 GMT</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/80715866-73d2-47ef-8f9f-e51d0ddfeb9c.jpg" />
            <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/reuters-videos/3228a8c6-ea2b-4b71-9e4e-8fa0b9253019.mp4" />
            <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
            </item><item>
              <media:title>Sibling love: a heartwarming journey of a big brother and his little sister</media:title>
              <media:description>In a heartwarming video captured by @yolandjimmy, a family in Padang, Indonesia, celebrated the arrival of their youngest member on 1st November 2022. The video showcased the beautiful bond between a 13-month-old boy and his newborn sister, with the boy eagerly embracing his new role as a big brother.

In the footage, the boy's excitement was palpable as he showered his sister with affection. He playfully kissed her face and gently touched her tiny ears, displaying his adoration for the little bundle of joy. However, in a moment of youthful exuberance, he accidentally hit her on the face. Fortunately, the mother reassured viewers that the baby was unharmed. </media:description>
              <media:keywords>baby,siblings,love,bond,joy,excitement,affection,newborn,brother,sister,video,adorable,playfulness,kisses,face,youngest,family,Padang,Indonesia,heartwarming</media:keywords>
              <media:city> Padang</media:city>
              <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
              <media:regionCode>ID</media:regionCode>
              <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
              <media:category>Heartwarming</media:category>
              <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
              <media:filmingDate>Tue, 1 Nov 2022</media:filmingDate>
              <guid>2199</guid>
              <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 19:47:07 GMT</pubDate>
              <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/55917b90-cc8d-4b2d-a2ac-4aa8a0338c64.jpg" />
              <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/reuters-videos/53490eef-dac9-446a-a515-f69de8234963.mp4" />
              <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
              </item><item>
              <media:title>Groundhog's eggcellent hat trick: a whimsical lunchtime surprise!</media:title>
              <media:description>In a charming incident that took place on May 28th, 2023, in Sichuan, southwest China, a pet-loving individual named @graygrayfertilizer delighted in capturing an adorable video of his groundhog donning a unique hat. The hat, ingeniously crafted from two eggshells attached together to resemble bunny ears, lent the furry creature an amusing and endearing appearance. 

As the author and his friends busily prepared their meal, the groundhog curiously hopped onto the table and locked eyes with its owner. Coincidentally, one of the author's friends happened to be stirring a bowl of eggs at that precise moment. Seizing the opportunity, the friend gently placed an eggshell hat atop the groundhog's head, evoking laughter and amusement among the gathering. However, as the groundhog prepared to scurry away on all fours, the hat slipped off, bringing an end to its brief but delightful stint as a fashion-forward rodent.</media:description>
              <media:keywords>groundhog,pet,hat,video,eggshells,bunny ears,lunch,friends,table,stirring,eggs,adorable,amusing,endearing,gathering,fashion,rodent,heartwarming,companionship,unexpected</media:keywords>
              <media:city>Sichuan</media:city>
              <media:country>China</media:country>
              <media:regionCode>CN</media:regionCode>
              <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
              <media:category>Animals</media:category>
              <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
              <media:filmingDate>Sun, 28 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
              <guid>2197</guid>
              <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 19:02:47 GMT</pubDate>
              <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/7aa60093-049d-428d-b8c5-488a8462a0a9.jpg" />
              <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/reuters-videos/1fe32188-2fc2-4e50-8237-d4e9583ed329.mp4" />
              <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
              </item><item>
              <media:title>Miraculous escape: elderly couple narrowly avoids injury as tree collapses on tricycle amid traffic jam</media:title>
              <media:description>In a heart-stopping moment captured on camera on 13th May, 2023, an elderly couple narrowly escaped injury when a tree unexpectedly fell on their tricycle in Shandong, East China. The incident occurred amidst a minor traffic jam, as the couple cautiously drove along the edge of the road. However, their peaceful ride took a sudden turn when a tree on the roadside came crashing down, landing directly on their tricycle.

Fortunately, luck was on their side as both the elderly man and woman emerged from the incident unharmed. Although shaken by the startling turn of events, they were able to walk away without any major injuries. </media:description>
              <media:keywords>accident,tricycle,elderly couple,traffic jam,tree,incident,shaken,lucky,escape,China,Shandong,video,road,roadside,unexpected,danger,safety,vigilance,congestion,hazard</media:keywords>
              <media:city>Shandong</media:city>
              <media:country>China</media:country>
              <media:regionCode>CN</media:regionCode>
              <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
              <media:category>Road accidents</media:category>
              <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
              <media:filmingDate>Sat, 13 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
              <guid>2196</guid>
              <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 18:44:54 GMT</pubDate>
              <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/7669ca10-2362-47fc-8e36-8029b2ca535f.jpg" />
              <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/reuters-videos/c7c1343c-3ecb-4c27-8afd-ce2e35307f14.mp4" />
              <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
              </item><item>
              <media:title>Feeding the fierce: a mother cat's protective growls caught on camera</media:title>
              <media:description>In a captivating scene captured in Shanghai, east China on 22nd April, 2023, @didAhChugetintotroubletoday stumbled upon a mother cat and her kittens residing in his garden. Determined to help the feline family, the author decided to offer them some nourishment in the form of cat food. However, the mother cat's fiercely protective instincts came into play as she guarded her kittens, exhibiting an aggressive demeanor. Undeterred, the author cleverly used a stick to safely deliver the food to the feline mother, all while capturing this intriguing interaction on camera.</media:description>
              <media:keywords>mother,cat,kittens,garden,Shanghai,China,overprotective,resist,food,growled,interesting,filmed,video,stick,aggressive,compassion,nurturing,wildlife,instincts,bonds</media:keywords>
              <media:city>Shanghai</media:city>
              <media:country>China</media:country>
              <media:regionCode>CN</media:regionCode>
              <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
              <media:category>Animals</media:category>
              <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
              <media:filmingDate>Sat, 22 Apr 2023</media:filmingDate>
              <guid>2195</guid>
              <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 18:26:39 GMT</pubDate>
              <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/84fbc556-db3c-4e26-973c-dba0d25ee53c.jpg" />
              <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/reuters-videos/24d8f628-40b9-408b-839e-f63b6c5e1181.mp4" />
              <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
              </item><item>
            <media:title>Falling camera: a serendipitous aesthetic mishap</media:title>
            <media:description>In a moment of uncertainty and against the backdrop of cloudy skies and a strong gust of wind in Wonosobo, Indonesia, @shierlya_ found herself capturing an unexpected and breathtaking video on  February 27, 2023. With initial hesitation, she pondered whether it was wise to proceed. However, succumbing to the thrill of the moment, she decided to hit the record button. Little did she know that fate had something extraordinary in store for her.

As the wind picked up, the unexpected occurred - her phone slipped from her grasp and began its descent, inadvertently continuing to record. In a split second, her friends' voices filled the air with a symphony of startled screams. The tumbling phone created a mesmerizing visual spectacle, capturing her friends' movements as if they were falling through the frame. </media:description>
            <media:keywords>cloudy,windy,video,aesthetic,uncertainty,friends,falling,mishap,serendipitous,moment,capture,thrill,descent,screams,spectacle,unexpected,mesmerizing,frame,captivate,awestruck</media:keywords>
            <media:city>Wonosobo</media:city>
            <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
            <media:regionCode>ID</media:regionCode>
           <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>      
            <media:category>Fails and Funnies</media:category>
            <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
            <media:filmingDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023</media:filmingDate>
            <guid>2193</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 20:49:47 GMT</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/9c677eea-7585-42e6-8cdb-7778e8c4c6c9.jpg" />
            <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/reuters-videos/9a19687b-f232-4173-ac78-389f50321210.mp4" />
            <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
            </item><item>
              <media:title>Wild elk's daring race: epic chase alongside Devyatkino Metro Station</media:title>
              <media:description>On the eventful morning of May 30th, 2023, the Devyatkino metro station in the Vsevolozhsk district of the Saint Petersburg region, Russia, witnessed a truly remarkable sight. Startling passengers and capturing their attention, a wild elk sprinted onto the platform in a daring display of speed and agility. The unexpected visitor, named Sokhaty, initially traversed the grassy terrain with confidence before ascending to the station platform, where it proceeded to race alongside a passing train. In a remarkable show of determination, the elk nearly succeeded in outpacing the locomotive but stumbled towards the end of the thrilling chase. Undeterred, the magnificent creature quickly recovered and darted off in the opposite direction, leaving spectators in awe of its wild spirit.
</media:description>
              <media:keywords>elk,platform,metro,station,Devyatkino,Russia,footage,non-trivial,race,passengers,wild,animal,grass,tracks,train,confidence,stumble,direction,video,speed</media:keywords>
              <media:city>Saint Petersburg</media:city>
              <media:country>Russia</media:country>
              <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
              <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
              <media:category>Animals</media:category>
              <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
              <media:filmingDate>Tue, 30 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
              <guid>2192</guid>
              <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 20:32:29 GMT</pubDate>
              <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2192.jpg" />
              <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/reuters-videos/2192.mp4" />
              <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
              </item><item>
              <media:title>Unexpected pitfall: friend's close call during inflatable pool adventure</media:title>
              <media:description>In a bizarre incident captured on video by @anjarsuzu, a day of fun turned into a close call for a friend in Muko Regency, Bengkulu Province, Indonesia on July 18, 2022. The video shows a friend, unknowingly, stepping into a hole pit while moving backward, moments after helping tie the children's pool on the car. The friend quickly regained his balance and lifted himself out of the hole.

The incident occurred when the author decided to inflate a children's pool and secure it on top of a car. With his friend's assistance, he successfully tied the pool to the vehicle. However, as the friend stepped back, he failed to notice the nearby pit and accidentally slid into it. Fortunately, his reflexes kicked in, allowing him to swiftly lift himself out of harm's way.</media:description>
              <media:keywords>pit,fall,video,friend,inflatable,pool,air,tying,car,hole,leg,quick,close call,adventure,incident,Muko Regency,Bengkulu Province,Indonesia,funny,captured,unaware</media:keywords>
              <media:city>Muko Regency, Bengkulu Province</media:city>
              <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
              <media:regionCode>ID</media:regionCode>
              <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
              <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
              <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
              <media:filmingDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2022</media:filmingDate>
              <guid>2191</guid>
              <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 20:16:16 GMT</pubDate>
              <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/136a1d01-99c4-4d56-a76d-6b67f2c3c56c.jpg" />
              <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/reuters-videos/d0d6b7b8-8cbc-44c6-a67b-8dfafdae92c8.mp4" />
              <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
              </item><item>
              <media:title>Terrifying moment: motorbike plunges into water as floating bridge swings wildly</media:title>
              <media:description>In a heart-stopping incident captured on video by @ferdipratamaa, a man's motorbike plummeted into the water after the floating bridge he was crossing swung violently due to strong winds. The dramatic footage, filmed on April 24, 2023, in Gunung Megang, South Sumatra, Indonesia, shows the man losing control of his bike as it teeters on the swaying bridge. Despite his desperate efforts to regain balance, he ultimately succumbs to the uncontrollable forces, toppling into the water below.

 Fortunately, the man escaped the incident with no serious injuries. The strong winds that day created a treacherous situation, causing the bridge to sway violently and making it nearly impossible for the motorist to maintain control.</media:description>
              <media:keywords>floating bridge,motorbike,incident,video,strong winds,swinging,dramatic,control,water,balance,danger,unpredictable,weather,risk,injuries,caution,preparedness,structure,adverse conditions,Indonesia</media:keywords>
              <media:city>Gunung Megang, South Sumatra</media:city>
              <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
              <media:regionCode>ID</media:regionCode>
              <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
              <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
              <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
              <media:filmingDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023</media:filmingDate>
              <guid>2190</guid>
              <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 19:57:07 GMT</pubDate>
              <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/374b5994-6b55-416e-a875-a3d8bca3b4c4.jpg" />
              <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/reuters-videos/275105de-71f7-4f55-8ff4-651617caf783.mp4" />
              <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
              </item><item>
              <media:title>Unlikely luck: rescuers save kitten trapped in metal pipe</media:title>
              <media:description>In a heartwarming incident captured by @phillyfoodgirl, a small kitten found itself trapped in a precarious situation inside a metal pipe in Philadelphia, USA. The video, shared on May 27, 2023, showcased the intense moments of the rescue operation. The desperate cries of the distressed kitten echoed through the pipe until the skilled rescuers stepped in.

With a sense of urgency, the rescuers skillfully cut through the pipe, allowing the tiny feline to come into view. The sight of the kitten, sitting at the bottom of the pipe, tugged at the heartstrings of all who witnessed the video. As one of the rescuers gently retrieved the scared kitten, it was evident that luck had been on their side. The caption accompanying the video, "I can't believe the cat distribution system finally picked us," highlighted the overwhelming relief and gratitude for the successful rescue.</media:description>
              <media:keywords>rescue,kitten,trapped,metal pipe,Philadelphia,video,meowing,cut,view,removed,luck,cat,distribution,system,captured,small,bottom,grateful,compassion,grateful,heartwarming</media:keywords>
              <media:city>Philadelphia</media:city>
              <media:country>United States</media:country>
              <media:regionCode>US</media:regionCode>
              <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
              <media:category>Rescue</media:category>
              <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
              <media:filmingDate>Sat, 27 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
              <guid>2189</guid>
              <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 19:32:51 GMT</pubDate>
              <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/6952e581-e893-4c15-bc8a-d39682373d6b.jpg" />
              <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/reuters-videos/5e096130-8082-47a1-9484-ecdaeac697f8.mp4" />
              <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
              </item><item>
              <media:title>Brave biker's close call: dismantled motorbike catches fire during test run</media:title>
              <media:description>In a harrowing incident captured on video, @rohadysajiedin of Serdang Deli, North Sumatra, Indonesia, narrowly escaped disaster when the engine of his dismantled motorbike caught fire during a test run on April 29, 2023. The heart-stopping footage shows him riding the bike before stopping for a moment when suddenly  flames engulf the engine. Reacting swiftly, the author brought jumped off the motorbike. 

Risking his own safety, he wasted no time in attempting to extinguish the growing flames. Everything ended well.</media:description>
              <media:keywords>video,testing,motorbike,dismantled,fire,engine,caught,flames,stopped,extinguish,Serdang Deli,North Sumatra,Indonesia,close,call,bravery,danger,quick thinking,safety,courageous,incident</media:keywords>
              <media:city>Serdang Deli, North Sumatra</media:city>
              <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
              <media:regionCode>ID</media:regionCode>
              <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
              <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
              <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
              <media:filmingDate>Sat, 29 Apr 2023</media:filmingDate>
              <guid>2187</guid>
              <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 07:48:08 GMT</pubDate>
              <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/04a13c6d-18ad-4dd4-ac23-c488c20c1e4e.jpg" />
              <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/reuters-videos/292879e8-564f-4ccd-b069-d1677cc5921b.mp4" />
              <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
              </item><item>
              <media:title>Prankster's surprise: hen wakes man with pants-pecking feat!</media:title>
              <media:description>In a hilarious video captured by @tatak_jodhipati in Temanggung, Central Java, Indonesia, on March 24, 2023, a clever prankster managed to wake a sleeping man in the most unexpected way. The footage shows the man peacefully dozing off while a chicken roams nearby. Seizing the opportunity for mischief, someone off-screen starts sprinkling rice grains on the slumbering man, specifically targeting his pants.

The chicken, quick to spot the free meal, wastes no time and begins pecking at the rice grains scattered on the man's pants. Surprised by the unexpected sensation, the man stirs awake, seemingly unfazed by the situation.</media:description>
              <media:keywords>hen,chicken,grains,prankster,video,sleeping,laughter,wake-up,pants,calmness,surprise,Temanggung,Central Java,Indonesia,mischief,pecking,amusement,unpredictable,moment,capture</media:keywords>
              <media:city>Temanggung, Central Java</media:city>
              <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
              <media:regionCode>ID</media:regionCode>
              <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
              <media:category>Fails and Funnies</media:category>
              <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
              <media:filmingDate>Fri, 24 Mar 2023</media:filmingDate>
              <guid>2186</guid>
              <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 07:28:32 GMT</pubDate>
              <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/d543617c-24d1-4c2f-810a-9011bc20cea0.jpg" />
              <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/reuters-videos/3ed379f3-4548-449f-884c-ae15700b9d54.mp4" />
              <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
              </item><item>
            <media:title>Unforgettable barefoot ride: sandal mishap captured in hilarious video</media:title>
            <media:description>A recent video captured in Tasikmalaya, West Java, Indonesia, has taken the internet by storm. The footage, shot by @alwidivraja on January 4th, 2023, shows him driving barefoot after his sandal accidentally fell off and got stuck in another motorbike passing by. In the video, the author can be heard laughing, while the oblivious owner of the other motorbike continues riding, seemingly unaware of the unusual situation.</media:description>
            <media:keywords>driving,barefoot,sandal,mishap,video,laughter,motorbike,stuck,hilarious,capture,Tasikmalaya,West Java,Indonesia,amusing,unexpected,carefree,social media,viral,joy,lighthearted</media:keywords>
            <media:city>Tasikmalaya, West Java</media:city>
            <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
            <media:regionCode>ID</media:regionCode>
           <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>      
            <media:category>Fails and Funnies</media:category>
            <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
            <media:filmingDate>Wed, 4 Jan 2023</media:filmingDate>
            <guid>2185</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 07:14:02 GMT</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/98013694-a007-4f14-b5f6-1865a6d09b9c.jpg" />
            <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/reuters-videos/387f4614-388f-42cf-a0f2-e3f082193d39.mp4" />
            <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
            </item><item>
              <media:title>Animal rising activist arrested in dramatic derby field confrontation</media:title>
              <media:description>In a dramatic turn of events at the Epsom Derby in Surrey, England, Animal Rising activists were arrested as they attempted to disrupt the highly anticipated race. Video footage captured by @Cumminz_ on 3rd June, 2023 showed a protester breaching security while the crowd jeered as police swiftly pursued the intruder and apprehended him, handcuffing him on the ground.

Earlier in the day, Surrey police had already made 19 arrests based on intelligence indicating that individuals were planning to illegally disrupt the Derby. The authorities had been on high alert to prevent any disturbances from taking place. Despite the heightened security measures, the determined activists managed to breach the barriers momentarily, causing a stir among the spectators. As the horses thundered past the finish line, the woman was swiftly tackled to the ground and handcuffed by the police, ensuring the safety and continuation of the race.</media:description>
              <media:keywords>protestor,arrested,police,Epsom Derby,field,Animal Rising,activists,racecourse,jeered,tackled,handcuffed,disruption,Surrey,England,UK,video footage,onlookers,screaming,intense,confrontation</media:keywords>
              <media:city>Epsom ,Surrey</media:city>
              <media:country>United Kingdom</media:country>
              <media:regionCode>GB</media:regionCode>
              <media:categoryCode>CWP</media:categoryCode>
              <media:category>News</media:category>
              <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
              <media:filmingDate>Sat, 3 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
              <guid>2184</guid>
              <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 06:51:50 GMT</pubDate>
              <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/f71118ca-7434-45cc-81ba-2aae786fd29b.jpg" />
              <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/reuters-videos/5d91777e-c3f7-46c1-9daa-2ae620d42239.mp4" />
              <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
              </item><item>
            <media:title>Chaos at Nagoya Station: dangerous congestion captured in video at Shinkansen Ticket Gate</media:title>
            <media:description>Nagoya Station in Aichi, Japan, was engulfed in chaos on June 3rd, 2023, as a video captured by @B8BXHzu6CLcP52V revealed dangerous levels of congestion. The footage showed a swarm of people crammed together at the Nagoya Station Shinkansen ticket gate, painting a vivid picture of the overwhelming situation.

The heavy congestion portrayed in the video raises significant concerns about public safety and highlights the urgent need for improved crowd management measures. </media:description>
            <media:keywords>congestion,danger,Nagoya,Aichi,Japan,video,crowded,chaos,public safety,risk,transportation,commuters,overcrowding,personnel,crowd control,protocols,communication,authorities,ticket gate,Shinkansen,footage</media:keywords>
            <media:city> Nagoya, Aichi</media:city>
            <media:country>Japan</media:country>
            <media:regionCode>JP</media:regionCode>
           <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>      
            <media:category>News</media:category>
            <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
            <media:filmingDate>Sat, 3 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
            <guid>2183</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 06:26:25 GMT</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/90bb272c-7652-4ad8-991d-59c6f390d33c.jpg" />
            <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/reuters-videos/bb508d44-da5c-49b7-8ece-c52b9500fbdf.mp4" />
            <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
            </item><item>
            <media:title>Devastating tornado approaching Samara: severe weather wreaks havoc</media:title>
            <media:description>On Friday, June 2, 2023, the Samara region in Russia experienced a rapid deterioration in weather conditions. Thunderstorms and heavy rain battered the area, causing concern among residents. The situation escalated when reports emerged of a tornado spotted in the Kinelsky district, heading towards the city of Samara.

Eyewitnesses recounted the sequence of events, stating that it all began with the sighting of a massive dust column in the village of Domashka. The swirling phenomenon gradually moved towards Barinovka, gaining strength and intensity along the way. Residents between Barinovka and Dmitrievka were the next to witness the tornado's awe-inspiring display. Presently, according to accounts from locals, the tornado is steadily advancing towards the city of Samara, heightening concerns for the safety and well-being of those in its path.</media:description>
            <media:keywords>thunderstorms,heavy rain,tornado,Samara region,weather deterioration,Kinelsky district,dust column,Barinovka,Dmitrievka,approaching,residents,concern,sequence,intensity,awe-inspiring,advancing,safety,precautions,emergency response,community</media:keywords>
            <media:city>Samara region</media:city>
            <media:country>Russia</media:country>
            <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
           <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>      
            <media:category>Weather</media:category>
            <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
            <media:filmingDate>Fri, 2 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
            <guid>2181</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 02:13:41 GMT</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/ae5023da-6a01-4aab-a65e-746d22e05425.jpg" />
            <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/reuters-videos/f7a5a743-ced3-4ff8-b591-2c672c3b7919.mp4" />
            <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
            </item><item>
            <media:title>Mysterious water trench intruder: cat's nap halts the flow!</media:title>
            <media:description>In a quiet town of Kluang, Malaysia, a peculiar incident unfolded as a resident, @zurlhairy, discovered an unexpected obstruction in a water trench behind her house. On the fateful day of April 22, 2023, perplexed by the stagnant water, she ventured out to investigate the cause of the immobility.

As the author approached the middle of the trench, her curiosity was met with a heartwarming sight. Nestled comfortably in the trench, oblivious to its role in impeding the water's movement, was a feline companion. The sleeping cat stirred awake at the approaching footsteps but showed no signs of relinquishing its cozy spot.</media:description>
            <media:keywords>cat,water,trench,sleeping,obstruction,Kluang,Malaysia,video,peaceful,unaware,flow,halfway,snuggling,nap,stagnant,curiosity,tranquil,feline,online,amusement</media:keywords>
            <media:city>Kluang</media:city>
            <media:country>Malaysia</media:country>
            <media:regionCode>MY</media:regionCode>
           <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>      
            <media:category>Animals</media:category>
            <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
            <media:filmingDate>Sat, 22 Apr 2023</media:filmingDate>
            <guid>2180</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 20:14:14 GMT</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/96feb834-742d-4eb3-9269-335a68cccf00.jpg" />
            <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/reuters-videos/5f5e7607-4f76-444e-86f4-24910696c1d9.mp4" />
            <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
            </item><item>
            <media:title>Feline freedom fiesta: cats compete in treat-licking contest to celebrate Indonesia's Independence Day</media:title>
            <media:description>In a heartwarming display of feline patriotism, a viral video captured the spirited competition among cats to commemorate Indonesia's Independence Day. Filmed by @wulandapriliani on August 17, 2022, in Pauh, Sarolagun, Jambi, Indonesia, the footage showcases the playful yet competitive nature of these furry participants. The video reveals a unique contest where the cats engage in a treat-licking challenge, adding an adorable twist to the celebration.

With treats hanging enticingly in a line, the cats eagerly lick their treats, attempting to be the first to finish. </media:description>
            <media:keywords>cats,competition,treats,clicking,video,viral,patriotism,Indonesia,Independence Day,feline,contest,licking,Pauh,Sarolagun,Jambi,adorable,playful,unity,pets,celebration,bond</media:keywords>
            <media:city>Pauh, Sarolagun, Jambi</media:city>
            <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
            <media:regionCode>ID</media:regionCode>
           <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>      
            <media:category>Animals</media:category>
            <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
            <media:filmingDate>Wed, 17 Aug 2022</media:filmingDate>
            <guid>2179</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 19:55:12 GMT</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/931447d1-9b79-4a35-8256-7bb02984dabf.jpg" />
            <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/reuters-videos/035c78dc-2b47-431f-94dc-4ea0e8cb4a6b.mp4" />
            <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
            </item><item>
              <media:title>Night market mishap: woman falls from 'banyu wave' ride in Sragen, Indonesia</media:title>
              <media:description>A woman had a terrifying accident at a night market in Cembreng, Sragen, Indonesia. The incident occurred on May 15, 2023, when everyone was in the process of getting off the "Banyu Wave" ride. It is believed that the woman fell due to nervousness or a lack of focus, possibly resulting in her holding on less tightly and suddenly losing her balance. the video footage was captured by @rian.sanjaya931. 

The victim, whose identity remains undisclosed, is currently receiving medical treatment at a hospital. The extent of her injuries has not been disclosed, but it is clear that the incident was serious enough to require immediate attention.</media:description>
              <media:keywords>accident,night market,woman,fall,ride,Banyu Wave,Sragen,Indonesia,nervousness,lack of focus,tight grip,balance,hospital,treatment,investigation,safety,precautions,mechanical failure,amusement park,attractions</media:keywords>
              <media:city>Cembreng, Sragen</media:city>
              <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
              <media:regionCode>ID</media:regionCode>
              <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>
              <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
              <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
              <media:filmingDate>Mon, 15 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
              <guid>2178</guid>
              <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 19:15:02 GMT</pubDate>
              <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/bc0dcde2-678c-4bc5-9147-e0c84b7161f8.jpg" />
              <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/reuters-videos/da7bfd01-5a42-4783-9c67-24c964d6ad99.mp4" />
              <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
              </item><item>
              <media:title>Explosions rock Berdyansk seaport: alleged rocket attack saises tensions</media:title>
              <media:description>
Several explosions shook the seaport of Berdyansk in the Zaporozhye region of Ukraine today, raising tensions in the area. The chairman of the pro-Russian movement "We are with Russia," Vladimir Rogov, announced that the blasts were a result of an attempted rocket attack by militants from the Armed Forces of Ukraine. According to Rogov, the Russian air defense forces successfully intercepted some of the incoming rockets.

While details are still emerging, Rogov stated in an interview with TASS that the attack targeted the territory of the seaport. Fortunately, there have been no reported casualties or injuries at this time. The incident has further strained the already tense relations between Russia and Ukraine, exacerbating fears of escalating conflict in the region. The author of the video says that they had came to ride and sarcastically says how cool it was.

The author says in the video that they came to ride and sarcastically says how cool it is.</media:description>
              <media:keywords>explosions,Berdyansk,Zaporozhye,Ukraine,tensions,rocket,attack,militants,Armed Forces,air defense,Russian Federation,seaport,casualties,injuries,conflict,investigations,perpetrators,international community,hostilities,developments</media:keywords>
              <media:city>Berdyansk</media:city>
              <media:country>Ukraine</media:country>
              <media:regionCode>UA</media:regionCode>
              <media:categoryCode>WAR</media:categoryCode>
              <media:category>News</media:category>
              <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
              <media:filmingDate>Fri, 2 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
              <guid>2177</guid>
              <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 16:24:14 GMT</pubDate>
              <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/302fb1fd-ceba-4cec-b852-cc0e97e165bc.jpg" />
              <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/reuters-videos/315fec25-3e3e-438f-a354-51b9f1e855b2.mp4" />
              <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
              </item><item>
            <media:title>Feisty feline defends favorite find: Pandora's passion for bras unleashed</media:title>
            <media:description>In a heartwarming yet slightly puzzling incident, a cat named Pandora has shown an unwavering affection for a rather unconventional item: bras. A video captured by @chausie_pandora on January 11th, 2023, in Moscow, Russia, showcases Pandora's intense attachment to these undergarments. According to her owner, Pandora's love for bras knows no bounds, and once she gets her paws on one, it becomes an irrevocable possession.

The video reveals a glimpse into the battle between owner and feline over the cherished bra. The author bravely attempts to retrieve the garment, only to be met with fierce resistance from Pandora. The cat displays defensive behavior, actively tying to claw at her owner's hands in an effort to protect her prized possession. It's clear that Pandora's possessiveness over the bra has sparked a protective instinct, leading to an unexpected display of aggression.</media:description>
            <media:keywords>cat,bra,Pandora,video,Moscow,Russia,affection,love,possession,irrevocable,aggression,scratching,defensive,owner,feline,unique,obsession,amused,netizens,struggle,cherished</media:keywords>
            <media:city>Moscow </media:city>
            <media:country>Russia</media:country>
            <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
           <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>      
            <media:category>Animals</media:category>
            <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
            <media:filmingDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023</media:filmingDate>
            <guid>2176</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 05:43:45 GMT</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/17e22521-b8d2-4a67-8f60-6fb8f32f3b42.jpg" />
            <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/reuters-videos/93399f39-2ec4-41e5-8e9a-4b5eb78ba814.mp4" />
            <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
            </item><item>
            <media:title>Intense duel: fierce canine clash over a chicken bone</media:title>
            <media:description>
In a captivating video captured by @richy_kira_thesalchis on May 3rd, 2023, in Santiago, Chile, two dogs engaged in a fierce growling battle over a single chicken bone. The dogs, both gripping one end of the bone, had their snouts touching as they vied for control. It all began when the author was in the process of cutting chicken for her beloved pets, and a chicken leg accidentally slipped from her grasp and fell. She realized that the dogs had taken the leg and had it in their mouths.

As soon as the author realized what had occurred, she quickly grabbed her camera to document the extraordinary scene unfolding before her eyes. The two dogs, determined not to let go of the precious bone, growled intensely at each other, their teeth clamped down firmly. Their fierce expressions and snarling noises painted a picture of rivalry and desire.

Realizing the potential danger and the need to intervene, the author bravely stepped in and took the bone away from the feuding canines. </media:description>
            <media:keywords>dogs,growling,chicken bone,rivalry,intense,video,capture,snouts,biting,duel,pets,instinct,domesticated,companions,confrontation,canines,fierce,gripping,determined,danger</media:keywords>
            <media:city>Santiago</media:city>
            <media:country>Chile</media:country>
            <media:regionCode>CL</media:regionCode>
           <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>      
            <media:category>Animals</media:category>
            <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
            <media:filmingDate>Wed, 3 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
            <guid>2175</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 05:24:42 GMT</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/8f8ca88a-6039-432f-aff8-e1487765bab6.jpg" />
            <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/reuters-videos/320bdb8d-3f20-4b17-aad3-f9b4de7bb4f1.mp4" />
            <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
            </item><item>
            <media:title>Fire erupts during well repair at Severo-Labatyuganskoye field in Russia</media:title>
            <media:description>An explosion rattled the Severo-Labatyuganskoye field in the Surgut district of the Khanty-Mansiysk Autonomous region, Russia, as repair work was underway on a well. The incident occurred on 30th May, 2023, during which a fire broke out, damaging the body of the lifting unit of a car. Fortunately, the oil workers at the site managed to extinguish the fire before the arrival of the fire service, averting any casualties or injuries.

The Ministry of Emergency Situations reported that the fire had engulfed an area measuring approximately 0.5 square meters. Although the flames were successfully brought under control, investigators are now working diligently to establish the cause of the fire. The Severo-Labatyuganskoye field, being developed by Surgutneftegaz, is known for its significant oil reserves and plays a crucial role in Russia's energy sector.</media:description>
            <media:keywords>explosion,repair,well,fire,damage,car,workers,extinguished,arrival,firefighters,Ministry,Emergency Situations,cause,investigators,Severo-Labatyuganskoye,field,Surgutneftegaz,Khanty-Mansi,Autonomous Okrug,Russia</media:keywords>
            <media:city> Khanty-Mansiysk autonomous region</media:city>
            <media:country>Russia</media:country>
            <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
           <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>      
            <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
            <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
            <media:filmingDate>Tue, 30 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
            <guid>2174</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 04:59:59 GMT</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/c945f894-5d73-40df-bbe5-bef926de87e7.jpg" />
            <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/reuters-videos/2acca68b-d194-4f80-b30d-1537652dc5c6.mp4" />
            <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
            </item><item>
            <media:title>Cart-tastrophe in Boyolali: hilarious overload lifts cart and spirits!</media:title>
            <media:description>In a comical turn of events that left onlookers in stitches, a recent video captured in Boyolali, Indonesia has gone viral. The footage, recorded by @ariwibowo7224 on December 24, 2022, showcases a light-hearted incident involving an overloaded hand-pulled cart . Fortunately, no one was harmed during the incident, and the unexpected turn of events resulted in uncontrollable laughter from the amused bystanders. The traditional cart, which was overloaded with wood, lifted up the author's friend as he tried to pull it.</media:description>
            <media:keywords>overloaded,cart,wood,hand-pulled,lifted,friend,video,mishap,laughter,incident,humor,Boyolali,Indonesia,lighthearted,unexpected,hilarious,bystanders,amused,noharm,laughter</media:keywords>
            <media:city>Boyolali</media:city>
            <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
            <media:regionCode>ID</media:regionCode>
           <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>      
            <media:category>Fails and Funnies</media:category>
            <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
            <media:filmingDate>Sat, 24 Dec 2022</media:filmingDate>
            <guid>2173</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 04:26:57 GMT</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/2a7dde6e-b6f6-49af-9640-22a8ea07d6c3.jpg" />
            <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/reuters-videos/caa8a812-5b0e-43e7-a995-61eca53ee805.mp4" />
            <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
            </item><item>
            <media:title>Miraculous escape: lone boat circles on Kama River as navigator survives being thrown overboard</media:title>
            <media:description>In a dramatic incident on June 1st, 2023, emergency services in the Republic of Tatarstan, Russia, received a distress call about a solitary boat drifting aimlessly on the Kama River. The boat's engine was still running, but no occupants were found onboard or in the water nearby. Upon arrival at the scene, inspectors from the Chistopol inspection department, part of the Center for GIMS of the Ministry of Emergency Situations, uncovered the truth behind the mystery. It appeared that the navigator had been forcefully thrown out of the boat by a powerful wave. Fortunately, the individual managed to swim to safety along the shore.

The rescuers promptly towed the unmanned boat back to land, ensuring it didn't pose any further risk or become a hazard to others navigating the river. The Ministry of Emergency Situations took the opportunity to issue a vital safety reminder to boat owners and enthusiasts. Regardless of their level of experience, it is crucial to always have a boat motor safety check in place. This simple accessory, whether attached to one's hand or securely fastened to clothing, can be a lifesaver in situations where the boat operator unexpectedly falls overboard.</media:description>
            <media:keywords>boat,circling,water,incident,Kama River,Chistopol embankment,Markina Street,engine,people,inspectors,GIMS,Ministry of Emergency Situations,Tatarstan,Russia,navigator,thrown,wave,rescuers,towed,safety</media:keywords>
            <media:city> Republic of Tatarstan</media:city>
            <media:country>Russia</media:country>
            <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
           <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>      
            <media:category>News</media:category>
            <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
            <media:filmingDate>Thu, 1 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
            <guid>2172</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 04:07:03 GMT</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/fc0d68aa-0aa2-4628-995e-0959e868fb37.jpg" />
            <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/reuters-videos/f4011d5e-1ed6-47e8-90c7-1493197620cd.mp4" />
            <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
            </item><item>
              <media:title>Dramatic rescue: girl saved from 15th floor window ledge by heroic rescuers in Kursk</media:title>
              <media:description>In a heart-stopping incident on 31st May, 2023 in Kursk, Russia, a young girl's life hung in the balance as she sat precariously on the window ledge of a 15th-floor apartment. Swift action from the emergency services and a heroic rescue operation prevented a tragedy from unfolding. The Ministry of Emergency Situations received a distress call, prompting firefighters, psychologists, police, and paramedics to rush to the scene. After four intense hours of negotiation, the girl slipped and fell, but quick reflexes from the rescuers saved her from a fatal plunge. Gripping her hands as she dangled perilously, they managed to secure her on a lower floor before eventually dragging her back to safety. This unprecedented operation, carried out by dedicated firefighters and rescuers, concluded in a matter of tense minutes, leaving those involved with a renewed appreciation for life and the bravery required to protect it.</media:description>
              <media:keywords>rescue,girl,window,ledge,firefighters,psychologists,police,paramedics,emergency,negotiation,fall,perilous,reflexes,safety,unprecedented,operation,tense,minutes,life,bravery</media:keywords>
              <media:city>Kursk</media:city>
              <media:country>Russia</media:country>
              <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
              <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
              <media:category>Rescue</media:category>
              <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
              <media:filmingDate>Wed, 31 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
              <guid>2171</guid>
              <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 03:51:50 GMT</pubDate>
              <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/261b04eb-d801-4da0-9995-fc919ddb094c.jpg" />
              <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/reuters-videos/71d78923-a441-459e-be2c-62631f90ebc0.mp4" />
              <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
              </item><item>
            <media:title>Terrifying encounter: polar bear narrowly misses attacking snowmobilers in Yakutia, Russia</media:title>
            <media:description>
In a heart-stopping incident in Yakutia, Russia, a polar bear nearly attacked a group of snowmobilers as they made their way to the village of Bykov. The encounter took place on the 31st of May, 2023, as the bear ran alongside the moving snowmobile, closely eyeing the people. Suddenly, it darted towards the sleigh where a passenger was seated, coming perilously close to biting him. The shocking moment was captured on video by a witness, who could only manage to shout out in alarm. Fortunately, the animal missed its target, leaving the snowmobilers shaken but unharmed.

Polar bears, known for their powerful land locomotion, can reach speeds of up to 40 km/h, making them formidable creatures capable of chasing down snowmobiles. Such encounters pose a significant risk to drivers and passengers, as demonstrated in this incident. While the motive behind the bear's actions remains unclear, it is speculated that the animal may have intended to frighten the people rather than actively attack them.</media:description>
            <media:keywords>polar bear,snowmobilers,Yakutia,Russia,Tiksi Bulunsky ulus,village,Bykov,chase,passenger,sleigh,attack,video,encounter,frightening,alarm,danger,remote,caution,wildlife,adrenaline</media:keywords>
            <media:city>Yakutia</media:city>
            <media:country>Russia</media:country>
            <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
           <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>      
            <media:category>Animals</media:category>
            <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
            <media:filmingDate>Wed, 31 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
            <guid>2170</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 03:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/814bafc6-05c6-4bbb-b43e-b73ebe43cbdc.jpg" />
            <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/reuters-videos/2170.mp4" />
            <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
            </item><item>
              <media:title>Heroic rescue: man saves stranded calf from torrential floods in Dagestan</media:title>
              <media:description>In a heartwarming incident amidst the devastating heavy rains that recently struck Dagestan, Russia, a small calf found itself in a life-threatening situation as it fell into the raging Sulak River on 31st May, 2023. Fortunately, an alert eyewitness noticed the struggling animal and quickly sprung into action to save it from the treacherous currents.

The footage portrays the calf desperately fighting against the turbulent waters, occasionally being submerged as it tumbled downstream. The person behind the camera, recognizing the dire situation, made a courageous decision to intervene and ensure the calf's safety. With swift and determined actions, the rescuer covered the shivering animal with a blanket, providing warmth and comfort. The rescuer's care extended further as they even delicately wiped the calf's nose with a napkin.</media:description>
              <media:keywords>rains,mudflows,bridges,destruction,calf,Sulak River,eyewitness,rescue,video,views,frames,current,animal,blanket,warmth,barbecue,nose,napkin,compassion,bond</media:keywords>
              <media:city>Dagestan</media:city>
              <media:country>Russia</media:country>
              <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
              <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
              <media:category>Rescue</media:category>
              <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
              <media:filmingDate>Wed, 31 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
              <guid>2168</guid>
              <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 17:58:01 GMT</pubDate>
              <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/3eb40c47-be95-482b-8acf-356d1bd8e14a.jpg" />
              <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/reuters-videos/2168.mp4" />
              <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
              </item><item>
            <media:title>Quick thinking saves the day: daughter's cool response stops stove fire</media:title>
            <media:description>In a remarkable display of composure and quick thinking, a young girl in Thái Bình province, Vietnam, averted a potential disaster when a fire broke out in her kitchen. The incident, captured by @ngothanhlam123456789 on April 8th, 2023, showcased the bravery and level-headedness of the daughter as she handled the situation with remarkable poise.

As the video footage reveals, the girl was cooking alone when the stove suddenly burst into flames. Instead of panicking, she immediately started looking for a way to put out the fire. Demonstrating her resourcefulness, she swiftly sought out a nearby fan to disperse the smoke and prevent the flames from spreading further. Miraculously, thanks to her calm and decisive actions, the fire was contained, with only the food falling victim to the incident.</media:description>
            <media:keywords>cooking,fire,stove,daughter,home,calm,quick-thinking,safety,protection,bravery,composure,resourcefulness,fan,smoke,emergency,incident,food,camera,thái bình,vietnam</media:keywords>
            <media:city>Quỳnh Phụ, Thái Bình province</media:city>
            <media:country>Vietnam</media:country>
            <media:regionCode>VN</media:regionCode>
           <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>      
            <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
            <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
            <media:filmingDate>Fri, 7 Apr 2023</media:filmingDate>
            <guid>2167</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 17:30:35 GMT</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/cbe312de-92d8-4a3c-8ce3-d03f397363cc.jpg" />
            <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/reuters-videos/0b521970-b941-4e48-b9b7-07b97187ca48.mp4" />
            <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
            </item><item>
            <media:title>Playful dog's spirited encounter with brother turns into a lively game in Buon Ma Thuot City</media:title>
            <media:description>In a captivating video captured by @le_xuanthao on April 11th, 2023, in Buon Ma Thuot City, Vietnam, a seemingly intense encounter between a dog and a person took an unexpected turn. As the person, who happened to be the owner's brother, entered the compound on a motorbike, the dog initially came running to the brother. The vigilant owner swiftly positioned himself between the dog and his brother, attempting to deter any harm. However, the dog persisted in its playful pursuit, circling around the person with uncontainable excitement.

To match the dog's exuberant antics, the brother displayed impressive agility, skillfully jumping from one side of the motorbike to the other. Although in the video the dog appeared hostile, the dog's intentions were not hostile, but rather a spirited invitation to play. Eventually, the dog's energy waned, and it joyfully disengaged from the interaction,</media:description>
            <media:keywords>dog,attack,video,Buon Ma Thuot City,Vietnam,owner,gate,motorbike,compound,deter,round,person,jumping,persistent,relent,protect,confrontation,fearless,footage,incident</media:keywords>
            <media:city>Buon Ma Thuot City</media:city>
            <media:country>Vietnam</media:country>
            <media:regionCode>VN</media:regionCode>
           <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>      
            <media:category>Animals</media:category>
            <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
            <media:filmingDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2023</media:filmingDate>
            <guid>2166</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 16:56:31 GMT</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/96e54591-1ef5-453b-82eb-c4ab17122b1b.jpg" />
            <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/reuters-videos/c2be3b84-0dbf-493b-8126-d85e2f2d0c9b.mp4" />
            <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
            </item><item>
            <media:title>A serene escape turned into a close call: a local gardener saves belongings from rising waters</media:title>
            <media:description>In a tranquil escape to the upper area of La Ngâu Stream in Tánh Linh District, Bình Thuận Province, Vietnam, @_thien1409 found himself in a heart-stopping situation on May 16th, 2023. The picturesque location seemed like the perfect spot to unwind and soak in the beauty of nature. Little did he know that his peaceful retreat would turn into a race against time to save his belongings from the rapidly rising waters.

As @_thien1409 briefly left his spot near the riverbed to retrieve his belongings from his car, nature unleashed its fury. The water levels began to surge, threatening to wash away everything he had left behind. Fortunately, a local gardener happened to be nearby and noticed the perilous situation. Acting swiftly, the gardener bravely waded through the rising currents and managed to rescue @_thien1409's belongings, sparing them from being swept away by the unforgiving waters.</media:description>
            <media:keywords>serene,river,video,belongings,car,water,nature,environment,local,farmer,rescue,safety,escape,rising,rapidly,close call,race,time,threat,community</media:keywords>
            <media:city>Tánh Linh District, Bình Thuận Province</media:city>
            <media:country>Vietnam</media:country>
            <media:regionCode>VN</media:regionCode>
           <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>      
            <media:category>Weather</media:category>
            <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
            <media:filmingDate>Tue, 16 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
            <guid>2165</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 16:26:42 GMT</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/56842024-146b-4626-a311-5bd3532edda8.jpg" />
            <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/reuters-videos/0c534d57-6e12-4245-88bd-7e1d6cf0e8ea.mp4" />
            <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
            </item><item>
            <media:title>Alberta braces against relentless hailstorm assault as nature unleashes its fury</media:title>
            <media:description>In a stunning display of nature's power, Alberta, Canada found itself under siege from a relentless hailstorm. On the 31st of May, 2023, residents witnessed a disaster as large hailstones pounded homes and streets. A video captured by @SeskaFuze_ showcased the intensity of the storm, with the caption "Crazy hailstorm here. Sheeeesh. Power/internet is out."

The footage revealed the sheer force with which the hailstones descended upon the area. </media:description>
            <media:keywords>hailstorm,alberta,canada,weather,nature,destruction,intensity,power,internet,video,footage,storm,damage,force,awe,concern,community,resilience,recovery,aftermath</media:keywords>
            <media:city>Alberta </media:city>
            <media:country>Canada</media:country>
            <media:regionCode>CA</media:regionCode>
           <media:categoryCode>DIS</media:categoryCode>      
            <media:category>Weather</media:category>
            <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
            <media:filmingDate>Wed, 31 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
            <guid>2164</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 15:58:17 GMT</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/45c1bd2c-e188-4203-957a-a0ec0b691a4c.jpg" />
            <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/reuters-videos/1de21e68-46c7-4ecc-a5f4-f11a59a6bf34.mp4" />
            <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
            </item><item>
              <media:title>Ukrainian troops shell Shebekino, Russia: local barbershop after the attack</media:title>
              <media:description>Shebekino, a town located in Russia, experienced a distressing attack as Ukrainian troops fired upon its center and outskirts using Grad rockets on 31st May, 2023.

Video footage captured the aftermath of the attack, revealing a building with its windows shuttered and damaged walls. The targeted building housed a barbershop, which bore the brunt of the assault, with its windows shattered and parts of its walls destroyed. The extent of the damage inflicted upon other structures in Shebekino remains unclear at this time. Governor Gladkov emphasized that despite the absence of enemy forces within the Belgorod region, the area continues to face relentless shelling. </media:description>
              <media:keywords>attack,shebekino,russia,ukrainian troops,gradov,governor,belgorod region,injured,shelling,victims,windows,destruction,barbershop,walls,video,evacuation,enemy,civilians,children,temporary accommodation</media:keywords>
              <media:city>Shebekino</media:city>
              <media:country>Russia</media:country>
              <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
              <media:categoryCode>WAR</media:categoryCode>
              <media:category>News</media:category>
              <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
              <media:filmingDate>Wed, 31 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
              <guid>2163</guid>
              <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 15:38:55 GMT</pubDate>
              <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/c9c5ec3a-7c3c-4344-9c67-1cffe450b5ef.jpg" />
              <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/reuters-videos/9235a5f8-ab8a-4df2-9fe2-18cf27102f84.mp4" />
              <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
              </item><item>
              <media:title>Intense clashes persist near Shebekino</media:title>
              <media:description>The Russian Volunteer Corps released a video on 1st June, 2023, providing evidence of ongoing fighting near the city of Shebekino, Russia, specifically in the vicinity of Novaya Tavolzhanka village as captured by @russvolcorps. The footage captures the intense and dangerous environment as gunshots echo through the air. In the video, a soldier can be observed taking cover behind bushes, while another group lies flat on the ground. The publication of this video underscores the persistent nature of the conflict in the region.</media:description>
              <media:keywords>fighting,shebekino,novaya tavolzhanka,video,gunshots,soldiers,hiding,bushes,ground,intense,conflict,raw,unfiltered,perilous,danger,ongoing,risks,impact,military,civilians</media:keywords>
              <media:city>Shebekino</media:city>
              <media:country>Russia</media:country>
              <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
              <media:categoryCode>CWP</media:categoryCode>
              <media:category>News</media:category>
              <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
              <media:filmingDate>Thu, 1 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
              <guid>2162</guid>
              <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 15:22:48 GMT</pubDate>
              <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/04866b48-1baf-4fcc-bee0-c6dc218672a9.jpg" />
              <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/reuters-videos/6ad8e424-9ae1-4a4b-8154-f231dba47e3d.mp4" />
              <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
              </item><item>
              <media:title>Armed Forces of Ukraine fired at Shebekino from "Grad"</media:title>
              <media:description>Ukrainian troops fired on the center and outskirts of Shebekino from Gradov. The governor of the Belgorod region Vyacheslav Gladkov announced this on his telegram channel on Thursday, June 1.

According to preliminary data, eight people were injured. According to the governor, one of the men had his arm torn off, another was shell-shocked, a police officer was diagnosed with an open fracture of the humerus, two women had shrapnel wounds to their arms and legs, the condition of other victims is being specified.</media:description>
              <media:keywords>war,russia,ukraine,shebekino,attack,fire,shelling</media:keywords>
              <media:city>Shebekino</media:city>
              <media:country>Russia</media:country>
              <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
              <media:categoryCode>WAR</media:categoryCode>
              <media:category>News</media:category>
              <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
              <media:filmingDate>Thu, 1 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
              <guid>2161</guid>
              <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 14:52:32 GMT</pubDate>
              <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/85f9db34-3a86-4714-b726-f989411d7c27.jpg" />
              <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/reuters-videos/713fd581-839c-40f0-b31b-b4d0713582e0.mp4" />
              <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
              </item><item>
              <media:title>Rocket attack on Premix No. 1 factory in Shebekino</media:title>
              <media:description>The plant "Premixes No. 1" came under rocket attacks on 1 June 2023 in the village of Shebekino, Belgorod Region. Rescue services quickly rushed to the scene of the accident. According to preliminary information, there were no casualties. During the shelling, power lines were hit.

It is known that this plant produces enrichment mixtures and biologically active substances. The company uses biologically active additives (BAA).</media:description>
              <media:keywords>war,shelling,russia,ukraine,fog,accident,attack,shebekino</media:keywords>
              <media:city>Shebekino</media:city>
              <media:country>Russia</media:country>
              <media:regionCode>RU</media:regionCode>
              <media:categoryCode>WAR</media:categoryCode>
              <media:category>News</media:category>
              <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
              <media:filmingDate>Thu, 1 Jun 2023</media:filmingDate>
              <guid>2160</guid>
              <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 14:35:26 GMT</pubDate>
              <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/6345a03b-5531-4d0d-9d34-1513b212b11f.jpg" />
              <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/reuters-videos/21433e83-85af-46a1-9585-b1660dc43487.mp4" />
              <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
              </item><item>
              <media:title>Unexpected overwhelm: child's tearful reaction to a playful encounter with a green frog mask!</media:title>
              <media:description>The incident took place in Thuận An Town, Bình Dương Province, Vietnam, and was documented by @ngobaotram0712 on April 1st, 2023. The child, who was seated outside, found himself face-to-face with the masked man, unaware of the surprise that awaited him.

As the man approached wearing the green frog mask, the child started crying after seeing him. Contrary to the adults' expectations, the child's startled reaction was genuine and unanticipated. The intention behind the playful teasing was to engage the child, knowing that he was not easily frightened. However, the unexpected sight of the man in the mask overwhelmed the young one, prompting tears.</media:description>
              <media:keywords>playful,teased,green,frog,mask,child,crying,outside,man,surprise,unexpected,curiosity,tears,startled,genuine,unanticipated,laughter,brave,overwhelmed,comfort</media:keywords>
              <media:city>Thuận An Town, Bình Dương Province</media:city>
              <media:country>Vietnam</media:country>
              <media:regionCode>VN</media:regionCode>
              <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>
              <media:category>Fails and Funnies</media:category>
              <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
              <media:filmingDate>Sat, 1 Apr 2023</media:filmingDate>
              <guid>2159</guid>
              <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 05:45:18 GMT</pubDate>
              <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/e2111e04-e98d-41b3-aba6-36714c9aa862.jpg" />
              <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/reuters-videos/d410813e-cf33-4282-82ee-5589a18baf60.mp4" />
              <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
              </item><item>
            <media:title>Caught on camera: brazen thief strikes at Milky Way milk tea shop in Hanoi, Vietnam</media:title>
            <media:description>A shocking incident unfolded at the Milky Way milk tea shop located in Hai Ba Trung, Hanoi, Vietnam, as captured in a video shared by @toanphungdeyy on 11th May 2023. The footage shows a brazen thief snatching a phone from the shop's counter while the staff was preoccupied with preparing foodstuffs to serve customers. Taking advantage of the understaffed situation, the thief patiently waited on a bench until the staff member turned their attention away, allowing for the opportune moment to strike. Despite their efforts, the shop owner and staff were unable to apprehend the culprit.

According to the owner, that particular day witnessed a severe shortage of staff, leaving him with no choice but to leave only one person at the counter. Unfortunately, this created the perfect scenario for the thief to carry out their nefarious act. However, there was a silver lining to the incident, as the stolen phone was eventually returned to its rightful owner.</media:description>
            <media:keywords>theft,video,shop,snatching,phone,counter,staff,serving,thief,bench,opportunity,understaffed,Hanoi,Vietnam,owner,returned,caught,brazen,incident,security</media:keywords>
            <media:city>Hai Ba Trung, Hanoi</media:city>
            <media:country>Vietnam</media:country>
            <media:regionCode>VN</media:regionCode>
           <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>      
            <media:category>News</media:category>
            <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
            <media:filmingDate>Thu, 11 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
            <guid>2158</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 05:19:32 GMT</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/5a1b9b9b-c159-47b6-840d-316115b3f477.jpg" />
            <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/reuters-videos/ebd549bd-29d2-41ef-a8ed-4f32f321fe65.mp4" />
            <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
            </item><item>
            <media:title>Father's love triumphs: heartwarming reconciliation with daughter over safety concerns</media:title>
            <media:description>In a heartwarming incident captured on video in Kendari City, South East Sulawesi, Indonesia, a concerned father was seen persuading his young daughter against crossing a busy road alone. The video, taken by user @gorogo_14 on May 23, 2023, showcases a tender moment between the father and his determined little girl. Despite her eagerness to explore a place filled with enchanting lights across the road, her father rightfully forbade her, emphasizing the potential dangers. Frustrated by his refusal, the girl refused to communicate with her father and turned away whenever he attempted to engage her face to face.

The video demonstrates the father's unwavering commitment to his daughter's safety. He patiently engages with her, explaining the risks involved in crossing the road independently. His persistence pays off as the young girl eventually agrees to converse with him. Overwhelmed by her father's love, she embraces him tightly, signaling their reconciliation. With their bond reaffirmed, the father scoops her up into his arms and they walk away together.</media:description>
            <media:keywords>father,daughter,road,safety,video,love,communication,parenting,concern,reconciliation,hug,persuasion,refusal,danger,trust,bonding,guidance,lights,capture,emotions</media:keywords>
            <media:city>Kendari City, South East Sulawesi</media:city>
            <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
            <media:regionCode>ID</media:regionCode>
           <media:categoryCode>ENT</media:categoryCode>      
            <media:category>Heartwarming</media:category>
            <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
            <media:filmingDate>Tue, 23 May 2023</media:filmingDate>
            <guid>2157</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 04:45:49 GMT</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/6042ac19-2173-4619-a4e3-6886625dcbbe.jpg" />
            <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/reuters-videos/85482dc5-4f10-4c07-9170-2361646aba97.mp4" />
            <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
            </item><item>
              <media:title>Mother's swift action: a heart-stopping moment captured in Bali</media:title>
              <media:description>In a heart-stopping moment captured on home camera footage, a mother's swift actions saved her children from a potentially dangerous situation in Karangasem, Bali, Indonesia. The video, recorded by @aryawiryaatmaja on April 9, 2023, showcases a scene where the mother is tending to her two young kids in front of their house.

The incident unfolded when the older child suddenly skidded and fell, resulting in a loud cry. The mother instinctively shifted her attention to attend to the fallen toddler, momentarily leaving the other child in a baby walker unattended. Little did she know that a shallow pit, a remnant of a religious ceremony, lay dangerously close to the path the baby walker was traversing.

As the child in the baby walker pushed it around, unaware of the potential danger, disaster seemed imminent. However, luck was on their side that day. The mother, displaying remarkable reflexes and agility, swiftly intercepted the baby walker just in the nick of time. She pulled both children closer to her, providing solace and comfort to the one who had fallen.</media:description>
              <media:keywords>mother,children,home camera,Bali,Indonesia,incident,rescue,swift,danger,toddler,fallen,baby walker,pit,religious ceremony,attention,love,vigilance,safety,parenting,social media</media:keywords>
              <media:city> Karangasem, Bali</media:city>
              <media:country>Indonesia</media:country>
              <media:regionCode>ID</media:regionCode>
              <media:categoryCode>GEN</media:categoryCode>
              <media:category>Accidents</media:category>
              <media:exclusivity>non-exсlusive</media:exclusivity>
              <media:filmingDate>Sun, 9 Apr 2023</media:filmingDate>
              <guid>2156</guid>
              <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 04:15:20 GMT</pubDate>
              <media:thumbnail url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/screens/8c1ac402-7344-4666-b3a2-3a54ec547fa7.jpg" />
              <media:content url="https://viralbear.storage.yandexcloud.net/reuters-videos/15dfbab7-5aec-4617-91cd-fed0eb8e4ab6.mp4" />
              <dfpvideo:lastModifiedDate/>
              </item></channel>
           </rss>